Chapter 508 – Out of Expectations

The videos were sent and examined carefully for an entire day. In the end, the Clubs grit their teeth and contacted Mo Qiang, who happily accepted the reward. Mo Qiang himself was surprised. He didn’t think that it would have been so easy! Why else would he have made a post online as a cover or record of all of the calls? The other side had taken a close look at the videos, so he thought there would be a huge argument between them, but contrary to his expectations, they simply responded with two words: bank account.

The deal went so smoothly, that Mo Qiang was somewhat astonished. He gave the other side his bank account’s routing number and called Ye Xiu.

“Really? Well that’s good!” Ye Xiu was quite calm and didn’t seem too surprised. This was because he had another window open on his screen. Loulan Slash was crying: “You guys have given us a lot of trouble!”

“What’s wrong?” Ye Xiu asked.

The Clubs have been scammed of 150,000 yuan and it turns out they weren’t just going to swallow it so easily. Mo Qiang? In their eyes, he was just a subordinate, so they didn’t make things difficult for Mo Qiang. Instead, they directly contacted Loulan Slash and sent him a message showing their disdain towards him.

The message was clear. The Clubs wanted to let Loulan Slash know that they weren’t stupid with more money than sense. This small amount of money wasn’t much to them, so if you wanted it, you could have it! We’re too lazy to bicker with you over this matter, but for you to actually plot something like this, we’re definitely going to look down on you.

Loulan Slash felt wronged!

He felt like earning profit like this wasn’t his style, so he had refused to collaborate with Ye Xiu. Who would have thought that the blame would be put entirely on him? Ye Xiu had come off clean without a speck of dirt. Loulan Slash also had to blame himself for overlooking this matter. Those five accounts had been his, so if someone else used them, then wouldn’t it be obvious what the outcome would be?

God replied, “Ha ha ha ha, it looks like I’ve wronged you.” Loulan Slash felt like he had been cheated!

“Just tell them I was the one who did it. Wouldn’t that solve everything?” God followed up with another message, making Loulan Slash feel at ease again. Taking a bit of blame was nothing, but if the other side really had intended on pushing the blame onto him, then he would have felt uneasy.

Seeing the reply and then thinking about his interactions with God, Loulan Slash now truly believed that this God didn’t care about this at all, so God didn’t have any intentions of making him a scapegoat. Everything had just been an accident.

“In any case, they’re already set on believing that I did it. I’m too lazy to explain, so that’ll be that then!” Loulan Slash decided.

“Are you sure you don’t want a share of it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No need no need.” Loulan Slash jumped. “Even though he had been made a scapegoat, he hadn’t thought of asking for compensation. A leader knew there were things that he should and shouldn’t do. Loulan Slash was clearly a very principled youth.

“The money has arrived!” Mo Qiang was very excited. His entire week of hard work had paid off! The Clubs displayed their demeanor, expressing how this matter was beneath them. They didn’t make any delays and immediately transferred the money over to Mo Qiang.

“Okay, then I’ll leave it with you for now! How are the other matters I talked to you about going?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Senior, it’s only been a day. Give me some time!” Mo Qiang said.

“See you then!” Ye Xiu said.

“It’ll be done, so don’t worry!” Mo Qiang received the reward and was in high spirits. Yesterday, he said how gathering those materials might have be difficult, but he seemed much more confident now.

In the time that it took for him to raise his hands, he had earned 150,000 yuan. In the same amount of time, the money he earned would be completely spent. From start to finish, the money never touched his hands. His trust in the other side was admirable as well.

“Time to level up!” Ye Xiu stretched and continued to kill monsters.

On the Clubs’ side, after sending the money to Mo Qiang’s account, they urgently convened for an online meeting, discussing the issue of the other two player’s bounty.

The rewards for the five open accounts might not have cost much, but money was still money. The money had flowed right out of their accounts and had even left a stain. The presidents of the Clubs may have a certain amount of financial power in their hands, but that power wasn’t their Club’s power. All of these things would be assessed in their annual financial record. The amount of money wasn’t much, but it would still be infuriating. It would make them seem like they had no ability.

For their appearances, this small amount of money didn’t matter.

For internal affairs, it was a deep cut to their hearts.

Heavenly Justice had cheated them of a portion of money. If Deception and Lord Grim cheated them too, they would be making the same mistake twice……. it would be unforgivable!

The loophole for this bounty was too big! Neither the public, nor the private, wanted to continue. Not long after holding the meeting, several presidents decided to withdraw. If someone left, then the burden would be split by the others. No one would agree to that, so after another ten minutes, they unanimously decided to stop giving out the bounty. Next time, if they had to make such a move, they had to be more careful.

The bounties had only been placed a week ago. Not only were there no signs of their target, the five dummies had cost the Clubs 150,000 yuan. This sort of result made them very displeased.

More importantly, the activity had created a huge wave of excitement. Ending it would require an explanation.

The 150,000 yuan couldn’t be spent for nothing. They provided the videos bought for 150,000 yuan as proof for the success of their move. In reality, they grit their teeth every time they saw those ten videos, especially those huge glamorous words “Xiaoqiang Productions”. The more they watched, the more annoyed they became and had the opening titles deleted.

Those five dummies had been dealt with, but those other two’s bounties had to be explained too!

Unfortunately, they hadn’t been able to kill either of them a single time. In the end, they could only express with a magnanimous voice how Lord Grim and Deception had committed crimes and then hid like cowards, abandoning their five brothers and letting them die over and over again.

Because everyone was very busy right now, we’ve decided to stop the activity and we can’t promise something like this will ever happen again. Scrap pickers, behave yourself!

It turned out that, for a majority of the players, they actually believed the Clubs had been hugely successful. The videos shared to the public were highlights picked from the ten video files. As a result, the normal players didn’t know about the loophole that had been exploited.

This time, the Clubs had used scrap pickers as a pretense to justify their actions. Who would have thought that their actions would actually help get rid of them? Afterwards, a lot fewer scrap pickers appeared in the Heavenly Domain. The players were smart. Facing the annoying scrap pickers, they used the actions of the club-backed guilds as a threat. The bounty had benefited the community and the Clubs were praised for it.

However, these were all things that came after a period of time. Right now, who did this affect the greatest? Ye Xiu, of course. Even though the danger was still there, he didn’t need to worry about how every piece of grass or stone might suddenly turn into an enemy.

Killing monsters over the next two days went relatively peacefully. Lord Grim steadily reached Level 54. With the amount of time Ye Xiu had spent playing the game, his leveling speed after level 50 was considered quite slow, but what choice did he have? He couldn’t run any dungeons.

Starting from this day, Ye Xiu was no longer busy with only in-game affairs. He started spending time outside the game studying and researching.

Why? Because the upgrade path for the Thousand Chance Umbrella was limited to this.

For Level 55, 60, 65, and 70, Ye Xiu needed to look all over the Glory world to find suitable materials for it.

In addition, the materials needed for these next few stages would be much more expensive than before. This was because starting from Level 55, the Heavenly Domain existed, making it even larger than the old Glory mainland, so there would naturally be many more items available. Finding suitable materials out of all of the materials available would require a lot of research. Ye Xiu became even busier.

As for Chen Guo, she was still the boss for the Internet Cafe and had other priorities besides the game. Every day, she would have to spend some time patrolling the Internet Cafe. Like usual, the first thing she did in the morning was get up and go for a walk. Outside the entrance to the cafe, she sucked in a breath of fresh air and stretched her arms. When she looked ahead, a person was crossing the street, heading towards Happy Internet Cafe.

When he arrived in front of the door, he gave Chen Guo a smile.

Chen Guo looked at him. He looked to be a bit over thirty years old and looked intelligent and capable. This type of person didn’t seem like someone who would go to an Internet Cafe first thing in the morning. He probably had something urgent come up and needed to use a computer.

Chen Guo studied him, while giving him a smile back. Who would have thought this person would be the first to speak: “Is Ye Qiu here?”

“Ah!” For a moment, Chen Guo was in a daze as she stared dumbly at this person. She suddenly felt like he looked a bit familiar. Was he a pro player? Chen Guo quickly recalled all of the pro players she recognized, but couldn’t register a match.

“Is he here?” The other side saw Chen Guo lost in thought and asked again.

“Oh, come with me.” Chen Guo nodded her head and led the person up the stairs. He was looking for Ye Qiu and because she wasn’t anyone too close to Ye Qiu, she didn’t feel like she had the right to ask about his business.

Right when she got upstairs, the door to the room opened and Ye Xiu walked out with a cigarette in his mouth. Ye Xiu saw Chen Guo and then looked in surprise at the person behind her.

“He came looking for you.” Chen Guo made way and introduced him.

The expression on Ye Xiu’s face didn’t change much. He simply nodded his head. He held open the door and invited the person in.

The person also nodded his head and then walked into the room with a smile on his face. Chen Guo followed after him, but she wasn’t as nice to Ye Xiu. She immediately asked him out of curiosity: “Who is he? He seems kind of familiar. I feel like I should recognize him!”

“Excellent Era’s boss.” Ye Xiu smiled as he walked into the room.

Chapter 509 – I Don’t Want Any of That

Chen Guo suddenly understood. That’s right! The person in question was none other than the CEO of Excellent Era’s club, the true boss, Tao Xuan. She had seen him before on some reports, but as the CEO, he didn’t get as much media exposure as the players. Therefore, there was much less attention fixed on him. As a result, Chen Guo only felt that his face looked familiar instead of immediately recognizing him. Upon hearing Ye Xiu’s words, she finally remembered.

Excellent Era’s CEO was personally paying a visit?

Chen Guo immediately realized that there was much brewing under the surface. She couldn’t help but follow the two into the room with all of her worries and curiosities. Upon seeing them staring at her, she found herself embarrassed on the spot, pointing towards her own room, “I’ll be going back to my own room.” While her words were still leaving her mouth, she had already moved with brisk steps. She quickly entered the room, closed the door… and then flattened herself against it.

“Sit.” In the living room, Ye Xiu gave his seat to Tao Xuan before standing next to the window.

“How’s everything going?” Tao Xuan asked Ye Xiu as he settled himself on the couch.

“Pretty good.” Ye Xiu answered and fished a cigarette out of his pocket. With a wave of his hand, Ye Xiu tossed it towards Tao Xuan.

Surprised, Tao Xuan paused for a split second. When he reached out to catch it, it was already too late.

Tao Xuan picked the cigarette up from the floor. After a he held it uncomfortably for a moment, he set the small offer on the table and looked up at Ye Xiu with a smile, “I quit.”

“Oh? Really? Well, I didn’t hear about that.” Ye Xiu spoke. He took a deep breath and blew the smoke out the window.

In another short silence, Tao Xuan looked around the room as he asked with a laugh: “You live here?”

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu nodded.

“Living with such beauty, aren’t you afraid of upsetting Mucheng?” Tao Xuan joked.

“Heheheh.” Ye Xiu chuckled three times and then wiped his smirk away. He looked at Tao Xuan in all seriousness, “State your business.”

Instead of avoiding Ye Xiu’s gaze, Tao Xuan met it straight on with his own before replying with the same smile, “Come back!”

“To where?”

“Back to Excellent Era.”

Bang!

The door Chen Guo’s room sounded as if something crashed into it. Ye Xiu shook his head, laughed, before calling out, “If you want to listen in, just come inside! Shame…”

The door was pulled open, and out of of it, Chen Guo appeared with a turmoil of emotions on her face ----- embarrassment mixed with anger.

Ye Xiu looked at her, smiled, then turned to Tao Xuan and continued the conversation,”What could I possibly do back in Excellent Era?”

“Coach.” Tao Xuan answered quickly.

“Oh? Me as a coach? Could this be part of your scheme?” Ye Xiu asked.

This time Tao Xuan didn’t reply as quickly. His gaze averted, as well and dropped to the table before him. The cigarette on the table laid all by itself in solitude. Chen Guo stared at him, suppressing the urge to scream in his face: how dare he come to ask Ye Xiu to go back? Did he have any sense of shame left? In the end, her gaze bounced back and forth on the two’s faces, as if she was trying to decode some hidden message from them.

“I have no interest watching from the bench. I like the stage the best.” Ye Xiu suddenly broke the stagnant silence.

This sentence put a smile on Tao Xuan’s face. He lifted his head, “Coaching would only be temporary. After the one year required leave, you can return immediately.”

“Of course I would go back immediately.” Ye Xiu laughed.

Tao Xuan understood the subtext in Ye Xiu’s words right away: I’m going back no matter what. Tao Xuan smiled bitterly, “What’s the point?”

“What is your point?” Ye Xiu shoveled Tao Xuan’s words back.

Tao Xuan’s expression turned agitated. Ye Xiu’s retort seemed to poke a nerve in him.

The answer to the question was that there was no point. There was no need for both of them to have this conversation in the first place. Additionally, when Ye Xiu replied, his answer seemed to imply more than returning to Excellent Era.

“Both you and I watched the league become what it is today step by step. Both of us know this well: the current league isn’t the same as before.” Tao Xuan opened his mouth again, “The big teams’ success helps the league grow; Brilliant stars help expand the League's influence. They are what the league need the most now. In a match, strategy and teamwork are surely important to determine the outcomes. However, stars! Stars are what drives ticket sales the most. Of all of your intricate strategies, if we sample a million audience members, how many of them do you think will understand them? None! That cannot grip the players’ hearts. What do the players like to see? One versus three in a challenge match and a lone hero in a team battle. These are the things that they talk about. These are what they want, like, and hope to see. These are what they view as miracles.”

Tao Xuan paused for a moment and observed Ye Xiu’s expression. He even looked at Chen Guo before he continued, “Why do they call Zhou Zekai the best in Glory? Is it simply because he looks the best? No. What’s important is that his skills are extravagantly displayed, and that his battles are splendidly fought. In the eyes of the players, splendor means difficulty. It means skill. You might say such opinions are extremely shallow, but what people like to see is exactly this shallowness. Your legendary technique, you said that you created it for fun, you said its practicality was limited, but what about it? All of the fans see it as your signature technique. Does it matter that its practicality is limited? No, it doesn’t matter. What matters is that it's irreplaceable. You are the only one who can perform it, so it became an irreplaceable splendor. When you stopped using it, people believe that your skill level dropped. When you used it at All Stars, you ignited the whole stadium’s excitement instantaneously. I don’t believe that you didn’t see all of these things!”

After an emotional speech, there was not a single trace of a smile on Tao Xuan face. He stared intently at Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu only smiled, “All of what you have just said are true, but I don’t want any of them.”

“What do you want?”

“Victory.” Ye Xiu gazed straight at Tao Xuan.

“You…” Tao Xuan looked as if he had lost all of his strength at once. After a while, he opened his mouth again. This time, a hint of sarcasm was mixed in with his words, “You honestly believe that you can still regain your former glory?”

“I will try.” Ye Xiu replied.

“You. Can. Not. Do. It.” Tao Xuan stated.

“Are you that sure?” Surprisingly, Ye Xiu still found the nerve to laugh.

“Yes.”

“Then we’ll see.” Ye Xiu promised.

“Very good. Let’s see it happen.” Tao Xuan stood up.

“Humph. Before that, make sure your Excellent Era doesn’t get kicked out first.” Upon realizing that the conversation ran aground, Chen Guo added, unable to hold herself back.

“Hehe.” Tao Xuan laughed, clearly belittling the threat, “Even if Excellent Era got kicked out, we can still rejoin the league after a year. We’ve set our sights on the future. We will not be tied down by our past. Those who stand in our ways will be kicked away mercilessly.”

“Yeah. About that, you did a very good job indeed.” Ye Xiu commented half-heartedly.

“I’ll take my leave.”

“I won’t see you out.”

Tao Xuan walked hurriedly to the door, but he stopped when he pulled it open. He didn’t look back as he added, “The league won’t be going back to the way it used to be in the past.”

“I know that, but I’m too old to keep moving forward. “ Ye Xiu spoke.

“Initially, you could have had a perfect end.” Tao Xuan said.

“Whether my end is perfect or not, I’ll decide that.” Ye Xiu retorted.

After standing in the doorway for a long time, Tao Xuan finally turned around, “For all these years’ sake, I will grant one wish of yours.”

“Oh?”

“Even if you want to move One Autumn Leaf out of Excellent Era.” Tao Xuan finished.

“That would be very costly.” Ye Xiu grinned.

“As long as you set the price, I will not make it any harder for you.” Tao Xuan promised.

Tao Xuan’s words shook Chen Guo’s heart. She knew that changing ownership of a character was far harder than changing the team of a player. The value of a player would fluctuate based on the player's’ performance, but character would not. The value of a character would only go up.

This was because characters were objects. As long as there was someone to command them, they would obey every order with perfect precision. Its value could be fully utilized. Players were a different story. If there was one who really wanted to change teams, the club would probably acquiesce because forced situation don't end well most of the time.

This logic applies to people, but not characters.

There were a lot of steps involved for a player to change teams. There were also a lot of negotiations about the money involved. However, if a character changed ownership, the buyer was almost guaranteed to face a ridiculous price proposed by the sales. As a result, during the transferring time window, there would always be a lot of players moving around. In comparison, there would hardly be any transferring of characters.

For Tao Xuan to actually let go of One Autumn Leaf, the trump card of Excellent Era, without setting barriers on the cost, the promise held a heavy weight.

“Very well.” Ye Xiu nodded, “I want Dancing Rain.”

“What?” Chen Guo exclaimed in confusion. Tao Xuan’s surprised appeared on his face as well, but he didn’t say much. He only nodded in consent, “Okay. I will keep my word.”

“Thank you.”

“Well then…” Tao Xuan turned around, “I never thought that I would ever be saying these words to you one day: See you on stage!”

“I thought of it way earlier. See you on stage!” Ye Xiu replied calmly.

Tao Xuan left. Chen Guo pressed herself against the window. Soon she saw him walk out of the internet cafe, striding across the street. Without hesitating or turning back, he stepped through Excellent Era’s entrance.

“You guys… were friends once upon a time, right?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“Yes.” Ye Xiu acknowledged. He walked past the table, picked up the cigarette on floor, lit it, and then walked out of the room.

“Where are you going?” Chen Guo asked hurriedly.

“The game of course. You coming?” Turning his head around, Ye Xiu asked with the same smile.

“Of course.” Chen Guo followed him right away, finding tranquility in her heart. She realized that her worries for Ye Xiu had being totally unnecessary.

In room 213, the two logged into the game together. In the past two days, Chen Guo was always helping Ye Xiu level up, so they were in the same place. Immediately after he logged in, Ye Xiu spotted a burn mark on the ground. With a momentary pause, Lord Grim spun around in a full 360 degrees circle, completely surveying the surroundings instantaneously. Something seemed to have tipped him off as Ye Xiu yelled at Chen Guo frantically, “Run!”

“What?” Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze just logged in when Ye Xiu shouted at her. She had no time to react when a pile of bright visual effects descended upon her like a fishing net.

Chapter 510 – Ambushed Online

“What’s happening?” Chen Guo only had time to call out in surprise before her screen was filled with resplendent lights. She hastily shifted Chasing Haze out of the way, but she was rooted as soon as she took two steps. Waves of attacks caused Chasing Haze to stay in a stunned state. Her health disappeared in chunks with a whoosh, Chen Guo quickly gulped down a health potion, but it didn’t ease the situation at all.

It’s finished… Chen Guo knew in her heart. Her reaction was too slow. The reason she was able to move a few steps in the beginning was not because the opponents failed to land an attack, but because every character was invincible for the first three seconds the moment they logged on, but after that, the opponents’ attacks were effective. Chen Guo didn’t have time to let Chasing Haze escape at all. In that instant, her eyes were filled with uncountable resplendent attacks that were targeted at Chasing Haze. She only saw a bunch of tightly-packed, varied debuff symbols, which resembled the densely-packed maggots found in corpses, causing her to feel nauseated.

It has already come to this, Chen Guo didn’t expect there to be any hope, she only glanced quickly towards Ye Xiu’s side. She was sure that an ambush this scale was aimed for him.

Tap tap tap tap tap…...

Intense and rapid typing taps came from Ye Xiu. His hands danced across the keyboard continuously without stopping. His expression was very serious, which showed that the situation wasn’t easy to handle. From his screen, Lord Grim was shown to be moving about at high speed. Continuous attacking lights and silhouettes brushed past Lord Grim, making Chen Guo feel worried as she watched.

The clear sound of the system’s prompt transmitted through Chen Guo’s ears amidst all the chaotic variety of attacks. From this, she knew that her Chasing Haze had fallen.

Chen Guo quickly opened her inventory to take a quick look. She heaved a long sigh of relief when she saw that her weapon didn’t drop. After coming upon the fact that she only dropped a ring, which was an inexpensive blue equipment, she turned a blind eye towards it.

As her ghost floated up, she could see a bird’s eye view from the sky. However, a ghost could only see everything in black and white, so she couldn’t see much apart from the lights from skills. Fortunately, these skills stopped after Chasing Haze was killed. Chen Guo was looking for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, when she saw a gray shadow move across her screen.

A character’s ghost is shapeless, so this character had come from her ghost’s position. It was why she felt as if the shadow had suddenly appeared in front of her.

Chen Guo glanced at the shadow that had passed by. Wasn’t that Lord Grim?

A helicopter blade spun above Lord Grim’s head. He had used Rotor Blade, a Mechanic’s skill, to fly across. Then, Chen Guo saw a Witch riding a broomstick fly over. The witch jumped in mid-air and swept her broom towards Lord Grim.

Lord Grim quickly retracted his mechanical rotors and returned fire with his gun before the Witch could sweep him down with her broom.

Bang! Flames spurted out from the gun’s mouth and the Witch fell to the ground. Lord Grim used the recoil from the bullets to fly out. Midway, he drew his sword and crashed to the ground with a Falling Light Blade. At nearly the same time, a sword light shot towards the sky.

Blade-Master Skill: Sky Plunging Blade

The sword light twinkled like the stars in space, brushing past Lord Grim. If not for Lord Grim’s Falling Light Blade, which sped up his fall, he would have been struck by the Sky-Plunging Blade.

Although this strike had missed, a second one followed up shortly after.

A streak of crimson sword light swung towards Lord Grim, who had not reached the ground yet. The Berserker’s Wild Blood Strike allowed the player to slice either vertically or horizontally. This Berserker sliced horizontally across. Lord Grim was unable to dodge the attack while in the air. He lifted his sword and parried the attack. He attacked to defend, making his sword collide with the enemy’s blade.

Parrying was essentially meeting an attack with another attack. The resulting damage would be judged by both side’s attack. Lord Grim was lower leveled and he didn’t use a skill either, so his strike couldn’t compare to the Berserker’s. Wild Blood Strike knocked Lord Grim’s offensive parry aside. The crimson sword light continued to move horizontally towards Lord Grim and looked as if it would cut Lord Grim into two.

Clang!

It resulted in another rattle. Lord Grim’s sword in his right hand had been knocked aside, while the umbrella’s shaft in his left hand swung forward.

Dual Sword Style!

Chen Guo was surprised. Even though she had played Glory with Ye Xiu for a long time, it was her first time seeing the Thousand Chance Umbrella use a dual sword move. This attack needed its corresponding weapon as a foundation. Out of the numerous weapons that existed in Glory, only Nightwalkers possessed dual blades.

The Nightwalkers consisted of Assassins, Warlocks, Ninjas, and Thieves.

Out of the four, the Assassin could use the Dual Sword Style to full effect. In the Pro Alliance, the player most famed for this was the captain of Team 301 Degrees, Yang Cong. His character, Scenery Killer, wielded a famous silver dual blade weapon in Glory, Chaotic Winding Shadow Swords.

It would be a waste if an Assassin, who used dual blades, didn’t delve into the Dual Sword Style. Yang Cong had perfectly mastered Dual Sword Style. In fact, the reason he was able to become an All Star was mainly because of his skills and performance. His character, Scenery Killer, couldn’t really be counted as top tier in the Pro Alliance.

The Dual Sword Style was the bane of parrys. Parrying using two swords had its advantages. At this moment, Ye Xiu made use of this advantage to block the Wild Blood Strike using two strikes. With the first parry, his weapon was knocked aside. The second time, he successfully parried against the attack, but it wasn’t enough to completely defend against the Wild Blood Strike attack. The light from Wild Blood Strike still swept across his character, but Lord Grim used the recoil from his parry in order to move backwards.

This movement allowed Lord Grim to escape from being caught by another chain of attacks. If he actually wanted to fully defend against Wild Blood Strike, Ye Xiu could have simply used the Blade Master skill “Guard”. As a skill, the effects were much better than something done through normal means. But at this moment, Ye Xiu needed to parry against the attack, so he didn’t completely negate the attack. If he had used “Guard”, the blow away effect from the Wild Blood Strike would have been reduced by a lot. By parrying, he was able to utilize the blow away effect in order to quickly move and dodge the next chain of attacks.

Lord Grim rolled when he landed on the ground… leaving Chasing Haze’s death camera.

The ghost’s line of view couldn’t be moved around, so when she could no longer see the fight from her screen, she looked at Ye Xiu’s screen. However, his high speed movements always made her feel dizzy. She could all sorts of flickering glows of attacks from Ye Xiu’s screen. Lord Grim was like a storm trooper weaving in between gunfire, using astonishing techniques to dodge.

Health. There would still be a decrease in health after being scraping by the attacks. For example, the parry used against the Wild Blood Strike. Even if he used skills like parry, under the limits of his level, it would be impossible to neutralize all of the damage, let alone a basic parry. However, more importantly, compared to his health was his rapidly decreasing stamina.

Stamina wasn’t only consumed when sprinting. Walking, jumping, rolling, even normal attacks consumed stamina. Lord Grim’s stamina decreased at such a rapid pace because he was using all sorts of movements to dodge attacks.

He was able to survive until now, but what would happen when his stamina ran out?

Chen Guo was very worried, but she wasn’t able to provide any sort of help. She even found it hard to look at Ye Xiu’s screen. Chen Guo peeked at her own screen, and saw people appearing and disappearing from her screen from time to time. Their direction was mainly turned towards the direction where Lord Grim had disappeared to.

Which guild did these people belong to?

Chen Guo noticed the names of the characters who entered her view, but no one’s guild tag was visible. She didn’t know whether they were deliberately hidden or that they just didn’t have a guild.

One, two, three, four, five…..

Ye Xiu played while he counted quietly to himself.

He didn’t have enough spare time to let Lord Grim identify who his opponents were. He could only judge the amount of people by the attacks he continuously dodged.

15…….

In the blink of an eye, he counted fifteen.

This was only a conservative estimate, based on his judgement, Lord Grim had dodged fifteen attacks from different classes so far, which indicated that there were at least fifteen characters who were besieging him.

It was a plotted ambush.

Ye Xiu knew it in his heart. The moment he logged on, he noticed the black trace marks on the ground. It was the remains of the Elementalist’s fire attacks. It hadn’t been refreshed yet, which indicated that the attacks were only done recently and that there were players around.

Ye Xiu would obviously be suspicious if there were people around him. He quickly spun his character’s camera around and instantly saw some other marks made by skills other than the scorched trace marks.

There was more than one person!

At that moment, Ye Xiu understood what was going on. The marks dealt by attacks were organized in Ye Xiu’s eyes, so he immediately tried to break out of range of the spell marks.

He was able to do it, but Chen Guo hadn’t been fortunate enough to escape from it.

The opponent’s intention was very clear, but at this moment, Ye Xiu didn’t have the time to think about their identities.

Boom boom boom boom!

A series of explosions. Lord Grim dodged a Launcher’s Stinger, which left a sea of fire behind him. Although he continually used his stamina to make enhanced movements he still couldn’t break away from his opponents. The enemies predicted Lord Grim’s movement and sent out attacks towards where he would be.

Apart from the wave of attacks in the beginning, the opponents no longer had the intention to kill their target in a single wave. The attacks were never ending and continuous, meaning that they were planning to grind Lord Grim to death. It was the very same technique Ye Xiu had used with Loulan Slash’s group to kill Sun Xiang.

Who would have thought that the skill he had just used would be used by someone else on him.

Fortunately, their skill level and teamwork were inferior to Loulan Slash’s group and Ye Xiu’s experience was far greater than Sun Xiang’s. By avoiding the significant attacks, while taking the insignificant attacks, Ye Xiu was able to allow Lord Grim to survive the enemy’s assault.

However, this wasn’t a good long-term plan. Dodging attacks like this consumed too much stamina. Even if you ignored the limitations of his own energy or his character’s HP and stamina, Lord Grim was only Level 54. If he continued on like this without fully escaping from the pursuers, he would certain die.

Chapter 511 – Expert Commander

The battle ensuing on Ye Xiu’s screen was a blur to Chen Guo’s eyes. She could still see his status clearly. Lord Grim’s life was dancing on a blade’s edge the entire time. This meant that the only thing Ye Xiu could do was survive longer than her Chasing Haze. It was hard to say if he would be able to escape or not.

What should she do?

Chen Guo was extremely worried. Whether she revived and rushed back or called for help, it would be too late now. Everything depended on Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu’s normal lazy look often made Chen Guo grind her teeth in anger, but at this moment, she really wanted to see the look on his face.

However, it wasn’t there. He had an expression of concentration on his face. The sounds of rapid tapping and clicking continued to be produced by his two hands. The screen had already made Chen Guo feel dizzy. Now, even the sounds made her feel uneasy.

In any case, she should try to do something!

Chen Guo revived her Chasing Haze and ran in his direction. She didn’t know if she would be able to arrive in time, nor did she know if she would be able to provide any help. She didn’t want to sit there and do nothing.

As she sprinted over like mad, Chen Guo glanced at Lord Grim’s coordinates and health from time to time.

Ye Xiu was still trying to hang on.

Chen Guo hated how she couldn’t just teleport there. Even if she could only block attacks for him, it would be enough…..

Suddenly, Chen Guo realized the room had quieted down.

Ye Xiu’s rapid tapping and clicking ceased.

Chen Guo was alarmed. She immediately turned her head, but discovered his screen was still colorful. Lord Grim hadn’t died. He was hiding behind a stone wall covered in moss.

“Ah? You escaped??” Chen Guo was overjoyed at the good news, but then she saw Lord Grim suddenly run forwards a bit. All sorts of bright effects from attacks could be seen exploding behind him. People were attacking his previous hiding place, but he had been able to run out in time.

“Not yet.” Ye Xiu replied to Chen Guo’s question.

But being able to talk meant that the situation had become much better than before. She looked at Ye Xiu’s current position: Milo Ancient Ruins.

Milo Ancient Ruins was one of the Level 55 leveling areas in the Heavenly Domain. The background lore described this place as the ruins of an ancient city, which had been destroyed a thousand years ago by an earthquake and volcanic explosion. Most of it was already buried beneath the ground. The remnants, visible above ground, had been weathered by time, badly damaged and in pieces.

Milo Ancient Ruins wasn’t a large area because it wasn’t a leveling area with many monsters. The surface remnants were only small portions of the ancient ruins. They were like a line, guiding players towards the real Milo Ancient City, which was buried underground. In the past, Milo Ancient City had been a huge hundred player dungeon, where countless players died.

Chen Guo looked at Lord Grim’s level. He was Level 54, but still needed half a bar of experience before he would reach Level 55. He wouldn’t be able to suddenly reach Level 55 and run into the dungeon to hide. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim run here in order to take advantage of the terrain and shake off his pursuers.

“20 players.” Ye Xiu pushed the microphone on his headphones to the side and spoke to Chen Guo. He was afraid his pursuers would hear his voice and figure out his position. Right now, Lord Grim was hiding in the corner of a stone room and was looking out from a small crack in the wall.

“Oh?”

“It’s just a guess, but it should be around there.” Ye Xiu figured out the strength of his enemies while hiding and running.

“Who are they?” Chen Guo asked.

“I don’t know. That’s not important right now. These players are all average in skill, but their commander is very troublesome.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who’s the commander?” Chen Guo was astonished. To be able to make Ye Xiu feel pressure, this person must be at the pro level!

“I’m not sure. I haven’t had the chance to see him.” Ye Xiu was helpless. He had been running for his life the entire time. Figuring out the enemy numbers was already impressive enough. Under the situation where the enemy commander was giving orders through text in a private chat, figuring out who the commander was among 20 people was nearly impossible.

“If I figure out who the commander is and kill him, the remaining subordinates will be easy enough.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck!”

Right as Ye Xiu finished speaking, he suddenly cursed out loud. He hastily tapped his keyboard and Lord Grim rolled out of the corner. Bang! Behind him, a hole suddenly appeared in the stone wall. Bits of gravel flew out into the corner. Only a Sharpshooter’s Thunder Snipe had that sort of penetration power.

“Bang!”

Following afterwards, an even louder sound erupted. A small mushroom cloud rose up in the corner of that room. A Launcher had fired a Heat-Seeking Missile into there.

Several characters suddenly popped up in Lord Grim’s line of sight. A Berserker charged forward using Colliding Stab.

The usage of this skill reflected Ye Xiu’s evaluation of their skill. Ye Xiu simply leaped backwards and the Berserker awkwardly stopped in front of Lord Grim. Colliding Stab had reached the limits of its attack range.

Ye Xiu didn’t give him a second chance to try again. Lord Grim knocked the Berserker high into the air and Flung him away.

Another two players followed after the Berserker, but how could they have known their ally would turn into their enemy? One of them jumped to the left, while the other jumped to the right, but they soon discovered that not only had Lord Grim thrown the Berserker at them, he had also lobbed a grenade. It was too late for them to dodge. The grenade exploded and all the three went tumbling through the air.

Ye Xiu didn’t bother with these three anymore and immediately had Lord Grim turn around. He pointed his Thousand Chance Umbrella straight ahead and fired rapidly. Ahead, at a small intersection, a Thief was laying a trap down.When he saw the gun aimed at him, he hastily rolled to the side, but his trap had been hit by the gun. The trap sprung out of the ground and became useless.

The Thief was furious. When the Gatling Gun finished firing, he wanted to jump out and show his fury. Suddenly, a bang sounded out from behind his butt and he was sent flying towards a pile of trash. While in the air, he turned his head and saw the scraps left behind by a Mechanical Seeker. However, he had no clue where it had come from.

Lord Grim turned around and fired twice diagonally. A Witch, who had been flying out, was hit down and the Spitfire who had jumped onto the roof went stumbling backwards.

Then, the Thousand Chance Umbrella changed into a spear. He released a Falling Flower Palm at the incoming Striker and Grappler and sent them flying backwards. These two were puzzled. Lord Grim had clearly fired in a different direction. How did he turn around so quickly and use a Falling Flower Palm?

In a single breath, he had attacked eight characters. He just happened to have turned around in a circle too. Ye Xiu saw an opening and immediately had Lord Grim charge through it.

“I don’t think any of these eight are the commander.” Ye Xiu suddenly spoke.

“Ah?” Chen Guo was afraid of bothering Ye Xiu, so she hadn’t said anything to him. She didn’t think Ye Xiu would be the one to speak. After a short pause, Chen Guo figured out Ye Xiu’s meaning: “ You’re saying none of those eight players are the commander?”

“Yes.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Or maybe this person is only good at commanding and doesn’t have any actual battle skill?” Chen Guo said.

“It’s possible.” Ye Xiu didn’t deny the possibility.

Lord Grim rolled and jumped. He took notice of a narrow opening ahead and headed towards it. Right when he was about to go through it, an Ice Wall suddenly appeared, blocking his path.

Six players closed in on him from behind. They didn’t give Ye Xiu any time to break the wall. Ye Xiu looked left and right. There were six enemies on his right and three on the left. It was obvious which direction he should head. At this moment, he heard a whirring sound from above. It was an enemy Mechanic’s Rotor Wing. Two winter melon like objects spiralled towards Lord Grim’s head. The stomachs of these things split apart and bombs fell out.

Lord Grim twisted his body and rolled to the left. At the same time, he fired twice towards the two winter melon-like objects.

These winter melon like objects exploded like grenades, turning into two balls of charred metal.

However, the air raid had just begun. A Witch broke through the explosion and flung a Lava Flask at Lord Grim’s head.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already turned back around. He hadn’t expected the enemy to hide such a move. Lord Grim jumped up into the air. His Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a spear as he stabbed at the Witch.

Pu!

The Circle Swing connected with the Witch and sent the Witch smashing into the ground, but this time, Ye Xiu had been a bit too slow and wasn’t able to block the Witch’s Lava Flask. The Lava Flask shattered and the ground instantly turned into an ocean of lava.

Right when Lord Grim was about to plunge into the lava, the Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into Rotor Wings and he quickly flew over the lava field.

After flying over the lava field, he charged towards the three on the left. The Warlock among them immediately formed a black ball of light with his hands. The Warlock positioned the Curse Arrow high up and didn’t charge it up. The black ball shot out and transformed into a rain of countless black arrows.

Ye Xiu had no way of dodging the attack by flying up and could only drop back down, but if he were to move any farther downwards, his feet would hit the ground. He might as well just run, so Ye Xiu canceled the Rotor Wings and had Lord Grim land on the ground. Following afterwards, he used the Shadow Clone Technique and instantly teleported in front of the Warlock.

The back throw input had already been entered, and so Lord Grim’s two hands shot towards the Warlock. At the same time, Ye Xiu saw the Warlock’s face covered by his mantle. It was a rough male face with a messy beard. With one look, he could tell it wasn’t a system generated face, but a scan of a real life photo.

“Old Wei?” Ye Xiu shouted out in astonishment.

Chapter 512 – Old God

“F*ck, why are you so troublesome! Hurry up and die so I can get my 500.” The Warlock, who Ye Xiu called Old Wei, responded in an extremely loud voice. Chen Guo could even hear his voice from Ye Xiu’s headphones clearly.

His hands didn’t stop moving either. The Warlock jumped backwards. He had predicted Ye Xiu would use a Back Throw and dodged it.

“You’re still looking at that 500? Did you not see the statement?” Ye Xiu said, while continuing to attack. Lord Grim shook the Thousand Chance Umbrella and it transformed into a spear shooting towards the Warlock.

“Hm? Statement? What statement?” The Warlock asked.

“The bounty has already been withdrawn.” Ye Xiu told him.

“F*ck, that happened?! Then all of the work this senior did was for nothing? Practicing the team’s coordination and studying your work and rest schedule?” The Warlock shouted.

“Not my problem. Why didn’t you start a day or two earlier? They only just withdrew it.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re not trying to trick me, are you? What statement? Send it to me.” The Warlock yelled.

“One sec.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was stunned. Could everything that had happened today have just been an accident? Who the heck was this guy?

Chen Guo was just about to ask, when she suddenly discovered that while Ye Xiu should be finding a link to send to him, he didn’t even have a web browser open. However, he had stopped controlling his character. Lord Grim stood there, not moving.

“You….”

Chen Guo only said one word, when a shadow suddenly appeared behind Lord Grim. The shadow lifted its hands and cut downwards in a cold arc.

Ye Xiu immediately input a string of commands. Lord Grim stepped to the side and turned around, allowing Chen Guo to get a glimpse of the attacker. The shadow was an Assassin, holding a dagger. The Assassin looked like a wild tiger, undaunted by dangers. Chen Guo couldn’t help but tremble. She recognized this skill: Life-Risking Strike!

Blood for blood. Life for life.

Life-Risking Strike didn’t consume mana, but rather used health. The Assassin’s health burned like mana for a final strike. As long as it hit, the health spent would do true damage to the opponent, ignoring all defenses. In other words, even if it were a weaponless Assassin, as long as he used Life-Risking Strike, he would guarantee that would do damage proportional to the amount of health he burned.

The amount of health that could be burned depended on the skill’s level. The higher the skill level was, the more health could be burned. The max-leveled skill had no limit to the amount of health that could be burned. One could even burn one’s health to zero. However, once the skill ended, the Assassin would certainly die.

Life-Risking Strike could be an instant kill move. It was the only skill in Glory that could kill a full health character in one hit.

Using one’s own life in exchange for damage was fair. The only thing which limited the amount of damage this strike did, was the Assassin’s own health. If one saw an Assassin equipped with Stamina increasing equipment, then one would be extremely wary of this move. These types of Assassins stacked health in order to fully utilize this Life-Risking Strike.

Assassins weren’t a class with high stamina, so they didn’t have much health. After an Assassin burned his health, he would just be an extremely weakened Cloth armor class, but if an Assassin stacked stamina, any class would have to match up against them careful.

This Assassin suddenly used Life-Risking Strike.

Lord Grim grew in a balanced manner, so while he didn’t have a lot of health, he didn’t have too little either. However, his level was low and his equipment were relatively weak. If this attack had hit, the true damage trading health for health was one thing. The skill’s base damage was already painful enough for Lord Grim. In addition, Lord Grim wasn’t at full health right now. An instant kill wouldn’t have been hard for this Assassin to achieve.

Even though Lord Grim stepped to the side, this Assassin had clearly burned a lot of health. Lord Grim had stepped to the side, but the Assassin quick movements from using this Life-Risking Strike made it so Lord Grim’s sidestep not only did not widen the distance between them, but closed the distance. With Lord Grim’s stats, dodging this Life-Risking Strike was clearly too difficult.

Chen Guo thought Lord Grim would certainly die from this strike. Suddenly, a dark light flashed, turning into a six-pointed star. A green goblin popped out from the six-pointed star right in between Lord Grim and the Assassin.

The poor little Goblin didn’t even have time to understand the situation when it made a shrill cry. The Assassin’s Life-Risking Strike smashed into its body.

“F*CKKK!!!!” The Assassin also cried out. The poor goblin had already exploded into a bloody corpse, but the Assassin didn’t feel sorry for the Goblin at all. The Life-Risking Strike, which he had burned almost all of his health for, had struck a weak little house pet. How could he not mourn!

After Life-Risking Strike was used, potions couldn’t be used for a certain amount of time and the user wouldn’t be able to receive any healing spells during this time either. Otherwise, if one could chug potions and receive help from a Cleric, there wouldn’t be any risk involved in using this skill.

Risking one’s life meant no regrets. When Jing Ke attempted an assassination on Ying Zheng, he hadn’t left a path for his retreat.

“D*mn! Even that didn’t hit! Is there still any justice in this world!” The Warlock roared in fury.

“Nonsense. I was prepared for it!” Ye Xiu said, while attacking back at the Assassin. The Assassin had burned his own health in order to kill a measly green goblin. He was still filled with grief and wasn’t able to react. Ye Xiu seized this opportunity to give him a quick beating and killed the Assassin.

Chen Guo heard the two speaking to each other and became dumbstruck again. Both of them harbored evil intents! That Warlock lied to Ye Xiu saying he could leave, but had an Assassin make a sneak attack. On the other hand, Ye Xiu pretended to be fooled, but then took the chance to kill the enemy Assassin.

Neither of them were sincere, but in any case, it was the Warlock who started it. In addition, the Warlock had set up an ambush as soon as he went online. More importantly….. Chen Guo was definitely on Ye Xiu’s side.

“Too despicable!!” Chen Guo moved closer to Ye Xiu’s headphones and shouted.

“Where’d this b*tch come from!” The Warlock answered back without a hint of politeness.

“Ambushing us as soon as we log in, how low can you get?” Chen Guo shouted.

“Ha ha ha ha, you can remember this senior’s name if you’d like!” The Warlock laughed.

“Peh, I’m not that shameless. If you’ve got the skill, 1v1 me!” Chen Guo spat.

“Ha ha, are you hot? If you’re hot, I can keep you company. If not, I don’t have that sort of free time.” The Warlock responded.

“Cut the crap! Do you dare to 1v1 me?” Chen Guo shouted.

“Ha ha, how fiery! How about you find a room and wait for me there!” The Warlock chuckled.

His wording sounded very dirty, making Chen Guo stamp her feet in anger. When she looked at Ye Xiu, she saw that he was still controlling Lord Grim to have him break away from the trap. He also glanced at her as if he were looking at a dead person.

“What’s with you!” Chen Guo said.

“Do you know who this person is?” Ye Xiu asked her.

“Who cares!” Chen Guo was so furious that she wasn’t afraid of anyone.

“His name is Wei Chen. Have you heard of his name before?” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t think so. Who is he?” Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu give a serious introduction to him, so she calmed down a bit. She reckoned his background wouldn’t be small. He was most likely a pro player. However, this name……. Chen Guo tried to think if she had ever heard the name before, but she really had no idea.

“He’s already retired.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…… he probably retired a long time ago then.” Chen Guo said. If he had retired a long time ago, it wouldn’t be strange that she had no impression of his name.

“Yes, before he retired, he was Team Blue Rain’s captain and Swoksaar’s former owner.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah…..” Chen Guo suddenly turned cold. Swoksaar was the number one Warlock in Glory and was currently in the hands of Team Blue Rain’s captain Yu Wenzhou. Chen Guo thought that this person would be a pro player, but she didn’t think he would be a captain-level player. In the pro scene, the captain of the team was often the team’s best player. Even if the captain wasn’t, the captain would at least be at an All Star level, let alone a captain of a powerhouse like Blue Rain.

“Why is he like a bandit…….” Chen Guo couldn’t help but say.

“Compared to normal citizens, he’s certainly a lot more crude. In those days, when we just entered Glory, he was already considered quite old. He retired after playing for only two years.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is he very good?” Chen Guo said.

“You know about Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian, right? He brought them up by himself. Their styles were pretty much inherited from him.” Ye Xiu said.

“Disabled hands and a chatterbox?” Chen Guo asked.

“Can’t you think of any positive traits……” Ye Xiu coughed blood.

“Uh……” Chen Guo had clearly said that intentionally. She knew very well just how good Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian were. She just had a hard time imagining how such an immoral guy could bring up two top tier experts.

“Comrade Ye Qiu, can you not hide? Come out and fight me in a battle to the death!” Wei Chen challenged. While Ye Xiu was chatting with Chen Guo, he immediately had Lord Grim break out of the encirclement after killing off the Assassin. Right now, Lord Grim was hiding in a corner.

“Don’t you have any shame! You brought so many people and you’re calling for a battle to the death?” Chen Guo couldn’t help but roar back.

“No one’s stopping you guys from calling for help though? Speaking of which, I’ve been waiting all day. Have you really not called for any helpers? Your b*tch doesn’t count. With that pathetic skill, all she’s good for is lying in bed and playing around with.” Wei Chen called out.

“I’M GOING TO KILL HIM!!!” Chen Guo couldn’t hold it back anymore.

“Calm down.” Ye Xiu urged, “In any case, you’re not his opponent, so why ask to be humiliated?”

“Then what should I do?” Chen Guo asked.

“Let me handle it?” Ye Xiu grinned.

“You…..”

“Ah! They’ve found me again!” Ye Xiu cried and had Lord Grim escape. Chen Guo felt depressed. His current sorry state and his confident “let me handle it” was simply too conflicting.

Chapter 513 – There’s Someone Behind You

Ye Xiu’s shout seemed quite pathetic, but his hands continued to input commands in a steady and orderly way. He even had time to talk. His current situation was much better than it had previously been.

Even so, Ye Xiu was far from having the advantage. Even though he had successfully killed off an enemy Assassin, he relied on the Assassin killing himself. The Assassin had burned most of his life by using Life-Risking Strike. If Ye Xiu couldn’t finish off the miniscule amount of health remaining, he didn’t deserve to play the game.

Following afterwards, another flashy show started and Lord Grim began hiding in corners again. The opponent’s commander might be strong, but he didn’t have that many people under his command. More importantly, Milo Ancient Ruins wasn’t a leveling area. Back in Wilderness Town, Ye Xiu not only had to avoid being seen by three guilds, but he also had to make sure he didn’t aggro any monsters, since it would have made it that much more troublesome.

But Milo Ancient Ruins? Ye Xiu had already lit a cigarette. He was having quite an easy time playing hide and seek.

“If he has such a background, then is this Blue Brook Guild’s doing?” Chen Guo saw how Ye Xiu seemed to be relaxed, so she didn’t need to stay silent.

“It doesn’t seem like it.” Ye Xiu shook his head, “Blue Brook Guild would have brought a lot more experts. At the very least, they wouldn’t have given him a random group of players, no?”

“Then if he’s not doing it for the Blue Brook Guild and there’s no bounty, then what does he want?” Chen Guo was puzzled.

Suddenly, she heard Wei Chen shout: “Listen to me, Ye Xiu. You’re completely surrounded. Coming out and dying is your only path left. Logging off would be very shameful of you. Resisting would be a waste of time. Hurry up and come out. Give me that five hundred yuan, so I can go eat dinner.”

“D*mmit, didn’t I tell you that the bounty was already withdrawn? Do you really not know about it or are you just faking it?” Ye Xiu replied.

“What was that? I can’t hear you clearly. Speak louder.” Wei Chen yelled.

Ye Xiu immediately shut up. Wei Chen was lying. He wanted Ye Xiu to speak up, so he could figure out his position!

“You don’t want to fight and you don’t want to log off. You’re hiding to stall for time. Are you really waiting for helpers to arrive? Are you forcing me to call for more people? F*ck, if I call more people, that five hundred won’t even be enough for me to buy water. Even with the 20 people I have right now, I’d still have to pay a bit out of my own pocket for a meal!”

Ye Xiu heard Wei Chen cursing and making a huge fuss over the five hundred yuan, but Ye Xiu had a hard time believing that Wei Chen didn’t see the announcement that the bounty had been withdrawn. After thinking for a moment, he suddenly said to Chen Guo: “Do you have any friends in other guilds? Ask them about the bounty.”

“The announcement was very clear. Didn’t we see it already? Even if they went back on their word, it shouldn’t be so quickly!” Chen Guo didn’t know whether to laugh or cry.

“No. I’m asking whether or not the guilds might have made another move internally.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Chen Guo was a bit surprised, but quickly understood.

She had been in the Heavenly Domain for so long. She wasn’t familiar with any of the big names, but she still had friends in other guilds. She asked them about it and they confirmed what Ye Xiu said.

“You’re right. The guilds all have a bounty on you. It’s five hundred every time you’re killed! Some of the guilds even have contribution rewards.” Chen Guo hurriedly told Ye Xiu.

“So he really is after the money!” Ye Xiu was speechless.

“How tragic.” Chen Guo commented. She could understand if he were a normal person, but according to Ye Xiu, he was a God-level player with an incredible background, and yet he was leading others just for five hundred yuan. It was quite tragic. How was he going to split the money with 20 people? Each person would get 25 yuan? Or was it the killer takes 300 yuan and everyone else gets ten yuan? In either case, it was quite pitiful…...

“That might not be the case. It’s more likely he’s just looking for fun. If he has free time and there’s an event with five hundred yuan as a reward, why not do it!” Ye Xiu analyzed his opponent’s motive.

“Ah, he’s going to find me soon!” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo and noticed the enemies were beginning to close in on his hiding place, so he immediately jumped and moved out.

By moving out, his location was revealed, but at least, he had taken the initiative. It was better than the enemies suddenly ambushing him and forcing him out.

“B*stard, running again. You really do have some skill. You’d better not log off today. Let’s see how long you can run for.” Wei Chen saw Lord Grim and immediately had his subordinates chase after him.

“More like you’d better not run.” Ye Xiu retorted.

“F*ck, you can still talk, while you’re running away. You really are Ye Qiu!” Wei Chen yelled.

The two fought back and forth, while shouting at each other nonstop. Chen Guo was staring speechlessly for a long time and then suddenly realized that this was what it was like when two pro level players fought! The trash talk never stopped.

“What are you planning on doing?” Chen Guo was somewhat at a loss. Ye Xiu didn’t have any helpers he could call on. Loulan Slash and his friends weren’t online. Apart from them, Ye Xiu didn’t know anyone else. He isn’t waiting for me, right? Chen Guo was worried. She really hoped she could help, but if he was actually placing his hopes on her, then she would feel very pressured.

“My helper is almost here.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who? You’re not talking about me, right?” Chen Guo asked. Ye Xiu’s glance at her made her want to die.

“If you check the system announcements, you’ll know sooner or later.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was puzzled. What did getting a helper have to do with the system announcements? Just when she was going to ask, she realized that Ye Xiu was busy.

A huge fireball flew in front of him, cutting off Ye Xiu’s escape path. The pursuers from behind had already arrived, cornering him in a small alleyway. Wei Chen had been shouting at Ye Xiu at how he kept on running and wasting his time, but now he had successfully found another opportunity to kill him!

Ye Xiu had nowhere to go in front or behind him. He saw a big chunk of the wall missing to the right of him and immediately had Lord Grim run up to it. He flipped over the wall and escaped.

He didn’t land on the ground after jumping and continued to fly using Rotor Wings.

“Sh*t, he’s too crafty! Hit him down for me.” Wei Chen’s Warlock was right outside of this gap. This had clearly been a trap set by him. A Thief had set several traps beneath the gap. If Lord Grim had stepped on them, he wouldn’t have any chance of escaping. However, Ye Xiu had seen this scenario in his head and didn’t land on the ground.

On the ground, several gunners shot at Lord Grim.

Rotor Wings wasn’t very quick and it wasn’t very nimble either. However, under Ye Xiu’s control, it appeared exceptionally agile, dodging all of the incoming bullets and making the enemy Mechanic watch on in astonishment.

Wei Chen wasn’t someone who simply ordered others around. He kept a close eye on Lord Grim and maintained a certain distance from him. He calculated how soon Rotor Wings would end and cast a Chaotic Rain at the place, where Lord Grim would stop.

Lord Grim landed just where Wei Chen predicted he would land, but the Thousand Chance Umbrella became an actual umbrella. Lord Grim walked straight out of the rain.

Compared to other shields, the Thousand Chance Umbrella was more convenient at blocking moves from above too.

“F*ck, what a despicable weapon!” Wei Chen cursed. Lord Grim had been forced into a position he wanted, but he didn’t think Lord Grim would just be able to walk out of it like that. He had a limited number of subordinates with him too. His opponent wasn’t someone who could be stopped by just one or two people.

“Team 3 come back. He won’t be going to your area. Head towards area 3958, 2564. Team 1 cut off his escape path. Team 2 circle to the left and converge with Team 4. Four players who have high movement speed come and see if you can circle in front of him.” Wei Chen was ordering everyone in the team chat.

Wei Chen gave orders, while circling to the right. His peak had passed already and he wasn’t as skilled as before. Of course, against normal players, he was an exceptional expert, but in the pro scenes, he wasn’t much anymore. He still had confidence in stalling for time against Lord Grim though. After all, he had a huge level advantage.

Wei Chen had his Warlock hide behind a line of collapsed stone walls, while looking forward. Before, he had been chattering nonstop with Ye Xiu, but now he remained silent. Right now, he didn’t want to expose his position. He heard Ye Xiu’s voice come closer and closer and prepared to attack at any moment.

He’s here!

Lord Grim directly jumped over the stone wall and landed not far away from Wei Chen’s Warlock. Wei Chen was ready and immediately fired Curse Arrows to block his path ahead.

Bind!

Under Wei Chen’s practiced hands, a curved ray of black light shot out from his Warlock towards Lord Grim.

Lord Grim hastily turned around in an attempt to dodge it, but the ray of black light seemed to come to life as it also turned.

“Oh! Hand control!” Ye Xiu shouted as he rolled forward. The ray of black light turned, but only hit air. Wei Chen once again had the ray of black light move downwards, while beginning to cast another spell.

Hexagram Prison!

From the sky to the ground, a purple and black prison of light began to form around Lord Grim. If Lord Grim touched the light prison, he would immediately be sealed inside the Hexagram Prison.

“There’s someone behind you!!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“Only a little kid would fall for that!” Wei Chen ignored him.

“There really is someone.” Ye Xiu was still yelling at him.

“A ghost?” Wei Chen continued to look down on him.

“Ha ha, there really is a ghost. A ghostblade.” Ye Xiu grinned. A blue light flashed from beneath Wei Chen’s Warlock and an Ice Boundary formed.

At the same time, Chen Guo checked the system announcements and finally noticed something.

System Announcement: Tenth Server player One Inch Ash has completed the Heavenly Domain Challenge and has entered the Heavenly Domain.

Chapter 514 – You Were Already Prepared!

One Inch Ash, Qiao Yifan!

Despite having had very little association with the person, Chen Guo still knew who he was. Ye Xiu didn’t hide anything from those who were around him everyday, including Chen Guo.

Although Qiao Yifan was still a nobody among pros, he was still one of the best of the best in the game. Chen Guo immediately checked his character; as of now, One Inch Ash was level 55.

After being left way behind during the Christmas event, One Inch Ash had not only made a comeback, but he was half a level higher than Lord Grim now. There was nothing Ye Xiu could do. Between levels 50 to 55, there was nothing he could do but kill monsters in the wilderness to level up, and there was no efficient way to do so. However, the regular servers had plenty of quest chains and an abundance of dungeons. As long as players were willing to spend enough time, they could level up pretty quickly during this period.

This not only applied to level 50, but 55, 60, 65 …..

All of these levels used to be the max level in the game. To make the game’s content more diverse at the time, there were a large number of dungeons for players to enjoy for each max level. When the level limit was raised, those dungeons became treasure troves of experience points.

Qiao Yifan started his quests for Heavenly Domain while he was still leveling up. After all, being a professional player, the skill tests required in the quest posed no problem for him at all. As for the Arena aspect, Qiao Yifan was not Tang Rou, and so keeping a winning streak against regular players was a piece of cake.

Nonetheless, with Ye Xiu as the leadoff, Qiao Yifan didn't spark off as much of a craze. His One Inch Ash was also unlike Lord Grim, who couldn’t gain any experience after reaching level 50 in the normal server and could only focus solely on the quest for Heavenly Domain. Lord Grim spent all of his time in the Arena, raking in victories, battle after battle. It was almost impossible for people not to notice him. Qiao Yifan, on the other hand, employed a much more gradual process. He saved up his victories one at a time, stretching it across a number of days, so no one noticed that he was another one who started the Heavenly Domain’s quests early.

Until he finished the quests, entered the Heavenly Domain and was announced by the system of his arrival did the tenth server explode in shock. Such announcements weren't that rare in Heavenly Domain, but it did surprise people for it had came from the tenth server. The highest level in the tenth server was level 58. This proved to everyone that whoever just entered the Heavenly Domain was undoubtedly a brilliant expert.

The moment One Inch Ash had stepped into the Heavenly Domain, a curious crowd had gathered. Chen Guo and Ye Xiu were too busy at the moment to notice the system announcement. Ye Xiu noticed through a different way soon though, because Qiao Yifan sent the news to Ye Xiu along with his greetings right after he had entered the Heavenly Domain. Ye Xiu immediately called him over to help.

“F*ck! You actually called helper!” Wei Chen, who had 19 helpers with him, roared righteously. Chen Guo was losing more respect for god-level players by the minute.

The Ice Boundary’s constant freeze damage immediately interrupted Wei Chen’s Warlock’s Hexagram Prison. Unfortunately, One Inch Ash’s level was still too low. Under such extreme level suppression, the Ice Boundary’s freezing effect was rendered completely ineffective.

Wei Chen didn’t know One Inch Ash, and so he thought that the ineffective freezing effect was nothing more than a stroke of luck for himself. After all, the chances weren’t 100% to start with. He jumped out of the Ice Boundary frantically, swung himself around, and saw One Inch Ash’s equipment. One look, he knew that he had been tricked.

He was no longer a pro player who had to put all of his focus on professional matches. Indulging his days in the game, he knew all kinds of items by heart, so it was no surprise that he recognized the weapon in One Inch Ash’s hand was a level 55 katana, Sword of Carnot. It used to be a very popular weapon, but its fame had faded away with the level 55 level limit. Even nostalgists wouldn’t bring such a weapon to an important PK match.

As the thought raced through his mind, Wei Chen clicked on One Inch Ash, whose level of 55 displayed truthfully in in front of him. With such as low level, Wei Chen knew the limit of the character’s performance even without checking out the character’s equipment.

“This is your long-awaited helper?” Wei Chen laughed. Suddenly, a glimmering flash shot into his view. The sword of Carnot was glinting right in front of him. Coming from a Ghostblade, the flash gleamed with a haunting wickedness.

“Woah! Not bad!” Wei Chen exclaimed, stumbling to dodge the blow. His Warlock raised his staff the following second, trying to cast another spell. Unfortunately, it was interrupted by the following strike from One Inch Ash.

Ghostblade and Warlocks both used cloth armor, but they had completely different attack power when it came to close-range combat. Even with weak armor, Ghostblades were still considered swordsmen. As for Warlocks, they were the same as Elementalists, possessing no martial skills whatsoever.

Trapped in such a tiny space by One Inch Ash, Wei Chen was actually in a pretty dire situation.

“Ah! Slow down!”

Under One Inch Ash’s constant slashing assault, Wei Chen’s Warlock’s left and right dodging was rather unsightly. Undignified words rolled out of his mouth ceaselessly. Even if Wei Chen started begging for mercy, no one would find it strange.

However, Wei Chen was not undignified to such extreme degrees. When he deemed his endless stream of useless words was unable to ease the ferocity of his enemy's attacks, his final cry was: “Help me!!!”

“Yifan! Don’t let your guard down! This guy will do anything to achieve his goal. He doesn’t have any sense of shame. Hurry up and chop him down! The faster the better!” Ye Xiu called out to stop Wei Chen’s distracting noise. He didn’t go over to help One Inch Ash out because some of Wei Chen’s guys had just arrived.

Killing Wei Chen was of utmost importance. Unfortunately, Ye Xiu and Qiao Yifan’s characters’ levels were too low to kill a level 70 character in such a short span of time. Consequently, the priority became stopping Wei Chen’s people from regrouping with their leader. Ye Xiu had no idea where this group of people came from, but he did know that they were just a group of nobodies. Without Wei Chen’s commands, despite Lord Grim’s low level, Ye Xiu was confident that he could defeat each one of them one by one.

“Sh*t! Ye Qiu, you shameless scum! I left the scene a long time ago, so I’m not going to talk about my past glory, but speaking of no sense of shame, why don’t you introduce yourself?! Stop framing good people!” Ye Xiu didn’t pay a single shred of attention to Wei Chen’s honorable speech. More importantly, the Ghostblade in front of him wasn’t distracted by his speech neither. Instead, his attacks only became more fierce because of Ye Xiu’s “Hurry up”.

“Little brother, pretty nice moves you got there. Which team are you from?” Although Wei Chen retired many years before, he still played Glory and his judgement was still very sharp. Qiao Yifan’s cautious and organized style exposed his professional background clearly in Wei Chen’s eyes.

No matter how fierce a regular player’s performance was, some wild habits would always be mixed in. This style was unavoidable for the older generation of professional players like Wei Chen and Ye Xiu. After all, they all entered the professional scene after playing the game on their own for a very long time. Some of the latecomers were able to learn from the earlier generation’s experience, and thus avoided a lot of mistakes and wiped away some of the bad habits from the chaotic gaming styles back in the day. Qiao Yifan’s performance bared such marks. This was how Wei Chen was able to recognize the boy in front of him was not only professional, but of a younger generation as well, hence the source of the title, “little brother”.

Qiao Yifan was an honest child. In addition, he figured the person knew Ye Xiu well from the way the two’s conversed, even though he didn’t quite understand their relationship. In the end, he replied truthfully, “Tiny Herb.”

“Oh! Tiny Herb! It’s a good team. Speaking of Tiny Herb, I have some personal connections with your team leader. Your skills are pretty good. I can talk to him later and see if he’ll let you play a starting position. It’s the end of the season anyways. Tiny Herb’s general situation is already set. It’s such a small chance to let the youngsters shine. I am pretty sure I can do at least that much.” Wei Chen gave a reasonable response, “You’re not bad. All you need is an opportunity to shine.”

Opportunity!

Starting position!

To a pro player, these were no words more attractive than those.

If it were the Qiao Yifan from a week before the All Star, if someone promised such things to him, he would probably be on the floor, thanking them for the offer with excitement.

But after he screwed up that Rookie Challenge and thought everything over, with Ye Xiu’s help, he finally came to a realization.

Talking about opportunities, wasn’t the Rookie Challenge an opportunity?

Yet he was unable to seize that opportunity.

No opportunity could be understood as bad luck. Being unable to seize an opportunity, should this be counted as bad luck as well? At least Qiao Yifan knew that he wouldn’t do that. He couldn’t use that opportunity because his level of skill wasn’t good enough, that’s all.

During recent times, he was no longer restless. He would not try his hand at another opportunity before he knew that he was skilled enough for another one.

Qiao Yifan could now laugh off the offer that was able to move him greatly in the past. He could even tell Wei Chen sincerely, “Sorry, I’m not ready to take that opportunity.”

“No!” Wei Chen sounded much more certain than Qiao Yifan, “The you from the past might not be ready, but you’re different now. You’re completely prepared now.”

Delivering such a passionate speech, Wei Chen even forgot to move his character. His poor Warlock just stood there stupidly like a sandbag as One Inch Ash splashed him twice in a roll.

Such honesty and compassion made Qiao Yifan slight embarassed. Right then Wei Chen cried out, “Your time has come! Fight for it, Zhou Yebai!”

Qiao Yifan was puzzled, “I’m not Zhou Yebai.”

“What are you talking about? If you’re not Zhou Yebai, who could you possibly be?”

“Hahahaha!” Ye Xiu’s laughter resounded from the other side, “Very impressive. To be more convincing, you even abandoned moving. You used two strikes just to get a name out. RIP. You’ve got the person wrong, bro!”

“Really? Who are you then?” Wei Chen asked.

“I’m Qiao Yifan.”

“Qiao Yifan?” Wei Chen mumbled. He stole a glance at the list of Tiny Herb’s members that he had just pulled up and added, “Isn’t Qiao Yifan an assassin?”

“Enough already. Are you still trying to trick him? Yifan, don’t listen to his nonsense. He has no connection with your team leader. He doesn't even know that Tiny Herb’s gate now opens from the South side.” Ye Xiu retorted.

“D*mmit! Who says I don’t know that?! I just met with your team leader for a meal just a few days ago.” Wei Chen protested.

“Our Tiny Herb’s has gate never opened on the south side.” Qiao Yifan added weakly.

“F*ck you! I told you that scum is worse than I am! I’m done with you!” Wei Chen roared and charged towards Lord Grim recklessly. A spell manifested in the Warlock’s hand.

Qiao Yifan was pretty confused by the exchange. He rushed forward, trying to stop Wei Chen, but only heard a warning cry from Ye Xiu, “Watch out!” With a flicker of his hand, the Warlock threw a binding spell behind himself.

Chapter 515 – This is an Ultimate

All of this happened in under a minute.

The guy, who just said “Your time has come!” in a very serious voice, might have gotten his name wrong, but Qiao Yifan still felt gratitude for his words. However, in the next instant, a dirty sneak attack suddenly came at him. Even though Ye Xiu shouted for him to be careful, it was too late for Qiao Yifan.

The two were only inches apart from each other. Qiao Yifan hadn’t seen Wei Chen mutter any spells. By the time he saw the spell coming at him, a black of ray light shot out from the Warlock’s hands and instantly wrapped around One Inch Ash.

“Sigh, young people!”

Ye Xiu and Wei Chen both spoke in unison.

“Shameless, too shameless!!” Chen Guo nearly jumped up in anger. On the other hand, Qia Yifan felt very embarrassed upon hearing the two sigh at him. He was usually a cautious and suspecting person. Whenever something bad happened, he would never denounce the opponent and instead look for how he could improve.

As a result, he regretted how he hadn’t been careful enough. He felt like the two sighing wasn’t wrong. He was too young and too inexperienced…..

At this point, struggling was useless. The Bind Spell didn’t do any damage, but it stopped the target from moving. It stopped the affected target’s movement for five seconds, which was enough to do many things.

Wei Chen seized this opportunity and he quickly cast another spell. Another ray of black light shot out from his hands and bored into One Inch Ash’s body. This ray of black light didn’t do any damage, but when the Warlock lifted his hands, One Inch Ash also lifted his hands and floated into the air.

Control Spell!

Control Spell was a Warlock skill, which allowed the user to control whatever the black light hit, but continually consumed the mana of the user. The heavier the target was, the greater the mana consumption. If the target was a living thing, like a player, mana would be consumed even faster.

It sounded like a fun skill to use that allowed the user to make a fool out of the target, but in reality, the skill was very easy to break out of. You wanted to control the target for a few minutes? Impossible. You might not even be able to for a few seconds because the spell could be broken with an attack.

As a result, this skill was mainly used to put the target in an unfavorable position or stop the target from moving.

Wei Chen used this opportunity to send One Inch Ash into the air and then prepared to throw him into a wall.

While in midair, Qiao Yifan could already see the crowd of enemies waiting by the wall. Being tossed into them would be like a lamb entering a tiger’s den.

“Do you think I don’t exist!” Ye Xiu shouted. Lord Grim raised his sword and slashed downwards.

“Ha ha, I know you’re there!” Wei Che laughed. He hastily retracted the ray of black of light and One Inch Ash fell to the ground. He immediately moved his Warlock out of Lord Grim’s attack range.

But during this small amount of time, he was able to give his allies enough time to arrive.

A Blade Master and Striker leapt up together and jumped over the short wall.

Lord Grim immediately turned around after completing the slash. He shot out a sword wind using Sword Draw and sent the Striker tumbling back over.

However, Ye Xiu couldn’t reach the Blade Master. These two hadn’t jumped over together. The two had some distance between them, one after the other. The gap between them made it so that Ye Xiu had no way of handling both at once. On the other side, One Inch Ash landed on the ground at around the same time as the Blade Master.

“Ice Boundary!” Ye Xiu shouted. Qiao Yifan didn’t dare to be slow and immediately cast an Ice Boundary.

“Interrupt him!” Wei Chen didn’t react slowly either and immediately gave an order. The Blade Master listened and sent a sword wind at One Inch Ash using Sword Draw.

Qiao Yifan saw how fast the attack was coming at him and knew he wouldn’t have enough time to finish casting. Helplessly, he cancelled the spell and dodged the attack. Even so, the light of a boundary appeared. It was a Sword Boundary.

“Slash!”

Ye Xiu ordered. One Inch Ash immediately countered with a Moonlight Slash after dodging the Sword Draw. The timing was perfect. The Blade Master was still in the middle of the Sword Draw animation and couldn’t dodge the Moonlight Slash.

Full Moonlight Slash!

Ghost Slash!

In one breath, One Inch Ash had completed two slashes, sending the Blade Master directly at Lord Grim. Lord Grim stepped forward. He grabbed the Blade Master and threw him towards Wei Chen’s Warlock. Wei Chen was in the middle of casting a spell similar to when Qiao Yifan had attempted to cast an Ice Boundary. He had no choice but to cancel his spell in order to dodge.

“Cast every single boundary!” Ye Xiu yelled and shot through the air, throwing another guy who was jumping over the wall back to the other side. Wei Chen roared in anger: “Why are you all lining up one by one to get over? Just get over all at once!”

It hadn’t been easy getting a Blade Master to help him, so his opponents wouldn’t be able to gang up on him one versus two, but after so long, a second helper hadn’t been able to get over the wall.

The two sides were only separated by a wall, so the players on the other side of Wei Chen could hear his voice loud and clear. They gathered below the wall and jumped up together all at once. Then, a blue light appeared from below the wall. A circle was drawn on the ground. The blue light rose into the air and the incoming players were thrown into the sky via the Rising Emblem.

“F*ck……” Wei Chen cursed, but he couldn’t do anything about it. Under Lord Grim’s protection, One Inch Ash had already successfully cast a Flame Boundary. Wei Chen was in the middle of it. It was already impressive for him to be able to avoid the damage from the flames. Where would he find time to cast a spell? The Blade Master didn’t need to be talked about. In front of pro players, the only thing he could do was attract damage. Under an AoE Flame Boundary, the Blade Master didn’t even have the ability to dodge the flames rising from the ground and was burned from head to toe. Luckily, the enemy was under leveled and the damage taken wasn’t too heavy.

All of their helpers were launched into the air by Lord Grim’s Rising Emblem. They looked like a complete mess in the air, making Wei Chen want to cry.

When they fell, some of them successfully Quick Recovered, while some of them failed. Some of the ones who succeeded were knocked to the ground by those who had failed. Lord Grim swept them away by using an Earthquake Sword. The ones who had managed to stand were knocked to the ground, while everyone else was sent into the ghost boundary.

Falling Light Blade, Back Throw…...

The damage wasn’t scary, but the most annoying part was the effects. Wei Chen’s subordinates were stacked on top of each other and couldn’t escape from it. It made Wei Chen want to scratch Lord Grim to death. Meanwhile, One Inch Ash continued to pile ghost boundaries one on top of the other. Even though the boundaries were low leveled, with so many boundaries layered over each other, they would certainly have an effect.

“How interesting. With your levels, trying to kill us is too hard.” Wei Chen’s group was in a sorry state, but he wasn’t worried. Lord Grim’s and One Inch Ash’s level disadvantage could be fatal. Even though they had controlled the situation, their damage output wouldn’t be enough to turn the tides of battle to victory. If they had been two Level 70 characters, Wei Chen would have surrendered long ago.

Right when he finished saying this, he heard a loud female voice shout: “Eat a bullet, you immoral b*stard!”

Boom!

How was that a bullet! It was a gigantic pillar of light!

A Launcher’s Satellite Beam descended from the skies and crashed directly at them. In that instant, the crowd was completely immersed in deadly light. When the pillars of light split, those who hadn’t been immersed in the light were swept into it. Between the two walls was a small alley, leaving them nowhere to run.

This skill didn’t come from a Level 50 character. This time, it was from a true Level 70 character. There wasn’t any level suppression due to the gap in levels. In addition, Satellite Beam was an ultimate.

“F*ck, why did this b*tch also come!” Wei Chen heard the female voice and responded in a very impolite manner because he knew that this time, the situation had turned bad. Don’t look at how the enemies only had three players. Lord Grim and One Inch Ash had strong control over the situation. They grouped them up like NPC mobs. Now, a Level 70 character had arrived. The character was a high burst Launcher too with a Sword Boundary increasing her strength. In addition, the enemy’s Plague Boundary decreased their defense. When the Satellite Beam descended, their health bars dropped like waterfalls.

When the Satellite Beam finished, she followed up with a grenade. Another explosion took another chunk off their health bars. She fired a Stinger, showering them with missiles for another AoE attack. This was all with the persistent damage from the ghost boundaries and Lord Grim adding to the fire. Wei Chen focused on avoiding the attacks, while watching the names on his team list turn gray. There was nothing he could do.

“Where’d that shameless one go!?” Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze stood on top of a wall looking down mightily. Right now, she was a killing machine. She swept across the bloody field, but didn’t see any signs of that Warlock..

“Did he die already?” Chen Guo asked. She had Chasing Haze shoot at the ground. With One Inch Ash and Lord Grim blocking the paths of the normal players, the players had no way of escaping. The field had turned into an execution ground. There was nowhere to run or hide. They could only wait for their deaths.

“He didn’t die. He got over the wall and ran.” Ye Xiu noticed Wei Chen’s movements and even shot at him. Unfortunately, he hadn’t been able to stop him.

“He has no loyalty! He really feels no shame!!” Chen Guo was dumbstruck. Could the guy have actually left his comrades to die, just so he could escape?

Chapter 516 – ln Close Pursuit

Chapter 516 - In Close Pursuit

The space between the walls had already become hell. It hadn’t been easy for Wei Chen’s Warlock to escape from it. He hadn’t left yet though and was on the side sneaking around like a cat.

What did it mean to have your troops defeated in a landslide of a battle? He was currently witnessing it. Two thirds of his team of 18 were instantly obliterated. Of the remaining six, two of them were close to death, while the other four were still fairly healthy. Wei Chen didn’t know why, so he asked them immediately!

When he asked, he found out that they were behind the wall on the other side and were sneaking about as well! These four heard Wei Chen’s orders and went over the wall together. However, they weren’t close enough and jumped a tad bit later than the others. Before the four had jumped, the rest had already been sent tumbling through the air by the enemy’s Rising Emblem. Thus, they didn’t dare be too careless and circled around to find a different area to enter from. Then, they witnessed their comrades slam into the ground and get blasted to smithereens.

At that moment, they weren’t sure if they should still rush over and help! Suddenly, they saw Wei Chen’s Warlock roll over and flip over the wall. The enemies even shot at his butt, so they immediately abandoned their original thought and retreated too.

“How sad! Be careful. Make sure you don’t get discovered.” Wei Chen said.

“You should be the one who should be careful! They’re heading towards you.” The remaining four reminded him.

“F*ck, then hurry up and come out so you can distract them!” Wei Chen threw his previous thoughts of concern out the window.

“Sh*t! You’ve got no sense of shame!!!” Even his own allies couldn’t bear it anymore.

The sounds of gunfire and explosions echoed throughout Milo Ancient Ruins. Amidst the noise, Ye Xiu shouted: “Old Wei, there’s no point hiding. Coming out and waiting for your death is your only route. Give me five hundred and I might consider letting you live.”

“Ye Qiu, go kill yourself! This senior vows to fight to his death!” Wei Chen replied.

“Don’t stop attacking! Don’t stop attacking!” Ye Xiu reminded Chen Guo, “As soon as this guy is out of combat, he’ll log off immediately. Don’t forget he has no morals.”

Boom!

A missile exploded near Wei Chen’s Warlock. Even though it didn’t injure him, this type of attack would keep him locked in combat. These guys just fired randomly, making it so he couldn’t escape from combat. Ye Xiu was right. As soon as his combat status cleared, he would definitely have log off without any delay.

“Think of your brothers. They sacrificed their lives for you. How can you be alright with being the only one to survive!” Ye Xiu continued to shout.

“Quiet down. You killed them all.” Wei Chen said.

“If you hadn’t ordered them to come back and save you, they might have survived. They’ve already lost faith in you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Shut up. They’re already on their way here.” Wei Chen responded.

“Your bluff won’t work on me. Even if you called all of Blue Brook Guild, you will still die today.” Ye Xiu said.

“You really have incredible foresight! Blue Brook Guild’s troops are about to arrive. Not just them either. Look at the world!” Wei Chen shouted. An announcement came up on the global chat.

Windward Formation: Lord Grim in Milo Ancient Ruins. Hurry and come!

“Ha ha ha, you think they can save you?” Ye Xiu looked down in disdain. Windward Formation was the name of Wei Chen’s Warlock.

“You’ve got guts not running.” Wei Chen said.

“I’ll leave right after I kill you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Say it when you find me.”

“Did you really think that our attacks were randomly aimed? I already know your position. You haven’t escaped from combat yet, right? So it’s not hard to figure out your position. Do you hear our footsteps? Probably not. We’re crouching as we walk. Watch your back!” Ye Xiu suddenly raised his voice.

“You’re going to die!!!!” Chen Guo was the one who got scared.

“It’s to scare him.” Ye Xiu said, while gestured to Chen Guo to look at his screen.

“Here?” Chen Guo whispered.

Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Shouldn’t we get closer?” Chen Guo asked.

“No need. If we get closer, he’ll notice us. That spot is a good position and has good range of vision, so here is the limit.” Ye Xiu explained.

“But even if we hit him, the distance is too far. He can still run.” Chen Guo lamented.

“We’ll take it a step at a time!” Ye Xiu wasn’t in a hurry.

As a result, Chen Guo positioned her Satellite Beam towards the spot Ye Xiu indicated: a place covered in straw.

The Satellite Beam descended from the skies. However, any player with a bit of reaction speed would easily dodge an attack like this without any setup. The three saw Wei Chen’s Windward Formation come out from behind the pile of straw and quickly escape from Satellite Beam’s range.

“Cancel your attack. Gatling Gun!” Ye Xiu called. His Lord Grim was already after him.

“Ah……” Chen Guo felt a bit unwilling to cancel her ultimate, but she still followed his orders. She took out a Gatling Gun and fired at Windward Formation.

Windward Formation’s movements didn’t look natural at all, perhaps it could even be considered a bit ugly. However, his erratic movements were effective and he dodged the bullets. This type of movements would be much slower than Lord Grim, who was running in a straight line, and the distance was quickly closed. As soon as Chasing Haze’s firing ended, Lord Grim immediately used his own Gatling Gun. Ye Xiu’s technique was much better than Chen Guo’s. Windward Formation’s movements suddenly became even uglier and wasn’t able to completely dodge all the bullets. A few of the bullets connected.

These stray bullets wouldn’t do much damage, but they still affected his running speed. Wei Chen was very gloomy and shouted: “Ye Qiu, do you have the guts to fight with this senior 1v1!”

“Okay, stand still. I’ll fight you 1v1.” Ye Xiu replied, but didn’t stop shooting.

“Pei, who would believe you.” Wei Chen spat and continued to run.

“Same to you.” Ye Xiu laughed.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash never stopped attacking. Right now, he was at the forefront and had closed in on Windward Formation. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze was chasing him now too. Gatling Gun was a Level 20 and under skill, so it didn’t have a long cooldown. If they kept on doing this, it was only a matter of time before Windward Formation was caught.

“We’re about to catch him!” Chen Guo was very excited. She was looking forward to obliterating this immoral guy.

“Hard to say.” Ye Xiu frowned.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo said.

“There’s a dungeon ahead.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Dungeon?” Chen Guo was startled and then looked ahead. Sure enough, ahead was Milo Ancient City’s dungeon entrance. Dungeons only had a lower bound, but no upper bound. Thus, Windward Formation could enter it. If he entered it, they wouldn’t be able to chase him.

“Isn’t entering this dungeon the same as dying?” Chen Guo was puzzled. Even though Milo Ancient City was a Level 55 dungeon, it was a hundred player dungeon. It wasn’t something that a solo player could clear, not even a pro player. Progress could be saved in hundred player dungeons, but saving progress didn’t mean one could leave the dungeon. It was similar to a pause, so one could come back when one had more time to continue progressing further.

“If you die in a dungeon, at least you can’t drop your equipment.” Ye Xiu said, “Did you not notice? His weapon is a Silver weapon!”

‘Really? I really didn’t notice! Where did he get it from? Did Blue Rain give it to him?”

“I don’t think so. He probably made it himself. He’s been playing for so many years, so it isn’t a surprise that he has his own Silver weapon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you think he wanted to kill you for your Silver weapon?” Chen Guo guessed. She still couldn’t accept that a former God that would actually stoop so low as to get five hundred yuan from a bounty.

“Probably not. Five hundred yuan is just a cherry on top. He’s mainly playing to have fun.” Ye XIu said.

“......” Chen Guo was somewhat speechless, but she could feel it. Wei Chen was cursing and fighting Ye Xiu, but he wasn’t actually angry. It was like sparring with an old friend. The two mocked each other and trash talked for fun.

However, their trash talking went beyond what Chen Guo could bear. Wei Chen was truly too immoral. Even Ye Xiu had his limits. In any case, Chen Guo didn’t dare be certain. Ye Xiu making her cough blood in anger over and over again was already enough.

“Senior, I don’t think we’ll be able to catch him.” Qiao Yifan had good judgement. After hearing Ye Xiu’s intent, he calculated their speed and Wei Chen’s speed and made a guess.

If they had reached this conclusion, Wei Chen naturally would have too and laughed in glee: “If you want to kill this senior, you’re still too green.”

“Give your mouse to me!” At this moment, Ye Xiu suddenly spoke to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo was slightly startled, but having experienced this before, she quickly handed the mouse over to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu took it and began controlling Chasing Haze to use Gatling Gun.

The bullets flew out and Wei Chen hastily tried to dodge them. A few of the bullets hit and caused Windward Formation to stumble a few steps.

Wei Chen was alarmed. There were still more bullets coming at him. He tried dodging again, but got hit by another bullet.

If he were a normal person, he wouldn’t have been able to react so quickly. However, Wei Chen immediately understood what was going on and cursed: “Ye Qiu, you shameless b*stard. You’re even using such methods! Where’s your spirit of fairness?”

“Then stand still. I’ll fight you one one one.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ptui!” Wei Chen spat. He clearly didn’t trust Ye Xiu at all. However, with Ye Xiu helping Chen Guo, the Gatling Gun’s effects were extremely different. In addition, her level was higher, so the effects from Chasing Haze’s Gatling Gun were much greater than Lord Grim’s. Qiao Yifan’s eyes lit up and he recalculated it. He wouldn’t have thought of doing such a thing.

One Inch Ash grew closer and closer and Chasing Haze’s firing became more and more dense. Lord Grim began firing with Chasing Haze.

‘Okay, hit him with anything you want!” With this done, Ye Xiu handed the mouse back to Chen Guo and immediately began controlling Lord Grim again. Lord Grim followed up with the suppressing fire. They finally caught up to Windward Formation.

“Slash!” Ye Xiu shouted and pounced on Windward Formation along with One Inch Ash.

Chapter 517 – Death's Hand

Wei Chen had experience with chasing, so he anticipated One Inch Ash’s slash. With a sigh, Windward Formation leaned to the side, wishing he could dodge and keep running. If it were any other ordinary player, Wei Chen’s move would be sufficient enough, but how could Qiao Yifan be considered an ordinary player? Even the most insignificant pro player was still an expert. They couldn’t be compared to normal players.

The sword light followed Windward Formation’s twisted body, Wei Chen saw it coming. He couldn’t do anything about it except attempt to dodge more drastically. If it were a 1v1 battle, it would have been better. Wei Chen would’ve been able to handle it, but Lord Grim wasn’t far away. By the time he escaped from One Inch Ash’s sword, Lord Grim would be there to take his place.

He now realized this was a dead end. His plans to enter the dungeon were hopeless.

Wei Chen immediately changed his mind, Windward Formation turned around and said to One Inch Ash: “Little brother, I can see that you’re a good man. If you pick up any of my equipment, you have to return it to me!”

Qiao Yifan was surprised. After a short pause, he answered “Okay”. As he was answering, he didn’t dare to move carelessly again. The previous experience remained fresh in his memory. Qiao Yifan was very good at learning from experience.

Right after he answered, Windward Formation quickly stripped off all of his equipment and pushed his chest forward: “Quick, kill me now!”

Qiao Yifan’s hand shook once again. He suddenly realized that his state of mind was still far from that of a top pro-player. He didn’t know who the person in front of him was, but he could at least tell that he wasn’t a normal player. Even among pro-players, there weren’t many geniuses like this guy.

“Quick, attack faster! Use more boundaries! Hey hey hey, you shouldn’t be this slow even if you’re level 55. Are you deliberately holding back? No no no, you should seize every possible opportunity to attack your enemy with the fastest speed. This is the only efficient way to reduce accidents, avoid mistakes, and decrease the effect of luck!” Wei Chen even started lecturing Qiao Yifan.

Qiao Yifan remained silent. Everything this man said sounded reasonable, but these words at this moment felt very weird and out of place.

“Boy, you did it on purpose!”

Finally, when he saw that Lord Grim had arrived and he still wasn’t dead yet, Wei Chen grunted in dissatisfaction and sent an angry face.

“Hahaha, he’s an honest man, but he isn’t stupid. Step aside Little Qiao and watch how I tidy up this old man.” Ye Xiu smiled. Lord Grim stabbed directly towards the naked Windward Formation extremely quickly.

“F*ck! You want to tidy me up by yourself?” Windward Formation re-equipped all of his equipment immediately, downed a huge potion, and said: “Little fellow, step aside, I don’t want to hurt you.”

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash actually listened and stepped back two steps. Ye Xiu stopped him in a hurry: “Qiao, why do you still listen to him! Get behind him and cut off his escape path.”

“Ye Xiu, you son of a b*tch!” Wei Chen’s trick was once again seen through and he cursed out rage. Windward Formation released a Curse Arrow shortly after.

It wasn’t focused towards anywhere. The light ball twisted and arrows flew out in all directions.

Wei Chen wanted Windward Formation to escape during the chaos, but Ye Xiu had already seen through his plan. Lord Grim used a Z-Shake to charge through the gap between the arrows and lunged at Windward Formation’s head with his spear.

Windward Formation had to dodge. Warlocks didn’t have many options in close range battles. All the strong skills had cast times, but when the enemy was close, who had that sort of time? Elementalists could teleport into a better position, but Warlocks couldn’t.

When a Warlock was attacked at close range, their only option was to dodge. They could also use moves like parries, but their physical damage was too weak. Even Dual Sword Style wouldn’t work. The result would be a knocked back by a powerful skill like Lord Grim’s Wild Blood Strike.

Bind Spell!

Cut Spell!

……

Wei Chen cast a few instant skills in an attempt to fight back, but his opponent wasn’t any ordinary player. He had the level advantage, but the effects of the advantage were all within Ye Xiu’s calculations. After considering these factors, Ye Xiu attacked Wei Chen. As a result, it was only Ye Xiu’s damage output that was a bit lower. Their ability to control the flow of battle were at about the same level.

If Wei Chen were a melee class, he could try to confront Ye Xiu head on and suppress his opponent, but as a Warlock, his level advantage was worthless in close combat situations.

A few moments later, Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze arrived. Seeing the black cannon aiming at him, he wouldn’t be Wei Chen if he didn’t have any words to say.

“Fine, today I recognize my defeat! You outnumber me, so I surrender!” Wei Chen said.

“Whether you’re outnumber or not is an entirely different matter. I can’t believe you’re still boasting when you’re about to die.” Ye Xiu wasn’t Qiao Yifan, so his hands weren’t shaking at all. In fact, he continued to attack fiercely.

“We have to make an arrangement! This silver weapon is the result of my painstaking labor. If I lose it, you have to give it back!”

“Sure, I will return anything as long as it’s not the silver weapon.” Ye Xiu said.

“Sh*t, don’t pretend that you don’t understand what I’m saying!” Wei Chen said in a great rage.

“If I don’t make you suffer, you won’t remember how powerful I am.” Ye Xiu said in return.

Wei Chen was originally going to stop, but he started operating madly again. However, if his madness could have helped, he would have done it earlier. Now, he was only trying to sting Ye Xiu a little before he died, but how could Ye Xiu give him the chance? Ye Xiu beat him up in a frenzy. Windward Formation’s life came to an end. A Circle Swing stabbed him and smashed him into the ground.

“Come out, silver weapon!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“Ye Qiu, go to hell!” Wei Chen cried. Windward Formation landed on his head and died.

“F*CK, Ye Qiu, are you a f*cking summoner?! GO TO HELL!” At the exact moment of his death, Wei Chen opened his equipment window. He immediately started cursing again. Ye Qiu was like a summoner and called out his silver weapon.

“Hahahaha, Old Wei, go cry!”

Ghosts couldn’t make a sound nor could they hear any sound. When Wei Chen saw these words and a laughing emoji floating above Lord Grim’s character, who was circling around his dead body, he almost died due to shock and rage. He opened his friend list and tried to add Lord Grim as a friend, but he got rejected immediately. Ye Qiu had turned the option to receive friend requests off.

“Ye Qiu screw you screw you screw you!” Wei Chen cursed angrily, even though he knew the person he was cursing would never hear it. Several people close to him in the Internet Cafe stood up: “F*ck, which sh*t eating dog is cursing at Ye Qiu!!!”

“This senior here! You got something to say?!” Wei Chen slammed the table and stood up. A dozen or so people also stood up with him.

The arguers saw that he had a dozen or so hoodlums by his side and suddenly lost confidence. Even though they felt offended on their idol’s behalf, their own safety was more important. As a result, one of them nodded: “Good man! Cursing Ye Qiu? We’ll join you!”

This shameless man was among the minority. Most of them slinked back into their seats when they saw the other side was more aggressive.

“Go play your game!” Wei Chen gave this person a dirty look. He didn’t even have the heart to curse. He knew full well that these tricks were useless against Ye Qiu, absolutely useless.

“What happened, Brother Wei?” One of his bros came up to him and asked.

“D*mnit, I lost my weapon.” Wei Chen said bitterly.

“Fuck!” All of his fellows shouted and looked to Wei Chen with the same murderous look, “What should we do?”

“Do what? Go play your games.” Wei Chen shook his hand. He saw Lord Grim was still showing off and chose to revive at the city. What the eyes didn’t see wouldn’t grieve him.

“Ah, he’s gone.” Ye Xiu felt that it was a bit of a pity when he saw the body was gone. He had a strong opinion against the fact that he couldn’t communicate with the dead. It’s a game, why does it have to be so serious? Wouldn’t it be great to hear the complaints of those who lost their weapon?

“Check the weapon, hurry!” Chen Guo couldn’t wait. She has been rattling and raring to see the silver weapon since Ye Xiu picked it up.

“Okay, okay!” Ye Xiu opened his inventory as he spoke. Before he had the silver weapon, he couldn’t see the weapon’s stats, only the color of the Windward Formation’s weapon. Only now could he see the weapon’s stats in detail.

This silver weapon was a Warlock’s Scepter.

Death’s Hand, Level 60

Weight 3kg, Attack Speed 2

Physical Damage 530, Magic Damage 777

Intelligence +45

Dark Element Strengthen +20

Dark Element Resistance +20

Magic Critical Attack Chance +10%

Magic cast speed +10

Cast Distance +2

“Amazing!” Chen Guo could tell if a weapon was good or not. It was a true silver weapon just by looking at the base stats. The attributes were higher than an orange weapon. The intelligence, dark element strengthen, magic critical attack, magic cast, cast distance…These were all very useful additional attributes for Warlocks. This was the embodiment of a silver weapon’s value.

Other than the stats being better than that of an orange weapon, the additional attributes of the silver weapon were customized according to the player’s need. You could create whatever you liked, whatever you needed if you just put in the effort.

Just by looking at the attack attribute alone, Death’s Hand was equivalent to a Level 70 Purple weapon. The value of Death Hand’s was way above a Level 70 Purple weapon with all the additional properties. Even a Level 70 Orange weapon wouldn’t have all these useful stats together, let alone a Level 70 Purple weapon.

“It’s not even Level 70 and it doesn’t increase any skill levels!” Ye Xiu could still find faults in it.

As he was speaking, someone messaged him on QQ, Ye Xiu opened it and laughed. It was Wei Chen. He couldn’t find Ye Xiu in the game, so he looked for him on QQ.

“Son of a b*tch! Give me back my silver weapon!” Wei Chen cursed.

“Don’t disturb me, old Wei. You just threw me under the bus on global chat, Now I have to concentrate on dealing with people you sent after me. If by any chance I died, and your Death Hand’s dropped…what do you think would happen?” Ye Xiu asked.

“F*ck, then why are you still online? Are you waiting to die?!”

Chapter 518 – Old Wei

“Ha, I need more time to study your silver weapon. How is it? Do you have a plan for future upgrades? Ye Xiu asked casually.

“If you’re not going to log off, then you’d better store it somewhere safe for this senior!” Wei Chen shouted out of rage.

“Relax, relax. Hey, do you have any extra materials?” Ye Xiu asked.

“F*ck off, I don’t even have enough for myself.” Wei Chen said.

“What do you need materials for? You don’t even have a silver weapon anymore.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck you, f*ck your mom, f*ck your dad!” Wei Chen cursed furiously

“To be honest, you’re only playing the game, so you don’t really need high-end equipment! Keeping it is just a burden for you. You have to worry about it all the time. Why don’t you let this brother help you sell it? We can split the money. You can easily get a set of weapons and equipment good enough for you to play like a king and I can upgrade my silver weapon. I need to hurry up and continue upgrading my Silver weapon. This is something that truly needs to be done urgently.” Ye Xiu said with ease and sincerity.

“Screw you… Mine is also a priority. Do you know how much effort I put into this just to upgrade it to level 60?” Wei Chen roared.

“Do you have the plans for future upgrades? If you do, we can increase the starting price.” Ye Xiu was considering the value of Death’s Hand to himself as if he did not see Wei Chen’s message.

“What price?! That’s my life and blood! It’s priceless!” Wei Chen said.

“Your life and blood work is quite different from the one you had before!”

“Dark Element strengthen, magic critical attack, Casting speed, cast distance…” Ye Xiu went over the additional attributes as he typed, “These are all strengthening personal attributes!

The style is very different from Swoksaar’s Curse of Destruction.”

“The style of my weapon is none of your f*cking business.” Wei Chen cursed.

“You must be very lonely, Old Wei?” Ye Xiu asked all of a sudden.

“What are you talking about? I don’t even understand what you’re saying.” Wei Chen frowned.

“Why didn’t you stay in Blue Rain? I heard that Blue Rain tried to keep you as a coach.” Ye Xiu said.

“This senior isn’t interested in that sort of thing.” Wei Chen said.

“You’d rather stand on stage!” Ye Xiu replied.

Wei Chen suddenly fell into silence. His hands were on the keyboard, but he didn’t know what to say.

“Can you find that feeling in the game? Ye Xiu asked.

“Do you really need me to tell you? ” Wei Chen replied faintly.

“Have you ever thought about returning?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Returning? Me? Don’t joke with me, God!” Wei Chen laughed bitterly.

“Don’t tell me you’re satisfied?” Ye Xiu said.

“Even if I’m not, so what?” Wei Chen asked.

“You can try again!” Ye Xiu said.

“Try again? Like this, at level 70, using a level 60 high-end silver weapon? Taking 19 brothers who follow me every day, but failed to handle two level 50s like you guys? Go back like this? Go back and do what?” Wei Chen’s words were mixed with pain. The helplessness brought by time had left a deep scar on him long time ago.

Ye Xiu asked him if he was satisfied.

He could answer without thinking.

Of course not!

He too carried hopes and dreams when he entered the pro scene, but his career had only lasted two short years.

Within two years, the Alliance grew rapidly from inexperienced to mature, but as for him, he was constantly on the decline. He desperately tried to prolong his career, trying to stay for even a single moment longer in the growing Alliance, but all of his efforts were useless. He could clearly feel his deterioration. Game after game, he soon reached the point where his ability fell short of his ambition.

What if I were born a few years later!

Wei Chen had imagined it countless times before.

But regretfully, there were no what if’s in reality. He could only admire and envy those lively youngsters. He had tried to lay his dreams and ambitions on these young people so that maybe he wouldn’t feel so lonely. He failed. He realized that he yearned for a chance to stand on the stage again. The feeling of existence that he wanted couldn’t be satisfied by entrusting his hopes to someone else.

When Blue Rain tactfully asked him to take on the role of a coach for the next season, he immediately knew that everything had come to an end.

He thanked them, but rejected the invitation. He also rejected invitations from other clubs, even though some were invitations for him to be a player.

He had dreams. He had hopes. He didn’t want to be like a piece of seaweed spread on the beach, getting beaten by waves over and over again. Therefore, that season, the second season of the Pro Alliance, he decisively announced his retirement. He ignored all the persuasions for him to stay and cleanly left the professional scene.

For a time, he wanted to give up Glory as well, but he couldn’t let it go. Thus, Windward Formation was created. He even developed a silver weapon for himself. There were countless times that he dreamed that he went back with Windward Formation and his silver weapon Death’s Hand, to the time when the Alliance had just begun. He too was like these youngsters, full of energy. He could play for two years, three years, five years, eight years, forever…

Wei Chen was laden with grief as these thoughts rushed through until he suddenly realized that all his friends around him were looking at him as if he were mad. He quickly pulled himself back together, and become his ruffian self again. He looked at the screen, Ye Xiu had already replied: “If you truly wish for it, there is no such thing as impossible.”

“Sh*t, do you still believe in the power of will?” Wei Chen quickly hid his regrets. He was Wei Chen! The same Wei Chen who didn’t know shame. The Wei Chen who could fight dirty. His hand speed may be gone, his skills may have declined, but his personality still remained. In this aspect, he remained true to himself. He was still the one who amazed Glory eight years ago, who got invited to build a team immediately after the Professional Alliance was formed, and became team captain as a top pro-player. He was the former captain of Team Blue Rain. The shameless Old Wei, although he didn’t like this nickname..…

“That’s right, will can determine victory or defeat. Just think of that fellow on your team.” Ye Xiu said.

“He’s a weirdo…” Wei Chen knew who Ye Xiu was talking about, “I have to admit, I made a mistake, a very serious one too.”

“I heard you lost to him. Was it that embarrassing defeat that determined your retirement?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Tch. Do you think this senior’s decision could be affected by such a trivial matter?” Wei Chen scorned.

“No?” Ye Xiu asked in return

“Of course not.”

“Not even just a little?” Ye Xiu asked again.

“Fine, a little…” Wei Chen said.

“How much is little?”

“A little is a little. Completely insignificant, negligible, little!” Wei Chen answered.

“No way, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“Sh*t, what do you mean?” Wei Chen shouted in rage.

“I can imagine the trauma of being defeated by someone whose hands were deemed as handicapped and would never be able to make it to the pro scene. I can imagine it...…” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck your imagination…..!” Even though Wei Chen said so, he couldn’t help but recollect the bitter blow of his defeat.

That’s right… The person they were talking about was Yu Wenzhou, the present team captain of Blue Rain, Alliance’s number one Warlock, Swoksaar’s controller.

At the beginning of the Alliance, he was just a young lad who signed up for the club’s team training camp. He wasn’t even close to having the qualification to enter a pro team.

From the beginning, the pros on the team, including Wei Chen, saw this youth as a passing guest. His hand speed could be considered decent amongst average players. But in the training camp for future professionals, his hand speed was considered unimaginably slow.

All of them thought he would be eliminated in the first round of selection. No one ever thought that he would manage to stay until the end.

He remained in the team by barely surviving every round of selection. Even though he stayed, he was only thought to be lucky. No ever thought about his growth because nobody expected anything from him. At that time, everyone’s attention was focused on another one, someone Wei Chen had brought back from the game.

According to Wei Chen, the precise eyes and techniques of the youth when killing steal showed much promise. However, most people believed that Wei Chen related to the youth because of their shared shamelessness.

This youth was truly talented. He quickly became the rising hope of the club. The Club began building up his his Blade Master carefully. At that time, the ace player of Blue Rain had been the Warlock Swoksaar at the time. Warlocks had strong crowd control, but the ace player of a Club usually had the burden of being the attacker to boost the morale of the team.

As a result, many Blue Rain fans named this part of history “The beginnings of the legends of the Sword Saint.”

Correct, this person was Huang Shaotian. The hopeful star who bore the weight of Blue Rain’s future. As for Yu Wenzhou, he was constantly being forgotten.

Until one day, during a training session when the trainees were being tested, Wei Chen lost to this opponent whose name he didn’t even remember.

“He was lucky.” Wei Chen repeated the comment he had said when Yu Wenzhou remained with the club after passing numerous selections. After all, there would always be winning and losing in a competitions. At that time, Wei Chen’s condition was already declining. He thought that he had just been too careless when he was competing against the youngsters of the training camp.

The second round…

The third round…

After being defeated by this irritatingly slow fellow for the third time, Wei Chen finally realized something. Everyone in the Club realized something.

“Thank you senior for your teachings.” He didn’t get proud because of his victory, nor did he lose heart because of his defeat. He was neither shy nor arrogant. This young man was like an immovable iceberg. Wei Chen immediately knew that he lost to this young boy in spirit as well. He suddenly felt that Blue Rain didn’t need him anymore.

This youth would become Blue Rain’s foundation and Huang Shaotian would become the blade that cut through any enemies in their path.

Chapter 519 – A Reason for You

Wei Chen’s thoughts slipped back to the beginning of the Alliance unintentionally. There was happiness and excitement, but that era eventually left him with boundless regrets.

Wei Chen had to admit in his heart that losing to Yu Wenzhou was not the sole reason why had stepped down, but it had been a large part of it. Otherwise, with his level of skill, even if he lost his status in Blue Rain at the time, he could still have easily drifted along in another place for a year or two. However, in Wei Chen’s eyes, drifting along was not an extension of his professional career, so he decided to end it.

He couldn’t tell his past feelings to the friends that surrounded him now. He always made himself look like a big shot in front of them. Ye Xiu was not as close as those friends were to him, but he was one of the people in the circle who understood Wei Chen’s situation back then.

“What about you? What are you doing? Returning right after retiring and all of the ruckus. Just what are trying to achieve?” Wei Chen retaliated at Ye XIu after much melancholy.

“Hey, after some consideration, I decided to stir up some noise again. I don’t want to end up like someone, all lonely and blue after just a few years.” Ye Xiu returned.

“F*ck off f*ck off f*ck off f*ck off f*ck off!” Wei Chen shouted out five “f*ck off”s in row.

“How about it? Let me bring you along for the ride. You can go back to those old times, too.” Ye Xiu offered.

Wei Chen maintained his silence. The other had the intention, and he was not at all without such desires. Recently, he often dreamt of returning to the Alliance. Honestly, it wasn’t like he had never given the idea any serious thought before. Nevertheless, the decisiveness of him leaving became the biggest obstacle of return. He had left so smoothly that he could not bring it to slap himself in the face in front of everyone now. Just like this, as time moved on, the distance between him and the Alliance grew and he found it harder and harder to gather enough courage to go back. Fortunately, today, there was a force pushing him to do so. In Wei Chen’s heart, the desire of returning has never being as strong.

“Don’t lose this opportunity. You even have the perfect reason this time!” Ye Xiu urged.

“What’s that reason?”

“Your silver weapon is being held hostage by me! In order to get it back, you have to return. For someone as shameless as you are, that’s a good enough reason, right?” Ye Xiu explained.

“F*ck off!” Wei Chen cursed.

“You can do it!” Ye Xiu replied.

This short phrase became another wall for Wei Chen. He was like a hesitating wanderer, insecure about his own strength.

“What do you think of me right now, compared to the me of the past?” Wei Chen asked.

“Your technical skill and speed can’t be compared to the past, but your shamelessness hasn’t changed. I’m really happy to see someone so familiar.” Ye Xiu answered.

“A few years ago, it was Yu Wenzhou who was learning from you in secret. Now you can reverse it. You can crush him by surprise. What about it? Doesn’t it sound great?” Ye Xiu added.

“Mm, it sounds good…” As Wei Chen thought about it, his heart was filled with yearning.

“Then what are you waiting for?” Ye Xiu questioned.

“What I suddenly thought of is that according to the regulations, you dirty b*stard still has to wait for at least an entire year, which means you will definitely miss the next season and will have to join the following season after that. Do you expect me to return at the old age of 32? Am I supposed to be grandpa to everyone?” Wei Chen spoke.

“32? You’re that young? Aren’t you like 40+ now?” Ye Xiu doubted.

“You f*cker!”

“We need time to get used to each other anyways. I’m assuming you don’t want return and just run back like a clown, right? Speaking of which, did you win any championships back then?” Ye Xiu continued.

Wei Chen was speechless. For the first three years, all of the championships in the Professional Alliance were snatched away by this guy’s Excellent Era. Who didn’t know that? And now this guy was pretending to be ignorant? So who was truly the most shameless person in the Alliance?

“You mean to say that the goal of your return is to be the champion?” Wei Chen asked.

“Besides that, what other goal would a pro player have?” Ye Xiu retorted.

“Good! This is a nice goal. Hahahaha, children of the Alliance, quiver in fear! This senior is coming back!” Wei Chen sent the message with a laughing emoji.

“You’ve decided? Are you sure?” Ye Xiu checked.

“Stop blabbing!’ Wei Chen snapped.

“Then we will have to face a real and important issue.” Ye XIu stated.

“What?”

“With your shamelessness, how can I believe that you aren’t lying to me just so you can get your silver weapon back?” Ye Xiu clarified.

“Ah… That really is an issue.” Even Wei Chen himself had to agree.

“Let him come to our place. Once we have the real person, there wouldn't be any more problems, would there?” Chen Guo, who had been watching the two’s conversation the entire time, added. She didn’t expect Ye Xiu to attempt to drag someone who had been away from the pro scene for so many years into his team. Still, after seeing Ye Xiu actually succeed, she immediately started to brainstorm ideas to help them out. If they were going to end up on the same team, then they would have to gather in one place eventually.

“Where are you?” Ye Xiu asked consequently.

“Siqi City.” Wei Chen replied.

“I’m asking about you in real life, not your character...” Ye Xiu was speechless. Siqi City is one of the major cities in the Heavenly Domain.

“Oh, I’m at City X.” Wei Chen replied.

“Come to our place. We can talk things out here.” Ye Xiu said.

“That will happen sooner or later, but I can’t leave just yet. That's what irresponsible youngsters do. I have a few things to settle before I come.” Wei Chen was already educating others.

“Well then, you can attend to your business first, but until then your Death’s Hand stays with me.” Ye Xiu agreed.

“If you f*cking lose it, kill yourself and wait for me to bury your rotting corpse. “ Wei Chen threatened.

“Okay. If you have some materials, you can offer them up now.” Ye Xiu went on.

“Ai. With the situation right now, it’s so hard to find some for yourself. I truly don’t have a lot. There are some low level and dungeon ones, but I’m really short on the rare materials too.” Wei Chen explained.

Ye Xiu knew that this was the truth. The current times were vastly different from the time when the Thousand Chance Umbrella had been invented. There hadn’t been any professional clubs back then, and there was no large-scale research done on silver class weapons. It was unlike current times, when every big club had a large demand of rare materials. Each club kept a close eye on the market and bosses that produced these materials. In the present environment, it was truly very hard to obtain rare materials.

“What do you have? Let me see if there are any that I can use. I am stilling trying to reach level 50.” Ye Xiu added.

They were chatting on QQ, outside of the game. In a moment, Wei Chen sent over a few screenshots of his own storage. Ye Xiu glanced over them and realized that, just like Wei Chen said, there were some common materials, but the rare ones could be counted on one hand. As for the three super rare materials that Thousand Chance Umbrella needed to reach level 50, Wei Chen had none.

Ye Xiu gave Mo Qiang money for the materials, but from Mo Qiang’s tone, it appeared that even with a few thousand yuan, they might not even be able to secure them. There was nothing they could do. Rare materials like this didn’t even have a market, so there was no set price. The prices were set when the buyer bumped into a seller, who actually had to sell it.

“Obsidian, aquamarine, and silk paulownia, can you get these three?” Ye Xiu asked Wei Chen helplessly.

“These are all from normal server’s wild bosses! These things are really hard to obtain, you should know this yourself.” Wei Chen knew what those were. After all, he worked on his own silver weapon for many years now.

“These are the three that I am having trouble finding. I can’t advance to level 50 without them.” Ye Xiu lamented.

“F*ck. It’s only level 50, yet you already need three super rare ones? That’s some expensive silver weapon you got there. Truthfully speaking, that thing is a bit unworthy. It’s true that I put a lot of time and effort into making my Death’s Hand, but I could treat it all as an investment. When I don’t need it anymore, I can find a team and sell it to them, but for your strange weapon, regular teams have no use for it. Unspecialized...talking about long term, there is no future for it. I am pretty sure that more developed teams would never invest too much into it, so your weapon is basically a dead end…” Wei Chen said.

“En, that’s true speaking of long term. However, if we look now, the power of an unspecialized with this weapon is unmatched, you see…”

The two began chatting about Glory in all seriousness surprisingly. Chen Guo, on the other side, felt a bit uncomfortable. However, her discomfort did not last for long. Soon, the two’s opinions disagreed and trash talking started right away.

“Trash!”

“Garbage!”

“Nonsense!”

“Is there anything other than sh*t in your brain?”

In that crazed trash talking, Wei Chen’s language was incredibly inappropriate. If this was in a competition, there would be red lights everywhere. He would be killed by the rules in moments. Chen Guo watched the two's argument for a while, knowing that she couldn’t interrupt in any way, so she could only put on her headphones silently and log into the game.

In the game, the three of them had already left the Milo Ancient Ruins. They didn’t see with their own eyes if Wei Chen’s message actually summoned a lot of players. Chen Guo asked her friends in the guild. According to them, some people said they wanted to come and see. No matter what, the three of them were no longer there.

In a level 55 wilderness, Ye Xiu was either cursing or discussing with Wei Chen while leveling up. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash needed to level up as well and Qiao Yifan played dedicatedly. Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze was more like a mercenary because her character had more attack power.

Qiao Yifan… would that child be a part of the team? Watching him setting boundaries, placing them, and killing monsters, Chen Guo wondered. She knew that he was still part of Tiny Herb, a member of a champion team. It was just his position on the team that was unremarkable. After this season, his contract would end and he would probably have some difficulty maintaining his position.

The professional scene was pretty harsh, Chen Guo thought quietly. However, watching her own team taking shape little by little filled her heart with hope.

Chapter 520 – Qualification Tournament

Seeing the team taking shape, Chen Guo was full of hope and felt very glad. She had a smile on her face the entire time at lunch.

“What’s making you so happy?” Tang Rou soon saw Chen Guo’s abnormal behavior. She wasn't there that morning, since she had been working downstairs at the front desk.

“The team is growing so smoothly.” Chen Guo commented on the recruitment of the old God.

“Think about it, we already have enough people to build a team. Our goal is the championship!” Chen Guo said excitingly.

“We’re still extremely far from that goal!” Ye Xiu laughed bitterly, pouring cold water all over Chen Guo’s excitement. “You already know Little Qiao. He’s a nobody in the champion team, but in our team, he’s our number two player. Don’t you think we’re still far away from being champions?”

“It was you who said it, so you must have some solution!” Chen Guo said.

“We’ll have to take things slowly for now!” Ye Xiu said.

“What about you, Little Tang?” Chen Guo turned to Tang Rou eagerly, “If you’ve truly decided to become a pro player, then stop working! Just focus on the game. I’ll still pay you your salary.”

“I…… Alright…...” Tang Rou was going to say something, and then she saw the expression of expectation from Chen Guo, so she nodded.

“Ha ha, that’s great. Work on leveling. Soon you can enter the Heavenly Domain as well.” Chen Guo said.

“How is Steamed Bun doing?” Ye Xiu asked Tang Rou.

“He’s usually there when I get online. Whenever I level up, he will send an “AHHHHHHH” to scream at me. He’s level 51 or 52.” Tang Rou smiled and answered.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was leveled by someone else. Even though his speed of leveling couldn’t compare to those new server accounts in the big guilds, it was much faster than a normal player’s levelling speed. Steamed Bun Invasion did the leveling by himself. He and One Inch Ash had started at the same level, but with the same amount of time, he had fallen behind a few levels.

“And Concealed Light?” Ye Xiu also asked about Concealed Light.

“He’s about the same level as Steamed Bun.” Tang Rou said.

“Oh.” Ye Xiu nodded without saying anything more.

“So, Concealed Light will join in too?” Chen Guo was quite familiar with these people. Concealed Light wasn’t like Tang Rou or Steamed Bun Invasion. These two people had incredible technical skill. Don’t underestimate them because they’re noobs. In a 1v1, if the opponent wasn’t exceptionally experienced, the opponent would get massacred. Tang Rou even had the glorious history of killing a pro player. That isn’t something that can be done through pure luck.

As for Concealed Light, he was somehow deficient in this aspect. His technical skill was completely obsolete and he had even chosen to play a Summoner. If it were just for fun, the technical skill required for a Summoner was extremely simple, but if one wanted to play it at a high level, the requirements for technical skill were extremely high. The thought of expecting a rookie summoner play at a pro level made Chen Guo shiver.

“Take it slowly, we’ll all have opportunities.” Ye Xiu replied in a comforting manner, “Why don’t you practice too? Maybe you can even be used as a sub or something.”

I’m only a sub…Chen Guo really wanted to smash him dead with a chair, but objectively compared to other people on the team, she fell short of everyone, except Concealed Light. What a tragedy!

After the meal, Tang Rou continued to work the front desk. Even though she had decided to play the game professionally, the schedule of the Internet Cafe was already set. Chen Guo couldn’t remove one person all of a sudden. She needed time to make adjustments. She might even have to employ a new attendant. This small investment was nothing to her. In theory, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were already pro players. Paying pro players the salary of an Internet Cafe employee was something Chen Guo should gloat on in secret.

They were all leveling in the afternoon, except for Qiao Yifan.

This kid was well-behaved. Even though there wasn’t a future for him in Tiny Herb, he still took his training seriously and completed it on time. It’s just his heart was now focused on his Ghostblade. He had the Assassin account at Tiny Herb, but he did not do much training for assassin related skills. His mind was occupied with how to use an Assassin to practice Ghostblade skills.

Chen Guo still helped them level. However, this afternoon she seemed to be busy. No one knew who she was talking to. They just heard the sound of typing. As time went by, her facial expression became heavier and heavier. By dinner time, she was completely different from the gleaming person she had been at lunch.

“What’s wrong?” Tang Rou was scared for her. She looked at Ye Xiu with an inquiring expression. She was smart. She knew that those two were together every day, so she would tell happy stuff to Chen Guo and ask Ye Xiu for troubling stuff.

“I don’t know!” Ye Xiu knew that something might have happened when she was chatting with another person that afternoon, but he hadn’t peeped on their conversation, so he didn’t know who Chen Guo was talking to.

“Err, there’s something…” Chen Guo looked as if she was afraid to look at them and was too embarrassed to speak.

“Yes?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Well…I was talking to Loulan Slash this afternoon.” Chen Guo said.

“Loulan Slash?” Ye Xiu was lost for a moment. What did she need to talk about with Loulan Slash that made her act this way?

“I asked him to give me some information on joining the Alliance. It seems like there are a few compulsory requirements.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh…” Ye Xiu started to understand the situation, but he did not reveal his thoughts. He smiled and asked: “And?”

“I’m afraid…I can’t meet some of the requirements …” Chen Guo finally said it. She wanted to cry. After Loulan Slash gave her an explanation in the afternoon, she felt her heart turn to ice. It wasn’t that she was afraid she wouldn’t be able to meet some of the requirements for applying to the Alliance. It was that she couldn’t meet even a single one of the requirements, not even if she were to sell the Internet Cafe. The requirement for a stadium with a certain amount of seats alone had sealed her hopes. She was even more desperate after Loulan Slash disclosed inside information to her. The next season, the live game would employ visual projection technology. All hosting clubs must satisfy the technological requirements.

“I’m sorry…” Chen Guo lowered her head. She had been the one excited for the formation of a team, but she failed at the crucial moment. She really regretted it. Why didn’t she learn about these things before!

“Don’t worry, I wasn’t going to apply for the Alliance like Loulan Slash did anyway.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Chen Guo lifted her head.

“You don’t know?” Ye Xiu looked at Chen Guo. “ Every year two teams drop out of the Alliance, so there are two places for new teams. One of them enters the Alliance like Loulan Slash. They apply for the Alliance,and the Alliance will examine them and approve the qualified team to enter. The other team is decided through a qualification tournament.”

“Qualification tournament…You mean, the revival tournament?” Chen Guo asked.

“Exactly…Due to a special reason, the qualification tournament is often called a revival tournament.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“For what reason?” Tang Rou wasn’t happy. It seemed like both of them knew the reason and had stopped there, but she was just a newbie who didn’t know anything, so she hurriedly asked.

“For this qualification tournament, there are only two simple requirements: enough team members and a participation fee. There are no other requirements, which means, the two pro teams that were relegated can still compete in the qualification tournament. Pro teams are much more competitive than any random team. Even though there are some strong teams that can cause problems for the pro teams in the qualification tournament every year, in all of the previous seasons, the teams that came through the qualification tournament were pro teams. That is to say, of the two teams that got relegated, one of them has always returned to the Alliance through the qualification tournament one year later. That’s why people call it the revival tournament, because it feels like an intended opportunity for the two eliminated teams to re-enter. Well, sometimes there aren’t two, there might be three or four previously relegated teams. The teams that failed to revive in the past will sometimes try again the next year.” Ye Xiu explained.

“Oh, now I see!” Tang Rou nodded.

“So all we need to do is participate in the qualification competition and win all the way to the end! The Alliance will figure out some way and help you complete the necessary compulsory requirements. But speaking of this, the Alliance has never troubled by an amateur team before through the revival tournament. It seems like I’ll have to make history.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“That’s not the point!” Chen Guo was frustrated, “ The revival tournament is a knockout tournament! Losing one game results in immediate elimination, a year wasted! What if…”

“There are risks in everything. Even if you apply for the Alliance, the risk still exists. There is probably more than one team applying for the Alliance. It’s not enough to barely reach the requirements if you want to be approved. The Alliance will inspect your investment. A team will never be taken seriously if they barely meets the minimum requirements. “ Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was stunned. She couldn’t even fulfill the minimum requirements. Now she knew that even if she were able to satisfy those standards, she would most likely get beaten by other more competitive opponents. The competition here was simply money.

Chen Guo was only the owner of an internet cafe! What financial strength did she have to compete with?

“The qualification tournament is our only way. Instead of thinking what could happen, concentrate on preventing those things from happening. We can make good use of this year to break in our team members and perfect our teamwork.” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes, that’s right!” Tang Rou nodded, she already looked full of hope.

“The qualification tournament for this season is happening right now. You can look into it. The qualification tournament and the league games take place at the same time. By the end of the season, the qualification tournament will produce its final result. That’s when twenty teams for the next season comes out. There are many teams participating in the qualification tournament. If it continues to develop, it should develop into a secondary league. Well, well, the Alliance is growing so very fast isn’t it.” Ye Xiu sighed.

Chapter 521 – Where Dreams Start

Chen Guo didn’t even want to eat after she heard what Ye Xiu had said. She quickly finished her dinner and went about learning the requirements for the qualification tournament.

On the official website of the Glory Alliance, Chen Guo soon found a complete introduction and advertisements for the qualification tournament. As soon as she opened the site, she saw the slogan for the qualification tournament: the place where dreams begin.

Cheesy! Chen Guo thought to herself and hastily went digging for information. As she learned more and more, she found that it was exactly as Ye Xiu had described to her. The only difference was that the official publication had a more of an advertisement tone to it. It said that every participating team “had a chance to fulfill their dreams”. Teams with outstanding performances were said to be “living their dreams”. The pro teams that re-entered the Alliance were said to have their dreams “saved”.

But the most appealing ones were the players who were discovered through the qualification tournament and were selected by professional teams. For these people, the qualification tournament was truly what the slogan had promised, a place where dreams began.

After Chen Guo read through everything, she became so excited and so eager that she wished that the qualification tournament would start tomorrow. They would first “have a chance to fulfill their dreams” and then “live their dreams”. Finally, the qualification tournament would “save someone’s dream”, while the others would “begin their dreams”.

How do we sign up?

Chen Guo couldn’t wait to find out. Then she found out that that signing up was extremely simple. The sign-up page would open at the end of the season. All she needed to do was follow the instructions provided by the website.

Why weren’t the pro games over yet?

Chen Guo immediately became anxious. She went to check the regular season’s timetable. There were eight games left in the regular season, which meant that there were still about two more months until the end of the season.

“Don’t be so hasty! The later the competition, the better it will be for us.” Ye Xiu was behind Chen Guo for a while. He saw she was checking this and that, and guessed her thoughts.

“True. We still need a lot of preparations. At least, you guys have to be max level first.” Chen Guo said.

“Obviously. The other equipment will come along later on in the process.” Ye Xiu said.

“Right now, you and Wei Chen are the only ones with silver weapons, so we are far behind on equipment! What if we meet god level character fully armed with silver equipment?” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had already fought against top players like Wang Jiexi, Han Wenqing, and Huang Shaotian in the game, but he hadn't met any God level character yet. The time when he had fought against Troubling Rain was in the Fixed Field.

Why were God level characters worshipped? There were three main reasons. First, the player had excellent skills that gained them fame through battle. Secondly, their skill points were high. The higher the skill points, the better the skill levels. It would enhance both attack damage and crowd control effects. The third was equipment. Equipment directly enhanced the character’s stats. If characters like One Autumn Leaf, Troubling Rain, Vaccaria, and Desert Dust were stripped of their equipment, they would be no different from any other max-level character in the game.

Ye Xiu was trying to create a new team. From a player’s aspect, at least, they would have to have a top player like Ye Xiu. All the others could improve their level through practicing, but from the equipment aspect, they were far behind. Even though Ye Xiu and Wei Chen character had silver weapons, they couldn’t compare to a character fully armed with silver equipment. The gap between two full set of equipment was obviously not the same with the differences between two pieces of equipment. As for skill points, that was something one cannot ask for. If one was extremely out of luck, one might still only have four thousand points after playing for ten years. There was nothing one could do about it, so Chen Guo did not even mention it.

“Yes, equipment is a huge problem. As you can see, there is a lot that we need to do this year. Winning the qualification tournament is only a small part of it.” Ye Xiu said.

“We can work it out!” Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu, she was also saying it to herself.

“We have to!” Ye Xiu said. He returned to his seat and started working immediately.

The second day, Chen Guo started rearranging the work schedule in the internet cafe to free Tang Rou from the front desk. She then posted an advertisement for employment and headed back to the reserved room. Her main task was still leveling with Ye Xiu. She wished she could be a pro player, but her age wouldn’t allow her to. She was too late to be trained. She didn’t possess Wei Chen’s talent, nor his experience.

Experience needed time to accumulate, that was for sure, but it didn’t necessarily mean that with the accumulation of time one could definitely gain experience. The forming of experience needed studying, thinking, and processing.

One had to actively work their brain to accumulate experience.

That was the exact reason why many old gamers might be playing longer than new pro players, but were less experienced than pro players.

Was it because pro players went through more battles? Of course not. The attitude was key. If the gamers played for fun, they were passively accumulating experience. What about professional players? They actively accumulated experiences, one battle, one game, one recording…They were constantly reflecting on these things.

Therefore even though Chen Guo had played Glory for many years, and had a lot of experience, the experience was divided into levels as well, and her experience level was honestly quite low.

She had to help everyone else in her own way under her circumstances.

Ye Xiu was leveling in the game. Outside the game, he received a QQ message from Mo Qiang.

“I’m here, what’s up?” Ye Xiu replied to Mo Qiang.

“I have two bad news, which one would you like to hear first?” Mo Qiang asked.

“Just tell me…”

“All your money is spent, but I don’t have everything you want.” Mo Qiang said.

“What’s missing?”

“Aquamarine. It’s not because there isn’t enough money. I’ve asked everywhere, and there is no stock of it anywhere. If there were, I would definitely have bought it for you.” Mo Qiang said.

“Well, thanks! It looks like I’ll have to figure that one out on my own.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll keep on the lookout for it as well.” Mo Qiang said.

“Okay. What about the others, do you have those?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I got them. You can come over and grab them. Damn, I’m too afraid to even go out of the city with these precious materials. What if I were killed and lost them, that’s one hundred thousand yuan right there! Even I want to hire a killer to kill myself, just to get these materials.” Mo Qiang said.

“I got it. I’ll come get it soon, but can you teleport somewhere close to where I am?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Sure. Where are you? I’ll head over.” Mo Qiang said.

In the Heavenly Domain, there were teleport portals between large cities. Otherwise, if gamers had to travel everywhere on foot in the vast lands of the Heavenly Domain, the Glory game company would have been bombed.

In some level 55 bordering cities, there were as few people as the level 55 levelling area. Within the Heavenly Domain, except for a few level 55, 60, and 65 characters who were abandoned from the time when these levels were the level caps, most characters were level 70. Gamers were active mostly in the Level 70 areas. The lower levelling areas were lonely, and the cities seemed desolate.

Arriving at the agreed place, Ye Xiu saw Mo Qiang’s character. Its name was Run Cockroach. The class of the character had a dirty style, it was a Thief.

Seeing Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim arrive, Mo Qiang clicked his tongue in wonder at his mix and matched equipment. He then traded every material he had bought.

“How are you going to get your hands on the Aquamarine?” Mo Qiang asked.

“I’ll go back to the normal server and ask around, see if I can steal a boss!” Ye Xiu said. He used the word “steal”. In Glory, it was almost impossible to kill a map boss in harmony.

“Oh, the new server. Your level shouldn’t be too disgusting there, right?” Mo Qiang said.

“Yes, but at your level, that would really be disgusting.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hahahahaha, with this level, I couldn’t do it even I hacked the system.” Mo Qiang laughed.

“Well, I’ve got to go. I’ll talk to you if I need anything.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay. Come find me when you have big deals!” Mo Qiang said.

“Of course, of course.” Ye Xiu sent Mo Qiang’s Run Cockroach away and saved the materials he had received. Even though the rare materials weren’t complete, it could upgrade some forms of the Thousand Chance Umbrella, but because he was in the Heavenly Domain, if he were to upgrade the Thousand Chance Umbrella now, according to the irreversible rule, the Thousand Chance Umbrella would not be able to return to the tenth server. Therefore Ye Xiu didn’t do it at the moment. He notified Chen Guo and teleported Lord Grim back to the tenth server.

The tenth server.

A normal system notification showed up. It would be common for anyone, but the tenth server exploded in an instant.

“F*ck, Lord Grim! Why is he back!!!”

Numerous Guild leaders received this notification because they all had this top expert as a friend. The expert had gone to the Heavenly Domain, and none of them had deleted him. It was nice to keep him as a distant memory. In the end, it worked in an unexpected way. Last time Lord Grim had returned, everyone was melancholy. They saw him break a few records and then leave. What did he want this time?

The tenth server hadn’t seen Lord Grim for a long time. The guilds were finally developing in their expected direction. They had dungeon records under control. Players gradually realized the strength of the big guilds. Happy was popular in the beginning, but with Lord Grim gone, there were no new records to excite the player, so right now it was out of the big guild’s line of sight.

But now, Lord Grim returned! Did he want to break more records and leave? The tenth servers were finally forgetting about him, why did he have to return at such times? Was it planned?

The core members of the big guilds were coughing blood after they learned of this news. They really wanted to throw a protest in the streets.

Chapter 522 – Managing the Guild Storage

Despite having added Lord Grim as a friend, the only guild leader who dared to talk to him at this time was Blue River.

“What are you doing back here again!” said Blue River, emphasising the “again”. With Lord Grim gone, his workload had been reduced by a lot. Competition with the other guilds was something he was used to no matter the situation, but against this God, he repeatedly suffered setback after setback to the point where he would cough up blood in helplessness. In Blue River’s opinion, against such an opponent, if he could hide, it would be better to hide. This was a thought he had even before the guilds had allied together against Lord Grim.

“I’m here for a boss.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Which boss?” Blue River asked.

“Topaz Knight. That’s the name right? The one that drops Aquamarine.” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you going to kill him for!” Blue River continued to be astonished.

“Didn’t I already say it?” Ye Xiu said.

“You want an Aquamarine?”

“Yeah, does your guild have any of it?”

“No.” Blue River replied bluntly.

“How many times have you guys hunted for the Topaz Knight? Which guilds have killed it?” asked Ye Xiu.

“......”

“Why aren’t you speaking?”

“I’m not your spy……” Blue River replied.

“You’ve already told me about your guild’s situation…... I’m asking about the other guilds.” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course I wouldn’t know about the other guilds.” Blue River replied.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed.

Blue River was depressed, but when he thought about it, the lies that he came up with could only fool noobs. Even if his side hadn’t killed the boss, he should at least know something as simple as which other guilds had killed it, no?

“The Topaz Knight has been killed three times so far by Tyrannical Ambition, Herb Garden, and Excellent Dynasty.” Blue River said.

“How could your guild be so weak!” Ye Xiu commented.

Blue River kept quiet. Our guild killed most of the other bosses. Do you think I would tell you that? Blue River thought.

“Have you helped manage Happy recently?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Once in awhile…...” Blue River felt embarrassed talking about this. The guild leader ran over to the Heavenly Domain, but he was still managing Happy quite meticulously. But speaking of this, this opened up a new world for Blue River as a spy. He felt like spies didn’t necessarily have to sell out information. They could also work on improving relationships between two sides and prosper together. This was also a good way of developing his guild.

“How is Happy doing?” asked Ye Xiu.

The question made Blue River feel somewhat confused. The leader of the guild was asking the spy how the guild was doing. What the f*ck was this? Blue River really wanted to remind the other side that he was a spy. However, the phrase “I’m a spy” wasn’t something he should be saying, yet it now turned into a phrase he could casually throw out. Blue River really didn’t have the courage to say it.

“The guild is quite stable and it’s growing quite well.” Blue River said.

“It’s about time to establish the storage system for the guild, no?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ah…..” Blue River was surprised again.

“Don’t tell me that you thought that I wouldn’t know about that?” Ye Xiu asked.

Blue River remained silent. He wouldn’t dare to think that the God would not know such things. It was just that a person of importance often forgot many things and he hoped that he wouldn’t have remembered this.

“If we don’t set up the storage system, the guild will disperse sooner or later, don’t you think?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yes…...” Blue River replied reluctantly.

“Hey, does your storagehouse have any excess equipment? How lending us a few?” Ye Xiu continued.

“No!” Blue River rejected it firmly.

“Stingy.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Go figure it out on your own!” Blue River replied. At this stage of development for a guild, the guild storage system was very important. It directly affected the continuity of a guild’s growth. For Happy, it was no longer a matter of growth, but rather, it was a matter of its survival. This guild was always a thorn in the side to the other Club guilds. Using the guild storage system was a method that would allow them to eliminate Happy without bloodshed.

A guild storage system was a system that helped to maintain the stability of a guild as well as something that could show its strength.

A guild’s storage has a much higher capacity than a personal storage and its capacity would increase along with the guild’s level. In a guild, the guild leader possessed the highest authority over the guild’s storage, which meant that a guild’s storage was no different from the guild leader’s personal storage.

But just having a large storage was nothing to be impressed by. The core of the guild storage system were the items stored inside.

How to allocate these items was the most important part of the guild storage system. Currently, all of the big guilds had different ways of setting up the guild storage, but the theory behind them were all quite similar.

Each guild stored a lot of equipment and materials in their storages. The guild leader had absolute authority over the distribution, which meant that they could be considered the guild leader’s personal property. These equipments weren’t just for show. They were to used by guild members. However, each guild managed the distribution of their stored equipment with their own sets of rules. This is the so-called guild storage system.

Usually, guilds gave each equipment a certain requirement for guild contribution points. When guild members reached a corresponding level, they could freely use equipment within that level. However, these items didn’t belong to the players. They only had the right to use them. The guild leader reserved the right to recall any equipment to the guild storage. This condition was only exempted if the guild leader officially gave a certain equipment to a certain player. The equipment would become his or her property if this condition was met.

If equipment was lost or damaged by a guild member, they would usually be punished by a deduction to their guild contribution points. Guild contribution points would also be deducted by the usage of consumables such as potions and materials. In a sense, guild contribution points could be said to be a form of currency.

How could guild contribution points be earned? Each guild had their own way, but the guild leader also held unlimited power over this. The guild leader could give a guild member unlimited guild contribution points and could also deduct the guild contribution points of any member.

With this, a guild leader would no longer simply be a servant for the guild members. A guild leader with rights to distribute benefits to the members was a guild leader that could command respect.

But this depended heavily on a guild leader’s ability. Guild leaders who handed out rewards and punishments based on impulse wouldn’t win the hearts of the masses and a guild like this wouldn’t last long.

A guild could only maintain a healthy growth with a complete system that had a clear guideline regarding rewards and punishments.

The Club guilds had an advantage in this matter. The could use their immense wealth to build up their storage. For a normal player, to achieve such a large scale with only his or her own effort would be extremely hard. The starting equipment in the storage couldn’t be bad. It had to be rare items that could make people drool and that would be the drive for guild members to grind for guild contribution points to get the equipment. To obtain guild contribution points, they could hand in materials and equipment to the guild. With this, the wealth of the guild’s storage would increase. The more items and materials owned by the guild, the more player-dependent it became.

Benefits seeable with their own eyes were the main reason why players were willing to stay in a guild. Loulan Slash’s ability to form Heavenly Justice, a guild with a scale as grand as the Club guilds was closely related to his status as a money warrior.

Money warriors enjoyed the same advantage as Club guilds in the early stages of developing a guild. They could pour money in, helping them build up a wealthy guild storage. Despite not having the charisma of Club guilds in terms of attracting fans, they could still depend on their wealth to attract players.

Happy at its current stage could only be considered an ordinary guild. Its rapid growth in the tenth server was mainly due to Lord Grim breaking dungeon records. The players in the new server were noobs who had no knowledge of the guild storage system. Once they learned about it, would their expectations and admiration towards the expert that they idolized be able to stand against the temptation of good equipment?

Players in the tenth server were already nearing the level 60 stage. At this point, Club guilds were already creating their own guild storage systems. They didn’t do so in the early stages as players levelled up too quickly. Equipments that were low leveled were meaningless even though they had very good quality. At this rate, players that finally had enough points to earn the rights to use the equipment would find themselves no longer in need of the equipments as their levels far exceeded the level of said equipment.

A lot of dungeons were available once players reached level 50, which meant that players could level up more quickly. This greatly diminished the worth of level 50 equipment. People were more tempted by the allure of equipment that were level 55 and above. Core members of the big guilds that were rushing for the level 60 stage were starting to be more conscious of the guild’s storage. The rare Orange Equipments that they came across would no longer be made personal property and they would donate all of them to the guild storage. The equipment that was still rare on the market at this stage became the core of the guild’s storage. Next, obtaining and assigning different contribution points to Purple, Blue, and items of other grades would cause guild members to realize the difference between having a high amount contribution points and having little to no contribution points.

If Happy didn’t implement such a system, they would never be able to contend with the Club guilds. The sheer temptation of such benefits would be enough to cause Happy to fall. Towards Happy, these Club guilds definitely wouldn’t give up the change to topple it.

Deep down, Blue River hoped that Ye Xiu would forget about it as he was quite expectant of making Happy disintegrate without the use of force. In his eyes, Happy was a strong competitor.

Chapter 523 – True Goal

Lord Grim returned to the tenth server. In a competitor’s perspective, only Blue River came to pry around. After Blue River finished his prying, he was caught in a dilemma. The other side said he was there to steal the Topaz Knight, but he said it in such a straightforward fashion. Was it true or false? If it was true, would he want all the equipment? If it’s false…… then what on earth is he planning to do?

Blue Rain felt very stupid, why did he even ask this?

In reality, he had just blurted out what was on his mind. He hadn’t thought the other side would directly answer him. As a result, he was now wondering whether Lord Grim was telling the truth or not.

Putting these conflicts as competitors aside, the main subject would be Guild Happy’s welcome back party. The guild leader went to the Heavenly Domain! After understanding the concept of the Heavenly Domain, the players of Happy Guild all felt proud. However, after feeling proud for a period of time, they slowly came to realise something. Frankly speaking, it was only the guild leader’s personal glory, in terms of themselves, what benefits did they have?

None, absolutely none.

Apart from having no benefits, there were even disadvantages. After Lord Grim entered the Heavenly Domain, he had only returned once. After not returning for a long time, many of the records in the tenth server were taken by other guilds. Guild Happy completely lost their imposing manner from before and now looked as if it would gradually fall to becoming just an average guild.

The people’s will had begun to waver, but not much yet. This was because in comparison to a normal guild, Happy was still quite incredible. However, compared to the surging rise of those Club guilds, they couldn’t help but feel jealous. Those who had joined Happy admired Lord Grim’s fame and power. They had thrown themselves under this expert hoping to bask in his light. Their current situation and the situation they imagined were very different though.

Suddenly, their guild leader returned. Quite a few immediately surrounded him in excitement. Last time Lord Grim returned, he swept through several records and raised their guild’s fame to greater heights. What would he do this time? Happy’s players hoped to participate.

“Guild leader, you came back!”

“Guild leader, what are you planning to do this time?”

“Guild leader! Are you going to challenge the records?”

Ye Xiu laughed heartily towards their excitement. He didn’t hide his intention and said, “I’ve come back to do great things!”

Why else other than to create a stir did the players of Guild Happy join the guild? The players who found joy in their own way wouldn’t rely on someone else’s power to do things. As a result, when the guild members heard that they would be doing great things, many of them enthusiastically asked to join. “Guild leader, what great things? We’ll do it with you!!!”

“To steal a boss!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Wow!” Everyone was in admiration.

Their guild leader was indeed extraordinary. Boss stealing was a phrase specifically for stealing wild bosses. Normally, a guild wouldn’t gather together for a random elite or rare boss. However, wild bosses would appear on TV every time they were killed. Until now, regardless of which wild boss was taken down, it was almost always the big guilds that made their names onto TV. Now, Guild Happy could finally fight for a chance to come into the limelight.

“I’ll go, I’ll go!!!” None of them bothered to ask which boss they would be stealing. All of them signed up excitedly.

“Everyone will go, everyone will go.” Ye Xiu replied, which made the whole guild bubble up in excitement. Many players with lower levels were worried that they wouldn’t be able to participate in such an important task, but it turned out that everyone could go. It was as if they had received an amazing prize.

“Which boss are we going to steal?” Only now did someone ask, eager to fight.

“Topaz Knight, a Level 50 boss. Do you know of it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Uh, not really…...” Many of the people replied. The majority of them had only heard of wild bosses from online databases. These bosses were all monopolized by the Club guilds.

“Those who don’t know about it, go search it up and do a bit of research. Those who know about it, go to the Western Wilderness to level up! Spread out. Message me immediately if you discover anything!” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Understood!” Many people replied with passion. The guild leader had yet to stay for five minutes, but he was already working hard.. This type of leading were very refreshing.

Players of Happy Guild set off towards the Western Wilderness. Even the players who needed to know about the boss online also moved out. They were only doing some reading, so they could multitask.

At the same time, every guild leader from the Club guilds received a message.

“What? He plans on stealing the Topaz Knight?”

Cold Night, Plantago Seed, Lonely Drink, Backlight Bomb, Hazy Mist…… they received this information only slightly later than Blue River. Moreover, the information came too easily. It came straight from Happy’s guild chat. Only a blind spy would miss it.

None of the guilds was willing to challenge Lord Grim alone. Thus, Cold Night contacted Plantago Seed, Plantago Seed contacted Lonely Drink, Lonely Drink contacted Backlight Bomb, and so on until another tenth server guild leader discussion group sprouted up again. The discussion was once again the same old issue: what to do with Lord Grim.

Lord Grim was going to steal the Topaz Knight!

Oh, you have spies right?

The discussion group started off with this line, making everyone stare at the screen in thought. Every time they fought against Lord Grim, there would always be a moment of silence.

“Isn’t this an issue?” The information came way too easily. It made everyone feel a bit puzzled. Plantago Seed raised the issue and then waited for everyone else to analyze it.

“I’ve never heard of anyone starting an operation in the guild chat.” Hazy Mist said.

“And there’s no way he doesn’t know we have spies in his guild, no?” Cold Night said.

“It must have been intentional!” Someone else agreed with this point.

“It was definitely intentional, but why?” Blue River asked.

“To make a declaration for the east and strike west? Cross the river Wei?”

“Perhaps he wants us to believe his goal is the Topaz Knight by sending a majority of his forces to the Western Wilderness, but his real goal might in fact be something else.”

“It’s certainly a possibility.”

“Then what is his true objective?”

“Wait one second. What if his objective really is the Topaz Knight and he’s making us believe it’s a misdirection in order to split our forces?” Someone else pointed out.

“Then why would he even say anything in the first place?” Another person said, “Our forces are split up in the first place. Who would spend the entire day watching a single boss?”

“True.” Cold Night expressed his agreement.

“So it’s a misdirection?” Plantago Seed said.

“His guild has already begun to move.” Hazy Mist said, “Everyone!”

“How?” Everyone was a bit dumbstruck. When they fought against a boss, they always send their elite and core teams. They rarely moved their entire guild. This was because they knew there would be competition for every boss. If every fight became a world war. Everyone’s strength would be greatly damaged, especially in a server that hadn’t stabilized yet. No one dared to act so rashly, which was why everyone restricted the strength used carefully. After all, these weren’t necessary items.

This was a normal server. The extremely rare items of the normal servers and the extremely rare items of the Heavenly Domain weren’t on the same level. The main reason was because there were ten normal servers, but only one Heavenly Domain.

But now, Happy wasn’t following the tacit agreement between the Clubs. He had dispatched his entire guild, making the Club guilds unsure what to do. If they dispatched their elite teams like usual, they would be wiped out simply due to the other side having superior numbers.

“F*ck, we should also send everyone out and completely turn over Happy!” Lonely Drink shouted.

“Wait a second.” A thought suddenly appeared in Cold Night’s head: “What if this is his real objective? Because he knows very well how we do things. What if he’s intentionally dispatching his guild to lure away our elites in order to do something else?”

“That’s extremely likely! If his real objective is at somewhere very far away, then by the time we receive the message, it’s too late to hurry back.” Plantago Seed agreed.

“You guys wait a moment. This is a wild boss. It doesn’t spawn at a specific time. If he uses the Topaz Knight as a distraction, what if the Topaz Knight spawns but his real objective doesn’t? Wouldn’t he have done everything for nothing?” Hazy Mist argued.

“No, no. He probably isn’t thinking like this. He’s gathering his forces at the Western Wilderness, so we have to send our forces to resist. If that’s the case, then as long as his true objective spawns earlier than the Topaz Knight, then his scheme will succeed. If the Topaz Knight really does spawn first, then he can just switch bosses and try again. It’s a 50/50 chance. No one knows which boss will spawn first, so he can’t completely grasp it no?” Cold Night was quite detailed.

“Which wild bosses can still spawn this week? Do you think we’ll be able to find anything by thinking about this?” Backlight Bomb suddenly spoke.

The top guilds had this sort of information. Soon afterwards, they looked at the map and looked for a leveling area far away from the Western Wilderness.

“Wait!” Plantago Seed suddenly said, “I just received a bit of information from my side. I don’t know if any of you have noticed.”

“What?” Someone immediately asked.

“If Lord Grim is misdirecting us, he must have his main force at his true objective, so I specially had my people pay attention to the movements of a few of these characters and my people have noticed something.” Plantago Seed discovered important information and told them of it.

“Are you saying your people have been paying attention to Soft Mist’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s movements?” Cold Night immediately reacted.

“It seems like you’ve been doing the same.” Plantago Seed said.

“Where are they heading towards?” Cold Night asked.

“I don’t know right now, but they’re definitely not heading towards the Western Wilderness. I’ll have my people continue following them.” Plantago Seed said.

“Okay, you have to watch them carefully!!” Everyone cried excitedly as if they had discovered the new world.

Chapter 524 – Complete Chaos

The discussion group went into a period of silence once again. Everyone was anxiously waiting for a final detailed report. At the same time, they sent several players to pay attention to the movements of Lord Grim as well as the few capable subordinates under him. These capable subordinates had been exposed cleanly already and the big guilds saw their names everywhere.

The scouting went smoothly. Soon, all of the guild leaders present in the discussion group sent out expressions of delight. They looked as if they had schemes prepared.

“It seems like everyone knows?” Plantago Seed, who knew about this intelligence awhile ago, spoke.

“Almarshan.” Cold Night said.

“Correct, the Setting Sun Hunter. So this is his target.” Lonely Drink said.

“It looks like we can present him with a little surprise.” Plantago Seed smiled.

“This time, we’ve got to kill his spirit.”

“Yes, not only do we need to steal away his boss, we’re going to have him experience a total wipeout!”

The guilds began their preparations in excitement. They didn’t dare be negligent of Lord Grim’s elite team, so they dispatched all of their elites. How many people was enough? They had failed so many times that they could no longer make an estimate. It wasn’t like they could go wrong with having too many.

“When does the Setting Sun Hunter spawn? I’m looking forward to it!!” These guys were already imagining the beautiful scene in front of them. Getting Lord Grim to eat sh*t would be such an amazing feeling.

“If……. his true target really is only the Topaz Knight, then what?” Seeing everyone’s appearances, Blue River couldn’t help but feel uneasy.

“Hmm….. that’s true.” Cold Night, who had crossed paths with Ye Xiu many times before, also had a sort of premonition, “We’ll go elites against elites, a sea of people against a sea of people. We should also send some people over to Western Wilderness. It’s only one guild, after all. They don’t have that many people, so if each of us send a few people, it’ll be enough. There aren’t any strong characters there anyways. If we have the safe number of troops as them, we have the advantage.”

“Right, right. This way we won’t have any holes.” Lonely Drink praised.

Western Wilderness, Level 50 leveling area.

In the tenth server, Level 50-55 was the prevalent level range. The players in Club guilds, whether they were normal members or elites, weren’t in this range; they were at the top in terms of leveling speed. All of them were above Level 55 with the elites having already reached Level 60.

As a result, the arrival of an army of high-leveled players suddenly appearing in Western Wilderness quickly attracted the attention of many. Everyone in the army had tags from top guilds beside their name. Any player with a bit of keenness could tell that something had happened.

These high-leveled players had already received orders from the guilds. They were to scatter across the Western Wilderness, look out for the spawning of the wild boss, and pay attention to the movements of Guild Happy players.

On the other end of the map, the situation was exactly the same for Almarshan, just with more people.

The waiting continued, but the boss never came. The Club guild players were already getting impatient, but they couldn’t act irrationally, especially in a leveling area with so many people watching.

The wind sweeping through the tower heralds a rising storm in the mountains. However, this wind was taking a bit too long. Moreover, the spawn time for a boss was far less accurate than a weather report. The Club guild players quickly began to get bored.

In comparison, the Guild Happy players were extremely busy because they weren’t high-leveled players. The Western Wilderness was a very suitable leveling for them, so they could kill monsters, while wandering around.

The morning passed.

The eyes of the guild leaders had already turned red from staring at the computer for so long. There was nothing they could have done. All of them were nighttime workers and usually slept in the morning. Who could thought that the devil Lord Grim returning would force them to work overtime and struggle to the afternoon. They were completely exhausted. Seeing that the boss still hadn’t spawned, the guild leaders told the others they were going to rest and to wake them up if anything happened.

At 3:07 PM, the guild leaders were brutally awoken from their deep sleep.

The suddenly awoken guild leaders immediately asked what the situation was, while struggling towards their computers. Before reaching their computers, they already learned of the news: the Topaz Knight had spawned.

“What are Happy’s players doing?” The guild leaders practically asked at the same time.

“There doesn’t seem to be any movements from them.” Their subordinates reported.

“Ha ha ha ha, as expected.” The guild leaders were delighted and they immediately to discuss it in the discussion group. But not long after, they came across a very contradictory issue. Shouldn’t they try and steal the Topaz Knight from each other? However, they had invested a bit too many troops into the operation, so they couldn’t act blindly without thinking. According to a report, a randomly put together team was currently fighting the Topaz Knight and was getting absolutely crushed.

A wild boss couldn’t be taken down by some random team, let alone randoms from this leveling area. As a result, none of the guild leaders were shaken by this. Their main opponents were the ones in the discussion group.

“Cough cough……. There’s quite a lot of people over there. If everyone starts attacking, it’ll be messy……” Plantago Seed spoke.

Afterwards, no one gave a response. Plantago Seed saw this and knew these b*stards had already come up with an evil scheme. None of them were going to talk about it. Thus, the discussion group immediately fell into silence. The guild leaders went to contact the people at the Western Wilderness to further understand the situation.

Thirteen guild leaders each with at least a hundred troops gathered together at the Western Wilderness.

The Topaz Knight and his cavalry weren’t far from them. The enemy boss had just killed off another random team. Another group of players took their place. The thirteen guilds didn’t bat an eye towards them and only paid attention to their real opponents.

The deadlock couldn’t last forever. They couldn’t just stand there staring at each other for the entire weekend. The first side to move might not necessarily lose because no one knew each other’s cards or plans. Every side had to adapt to the situation every time a battle for a boss took place. Strength, strategy, luck. Any one of these could determine the result.

At the Western Wilderness, the small scale conflicts gradually began to spread out. Soon afterwards, even those who wished to join the fray until all others were exhausted first were wrapped into the chaos. Killing a boss entailed killing each other. One moment, two sides might be attacking and defending together. The next moment, the two sides might be at each other’s throats.

The boss’s health went down as players fell. As for those random teams, the smart ones had already fled. The dirty ones remained as scrap pickers. However, the scrap picking business wasn’t as developed in normal servers because the drop rate couldn’t be compared to the Heavenly Domain.

Amidst this chaos, the guild leaders suddenly received an intelligence report from spies. Lord Grim had ordered his guild to set out for the Topaz Knight.

“What? At this time??” Everyone stared in astonishment.

“The mantis stalks the cicada, unaware of the oriole behind?"

Guild Happy players saw Lord Grim’s message and began gathering towards that direction. Outside of the chaotic battle, players with the Guild Happy tag on top of their heads began to appear. One, two, ten, twenty, a hundred, two hundred…...

They weren’t high-leveled. Some weren’t even Level 50. They couldn’t compare at all to the players from the big guilds. However, they had more players on their side and happened to appear just when the thirteen guilds were fighting amongst each other.

“Stop stop stop, stop over there. Don’t give Lord Grim easy pickings.” Someone in the discussion group immediately shouted.

‘Could this guy’s real target actually be the Topaz Knight?”

“F*ck, get Almarshan’s people to hurry over.”

“They won’t get here in time. And what if this is just a trick of his?”

They were all pulling out their hairs in conflict! However, at least they understood one thing. If this chaotic battle continued, Guild Happy might become the oriole.

“We’re stealing a boss anyways. There’s no need to be nice. Let’s all kill the players from Happy first!” Someone suggested.

“It looks like that’s our only choice!”

Everyone unanimously agreed and made the command. In the blink of an eye, the thirteen guilds went from fighting each other to standing shoulder to shoulder with each other. They turned to look at Happy and suddenly charged at them.

“RUN!” At this moment, an order came out from Happy.

Happy’s players suddenly turned tail and ran. The big guild players were still far away and wouldn’t be able to attack them.

“F*ck, what is this sh*t?” The guilds were pulling at their hair. In this moment of confusion, the Topaz Knight suddenly led his cavalry towards an aggroed target.

The target couldn’t just stand there and do nothing. He hastily attacked back. The other guilds saw this. Not good! If this continued, the Topaz Knight would be killed by him. Thus, they immediately went to stop him. With the guilds fighting amongst each other again, Guild Happy’s players came back.

Guild Happy didn’t try to conceal their actions either. Lord Grim gave his order in the public chat, so the guild leaders received the message at the same time too.

What should they do this time? Should they turn and attack? If they attack and the other side runs, the boss will attack and nothing will change!

“Split our troops into two!” Someone suggested.

“Right!” Everyone nodded their heads. If they sent half of their troops to chase after Happy’s players and had half their players continued to attack the boss, wouldn’t that work?

The order came out. Half of the troops from each guild chased after Happy’s players. Happy’s players ran away again, but this time the pursuit didn’t stop. The big guild players continued to chase them. Even if they couldn’t kill them, they could at least push them far away.

Not long afterwards, Happy’s players were pushed to one area. The guild leaders received a message saying Lord Grim had called for everyone to group together.

“Not good! If we chase them randomly, our troops will be scattered……” The guild leaders suddenly realized the situation wasn’t good.

“Don’t chase them impatiently. Stay in formation. Don’t scatter!” The guild leaders immediately warned the pursuit team.

A response from the pursuit team hadn’t even come yet, when the boss team sent a message: “We can’t hold on!”

“What can’t you hold on?” The guild leaders were confused.

“Boss! We can’t hold the boss.”

Chapter 525 – Can’t Hold the Boss

"You guys can't hold the boss? F*ck, who's holding the boss' aggro? You guys can't get the last hit in??" After receiving the report, the guild leaders hastily asked in surprise.

Simply speaking, the monster belonged to whomever the monster was aggroed on. The items dropped would be protected by the system for that player. For the next 30 seconds, no one else besides that player would be able to pick up the items during that time period.

It all sounded very simple, but calculating aggro was actually quite complicated. Normally, the last hit counted for everything. It's worth several times more than a normal hit. This was easy to understand. After all, the last hit was the hit that took the other side's life. The other side would obviously have enmity towards the killer.

Apart from this, the first hit was also very significant. The amount of aggro gained for the first hit depends on the situation. There was a difference in aggro between the first hit from a player who took the initiative to attack the monster and the first hit of a player counterattacking a monster's attack.

In short, the general rules were very simple, but the details weren't simple at all.

Especially against a boss. Bosses had names, background stories, and personalities. Each detail affected how the aggro would be calculated for each boss different. For example, if you took the last hit, some bosses would have five times the aggro for it, but other bosses might have ten or twenty times the aggro for it.

Some bosses had increased aggro after falling into a red blood state. Some bosses were very sensitive to the first hit…...

Thus, understanding the rules behind a boss's aggro was a very important part of stealing a boss. Usually, the last hit never disappointed, which was why all of the guild leaders asked their subordinates about it. When two teams accumulated similar amounts of aggro, the last hit would often be the deciding factor.

However, the reply they received made them even more flabbergasted: "No, it's not that we can't steal the boss."

"Then what is it?"

"We can't hold the boss off!"

"What? Whose scheme is this?"

"This isn't a scheme. None of us can hold on!"

"What type of stupid joke is this? You guys....." At this moment, the guild leader suddenly stopped. He realized why this was happening at the same time, the discussion group exploded into a commotion. Clearly, the "can't hold on" wasn't pointing towards any one guild, but every single guild there.

They actually couldn't hold the boss.

Why?

The guild leaders originally found it hard to believe. They were about to call it nonsense, but while typing their response halfway, they suddenly realized what had happened!

Why?

It was because the ones killing the boss were new!

These players might be relatively high leveled compared to the mainstream players, but they were still normal players. Usually, the core elites hunted wild bosses. These elites were from the Heavenly Domain with many years of Glory experience and had a good understanding of the normal servers.

They could clear dungeons and kill bosses.

But these normal players? This was their first time doing it!

The Aquamarine Knight had only been killed three times in the tenth server so far and had only been killed by the guild elites each time. How could these normal guild members have experience in killing these types of bosses?

When trying to kill a boss for the first time, even if your team read a guide beforehand, wiping out several times wouldn't be strange at all!

The reason why the Club guilds could bring their normal guild members to levels higher than the norm wasn't because these guild members were crazy levelers. More importantly, the Club guilds had experts and veterans watching over them. What did this entail? When an expert or a veteran led a party into a dungeon, there would be fewer casualties.

As for five noobs, whenever a new dungeon became available, the noobs would die many times before clearing it once. In Glory, dying would result in a loss of experience. Dying would reduce your leveling speed, no? As a result, there would obviously be a difference in levels between Club guild players and non-guild players.

And now, these normal players, who had experts and veterans helping, finally encountered a snag. Against the Aquamarine Knight, an existence far stronger than a dungeon boss, these normal players had no way to hold on.

In the beginning, the guilds had a lot of players. The chaos made it difficult for them to see the struggling players near the boss. Afterwards, half of their memebers went to chase after Guild Happy's people. When information arrived about Guild Happy grouping together and the guild leaders became worried that something had happened on that side, the ones who had been left to hold the boss were already defeated.

The Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry had already summoned their war horses. They took formation and launched an assault. Their iron hooves lifted the yellow sand into the air, creating a huge cloud of dust in the Western Desert. The cavalry and the yellow sand blasted the players and enveloped them.

The players had never seen this sort of scene before. Glory didn't have any mounts. The Knight in the Knight class only symbolized a type of ideal. It didn't indicate a soldier on a horse.

The Aquamarine Knight and his entourage were a huge and menacing cavalry. Should they attack the horse or the person? If they attacked the horse, which part of the horse should they attack to have the greatest effect? If they attacked the person, what if their weapons weren't long enough? While the players pondered over these questions, the cavalry trampled them into the ground. The unlucky ones were even trampled on a few times. Those cut down by the knights on the horses took heavy damage. The ones that were charged down several times turned into corpses on the spot.

A few veterans led the teams, but they couldn't control the situation. Helpless, they asked their guild leaders for help, while hastily transferring the ones in pursuit of Guild Happy over to their side.

When the troops in pursuit heard their call for help, they were also confused. They had a hard time understanding why the other troops were being cut down by the boss, but when they went back to see, all of them froze.

What was this? What were they supposed to do? How do we hit the ones on top of the horses? It doesn't look like hitting the horses did anything. Ah, I fell! Ah, the horse stepped on me! Ah, where did that sword come from? Ah, I'm dead!

Corpses everywhere described the battlefield well.

How strong was a wild boss? Against cloth armored character, some skills could even one shot them. The Aquamarine Knight's cavalry might not be as strong as the boss, but they were still comparable to elite monsters. Their strikes were enough to deal heavy damage to any player.

The discussion group transformed into chaos because they clearly knew about the Aquamarine Knight's strength. When they took a closer look, the dispatched troops weren't enough to deal with him. No matter how numerous the troops, without an effective strategy, the troops would only be cannon fodder in front of a wild boss. The boss could easily wipe them all out!

It was too late to ask for help. The rest of the guild had gone to Almarshan.

The guild leaders looked on with deathly pale expressions. They realized what Lord Grim had done. Lord Grim had lured away the elites with his elites and left everyone else to take care of this boss. Their sea of people wasn't enough to defeat the boss though. What about Happy?

"If our people can't do it, how could Happy possibly do it?" Someone asked in puzzlement. Another person immediately answered back: "It's different."

"How is it different?"

"The commander is different..."

Everyone fell silent.

Commander.... It was truly different. Lord Grim was at the top in all of Glory, and their side? It would be too embarrassing to even make a comparison.

At the Western Desert, players from the thirteen guilds ran around the map in chaos. The Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry continued to chase and kill the remaining stragglers. Whoever they pursued, died. After all, the enemies had horses.

At this moment, Guild Happy had already gathered together and climbed up a sand dune. The troops were lined up neatly and organized. They appeared from behind, welcoming the Club guild players running for their lives. These players saw the towering troops and were so frightened that they didn't know which way to run. In an instant, the Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry wiped them out completely.

The Aquamarine Knight's aggro had already gone into disorder. It was now taking the initiative to attack instead of retaliating against enemy attacks. The Aquamarine Knight saw more targets in his line of sight and charged towards them without hesitation.

The yellow sand billowed under the cavalry's' hooves. The cavalry moved like the wind towards Happy's players. The sounds of horses pounding against the sand were only sound effects and didn't do any damage.

"Mages!" Ye Xiu ordered in the guild chat. Because he was commanding the entire guild, he spoke in the guild chat. When he yelled "Mages!", all of the mages lifted their staffs into the air. The gems on their staffs glinted in the sunlight.

"Ice Wall!"

Ye Xiu gave an order. All of the mages immediately began casting the spell. Magic waves rippled and in an instant, nearly a hundred ice walls shot out of the ground like a mountain range, blocking the Aquamarine Knight's and his cavalry's assault.

Bang!

An enormous sound reverberated into the air. The Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry didn't waver in front of the ice walls and continued their charge.

Bang bang bang bang!

Ice walls shattered one after the other.

"Thieves, advance!" Ye Xiu gave another order. Twenty or thirty thieves began to hide themselves within the cracks between the ice walls.

Chapter 526 – Killing Amidst the Chaos

The Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry pressed forward, but after crashing into several ice walls, their momentum finally slowed. Happy’s Thief team closed in. They didn’t ask for any single target or look for any route. They simply placed a trap wherever there was free space. Everyone put down as many traps as possible and then immediately ran far far away.

Peng peng peng peng!

Moments later, the sounds of ice walls breaking stopped. The charge made by the Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry had been stopped. Numerous ice walls still stood. Needless to say, after the cavalry was forced to a halt, the leading Aquamarine Knight brandished his sword and shattered the ice wall in front of him with a swing.

Advance! The Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry continued to head towards their intended target. Several ice walls were quickly smashed apart by them. The ice fragments sprinkled onto the ground. The scene didn’t look like it belonged here in the desert. However, no one had any time to appreciate it. Everyone could already see the light glinting from the Aquamarine Knight’s sword.

At this moment, the mage team fell back. The Knights moved forward to be the defensive line.

“Shields up!” Lord Grim ordered. The Knights in front lifted their shields and hid behind them.

“Cleric, get ready!” When Lord Grim gave his second order, the Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry arrived. Except this time, the short distance between them wasn’t enough for a full charge. The Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry strided over and raised their swords.

Dong dong dong dong!!

The sounds of metal colliding with metal repeatedly rang. The Knights didn’t care if there were even enemies in front of them. All of them raised their shields in front of them at a 45 degree angle. The Knights who were attacked could clearly feel their shields jumping back and forth. Blocking the fierce attacks affected their control over their characters. Their health also fell like waterfalls with every attack. In this type of situation, even if there were Clerics healing, the Knights were already worried if they would be able to properly block the second attack.

Fortunately, Lord Grim didn’t have them take the second attack. When the Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry made their first swing, Lord Grim gave another order.

“Ninjas!! Underground Tunneling Technique, Body Bind Technique!”

While the Aquamarine Knight had been breaking through the ice walls, the Ninjas had hidden themselves under the sand. Now, they popped out of the sand into the air and threw the rope attached to their ninja blades towards the knights on horseback.

They didn’t have any targets in mind and simply aimed at the most convenient target. There might be slip ups or repeats, but those weren’t important. It was more important they took the opportunity in front of them.

Ye Xiu knew very well how unskilled his Happy players were, so he didn’t set up anything complicated or difficult.

The mages cast ice walls, easy.

The thieves set traps, simple.

The knights block an attack, no need to talk about it.

The Ninjas had a slightly more difficult task because their Underground Tunneling Technique and Body Bind Technique were combos. Both of them had to be chained correctly and the Body Bind Technique had to used in the air. It was an easy task for any Heavenly Domain player, but it wasn’t so easy for these tenth server noobs. As a result, Ye Xiu didn’t have any requirements. All they needed to do was hit whatever target they could and not care about anyone else.

A few of the attacks might be repeated, but a single person’s mistake could be made up by someone else. A few attacks might miss, but even more mistakes would occur with anything more complicated anyways.

The thirty or so Ninjas launched their attacks against the nineteen Aquamarine Knight cavalry. It was nearly a two to one ratio. But because Ye Xiu didn’t put any requirements for them, there might be a target hit by several attacks or there might be a target hit by none.

In any case, people went up and horses flipped.

The majority of the knights hit by the Tunnel Bind combo were dismounted. Some of them were hit but didn’t fall and the Ninjas ended up on the horses.

This wasn’t strange. After all, the Aquamarine Knight was a wild boss. All of his underlings were powerful elite monsters and had strong resistance towards many attacks. If the player didn’t aim correctly, the intended effect might not occur.

“Battle Mages, Circle Swing!”

At this moment, another wave of attacks flew out. The Battle Mage team pincered from the left and right. After the Ninjas used the Tunnel Bind combo, the Battle Mages immediately stabbed at the knights who hadn’t fallen off their horses.

Some of their attacks might miss or might be late, but in the end, the remaining mounted knights were thrown off. One wave after another wave came.

Moreover, when these knights fell, there was even a small shockwave, knocking the ones lifted off by the Ninjas back down to the ground.

“Witches, Level 50 and up use Doll Shururu, under Level 50 use Lava Flask, Ice Rain!”

“Launchers, Stinger!”

“Spitfire, Incendiary Device!”

“Mechanics, Machine Drop!”

“Summoners, surround them with pets!”

“Berserkers……”

“Brawlers……”

“Qi Masters……”

Lord Grim gave out order after order. Ye Xiu had already set the chat up so that besides him, no one else could speak, so no one would be distracted by any messages other than the orders. Happy’s players continued doing their tasks.

Witches flew through the air, bombarding the cavalry with the items that Lord Grim had instructed them to throw down.

Bang bang bang bang!

The Launchers stood at the backlines and shot their Stingers into the air. The Stingers flew over everyone’s heads and exploded above the cavalry. Each missile exploded into eight smaller missiles, which rained down onto the battlefield.

The Spitfire’s Incendiary Devices worked together with the Lava Flasks thrown down by the Witches and covered the sand with a sea of fire.

The Mechanics’ Air Drops filled the skies with winter melons. Their stomachs opened and poured down trash.

The summoned creatures advanced and filled up the little space left.

The other classes also attacked. In an instant, the Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry were submerged in attacks. In this area, the only thing that could be seen were struggling shadows. Nothing else could be seen clearly.

“Don’t squeeze. Let me go through. I still haven’t used my skill!!”

“You Berserker, you’ve already used your skill, right? If you’re done, move aside!”

‘Who’s Goblin is this? Can’t you let me go through? Don’t make me kill it!!”

“Ah, who hit my butt???”

Amidst the noise from attacks, the constant yelling from Happy’s players could be heard too. The spies within Happy followed along, but couldn’t see anything properly.

As Glory veterans, Happy’s way of fighting the boss was unbearable to look at. Everyone was crammed together as if they were in a crowded train.

But they also discovered that their coordination might look unsightly, every person contributed to the fight. Everyone attacked and moved. Of the around six hundred people in the guild, not a single one was left doing nothing.

The spies were at a loss. They had already received orders to find some way to stop Happy from killing the Aquamarine Knight. But in this chaotic mess, there was nothing they could do because the battle had already reached an unimaginable step. It might be chaotic, but the attacks continued. How were they supposed to stop it? Make the battle organized?

Watching from inside the battle, Happy looked like a complete mess, but from afar, it looked like a war zone filled with fire, spells, sword light…...

It looked like a highlight reel for skills. Currently, all of the Level 50 and under skills were flashing left and right. The surrounding players entered and exited kept this bustling movement going.

The remaining players of the thirteen guilds stared in complete astonishment. The feeling they got from the spies was completely different. They felt it was a next level boss battle. The Aquamarine Knight’s cavalry had been surrounded by these players and were struggling helpless to do anything.

“Pay attention, don’t harm your own allies!!!”

Ye Xiu repeatedly sent out this order.

There was nothing he could do about it. Apart from special events, a hundred man group was the largest unit in Glory. Those in the same group couldn’t injure each other, but anyone outside of their group could be hurt. Happy had six or seven hundred players, so there were six or seven groups. In this type of situation, it was hard to avoid self-injury. These noobs weren’t good at controlling their attacks!

“Ah! I think I killed one of them!!!” Someone suddenly shouted in surprise. The system had clearly notified him that he had killed off one of the Aquamarine Knight’s subordinate.

“Ah! I killed one too!”

Even though there were around six hundred players, the system could tell them apart and gave out system notifications accordingly.

“I killed one!!”

“I also killed one!!”

The Aquamarine Knight's underlings had the same stats. Against a relatively similar offense, they would fall around the same time.

Chapter 527 – Treasure

Around six hundred players were attacking. How long would it take to kill a boss? Very few knew the answer to this question. It was also difficult to find a precise answer to this type of question. Coordination, skill, equipment, levels, classes, target…… there were simply too many factors involved.

However, the speed at which the Aquamarine Knight and his cavalry were being destroyed by Guild Happy was extremely frightening. The Aquamarine Knight’s underlings fell one after the other until only the Aquamarine Knight remained.

And the Aquamarine Knight? He was stronger than his subordinates, but his current situation was even worse than before.

Before, against the strong offense, his knights had taken a defensive formation around him. His eighteen knights formed a circle with him in the center; they even blocked the aerial attacks from above.

But now, all of his underlings had fallen. Surrounding him, a mob of summoned creatures now took their places.

“Okay, besides team one, everyone stop attacking!!” Ye Xiu immediately ordered.

The poor summoned creatures had previously been there in order to act as meat shields against the enemy attacks. If Ye Xiu didn’t order everyone to stop, these creatures would die under their master's hands.

The benefit of the people was that they listened, even moreso for someone they admired like Lord Grim. Under Ye Xiu’s command, everyone else apart from team one stopped attacking and withdrew. When they looked back, they couldn’t even see the boss anymore; the summoned creatures had completely enveloped the Aquamarine Knight. The light shining from his sword could still be seen though. Every time the Aquamarine Knight slashed, several summoned creatures let out shrill shrieks and died.

When a summoned creature died, the creature could be summoned again, but the skill had a cooldown. The stronger the creature, the longer the cooldown and the greater the mana cost would be. Summoners frequently ran out of mana.

“Team one, advance. Team two, get ready. Team three, rest!” Ye Xiu had split the Summoners into three teams and controlled their pacing.

“Launchers, continue firing! Don’t stop!” Team one also had Launchers. Even though the summoned creatures were in their way, it didn’t affect them.

“Elementalists, keep firing too!” Ye Xiu ordered the Elementalists to attack.

“Too easy.” Ye Xiu sighed. The Aquamarine Knight could see his health falling rapidly. All of his attacks just ended up hitting the summoned creatures. Even though he sometimes used a Whirlwind Slash to clear them away, he was facing a team of Summoners. Each summoner could summon several creatures. With three teams rotating, he could hack at the creatures all he wanted, but he would never kill them all. Ye Xiu had understood the Aquamarine Knight’s patterns already. Killing it off like this wouldn’t be a problem, even when the Knight entered its Enraged mode at 10% health. The Knight’s fury wouldn’t change the situation.

The only variable was the Club guilds. However, their elites were currently all the way at Almarshan.

The people from before….. Ye Xiu looked at them. They were scattered around the desert, observing from far away. They didn’t even dare to come close. What could they do?

If back-up arrived……. But at this point, it was already too late for the back-up to do anything.

The traps he had the Thieves set up ended up being unnecessary.

Ye Xiu carefully calculated and finally relaxed: this Aquamarine Knight wouldn’t be able to escape.

The Aquamarine Knight struggled….

The Aquamarine Knight went berserk…..

The Aquamarine Knight fell…..

Everything happened extremely quickly. The spies could only give this description in their reports to their guild leaders.

What type of boss battle was this? They thought about it deeply.

It looked like everyone was just randomly attacking, but they could clearly see the orders Lord Grim gave. With a commander leading everyone, how could it be called randomly attacking? It must be some sort of profound art!

The spies screenshotted the orders Ye Xiu gave and treated them like great achievements in their careers. Afterwards, they quickly sent them to their respective guild leaders, detailing Lord Grim’s incredible feat.

Around six hundred people killed a boss by attacking randomly.

Whenever the spies chatted with others, they loved to talk about this experience. In their circle, this opening remark continued to stay popular for a long period of time.

In the Western Desert, cheers erupted, becoming the only noise that could be heard in this area.

Guild Happy’s name appeared on TV!

This made every single member of Happy feel extremely proud. Happy’s fame had previously entirely been brought up by their guild leader, Lord Grim. They had joined Happy, hoping to have their fame echo throughout the entire server just like Lord Grim. This time, they finally got what they desired. Even though the system had only announced their guild’s name, they could see their own names within the two words Guild Happy. At this moment, they didn’t even pay attention to see what the boss dropped. This was supposed to be the reward for killing a boss, but right now, Happy had completely forgotten about it.

It was only until half a minute later did someone finally think about the drops. In the guild chat, their guild leader Lord Grim had already announced what had dropped.

“Orange equipment!!” Everyone grew excited.

For normal players, there was no need to hold any expectation of getting a Silver weapon. Those didn’t even drop anyways. Orange equipment was their end goal. In Glory, Orange equipment had the lowest drop rate. Many players could only admire the pictures of one online, especially for those only dropped by wild bosses. Wild bosses were monopolized by the big guilds, so how would a normal player ever get the chance to possess one?

Everyone was still admiring this Orange weapon, when Lord Grim sent another message.

“This Orange equip is the result of everyone’s hard work, so this piece of equipment belongs to the guild! In a bit, I’m going to put it into the guild storage. When you go into the guild storage, you’ll be able to see the rules for borrowing it.”

“Oh????”

Happy’s players didn’t really understand it yet. They were somewhat at a loss at what Ye Xiu meant by guild storage. Only the few experienced players understood what he meant and immediately became excited.

If the equipment was put into the guild storage, it meant that once one reached a certain level of guild contribution, one could use it!

Orange weapon! Even for old players, the majority of them had never possessed one before. Even though they might not be able to personally own one, they would still get the chance to use one if it was in the guild storage. These old players wanted to know what the necessary guild contribution was in order to use this weapon. An Orange weapon should require quite a high amount of guild contribution. If they spent too much time accumulating points, their levels might become too high. Using a Level 50 Orange equipment at higher levels would still have lower stats than other equipment at the suitable level, but the word “Orange” was too enticing. Some players didn’t even care about stats and cared more about the rarity of an equipment. For them, equipment was more for showing off to others than the stats.

In terms of stats, the Orange equipment that dropped from the Aquamarine Knight was quite good.

Desert Badge, Level 50. Apart from basic magic resistance, it had +22 Stamina, +5 Movement Speed, +5 Jump, +5% Magic Resistance.

This was a suitable accessory for any class.

Magic Resistance was the basic component for an accessory, but the additional stats: stamina, movement speed, jump, percent magic resistance increase. All four of these were useful for any class. This dictated the value of Desert Badge compared to other accessories.

Even Ye Xiu was happy to see this item. The guild storage needed this type of treasure. An Orange weapon might be more valuable than this Desert Badge, but a weapon could only be used by one or two classes. In other words, only 4-8% of Happy’s players would want to use this piece of equipment.

But a piece of equipment that could be used by any class was different. Everyone wanted it. This was exactly what he was hoping for.

Ye Xiu concluded the boss hunting activity and sent Blue River a message: “Let me take a look at your Blue Brook Guild’s storage!”

Blue River was looking at the exploding discussion group, when he suddenly received a message from Lord Grim. He couldn’t help but feel a bit diffident.

“What did you get?” Blue River asked.

Ye Xiu sent a picture of the Desert Badge.

“Wow!” Blue River was astonished. He was also considering it from a guild storage point of view. This equipment was extremely valuable.

“Are you selling it?” Blue River asked.

“In your dreams.” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River suddenly remembered Ye Xiu had asked to see his guild’s storage. Ye Xiu was clearly planning on setting up Happy’s storage system the same way as Blue Brook Guild’s.

“Should I give it to him? Blue River hesitated.

“Hurry up! There’s no point hiding it. Who in Blue Brook Guild can’t see it? I’m just too lazy to copy it down. It’d be more convenient if you just sent me a doc instead.” Ye Xiu said.

“You don’t have any spies in Blue Brook Guild?” Blue River was astonished.

“If I had a spy, why would I need to ask you!” Ye Xiu questioned Blue River’s intelligence.

Blue River swallowed his anger. There really wasn’t any point hiding it though, so he sent Ye Xiu a list of items in Blue Brook Guild’s storage.

Ye Xiu quickly found the important parts and adjusted the values for Happy. Then, he copied and pasted it into Happy’s storage system.

Ye Xiu quickly received a message from Blue River: “God, could I trouble you to replace the guild’s name? Thanks.”

“Guild’s name?”

“You’re using my guild’s system setup. It has my guild’s name on it. Don’t you think you should change it to something like Guild Happy or something?” Blue River was about to grind his own teeth into dust. As soon as Lord Grim setup the system, he immediately announced it to the guild. Happy’s players went over to look and saw Blue Brook Guild’s name everywhere in the rules. This information was quickly reported by Blue Brook Guild’s spies. Blue River really wanted to smash his head into the wall.

Chapter 528 – Beginning to Take Shape

“Oh, so that’s what you meant. My bad!” Ye Xiu felt ashamed too. He really hadn’t noticed that Blue Brook Guild’s storage system rules had Blue Brook Guild’s name written all over the place.

“Send me another copy.” Ye Xiu messaged Blue River.

“Why do you need another copy?” Blue River was puzzled.

“I already deleted the first one.” Ye Xiu replied.

Deleting it after using it! Another way of saying it was burning the bridge after crossing it. Blue River really didn’t want to give him another copy, but he couldn’t let him just shamelessly copy Blue Brook Guild’s system word for word could he? He didn’t care about the plagiarism, he just didn’t want anyone from Blue Brook Guild bothering him!

Helpless, Blue River found the storage system document again, but he started having second thoughts. Once Ye Xiu took the document, he would, at most, replace Blue Brook Guild’s name with Guild Happy’s. The spies would immediately recognize it and bother Blue Brook Guild about it. Blue River didn’t want this information to stay stuck to him! He grinded his teeth and quickly deleted a bunch of parts in the document. Then, amidst Ye Xiu’s constant bothering, he sent it over.

“Hm? This document seems a bit different?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I changed it a bit.” Blue River coldly replied.

“Not bad. It’s even better than the previous one. You’re quite the literary talent! Who wrote the last one? It was way too long-winded. So many words and so effeminate too. Not even web novelists can cheat the word count like that!” Ye Xiu said.

“I wrote that too…..” Blue River looked up at the sky.

“Oh…… you’ve really got some literary talent. Do you have any interest in my Guild Happy? Our guild just happens to be missing a cultured person such as yourself.” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River closed the chat window.

Meanwhile, Ye Xiu quickly swapped out the old system rules with the new ones and then tossed the Desert Badge into the guild storage. This Level 50 Orange equipment was placed in the guild storage’s Orange equipment Stage 6. Players needed six thousand guild contribution points in order to have access to Orange equipment Stage 6.

Because the Desert Badge belonged to the guild, this badge couldn’t be traded or discarded. However, it could still be dropped when the owner died. When a guild member lost the item in this way, there would usually be penalties, often in the form of guild contribution points. Some guilds even required a down payment for very valuable equipment. Every guild had their own way of managing their own storage.

After Ye Xiu placed the treasure into the storage, there were still two other pieces of equipment dropped by the Aquamarine Knight, both Level 55 Blue equipment. He threw those into the guild storage as well. Level 55 Blue equipment had similar base stats to Level 45 Orange equipment. However, an equipment’s value largely depended on the additional stats. As a result, a piece of equipment might not be high leveled, but because of its amazing additional stats, it could be kept, even at high levels.

These two Level 55 Blue equipment were fairly ordinary. It was easy to find equipment of this value from dungeons, so he put them into the storage’s Blue equipment Stage 5, which only required 700 guild contribution points. The difference between Blue and Orange equipment could clearly be seen here. In reality, Orange equipment wasn’t ten times stronger than Blue equipment, but it was certainly much rarer. Bosses in dungeons always dropped Blue equipment, so Blue equipment would naturally be more common.

After putting away the equipment, he explained how guild contribution worked to the guild members. He also gave Chen Guo’s alternate account authority equivalent to the guild leader. The only power Chen Guo didn’t have was removing the guild leader…..

“It’s not convenient for me to keep returning to the tenth server, so I’m giving you authority over the guild.” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

“Don’t give me the title of guild leader. Your name has to stay there for everyone to see.” Chen Guo advised.

“I know that.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“We only have this one piece of Orange equip in the guild storage. It’s far from being enough.” Chen Guo had been in a big guild before and knew the importance of the guild’s storage. In truth, not all of the players in Club guilds were loyal fans. Quite a few knew that the guild’s storage for these Clubs were wealthy, so they pretended to be fans in order to get in. In any case, it wasn’t easy to distinguish between an actual fan and an actor. Everyone liked playing Glory. There were only so many pro teams. Whether or not they were fans, they all knew about the same as other players.

“I have a few materials here. You can go ahead and sell the ones that aren’t so rare and buy some high leveled equipment to help fill up our guild storage. Remember to buy high leveled ones. The higher the better. Ignore the low-leveled ones. When the guild members start contributing, they’ll put in low-leveled ones.” Ye Xiu said.

“You don’t need the materials?”

“I’m already in the Heavenly Domain. These materials still aren’t that cheap in the current tenth server, so if you can sell them, it’s best to sell them here. Later, if I need them, I can buy them again. It’ll be cheaper later.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo immediately understood Ye Xiu’s reasoning. Without any delay, she followed Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and moved almost all of his tenth server personal storage to the guild’s.

“You can sell some stuff from here too.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay!” Chen Guo nodded her head. Guild storages didn’t only have equipment. They had materials, potions, anything. By providing all of these resources to the guild members, the guild could show the benefits of being in a guild.

“However, our high-leveled equipment can’t only come from buying. We have to create an elite team and have them fill up the guild storage’s upper levels.” Ye Xiu said.

“I can do this stuff. We have a few veterans in the guild. I’ll pick out a few and see if we can create a few elite teams.” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu nodded his head. He looked around. For now, there wasn’t anything else to do, so he closed the guild interface.

The Aquamarine Knight had dropped several material including the Aquamarine. Of course, Ye Xiu kept the Aquamarine for himself. After all, it was the reason he had come back to the tenth server. This type of special material was almost always dropped. Wild bosses only spawned once a week If the drop rate was too low, no one would be interested in the boss. As a result, wild bosses often dropped Orange equipment and rare materials. If none of them dropped, then something else dropped: luck.

After pocketing the Aquamarine, Ye Xiu didn’t hurry back to the Heavenly Domain to upgrade his equipment. There were still a few things that he needed to do in the normal server before he returned.

Even though he didn’t gain any experience here, there were still a few required quests that he had to complete. These quests rewarded bonus skill points or extra stats.

Ye Xiu had piled up quite a few Level 50-54 quests. He was already here, so he might as well clear them out. He searched up a guide and went to complete the quests.

These quests weren’t difficult for Ye Xiu, but Chen Guo seemed excited, as if she were having even more fun than watching Ye Xiu battle in PvP.

Glory had such a large world. With a guide, Ye Xiu didn’t even need to even move his hand sometimes, making it quite boring.

Finishing up all of the required quests took up most of his day. Ye Xiu was doing these quests for the end rewards, but Lord Grim wouldn’t get any experience from any of the previous segments of the quests, making it was all very tedious.

Just when he finished all of these tedious quests, Steamed Bun Invasion kindly invited him to dungeon together. Ye Xiu felt like it had been a long time since he had last played with this little bro, so they partied up and dungeoned together for some equipment.

The majority of day in the tenth server had gone to contributing to the guild. The guild’s storage had filled up quite a lot now. None of them wanted any of the equipment dropped from the dungeons, so the equipment all went to the guild instead. Even though they were only Blue equipments, Blue equipments still had their advantages! They required fewer guild contribution points and usually made for quite decent equipment too.

As for Chen Guo, after leaving some of the materials in the guild storage, she went to the market to sell the rest. She wasn’t in a hurry and sold them off in small amounts. She didn’t bother with the guilds or studios who bought materials in bulk at a low price.

The big guilds saw Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze selling materials and grinded their teeth in frustration.

Who was Chasing Haze? All of them knew. Guild Happy had spies, after all. She wasn’t high-leveled, but she had a lot of authority in the guild.

Where did she suddenly get all of those materials? The guilds immediately knew! Lord Grim had earned it from them!

He had earned it from them and now they had to buy them back! Just thinking about it made them flush with anger. However, materials were important to the Clubs. If there were materials available to buy, then they had to get them, but when they went over to buy it from her, the price was high! No matter how high their priorities were, the guilds couldn’t help but hesitate. If they bought their own materials back at such a high price, their faces would explode from anger. They just couldn’t accept it.

Helpless, they could only watch as these materials were sold off at a high price.

Chen Guo wasn’t in a hurry at all. She sold, while looking around the marketplace and bought equipment either with materials or with money she earned from selling the materials.

Thus, the two sides busily worked for the entire day. When they checked up on the storage at night, they saw that the storage had changed greatly. The storage didn’t only have the items they had put in initially. The guild members began understanding the benefits of the guild storage and made their own contributions to it.

Potions, food…...

The guild storage was immediately filled with many subclass-created items. These items could be traded in for contribution points and taken out with contribution points. Once the items in the guild storage began circulating, it would gradually move onto the right track. Later on, no one would need to manage it anymore. It would operate smoothly on its own. The guild just had to make sure there were high-end goods inside. These items were difficult for normal players to get on their own. Only by putting in these types of goods into the guild storage would players make contributions. While earning guild contribution points, the player would be adding to the storage, which would circulate around.

A guild could only grow prosperous with a strong guild storage as a foundation.

Chapter 529 – Spies’ Contributions

“Comrades, work hard. I’ll be waiting for you in the Heavenly Domain!” When he finished his one day visit to the tenth server, Ye Xiu encouraged the players of his guild.

The players laughed in response. None of them really took it too seriously. Only Steamed Bun Invasion, being such a strange person, answered sincerely, “Boss, rest easy! I’ve got the tenth server covered!”

“Good luck everyone….”

Ye Xiu logged out. His return to the tenth server for just one short day turned Guild Happy upside down.

The establishment of the guild storage is a symbol. Without a mature guild storage, then the guild would still be a regular guild just for fun. However, with a storage, the guild would become more attractive to the players and become more cohesive.

The change in Guild Happy was quickly reported back to the guild leaders by the spies. Still, nothing was as important as Lord Grim going back to Heavenly Domain. Upon hearing the news, the guild masters felt that their holiday was finally there….

Guild Happy’s storage was too easy to deal with.. The guild masters were all snickering in the dark. Lord Grim, no matter how godly you are, you’re too careless this time!

Next day, when Lord Grim logged back in, Ye Xiu was already back in Heavenly Domain. On the other hand, Chen Guo knew that building the storage was an important step for Guild Happy. There was some management required at the beginning, especially since she hadn’t sold out the materials that Ye Xiu had given her. She sold them in small amounts instead of in bundles, so selling all of them out was going to take a few days.

Right after she logged in and opened up the management window of the storage, she received a system message. She jumped in surprise when she glanced at the message and called Ye Xiu.

“It’s too fast! Some people already have 6000 contribution points! They’re going to get the Desert Badge soon. What should I do?” Che Guo asked Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu tilted his head, glanced at Chen Guo, and smiled, “As expected.”

“To be able to get 6000 contribution point overnight, they must have donated a lot of things. “ Chen Guo concluded while running to the guild management place in the city center to check on the guild storage. Unsurprisingly, the storage became much more filled. As for the donation records, expectedly, the players with 6000 contribution points each had a long list.

“Haha. All of these are spies.” Ye Xiu explained.

“Hm?”

“To have 6000 contribution points in one night, they must have one of the big guild’s support. They’re trying to cheat away our treasure.” Ye Xiu continued.

“Oh!” Chen Guo immediately understood why Ye Xiu set the Desert Badge as a non-auto distributed award. She also realized that Ye Xiu had expected many to gain 6000 contribution points so quickly.

“Rotten b*stards! Let’s kick them all out!” Chen Guo was outraged yet excited. Their scheme had been seen through. If they get kicked out now, then it would mean that they donated items and helped Guild Happy to grow for nothing. Just thinking about theses people’s reactions after they got kicked out filled Chen Guo with happiness.

“Don’t. There are definitely spies, but there might be a few special cases. Kicking them all out might end up punishing the wrong people.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Then what do we do? We can’t drag it out forever! The system has a time limit!” If no player with the authority distributed the reward within the time frame, then the system would automatically distribute it.

“Who currently has the highest level in the guild?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Tang Rou’s Soft Mist.” Chen Guo answered.

“Give her some materials so that she can rack up 6000 contribution points. Let her take the Desert Badge. Then send out an announcement. Say that there were a lot people who sent in requests, so the guild gave the matter some consideration and awarded it to the player with the highest level, Soft Mist. This way, there shouldn’t be any objections.” Ye Xiu laid out the plan.

“Shameless.” Chen Guo exclaimed, then followed with a question, “What if someone says he or she was there first?”

“Nonsense. If order mattered in the first place, why would we set the distribution system as mandatory? If someone asked you with this nonsense, then educate him properly.” Ye Xiu replied.

Chen Guo was speechless after that. She found Tang Rou and explained the plan. Tang Rou had no objections against it whatsoever, making Chen Guo feel that the girl had truly found the wrong teacher. She didn’t learn anything honorable!

Chen Guo asked Tang Rou how many points she still needed, and answer shocked her.

“You only need this tiny amount?” Chen Guo asked again.

Tang Rou suddenly understood, “No wonder he asked me to donate all of the items from yesterday’s dungeon.”

“So you had this all planned out.” Chen Guo turned her gaze onto Ye Xiu.

“It’s only to be expected. If it was a well-developed big guild, then this kind of trick is totally useless. There are a lot of things in the storage, so it wouldn’t hurt the guild too much. However, we just started. If they took the Desert Badge like this, then it would really be a loss of us, so I took some precautions. “ Ye Xiu elaborated.

While he was talking, Chen Guo met up with Tang Rou in the game. After she got the materials, Tang Rou soon also had 6000 contribution points. She then proceeded to take the Desert Badge.

Whether the award was distributed by the system or a player wasn’t shown unless someone with authority willed it. To Tang Rou, who had 6000 contribution points, the emblem was already unlocked. It was only when she tried to take it did the system notify her that a request had been submitted and there would be a reply within 48 hours no matter what.

Chen Guo received the message and acted right away. The Desert Badge was given to Tang Rou without any delay. Chen Guo also sent out an announcement in the guild. Just like Ye Xiu said, it reasoned that due to the numerous requests, the badge was given to the player of the highest level.

“You should also urge everyone to learn from these people. Don’t forget to encourage people to level up. There are benefits to having a high level. Soft Mist is a perfect example.” Ye Xiu instructed Chen Guo to add more content to the announcement.

When the announcement was posted, a lot of people among the request list found themselves choking. After waiting restlessly for an entire night, they couldn’t have dreamed of this result.

These people were,naturally the spies from other guilds. If they were the regular players, level priority would have been a perfectly sensible reason. In addition, the contribution points they gained were still useful, so they didn’t lose anything in donating items. It was only the spies who were dying in bitterness because they had helped Guild Happy grow for utterly nothing in return.

When the news travelled back to the guild masters, all that changed was an increased number of bitter people. Was Lord Grim careless? Apparently not. It was them who were careless.

A mandatory distribution and a level priority were all it took to cheat more items out of them.

“How about we let our guys hurry up on leveling so we can surpass that Soft Mist. Then we can get that Desert Badge easily.” Someone was still trying, unwilling to give up.

“What kind of idiot are you?! This situation is proof that they were prepared for these types of tricks! Trying more schemes is simply a waste of time !” The man who proposed the idea got scolded right away.

“Why don’t I take equipment out? Then you guys can kill steal it.” A spy suggested.

“Wouldn’t that expose your identity?”

“Boss, based on the current situation, do I look like I’m not exposed?” The spy lamented.

A long silence settled upon the participating guild leaders and spies. They realized that, no matter what they do, they wouldn't be able to do any harm to Guild Happy.

As for Guild Happy, besides the bitter group, other people had no disagreement against giving the Desert Badge to the highest-leveled Soft Mist. Instead, they were very curious about the people who got 6000 contribution points at this extraordinary speed and went to visit these people.

The poor spies were still worrying with their own guilds like idiots when the crowd from Guld Happy came, praising them like heroes. There were no words that could describe their conflicted hearts in that moment.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had long returned to Heavenly Domain. He didn’t pay any more attention to the matter after instructing Chen Guo on how to fix the mess.

He put Aquamarine and the other materials that Mo Qian helped to gather all into the Equipment Editor. Ye Xiu was ready to upgrade the level 50 of Thousand Chance Umbrella.

For this upgrade, even the window of the Editor was different from before. The parts are no longer just the simple parts like the sword, spear, rifle, and the umbrella. The tedious blueprint separated Thousand Chance Umbrella into tiny individual components to be reassembled later.

These parts all had templates from the earlier trials. Ye Xiu checked every materials carefully, replicating them one by one. However, when the only material left was the Aquamarine, Ye Xiu had ran out of templates. There wasn’t one for the component that the aquamarine was supposed to be molded into.

Ye Xiu sighed softly. In fact, Thousand Chance Umbrella wasn’t a completely successful weapon in the first place. Otherwise, instead of a level 5 prototype, what should have being left from the research years ago would be a level 50 Thousand Chance Umbrella.

The reason behind that year’s failure was the problem with the last material. Trials after trials failed on the last component. Still, every failure means one step closer to success. This is because they had already determined all of the possible materials. With every failure, they could eliminate a possibility. Aquamarine was the only material left that they hadn’t tried. Regretfully, before they could carry out the final trial, Glory killed the brilliance behind the Thousand Chance Umbrella's existence.

Now, so many years after that, Ye Xiu was finally here to complete this unfinished step from that time. Unable to calm himself, he went through three cigarette before he returned to the room. After taking a deep breathe, Ye Xiu settled himself in front of the computer.

Without a template, he needed to forge the component himself. The performance required wasn’t as complicated as combat in the game, but it had no tolerance for the slightest mistake. Even the smallest error would destroy the material completely. Otherwise, why would people call the Equipment Editor an bottomless void for money?

So it begins!

Ye Xiu noted in his heart, clicked open the polishing window for materials and put the Aquamarine into the slot.

Chapter 530 – Level 50 Thousand Chance Umbrella

Chen Guo saw what Ye Xiu was going to do.

Equipment Editor! All Glory players had access to it, but very few knew how to actually use it. Chen Guo had obviously tried it before, but she just didn’t get it. In the end, her attempts only resulted in wasted materials and equipment.

The Equipment Editor really wasn’t complicated. It’s just a tool like a pen. Everyone knows how to use a pen. However, some people could use it to write novels and some could use it to draw pictures. The key is what one could do with the tool.

Chen Guo had stopped at the using-the-pen stage. As for creating literature or drawings, she was just going in blind.

In the beginning, Ye Xiu simply used a template and placed the materials accordingly. As long as he had the correct materials, everything else was simple. But now, after using the polisher, Chen Guo’s eyes lit up. This time, Ye Xiu would truly be using the Equipment Editor to polish a material.

Even though Chen Guo couldn’t use the Equipment Editor, she at least knew that he couldn’t be careless here, so she didn’t say anything and only gave furtive glances to see the situation.

Ye Xiu put in the Aquamarine into the polisher and immediately began working.

Cut, drill, string, smooth…...

Chen Guo had played around with these functions before, but she had just been doing it randomly to a piece of material. On the other hand, Ye Xiu clearly had a plan and goal.

He gradually shaped the Aquamarine. It couldn’t be shaped using a simple circle or rectangle function. It would be shaped according to the operator’s desires until it became a completed component.

It had a core for structural stability and places to link together with other components.

Movable area, immovable areas, areas with limited movements.

The structure of the Aquamarine became more and more complex and delicate. All of this was done by Ye Xiu through the polisher.

Simple techniques produced miraculous results. So miraculous that Chen Guo even had a hard time believing it.

Half an hour.

The polishing for the Aquamarine took a full half an hour. When Ye Xiu suddenly stopped, Chen Guo snapped out of her daze. She had been watching out of the corner of her eye for the full half an hour. When she came out of her daze, her eyes felt a bit sore. Watching out of the corner of one’s eyes for a long time is very tiring.

When she saw Ye Xiu stop operating the polisher, she waited a moment before asking: “Is it done?”

Ye Xiu nodded his head: “It’s done.”

Then, he took out the polished Aquamarine and put it with the other materials.

He opened up the interface for adding the materials into the weapon. The Thousand Chance Umbrella’s many parts as well as the dazzling line-up of materials lay there. Ye Xiu didn’t hurry up and begin. He took a rest, while opening up a document from his email. Chen Guo looked and saw it was the blueprints for the Thousand Chance Umbrella. She immediately turned her head back to her screen.

This sort of thing was very secretive in the Glory scene. It was like a secret martial arts book. It wasn’t right to look at it without the owner’s permission.

“It doesn’t matter. If you want to look, you can look.” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Can I really?”

“When I was polishing the materials, you didn’t avoid looking at them either. What’s so different about this?” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly and immediately felt very embarrassed.

“I forgot. I’m sorry…….” Chen Guo sincerely apologized. If she couldn’t look at the blueprint, then it meant she couldn’t look at the upgrade process either. Chen Guo had forgotten about this, but it was also because she didn’t have any intentions of stealing his knowledge or anything like that.

“I said it doesn’t matter!” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re going to assemble the Thousand Chance Umbrella?” Chen Guo felt too ashamed to sneakily watch, so she changed the subject.

“Yeah, I’m going to take a look at the blueprint again.” Ye Xiu said.

“Good luck.” Chen Guo said. She had already turned her head back. This time, she wouldn’t glance at him working at all.

Ye Xiu smiled and didn’t say anything. He didn’t care if she looked and he obviously didn’t care if she didn’t look. He carefully studied the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s Level 50 blueprint again.

With the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s complexity, learning the flowchart for it was impossible. Ye Xiu branded the theory and its applications to the umbrella into his mind. Remembering the fundamentals would save time and lead to better results.

After reviewing the flowchart, Ye Xiu didn’t take out a cigarette to relax and quickly began assembling the Level 50 umbrella.

The room became extremely quiet. There would be usually be some noise from Chen Guo and Tang Rou playing the game, but at this moment, no sound could be heard from them.

They weren’t trying not to make any noise. They deliberately gave Ye Xiu an environment where he could fully focus.

Ka ka, ka ka…….

In the room, only Ye Xiu’s mouse could be heard. One step at a time without any margin for error.

After a short moment, it was time to put the Aquamarine into it. Unsuitable materials could be polished into the correct shape, but when placed into the desired equipment, the equipment would fail. If one were unlucky, the equipment would be damaged in the process. If one were lucky, the equipment could still maintain its form. However, the equipment would soon break after a few uses.

With the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s complex parts, if a single component failed, everything would fail. The creator had analyzed the structure of each part separately. The results of the analysis appeared in the previous forms of the Thousand Chance Umbrella. This saved a lot of effort in manufacturing it. However, this couldn’t be done for the completed form.

“Ka!”

Ye Xiu didn’t hesitate when putting in the Aquamarine and accurately planted it into the weapon. A light comfortable sound rang in his ears. It was a signal for a successful placement.

Ye Xiu didn’t stop to take a pause. The Aquamarine was only one part and not the end. He continued according to the flowchart.

He spent another half an hour on assembling it all together.

After hearing Ye Xiu let out a sigh of relief, Chen Guo stopped herself from turning her head to look until she heard Ye Xiu personally say “It’s done.”

“Was it a success?” Chen Guo turned her head over. Even Tang Rou stole a glance.

“I’ll have to try it out to see!” Ye Xiu said. He exited the Equipment Editor and returned to the game.

Chen Guo anxiously looked. At the same time, she was somewhat curious about the wonders of this Level 50 Thousand Chance Umbrella. Who knew that when Ye Xiu went back to the game and picked up his Thousand Chance Umbrella, he didn’t look for any monsters. He just swiped at the air a few times and the nodded his head: “It’s a success.”

“That’s….. done?”

“It’s done!” Ye Xiu exclaimed.

“Just a few swipes? You’re certain there’s no problem?” Chen Guo doubted.

“It sounds like you were hoping there were problems?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No…… it’s just isn’t your inspection too careless?” Chen Guo questioned.

“Ah that’s what you mean. What did you think I would do?” Ye Xiu swiped at the air some more, “See, there aren’t any loose parts. It’s a big success!”

No loose parts….

Chen Guo was considering whether she should go into her Heavenly Domain account and run over to admire the Thousand Chance Umbrella’s might. But if the end result was just “no loose parts”, where was there to admire?

“Let me see the stats.” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu opened up his weapon’s profile. Chen Guo looked and saw a lot of words.

If she recalled correctly, in the beginning, the Thousand Chance Umbrella didn’t have anything except for the basic stats. Even though the stats surpassed an Orange weapon at the same level, without any additional stats, this weapon wouldn’t be very good. It would be at the same level as the lowest ranked White equipment, which had no additional stats.

But this Thousand Chance Umbrella had quite a few additional stats.

The Thousand Chance Umbrella was currently in its umbrella form. It had 535 Physical Attack and 535 Magic Attack. It also added 10 to Stamina, Strength, Intelligence, and Spirit.

The same magic and physical attack and +10 to all four main stats.

With just this, Chen Guo could tell that this Thousand Chance Umbrella could be considered as a pro level weapon.

This was a feature of the scepter, which Knights often used.

Apart from the +10 to the four main stats, Chen Guo continued to look down and thought of another issue: “Do all of the Thousand Chance Umbrella forms have different stats?”

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu said and had the Thousand Chance Umbrella switch to the spear form. It added +41 to Strength.

“Then what are your overall stats?” Chen Guo cried out in alarm.

Ye Xiu was a bit startled, but quickly figured out why Chen Guo was so alarmed. He opened up his character profile.

“It seems pretty normal…….” Chen Guo hesitated. After all, when facing a God, she was afraid she misinterpreted something because her skill level wasn’t good enough.

Right when she finished, Lord Grim’s stats suddenly changed. His Strength decreased and his Intelligence increased.

“This…..” Chen Guo looked. Lord Grim’s Thousand Chance Umbrella had changed forms. She immediately understood: “It’s not that every weapon gives you permanent stats?”

‘Of course not.” Ye Xiu said, “The stats depends on the form of the weapon being used.”

“You can’t have all of the forms’ additional stats add together?” Chen Guo felt like if that could happen, then it would be incredible. Wasn’t it a single weapon? All the stats were there, so perhaps there was a way to sum them all up?

‘If that was possible, then why would I need any additional stats? My base attack would be ridiculous.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…..” Chen Guo didn’t say anything. Sure enough, her imagination had gone too far.

Chapter 531 – What Are We Here For?

Chen Guo dreamed about the unrealistic possibility, then looked at Thousand Chance Umbrella's stats, finding it to be rather ordinary. No matter what, Thousand Chance Umbrella was only a level 50 weapon. It could not shock a player who had seen a level 70 weapon too greatly. Still, the brilliance of it was not in its stats, but in its unpredictable nature. Chen Guo knew this well.

“Okay. Let’s hurry up on leveling now!” Ye Xiu said.

Lord Grim was currently level 54. Once he reaches 55, the dungeons would be open to him. There are countless level 55 dungeons in Heavenly Domain. On top of that, these dungeons have more experience points than the dungeons from the regular servers. Once he reaches level 55 and starting to use the dungeons, his level was bound to skyrocket.

“Okay. Hurry up!” Chen Guo said and turned to manage things in Guild Happy in the tenth server.

Ye Xiu resupplied Lord Grim a little in the main city. Just as he was leaving for the wilderness, a stream of messages came rushing down. The alert kept blinking endlessly as the sender continued sending messages. It was none other than Wei Chen, whose Windward Formation just joined Ye Xiu’s friend list two days ago.

“Where are you?”

“What do you want?”

“Come here!”

“Hurry up!”

“Talk to me!”

Wei Chen burned his cosmo and a storm of messages came crashing down. Ye Xiu read the text one by one and asked, “What do you want?”

“Poison Fang Swamp, location 27586, 45866. Hurry up!” Wei Chen answered immediately.

“Level 65 leveling area? Why should I go there? I can’t get any experience points.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Stop being stupid! Hurry up!” Wei Chen yelled out.

Ye Xiu was helpless. Lord Grim teleported to a main city near Poison Fang Swamp. Right as he set foot outside of the the teleportation circle, a group of players from Herb Garden came running past. Lord Grim hid to the side hurriedly. In the Heavenly Domain, the main cities weren’t safe areas. It depended on whether the character had any fame in that city. Lord Grim came to Heavenly Domain when he was only level 50, so he couldn’t take any quests. Even killing monsters for him meant overcoming a big level gap. He had no fame to speak of in the main city of level 55 area, let alone the city of level 56 area. A character gains fame through quests. Without a sufficient level, where could Lord Grim possibly find quests?

Therefore, to Lord Grim, the current Heavenly Domain didn’t have a safe area. Thus, a sudden encounter with people of any guild was not to be taken lightly for Ye Xiu.

Apparently, this group of Herb Garden was too busy rushing to pay attention to their surroundings. They sped off out of the city the moment they were out of the teleportation circle. Ye Xiu knew that the teleportation circle was too dangerous for him, so he let his character stay far away from it. Lord Grim quickly took another route, even though he and the people from Herb Garden were essentially going to the same place. Seeing how rushed the club’s people were, Ye Xiu was more confident about Wei Chen’s purpose for calling him over. Undoubtedly, the field boss in Poison Fang Swamp refreshed. At the same time, Wei Chen’s Death’s Hand was currently level 60. To advance, he needed level 65 materials. It looked like one of them came from Poison Fang Swamp.

Unlike the normal servers, Ye Xiu had a clearer memory of the Heavenly Domain. Even after he became a professional player, Ye Xiu still visited Heavenly Domain for fun from time to time. On top of that, when he became a professional player, the max level wasn’t level 70 yet. During his career so far, Glory changed the level cap a couple of times, so the professional players had to level up their characters in the Heavenly Domain.

Poison Fang Swamp’s field boss, Swamp Hunter Leipu, is a mix between assassin and thief who lurked unpredictably around Poison Fang Swamp.

Of course, “unpredictable” was an adjective given to the character by the system setting. To the players, every field boss was unpredictable because their spawn was too random. However, the bosses were always found not long after spawning. Even as Wei Chen was texting Ye Xiu, Herb Garden's people were heading towards the scene.

Herb Garden wasn’t the only one. Just as Lord Grim was rushing over, the guilds that had arrived already numbered four. Herb Garden, Misty Castle, Tyrannical Ambition, and Samsara all belonged to Clubs.

This was truly a close one. Ye Xiu have no idea what kind of schemes Wei Chen used this time to gain an advantage on the big guilds. How rare! Looks like Wei Chen really spent a lot of effort on Swamp Hunter Leipu.

Ye Xiu thought to himself, not daring to lower his guard just yet. He ran towards the location Wei Chen had provided with incredible speed. He expected the place to be a storm of blades and spells, locked in a fierce battle with the boss as Wei Chen tries to kill the boss before the guilds arrive. Ye Xiu did not expect to find the ominous silence when he arrived at 27586, 45866.

Just as he was planning to ask Wei Chen through a message, the mud splashed in a puddle near him. A dirty poisonous fly jumped up, lunging toward Lord Grim with its sting.

What extraordinary reflexes Ye Xiu had! Without even closing the chat window, he tapped out the command. With a silvery flash, Thousand Chance Umbrella folded into a sword. With a Sword Draw, the fly was smacked down in midair.

Without any hesitation, the fly flapped its wings, flying towards Ye Xiu right after it landed. These kinds of monsters in Poison Fang Swamp held the top place on the list of “least favorite monsters in Glory”. Its small size and quick movements as well as its tendency to hide in the swamp, made it hard to kill for any class. Because of this, Poison Fang Swamp was one of the most extremely disliked leveling areas.

Still, in front of a god like Ye Xiu, what could a lowly monster do? Although the fly got back into the air pretty quickly, Lord Grim’s sword was faster. Ye Xiu didn’t even bother using Thousand Chance Umbrella’s stats enhancement. With his bare hands, he smacked the fly into a corpse.

“Excellent skills.” A voice rang out nearby. The owner of the voice was none other than Wei Chen himself. Based on his muddy equipments, Wei Chen lookd like he just appeared out of a mud puddle.

“Where’s the boss?” Ye Xiu asked.

“There, be careful.” Wei Chen warned.

“How can I be careful?” Ye Xiu retorted. They were already deep inside Poison Fang Swamp. Mud puddles of all sizes were everywhere. Even if one knew which puddle hid poisonous flies, avoiding encounters were still impossible.

“Tch, and you call yourself a god? Useless!” Wei Chen’s Windward Formation led the way. He fished something out of his pocket, lit it, and threw it onto the ground. A thin blue smoke rippled out into the surroundings. Everywhere it went, poisonous flies jumped out of the mud like frightened birds and flew away.

Ye Xiu wanted to use an insect repelling smoke, but that was a level 70 item. This is where Wei Chen had lost his standards: using such an avoidable thing to label Ye Xiu as useless.

They didn’t walk far from the location provided by Wei Chen. When Ye Xiu saw that Wei Chen had actually bothered to come personally, an ominous feeling rose in Ye Xiu’s heart.

“How could you walk away from the boss? You’re not going to tell me you don’t have any plans in mind?” Ye Xiu questioned.

“As expected of a god! Looks like you are crafty enough to foresee my clever scheme.” Wei Chen praised.

“What’s the situation now?” Ye Xiu asked.

“There are five guilds already. No one dares to move yet. They’re all still scheming.” Wei Chen said.

“What’s your plan?” Ye Xiu continued.

“My plan was waiting for you to come over. That was all. Now you’re here, we can start to plan the next step. Come on, don’t be shy.” Wei Chen’s Windward Formation stepped around a few trees, finally stopped, and called Ye Xiu over. Lord Grim walked over and saw a group of people with familiar IDs. They appeared to be the group that fought with him just days before.

Ye Xiu greeted the group causally and the group returned the greetings. There were no noteworthy feelings involved. Everyone was facing forward.

What was happening in the front then? Ye Xiu turned Lord Grim’s camera and found himself immediately outraged. There were the players from all the big guilds in the front. Swamp Hunter Leipu wasn’t even in sight. What was in sight was the wall of people built by the guilds that surrounded Swamp Hunter Leipu. They were so far out that it would be completely logically to call themselves spectators.

Yet here Ye Xiu thought Wei Chen had grasped some advantages. Based on the current situation, they would call themselves lucky if the guilds didn’t start attacking them as kill stealers.

“Are you here to kill the boss, or are you here just as a killstealer?” Ye Xiu was starting to doubt Wei Chen’s motivation. He felt he had need to clarify this question.

“Killsteal? Shameless! As a god, do you still have any standard? How could you possible think of kill stealing? Of course we’re here for the boss. Unless we truly can’t kill the boss, then maybe we’ll resort to kill stealing.” Wei Chen retorted.

“With this situation? Please, teach me how to kill the boss.” Ye Xiu ridiculed.

“No. You should teach me. Let your despicableness help me!” Wei Chen answered sincerely.

“How about all of you go out and run around naked? That should get everyone's’ attention. Then I sneak in and kill the boss with one strike. What do you think about it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Running around with no equipment is no problem. The problem is how are you going to insta-kill the boss?” Wei Chen replied with a question.

“I have my ways. You can lead your people to run around naked now.” Ye Xiu answered.

“Hmm. Wait a moment. Let’s check on the other’s status first.” Wei Chen agreed.

“You’ve been here for awhile now. Are you done yet?” Ye Xiu was starting to feel a little exasperated.

“The situation is constantly changing. Look, look! There’s a new guild now.” Wei Chen continued.

“I saw four on my way here.” Ye Xiu added.

“Are they same as the ones before us?” Wei Chen asked.

“Two of them aren’t.” Ye Xiu replied.

“So, eight guilds are already here. Awesome. I say why don’t we go back first?” Wei Chen suggested.

“You should have done that a long while ago.”

In the end, despite what they said, their characters didn’t move backwards half an inch. As a matter of fact, they even stepped forward a little to see the situation more clearly.

“F*ck! Can’t you lower yourself a little? Don’t expose your ID. Your name is like sh*t these days. It attracts flies!” Wei Chen cursed.

“Hello, fly.” Ye Xiu said to Wei Chen.

Chapter 532 – A Peaceful Way

In Poison Fang Swamp, players from Herb Garden, Misty Castle, Tyrannical Ambition, Samsara, Excellent Dynasty, Blue Brook Guild, Blossom Valley, and Void Walk wandered around on the lookout.

The guilds discovered the boss at different times. The first guild to see the boss weren’t stupid, but they couldn’t kill the boss in time. After the other guilds noticed the boss, the first guild immediately gave up on attacking the boss and the situation resulted in a deadlock.

None of the eight guilds dared to act rashly. They were naturally waiting for their guild leaders to make a decision. A Level 65 wild boss wasn’t a small matter. The guild leaders personally set out to handle it.

When the eight guild leaders gathered together, they felt somewhat awkward. Even though they were still competitors, everyone had gotten closer due to recent events. The guild leaders had even assembled the day before to curse at Lord Grim’s activities in the tenth server. Now, they had assembled again, but this time, instead of fighting shoulder to shoulder, they would be at each other’s throats.

Although the guild leaders knew this would happen, it still felt a bit uncomfortable. In the end, allying together to deal with Lord Grim was a different matter. A friend in need is a friend indeed. They had suffered whenever they countered Lord Grim. This shared suffering cultivated a feeling similar to working together to take advantage of another.

“That b*stard Lord Grim isn’t going to come over and make a mess is he?”

Someone saw a familiar crowd gather around and couldn’t help but turn the subject to Lord Grim.

When he said this, the others gave expressions of approval.

“I just looked. Lord Grim is online. We have to defend against him!”

“That guy just returned from snatching the Aquamarine Knight in the tenth server. It seems like today, it’s very likely he’s fixed his attention on our Swamp Hunter Leipu.

“In the tenth server, he has a guild! Over here…..”

“Loulan Slash!” Someone suggested.

“Even if he doesn’t try and steal the boss, he might go scrap picking with his comrade Deception!” Another person guessed.

“We must take precautions!” After discussing it, everyone nodded their heads. They had reached a consensus in regards to Lord Grim. However, their friendly and peaceful discussion had come to an end. Once they reached an agreement with the Lord Grim issue, everyone was in an awkward situation again.

“Should we scout around the perimeters to see if Lord Grim is here?” Someone proposed.

This proposal was unanimously agreed upon and the mood became harmonious again. At this moment, Blue Brook Guild’s leader Changing Spring couldn’t hold it back anymore and stood out: “Everyone, is there any point in lying to ourselves?”

The discussion immediately fell silent. Indeed, they were talking and talking, avoiding the issue of stealing the boss and using Lord Grim to keep the peace. It was certainly somewhat deceitful. Even if they allied together to face Lord Grim, they had to face the boss eventually. Not just today either. Fighting bosses was one way for the guilds to compete against each other.

Now that Changing Spring had directly burst the bubble, the other guild leaders felt somewhat embarrassed. Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You stood out: “Everyone, Changing Spring is correct. We can’t deceive ourselves, but I think everyone understands our current feelings. With such a strong opponent, disputes between each other will give our opponent an opportunity. I have a proposal. For this boss, how about we find a peaceful way of resolving the situation?”

“A peaceful way”. After these words came out, many of them objected. Because in the history of fighting for bosses, “a peaceful way” was a phrase used too many times. Whenever it was proposed, people would use it as a coverup for darker schemes. Nowadays, everyone had developed a resistance to these words. To everyone, the words “a peaceful way” was the same as “I’m about to take a go at it.”

An experience guild leader like Jiang You understood this. He immediately followed up: “A peaceful way sounds like a joke no? Ha ha, but I believe everyone understands logic. Today, the reason we’re able to take this step is because of a pre-requisite. Lord Grim, Heavenly Justice. I doubt anyone wants to see these two grow. Right now, if we go into another large battle over a boss, we’ll only be giving them more and more opportunities. In particular, we don’t know if they already have the strength to infiltrate into our ranks. When we compete, we don’t know if their people will turn around and stab us in the backs.”

“Then tell us, what peaceful way do we have?” Blossom Valley’s guild leader Blooming Blossom asked.

Jiang You smiled: “Fight. We’ll still have to fight, but we won’t have to fight such a large battle. We’ll go to the Arena, fight a few rounds, and determine who the boss belongs to. How about it?”

“Not a bad idea. I agree.” Changing Spring said.

“It’s not like we haven’t heard of this method before, but who can guarantee that the losers won’t go back on their words and use this tactic to get rid of an opponent?” Misty Castle’s Misty Lock said in an unhappy manner. It seems like he had fallen for this type of plan before.

“At worst, we can record our agreement and post it online. We can have the people on the Internet supervise it. I don’t think anyone will feel wronged doing that?” Jiang You said.

These Club guilds placed a great amount of importance on their reputation. If everyone could see the agreement, no one would go back on their word. Once Jiang You said this, no one else spoke up. In the end, Jiang You added: “In order to stop anyone harboring ill intentions, the guilds who lose in the Arena will protect the winner to prevent anyone from disturbing them. How about it?”

Everyone listened. This was to stop anyone from sending out open accounts to cause a disturbance. If everyone supervised the whole thing, that plan wouldn’t work.

“Does anyone have any objections?” Jiang You asked.

“I accept.” Misty Lock said, “If this really works, then I suggest we do the same every time. That way, we can walk towards a positive competition. We won’t need to keep plotting schemes all day and simply compete with strength.”

“Mm, I also accept.” Blooming Blossom nodded his head.

“I also accepted.” Void Walk’s West Riding Wind said.

It wasn’t without reason that these three happily accepted because compared to the Three Great Guilds and even the recently declining Excellent Dynasty, their strength was somewhat lacking. In a competition for bosses, they rarely won, usually because they noticed the boss first and killed it before others found out. As soon as another guild contested for it, they had little confidence in winning.

However, with Jiang You’s suggestion, it would be a PvP between elite teams. Their overall strength couldn’t compare to those guilds, but their elite teams weren’t any weaker. Compared to a contest of overall strength, they had a greater chance of winning. Moreover, if this became the norm, everyone would only need to focus on strengthening their elite teams, which would require less resources.

After all, to get strong equipment for a few characters, whether they had 1000 resources or 5000 resources didn’t matter too much because they wouldn’t even need to use 100 resources.

Those three guilds didn’t object. At this moment, Samsara’s guild leader Three Worlds Six Paths questioned: “How are we going to determine the winners in the Arena? Individual competition? Group arena? Team competition? Or…… war?”

There were several modes in PvP that the players could freely choose between. Unlike in pro competitions, the group arena didn’t necessarily have to be 3v3 nor did the team competition have to be 5v5 with one sub. In Glory, the numbers could be decided by the players. When one side had more than ten players, it wouldn’t be called a team competition anymore, but a battlefield. A 100v100 battle would be a war.

The pro scene definitely couldn’t play these modes. Have a team train 100 pro players? That would be insane.

“Okay, like Three World’s said, what mode should we use?” Jiang You asked.

“We’re all under the Clubs, so we should just do it according to the pro rules.” Three Worlds Six Paths answered immediately. He wouldn’t agree to a war. If the scale became larger, then overall strength would be more important. He was afraid Jiang You had thought of this, which was why he had intentionally proposed the idea.

Misty Lock, West Riding Wind, and Blooming Blossom naturally stood with Three Worlds Six Paths. They hadn’t asked about it before because they hadn’t thought of it. As soon as Three Worlds made a suggestion, they immediately supported his idea.

“I have no objections. What about everyone else?” Jiang You didn’t hesitate to reply.

Herb Garden, Blue Brook Guild, and Excellent Dynasty remained. This type of method forced them to give up their advantage. It would put them on the same footing as the other guilds. Tyrannical Ambition might agree, but the others might not.

Among these three, Changing Spring was the first to accept Jiang You’s proposal and didn’t immediately expressed his approval.

The other two saw this and also approved, seeing the general trend. However, the two guilds only said “Then I guess I’ll go with it for now.” Their words implied they would do it this time, but whether or not they continued doing it in the future would depend on the situation.

Chapter 533 – If There Aren’t Any Opportunities, Create Your Own

This time, the guild leaders personally led the teams to fight for the boss, so they didn't need to go through the trouble and open up a discussion group outside of the game. Everyone gathered together in the middle of the circle and quickly came to an agreement.

It was too bad for Ye Xiu and Wei Chen said. The two pro level players couldn't see or hear anything. They shamelessly snuck into the circle and tried to eavesdrop, but the guilds suddenly stopped moving. They clearly weren't going to fight the boss and were still negotiating with each other.

"How boring! What's there to talk about? In the end, they'll each have their own plans. Such a waste of time." Wei Chen spoke in an unhappy voice.

"It seems a bit different this time." Ye Xiu said.

"How?"

"Normally, the negotiations are a part of their plan. They should have already begun dispatching their troops by now. However, look at their troops. No one is moving. There haven't been any ambushes or any reinforcements arriving. Doesn't this look like a real negotiation?" Ye Xiu said.

"No way. They've been fighting for so many years. Why would they suddenly have a change in heart?" Wei Chen didn't believe it.

The two continued guessing. The discussion between the eight guild leaders finally concluded. In the end, they went with Jiang You's suggestion. The top guilds, like Herb Garden and Excellent Dynasty, left room for discussion in the future though. The slightly less powerful guilds, like Misty Castle and Blossom Valley, hoped this plan would pave the path for future conflicts.

After drawing up their new plan, the eight guilds immediately signed an agreement and had the public be the judges. Then, they made an announcement in their respective guild forums, as well as their guild's web page as proof. After making the arrangements, everyone returned to the game and prepared to enter the Arena to decide who the boss would belong to.

Chen Guo had her materials displayed out on the streets. She didn't even need to be at her keyboard to do this, so she wasn't busy right now. From time to time, she would go back to the game and take a look, but most of the time, she was browsing forums. A post suddenly caught her eye. Something about eight guilds and proof. It all seemed very grand. Chen Guo clicked on it and suddenly felt like she was in a dream.

It can't be a coincidence, right?

Chen Guo mumbled. She didn't have much to do and Ye Xiu was no longer on the Equipment Editor, so she would see what Ye Xiu was up to from time to time. Ye Xiu had received a call to go to Poison Fang Swamp and went to check out the wild boss with Wei Chen's gang. She didn't have any urgent matters to take care of, so she had even hesitated on whether or not she should join them. Before she could make a decision, she noticed the post.

"Hey, look at this." Chen Guo called for Ye Xiu.

"Hm?" Ye Xiu turned his head in a bored manner, but when his gaze hit Chen Guo's screen, he immediately stared blankly for a moment, before quickly reading the content of the post more carefully.

At the same time, the eight guilds had already begun to move. Ye Xiu heard Wei Chen say: "Huh? What's going on? Why are they leaving?"

Ye Xiu's gaze returned to his computer and saw the eight guilds begin to move. The guilds had made an agreement and began to disperse.

"We have to go back too." Ye Xiu saw their movements and knew it would be difficult for them to hide, especially with Wei Chen's bros. Their skill level was only average and they definitely weren't good enough to deal with this situation.

"You just worry about yourself!" Ye Xiu heard Wei Chen say in delight. Ye Xiu turned his camera around to look and was left completely speechless.

Wei Chen's Windward Formation led two team of players. At this moment, they had put on their guild tags, all from big guilds. Wei Chen's Windward Formation was from Blue Brook Guild, as well as three others. Apart from them, there were tags from Herb Garden, Tyrannical Ambition, Excellent Dynasty.... All twenty of them had tags from the eight guilds.

"He's in the mountain there. Deep in the clouds somewhere." Wei Chen recited and chuckled. Clearly, nothing could serve as better protection than a guild tag in their situation. Let alone lesser known guilds, no one knew everyone in their own guilds.

"Stop acting as if you're cultured. If you're so good at reading, hurry up and check the forums!" Ye Xiu said and then had Lord Grim retreat.

"The forums? Why?" Wei Chen saw Lord Grim had already run away, so he typed it out.

"These guilds actually came to an agreement on something this time." Ye Xiu said.

"What type of agreement?" Wei Chen asked.

"A peaceful solution." Ye Xiu said.

"F*ck, no way." Wei Chen doubted. He had wanted to steal a boss from the big guilds' mouths and there was only one way to do it: to take advantage of a crisis. The more chaotic the battle was, the more numerous the opportunities, but if they decided on a peaceful solution, then how was he supposed to cause a ruckus?

Wei Chen told his bros to hurry and hide. At the same time, he reminded them to avoid players from their guilds. A word bubble appeared above his head and then he left the game to look at the forums.

The post had a lot of stickies on it, so Wei Chen easily noticed it. He opened it and skimmed through the contents. He quickly returned to the game and let out a few curses in his private chat window with Lord Grim: "****, you're plain bad luck!"

"Brother, why do you say that?" Ye Xiu replied.

"Stop pretending!" Wei Chen was furious. The eight guilds made a post as proof and didn't say much about it, but Ye Xiu and Wei Chen could figure out the reason. If he could figure it out, Ye Xiu had most definitely figured it out too. He might be older than Ye Xiu by a few years, but they had the same experience in terms of Glory.

Why did these eight guilds suddenly come up with a "peaceful way" after so many years of fighting and scheming with each other? All because of the pressure from Ye Xiu!

Even though they always felt like Ye Xiu should be powerless as a single individual, this single individual had made them suffer losses who knew how many times! So what if he was just an individual? He was constantly a source of their misfortune. How could they ignore him as an opponent simply because he was a single individual?

Against such a strong foe, the guilds didn't dare expose any openings, especially after the Wilderness Town fiasco. This individual had picked up a few friends. Deception and Heavenly Justice, with such powerful helpers, how could he be considered powerless?

Wei Chen was just about to loot a burning house, but because of Ye Xiu's existence, the fire disappeared. What could that be called other than a robbery? Wei Chen wasn't some powerful manager. For him, let alone killing a wild boss, just seeing one wasn't easy. If not, why would he not have any materials? Why else would his Death's Hand still only be Level 60 after all these years?

This time, a rare opportunity came, but because of a reason like this, the opportunity vanished like thin air. Wei Chen wanted to murder Ye Xiu right now.

"Don't be anxious. Seeing how dirty your two teams are playing, let me think of something." Ye Xiu said.

"Don't tell me to attack them directly and stir up trouble! We're too low-leveled. Everyone present is a core elite. To tell you the truth, I'm afraid they've already seen through our guild tags. If you do that type of method, we'll easily be spotted." Wei Chen said.

"Timing and method are important in stirring up trouble. You're method is too direct. We can be a bit more clever. For example, they'll be organizing their experts to fight in the Arena. They'll definitely be taking the top players from their guilds, so we can act while they're not there. Moreover, we don't have to directly attack them. We can send in a poisonous worm or take the chance to attack the boss. In any case, they'll have a lot to deal with." Ye Xiu said.

"Maybe we can announce the boss to the world." Wei Chen said.

"We can do that too. However, if the eight guilds have already publicly announced it, the eight guilds will have allied together. Who has the strength to compete with them now?" Ye Xiu said.

"Don't say it like that! We're going to have to do it!" Wei Chen said.

"Right right right, I forgot." Ye Xiu replied.

"The things you talked about are possible..." Wei Chen began thinking, "If they've made the post, then they must have welcome people to come watch as proof. It should be obvious when they fight the boss. We can begin then."

"We can make our arrangements now." Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, I'll get busy. This senior will gather a bunch of poisonous worms to receive these young masters!" Wei Chen cackled.

"Do you see the boss? If the opportunity comes, aggro it, even if it costs you your life." Ye Xiu said.

"That must be done." Wei Chen replied.

"That's good then."

"Now that I think about it, isn't your existence worthless right now?" Wei Chen said.

"How uncultured. When the time comes, I can come out and make a stand. Just my head and name will gather lots of attention." Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen went silent for a long time. He couldn't help but admit that this was true and sighed: "D*mn, you really are sh*t!"

Everything went as they had predicted. The eight guilds made a post for proof. The more witnesses the better. They quickly announced the competition and all spectators were welcome. The players knew the competition would be between the top experts of each guild. Even though they weren't pro level players, they were still far better than everyone else. They were also easy to find in the game and were a sort of grassroot celebrities.

"Observe the areas under each guild's control. We'll have an order in which we stir up trouble, so we should do some research." Ye Xiu said.

"Hm? Have the ones who lose cause trouble." Wei Chen immediately understood.

"I'll be watching them. Wait for my message." Ye Xiu said.

"I'm not ready yet. Don't rush it." Wei Chen hurried with his work.

"And that's my fault?" Ye Xiu was speechless.

"Aren't you a God?" Wei Chen began arguing again.

Chapter 534 – Venomous Flies

The entrance to the Arena in every major city of the Heavenly Domain suddenly became bustling with noise. After the surrounding players found out about the news, all of them ran to the Arena to watch the competition.

Every week, pro players provided matches for everyone to watch every week. But what about these guild experts? Even though they were closer to normal players, very few had really seen them play in PvP. Now that the news came out, some people went to cheer for their guild seniors. Some went to see what the noise was all about. Some took the opportunity to make bets. All sorts of people came to the Arena towards a single room. The room quickly filled up with people.

The eight guilds intentionally waited for the spectators to come. Seeing that there were enough people, they began the competition. They had thrown dice beforehand to determine the order and knew the results. The first match would be between Misty Castle and Herb Garden. The experts of the two sides were already standing on stage.

Meanwhile, Ye Xiu borrowed Chen Guo’s computer to watch. He wasn’t interested in the fights. From time to time he would glance at her screen, while typing to Wei Chen: “What if it comes to Blue Brook Guild? Will you be under pressure?”

“Nonsense. Of course. Don’t you see I’m part of Blue Brook Guild? If I get kicked out of the guild, it’ll be a huge loss for me. You should know the benefits of being in a big guild.” Wei Chen replied.

“You really are shameless.” Ye Xiu disdained.

“This is called competitive integrity. If you see Excellent Era, would you go easy because of your memories with them?” Wei Chen said.

“That depends on who I meet.” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch.” Wei Chen didn’t believe him.

Afterwards, Ye Xiu continued to glance at the matches from time to time, but most of his attention was traveling around Poison Fang Swamp. He had to avoid the eight guilds, but he also didn’t want to stray too far from the boss.

Poison Fang Swamp was very quiet today. The eight guilds were afraid of outsiders interfering, so while waiting for the results of the competition, they didn’t reveal the boss’s whereabouts. The Heavenly Domain was huge. Trying to find it through pure luck wasn’t very logical. As for the other guilds, even if they got the information, when they saw the attitudes of the eight guilds, they knew that trying to join now was already too late. It wouldn’t be good to provoke them.

In the Arena, the eight guilds didn’t play according to all of the pro scene’s rules. If they did, it would take way too long and they didn’t have such time to waste. As a result, they only played team competitions to determine the winner with the same rules as the pro scene. Five versus five with one substitute each.

Because the competition had been quickly devised and set in motion, the map was chosen randomly, so neither side would have any tactical advantage. After fighting back and forth several times, Misty Castle finally couldn’t hold on any longer and Herb Garden won the first match.

Even though MIsty Castle was somewhat disappointed, they weren’t suffering. If they had fought for the boss the normal way, their chances of taking the boss was very small, so it wasn’t hard accepting their defeat.

“Misty Castle lost.” Ye Xiu told Wei Chen.

“I don’t think we should act yet. Wait a moment. We can still do a bit more preparing. Wait for an unexpected result. That would be the perfect time to act.” Wei Chen was extremely dirty.

“Wait for my next message.” Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more.

Next was Blue Brook Guild versus Tyrannical Ambition. Tyrannical Ambition lost. Jiang You was the first to propose the plan. Even though the plan had already gone this far, everyone was still a bit hesitant. Seeing how quickly Tyrannical Ambition had been eliminated, they began believing Jiang You didn’t have any ulterior motives.

Jiang You laughed and expressed the acknowledgement of their defeat.

Excellent Dynasty versus Blossom Valley. Excellent Dynasty won.

Samsara versus Void Walk. Samsara won.

Four guilds were eliminated. None of them were too surprising. The four matches ended relatively quickly. Even so, an hour had already passed. Wei Chen worked busily making preparations during that hour. The next round of matches between these four guilds began. Enough people had come as witnesses for their matches, so they decided to hurry with the matches and played both at once.

Samsara versus Herb Garden.

Excellent Dynasty versus Blue Brook Guild.

The first matched ended with Samsara beating Herb Garden, which was certainly a surprise. When the results came out, the spectators immediately dispersed and went to watch the other match. Chen Guo also went along. The other match quickly ended too. This time, Blue Brook Guild lost.

“We can act now.” Ye Xiu messaged Wei Chen.

“What’s the situation?”

“Herb Garden, Blue Brook Guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“My god. Blue Brook Guild? Are you serious?” Wei Cen asked.

“Competitive integrity.” Ye Xiu reminded.

“F*ck it. Let’s go!” Wei Chen replied. By this time, the eight guilds had already stopped scouting around. They had confirmed no outsider had come to cause trouble and returned to guard the boss. Wei Chen had finished his preparations. It had been a busy hour! Getting the monsters to gather towards a desired direction wasn’t an easy task. The one advantage Wei Chen had was the gang of bros beside him. He could lead them step by step. If they failed, he could personally step in and fix the situation. Ye Xiu finally sent him the go-ahead. Wei Chen picked out a few people and had them start the task.

His gang was impatient to move. When they heard the order, they nearly let out a cheer. They controlled their characters and threw insect repellant smoke from their pockets towards the direction Wei Chen had forced them to memorize.

After throwing the insect repellant, they heard a buzz that boomed like thunder. A huge swarm of venomous flies had taken flight.

Countless venomous flies flew out from the swamp away from the insect repellant. The flies seemed to cover the skies as they moved towards a single direction. Where else could they fly? The insect repellant smoke was in the other direction. In order to get away from the repellant, they had to fly away!

The loud buzzing frightened the guild players ahead. When they looked back, they turned pale with fright.

“F*ck, where’d all these venomous flies come from?””

The venomous flies moved swiftly and arrived in an instant. Wei Chen’s bros had already hidden themselves among the guild and threw a bit more insect repellant.

Players who came to Poison Fang Swamp often brought insect repellant smoke. It was used very frequently too. Even if they hadn’t done this, they probably wouldn’t have gotten caught in any case because everyone else was doing the same thing.

Insect repellant smoke might be effective, but no matter how much the guild players used at this time, they wouldn’t get the desired effect. Insect repellant smoke was just something the insects didn’t like; it didn’t kill the insects. If the insect repellant smoke surrounded the venomous flies, the flies would buzz around randomly like houseflies. They wouldn’t receive any damage. If the player walked too close, the flies would still bite.

Players unaware of this bit of knowledge now learned the lesson through their own flesh and blood. One bro threw out some insect repellant, but the repellant surrounded these venomous flies. The flies began flying around randomly and a few still headed towards him. Who knew how many flies came at him, but this bro quickly fell to the ground.

This was one reason small monsters like these were scary. Because of their small size, they could fly and attack at the same time, allowing them to cover a wide range. This was one reason why Ye Xiu and Wei Chen chose to use this tactic. If they had been goblins, no matter how many goblins there were, they wouldn’t have much killing threat. It was the same theory behind surrounding bosses. Even if you had thousands of troops, only a few could get close to the boss no?

These flies avoided this issue. They could cover above, below, left, right, all around, while attacking the player. No matter how little damage they did, with so many of them, they would certainly be able to kill. These venomous flies did quite a lot of damage too. The players were Level 70. The flies were Level 65. The level difference wasn’t significant enough. Moreover, their attacks had a chance to poison. The corpse of the dead player had turned green.

One person had died instantly, making the others extremely frightened. The second to face the flies was a Knight, who instinctively raised his shield.

Constant blocking noises could be heard from the venomous flies crashing into his shield. It sounded very comforting, but the Knight himself wasn’t looking good. Just because the shield blocked the flies didn’t mean the Knight wasn’t taking damage. The shield only reduced damage. With so many flies, the blocking noise continued to echo and the Knight’s health fell rapidly. In fright, the Knight shouted for the Clerics to help him.

When he looked back, the Clerics had been surrounded by venomous flies too! These venomous flies automatically attacked and wouldn’t only attack a single target. They had each found their own target. Players who only had one fly targeting them weren’t afraid, but with everyone packed together so closely, the flies would eventually get them.

The swarm of venomous flies had come from nowhere, catching everyone off guard. Many players instantly died. The remaining hastily moved into a defensive formation. The flies wouldn’t be enough to wipe out their entire group.

The news of being ambushed quickly reached their guild leader’s ears. The ambushed guild happened to be the guild just about to enter the deciding match: Samsara.

“WHAT!!” Samsara’s guild leader Three Worlds Six Paths became furious and immediately became suspicious of Herb Garden, who had just been defeated by Samsara. When a big guild lost a big opportunity, it was hard not to be resentful. When he thought of the initial agreement from every guild, Herb Garden’s response had been somewhat reluctant. Now, his guild had been ambushed by venomous flies. Of course! After all, the agreement was up for everyone to see, so it wasn’t possible to directly make an attack, so they made an indirect attack instead.

“Despicable!” Three Worlds Six Paths cursed in anger. The other guild leaders also received the news and immediately knew who Three Worlds was angry at. Jiang You, who had proposed the idea, hastily said in defense: “Three Worlds, don’t be rash. We don’t know the whole situation yet!”

“All eight guilds cleared the field together. There couldn’t have been a problem. If it wasn’t us, then who could it be? The venomous flies couldn’t have just happened to all come out and attack them. Even the noobs of the tenth server would laugh!” Three Worlds Six Paths spat.

Jiang You was just about to respond, when he suddenly received more news: his own guild had been attacked by venomous flies and Blue Brook Guild had started fighting the boss!

Chapter 535 – Fierce Mantis

This piece of news surprised Jiang You. He still wanted to calmly figure out what exactly happened, but the other guilds had already begun stamping their feet in anger. Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t the only one who had been attacked by a swarm of venomous flies. All of the guilds had been thrown into disorder. The sudden ambush by the venomous flies wasn’t easy to deal with.

“Is this the so-called ‘peaceful way’?” Three Worlds Six Realms couldn’t sit still once he learned that Blue Brook Guild had started fighting the boss. His guild hadn’t been eliminated yet and now someone had caused a ruckus. Did this mean everything before had been for naught? How could he stay calm?

Excellent Dynasty was in a similar mood. They had also won two matches in a row and were one of the last remaining guilds in the competition. When they heard about the disturbance, they immediately denounced Blue Brook Guild too. Apart from them, Misty Castle, Void Walk, Blossom Valley had truly hoped this would be a peaceful way of determining the owner of the boss. Seeing such an act of betrayal, they naturally felt extremely angry and also lashed out at Blue Brook Guild. They did it in the public chat too, directly exposing the misdeed to all of the spectators watching the deciding match.

The spectators heard the news and also went into an uproar. Blue Brook Guild immediately became the target of a rain of arrows.

Ye Xiu saw the situation from Chen Guo’s screen and felt somewhat disapproving. He sent Wei Chen’s Windward Formation a message: “Don’t you think that pretending Blue Brook Guild is fighting the boss feels a bit too fake? All of them can confirm it. This approach is too stupid. It’s not realistic at all.”

“He he, you have to link it with the actual circumstances. When something like this happens, it can easily be explained, but for some reason, Blue Brook Guild’s guild leader Changing Spring seems to have some sort of mental block towards typing words. If you want this guy to give an explanation to dissolve the situation, it’s not going to happen.” Wei Chen replied.

Ye Xiu was speechless. He didn’t think Wei Chen would be so merciless to Blue Brook Guild. He truly deserves to be considered one of the most shameless pros in the competitive scene.

“You truly have no sense of kindness.” Ye Xiu sighed.

As they discussed this with each other, the situation had already devolved into a complete mess. Nearly all of the eight guilds had been ambushed by venomous flies and had no time to deal with others. They could only watch with eyes dripping blood as Swamp Hunger Leipu pounced at Blue Brook Guild.

As for Blue Brook Guild? They had no idea what was going on. The venomous flies didn’t attack them. At first, they felt lucky and put up their guards. Who knew the other guilds had already put the blame on them and were looking at them with murderous intentions?

Finally, Blue Brook Guild encountered an attack, but it wasn’t by venomous flies. It was by the boss. For the other guilds, this completely confirmed the conspiracy theory. If it weren’t for the venomous flies attack them, the other guilds would have already started attacking Blue Brook Guild.

In reality, Blue Brook Guild had no idea the boss would suddenly charge at them. It seemed like someone had accidentally attacked or entered the boss’s aggro range. The problem was in this mess, no one had been paying attention.

“Who was it?” The team leader even asked, but the boss wasn’t going to wait for them to talk.

Swamp Hunter Leipu!

An Assassin and a Thief dual class. His movements were incredibly swift. He took a single step and became a blur. In an instant, he appeared in front of Blue Brook Guild’s boss team. He lifted up his two hands and pulled out two daggers. One of them was held in an upright position, while the other was held in reverse. He stabbed with one dagger and slashed with the other, sending two people tumbling backwards.

“Blue Brook Guild has started attacking the boss!!”

Someone suddenly yelled from nearby.

“We didn’t!” Blue Brook Guild’s team leader immediately yelled. He clearly realized pulling the boss in this situation was a very serious problem.

“Blue Brook Guild set up venomous flies to attack us and is now taking the opportunity to kill the boss! Blue Brook Guild is too despicable!!” Shouts of criticism came ceaselessly. The team leader of Blue Brook Guild was sweating like mad. The top core experts in the guild were peak experts and had gone to the Arena to fight. The team leader had been left here and had now encountered a difficult problem. In panic, he hastily asked the guild leader for help. How could he know the guild leader was in an even worse situation than him? He was drowning in spittle right now.

“Everyone retreat! Do not attack back!!”

The team leader couldn’t get a reply from the guild leader, so he could only give instructions on his own. He told his guild members not to touch the boss to prove their good faith.

But who was Swamp Hunter Leipu? A wild boss. Standing there taking a beating and not attacking back wasn’t something he would understand. If the Clerics started healing the injured, the boss would immediately switch targets to the Clerics. Even if the Clerics healed each other to tank the boss, they wouldn’t last long. Under this vicious cycle, the team would wipe out.

If they didn’t attack back, they would prove their good faith. It might be effective, but against Swamp Hunter Leipu, they would certainly die in order to prove this point.

The team leader never said clearly if this was his intention. The team members didn’t plan on sacrificing their lives for principles. If they couldn’t fight back, then what else could they do other than run? As a result, they began to retreat.

They didn’t fight back, but by running, it looked like they were trying to move the boss away from all of the other guilds. Were they trying to prove their good faith or did they have other evil schemes in mind?

“They want to leave!” The other guilds fending off venomous flies saw what was happening and thought their true objective was to pull the boss away.

“Blue Brook Guild is about to pull the boss away. Guild leader, do we kill them or not?”

“Guild leader, kill or not???”

At this moment, the guild leaders saw the news and became furious. Everything had already reached this step, who would listen to Changing Spring’s excuses? Samsara’s Three Worlds Six Paths directly left. Excellent Dynasty’s Chen Yehui quickly followed suit. On the other hand, the other guilds were in a bit of a predicament though.

According to their agreement, Samsara or Excellent Dynasty should be the ones to kill Swamp Hunter Leipu. Even though someone had broken the agreement first, if they used this opportunity to fight for the boss, they wouldn’t be any different from the original betrayer. With so many spectators as proof of their losses in the previous matches, it wouldn’t be appropriate to fight the boss.

They didn’t dare to act rashly in this type of situation. Was Blue Brook Guild really that sh*tty?

Everyone mumbled to themselves, but none of them said it out loud. They had already lost their opportunity to kill the boss. In any case, it would be better to watch the events unfold. Why should they speak up for Blue Brook Guild? Even if one day everyone finds a peaceful way to walk on, thoughts of hoping the other side to fall would always stay.

Deep down, everyone knew a peaceful way of competing for objectives was just an ideal. The reason for their temporary agreement wasn’t the norm. Against a God like Lord Grim and an eye-catching Heavenly Justice, they had to give them their attention. None of them truly had much good faith towards each other.

“KILL!”

Three Worlds Six Paths was the first to give the order.

He had taken a huge mental blow and felt like he had been duped. Right now, it was either the fish died or the net split. Even if his guild couldn’t get the boss, he would make sure Blue Brook Guild would suffer. Three Worlds Six Paths could be hot-blooded at times. He wasn’t someone who only planned carefully and meticulously.

With his personality and at this type of battle, the morale he could muster up was frightening.

Nothing else mattered, but to kill!

Samsara was the first to be hit by the venomous flies and had suffered a few losses, but they were also first to stabilize the situation. Anyone who came to kill the wild boss would naturally be the guild’s elites. A disturbance like this wasn’t something that would stop them.

Even though they hadn’t completely cleared away the venomous flies, when they received their guild leader’s order, several of them took up their weapons and charged towards Blue Broo Guild.

“Brothers! Forward! Kill those despicable, shameless Blue Brook Guild dogs!!” Samsara’s team leader roared and took the lead. His face had already been torn apart and his voice didn’t sound pleasant.

At the same time, Three Worlds Six Paths gave a reply on the post on their agreement. He announced that Blue Brook Guild would reap the consequences for going back on their word. Samsara had been tricked and they weren’t going to tolerate it.

Fight! Your Blue Brook Guild might be one of the Three Great Guilds, but our Samsara isn’t afraid. Today, we’ll teach you a lesson!

It was very rare for a guild leader to make a declaration. With how the Club guilds operated, even though there had been many conflicts across all of the servers, no one had ever made such a powerful statement. Let alone challenging a stronger guild, it wasn’t wise to do so from a business perspective either.

Three Worlds Six Path’s reply was picked out and made as a post. Supporters gathered together, not just Samsara fans, but the neutral fans also stood by Samsara. Team Blue Rain fans didn’t know the truth and with just the revelations given by the spectators, they had no way of justifying their guild’s actions.

“KILL!”

In Poison Fang Swamp, Samsara charged at Blue Brook Guild, who were still trying to prove they weren’t attacking the boss. How could they have known the others thought they were trying to pull the boss away? When they saw Samsara suddenly rushing at them, they once again panicked. Samsara was smart too. They only attacked Blue Brook Guild and wouldn’t aggro the boss. Swamp Hunter Leipu would be focused on Blue Brook Guild and would act as a helper to Samsara.

“F*ck, what are you guys going?” Blue Brook Guild’s team leader still wanted to try explaining the situation, but Samsara directly chopped him into pieces and turned him into a corpse. Samsara shout their resentment and went berserk.

Blue Brook Guild no longer had a leader and fell into disarray. They formed small groups and defended against the attack.

The other guilds had stabilized their teams, but because they had lost the matches in the Arena, their guild leaders ordered them not to interfere. However, one guild was different. Excellent Dynasty had stabilized themselves after the venomous fly ambush, but didn’t directly charge forward like Samsara. They simply smiled as they watched Blue Brook Guild get slaughtered.

“Samsara brothers. Our Excellent Dynasty has a share of this boss!” Excellent Dynasty’s team leader felt like very pleased with their circumstances.

“Okay, come! Even if you two both fight together, our Samsara isn’t afraid!” Samsara’s players didn’t plan on stopping. Excellent Dynasty was surprised. What a fierce mantis! After finishing off the snake, the mantis was also planning on taking down the oriole.

Chapter 536 – Nobody Move!

Excellent Dynasty thought that they would be the ones to give Samsara a surprise, but they never thought that they would be the ones surprised by Samsara. There wasn’t much interaction between them. As soon as Excellent Dynasty started shouting, Samsara immediately pounced on them as if they were mad.

“F*ck! Did you guys go crazy?!” Excellent Dynasty had tried to deliver shock to their opponents but turned out to be the ones shocked. They confidently thought that they could hold their ground against Samsara. After Samsara’s vicious fight against Blue Brook Guild, they must have suffered heavy losses. Right after Excellent Dynasty made their intentions clear, even if they didn’t compromise, they could at least negotiate. They wouldn’t be in too terrible of a situation.

However, Samsara was extremely unreasonable. Despite the obvious difference in strength, they were still actively engaging their enemies in battle, with absolutely no intentions of negotiating. Were they delusional?

Despite not having good intentions, Excellent Dynasty didn’t expect that they would have such a major fall out with Samsara. They hadn’t been prepared for Samsara’s response. Samsara’s fierce attack caught them by surprise and just like Blue Brook Guild, they were beaten into submission.

Before they could come to their senses, several of their players had already fallen.

“What are you doing Samsara!” Excellent Dynasty players were angry, but they didn’t want to be so irrational like Samsara and go straight for the blood of their enemies. If both sides fought each other, wouldn’t others take advantage? They were there for the boss, not to PK!

Boss！

Right! Where’s the boss?

When they thought of this, the players from Excellent Dynasty immediately looked towards Blue Brook Guild to look for the boss. Blue Brook Guild was having a rough time today. They didn’t dare to fight back against the boss’s attacks and they felt wronged by Samsara’s attacks. Facing attacks from both sides, the casualties were very heavy. Even with Samsara’s sudden change of attention towards Excellent Dynasty, the boss was still wreaking havoc, though the boss was finally pulled away by someone else.

But such an action didn’t feel right in the eyes of the other guilds, especially Excellent Dynasty that had been plotting to get the Boss rationally. However, the boss had already been pulled far away. The ones dragging the Boss away were three players with Blue Brook Guild tags.

“The boss has already been stolen away, why are we fighting?” The team leader of Excellent Dynasty roared in frustration.

“Our Samsara isn’t fighting for the boss today, we fight for our honor!” Samsara replied in an arrogant manner, not backing down a single inch.

Excellent Dynasty’s players coughed up blood. Samsara didn’t have the rationale that a Club guild was supposed to have.

“Fine. You want your honor, go play with Blue Brook Guild. Stop bothering us! We still have important matters to tend to.” Excellent Era’s team leader shouted.

“Hmph, don’t think we don’t know what Excellent Dynasty is planning.” Samsara’s people yelled back.

All said and done, Excellent Dynasty felt somewhat guilty. Right after Blue Brook Guild’s trickery was exposed, Samsara immediately charged in. On the other hand, Excellent Dynasty bided their time, waiting for Samsara and Blue Brook Guild to beat each other up and then planning to appear out of nowhere to make their presence known. However, Samsara clearly didn’t care anymore and continued fighting.

“You think Excellent Dynasty is afraid of you?” Excellent Dynasty’s team leader felt angry too. He originally hadn’t wanted to fight with Samsara, but how could he hold himself back anymore? He couldn’t. With a shout, Excellent Dynasty immediately engaged Samsara in a vicious battle.

“Fine! We didn’t have the chance to fight each other in the Arena, so let’s settle our scores right here right now!” Samsara players didn’t show even a hint of fear; their morale was high as ever.

The other guilds could only stare at each other with wide eyes. They couldn’t understand Samsara’s irrational behavior either. Going against Blue Brook Guild could bring honor to your guild and could return the rights to fight the boss to the rightful guild, but the fight against Excellent Dynasty was just pure anger at them. They threw away any gains for their honor.

The guilds had also finally stabilized the situation after the ambush by poisonous flies. They were too embarrassed to join the fight for the boss. However, with two guilds already fighting against each other and the boss being dragged further and further away by Blue Brook Guild members, they really wanted to move. But as soon as they made even the slightest of movements, they were intercepted by players from Blue Brook Guild.

“Nobody moves!” Blue Brook Guild’s players shouted, “We have to clarify this matter right now!”

“F*ck, the Boss is being dragged away by your guys and you’re still telling us to remain where we are. What’s there to be discussed?” Everyone was angry after listening to Blue Brook Guild.

“The boss is gone, but this has nothing to do with you. According to our agreement, do you guys have the rights to kill it?” Somebody from Blue Brook Guild said in a cold voice. It was Blue Brook Guild’s leader, Changing Spring.

It wasn’t possible to get over here from the city so quickly, unless a teleportation scroll was used. With chaos erupting at both sites, Changing Spring had a lot on his hands. But the situation in Poison Fang Swamp was somewhat cleaner. Everyone there was from the eight guilds. In comparison, there were numerous spectators in the Arena. Changing Spring thought it out and decided to settle things in the swamp first. Once he teleported, he found that the situation had already reached such a critical step.

“We agreed to maintain order here, but your Blue Brook Guild broke its promise, took the boss away, and is now stopping us from following it. Do you think we’re stupid?”

“You’re not stupid, but we’re not idiots either. Anybody who thinks that this is caused by Blue Brook Guild has a brain full of sh*t!” With Blue Brook Guild treated unjustly, courtesy was the last thing on Changing Spring’s mind.

Suffering from attacks by Samsara and the boss, only a few Blue Brook Guild players remained, but they clutched tightly to their weapons and went into formation, giving out a tenacious aura just like Samsara.

“You’re still putting up a farce? The three men that pulled the boss away had Blue Brook Guild tags hanging right on top of their heads. Everybody saw it.” Someone shouted.

“Just having a guild tag proves that they’re our men? Is this your first day playing Glory? Are you that naive?” The person was instead ridiculed by Changing Spring and he couldn’t come up with a response. Framing wasn’t impossible. All the guilds on scene had several accounts in hand that bore the Blue Brook Guild tag.

“I swear that this matter today has nothing to do with Blue Brook Guild. And I am almost certain that the guilds present here wouldn’t do such shameless acts either. This must be the work of an outsider.” Changing Spring said.

“You can say anything you want, but who knows if this isn’t a plot by Blue Brook Guild?” Someone still questioned.

“Destroying our own reputation for a mere Level 65 Boss. Think about it rationally, is that worth it?” Changing Spring responded with a question of his own.

The players went silent again. They were all the elites of their guilds and they understood his reasoning.

Since Changing Spring was already on the scene. The leaders of the other guilds weren’t far behind, some of them had even arrived earlier than him, but as the losers in the Arena, their positions became awkward. As a result, they kept quiet, waiting for a change in situation just like Excellent Dynasty did earlier on.

Excellent Dynasty was one of the victors in the duel. After waiting for chance to come, they switched from being passive to aggressive. They tried to grab the prize, which resulted in their clash with Samsara that ended with massive casualties on both sides. The other guilds were also observing from the sidelines and made the decision to strike and grab the benefits for their own. But just as they were sneaking up on the Boss, they were stopped by Changing Spring.

The guild leaders had no choice but to continue staying at the sidelines, waiting for Changing Spring to handle the current situation. It seemed like it wouldn’t hard for him though, as long as no one else was in a complete frenzy like Samsara was. Changing Spring’s analysis on the situation was acceptable.

After noticing that the chaos had subsided, each guild’s leader could no longer hide their presence and had to speak up for their guild.

“What Brother Spring said made sense, but it’s also true that the boss was stolen. Are we just going to sit here and watch?” The guild leader of Herb Garden, Arisaema, asked.

“Ha ha...… Sit here and watch? I don’t think so! I don’t believe that a simple ‘Don’t move!’ from me could stop you guys. Let me guess, the ones that are secretly tracking the boss aren’t of the minority, right? Not a single member of Blue Brook Guild took part in such an action and I hope that the guilds that did will watch carefully. We’ll see clearly who got the boss in the end. I’d like to ask for you guys to record the entire process. My Blue Brook Guild needs it as proof of our innocence. Thanks.”

The guild leaders were silent again. Changing Spring’s deduction was correct. They didn’t let Blue Brook Guild stop them and had already sent people out to secretly track down the Boss. As for the words that came after, they didn’t object to them. Those were formalities. If it was a plot by Blue Brook Guild and they sent out a team carrying the Blue Brook Guild’s banner to meet up with those three at this point, then they were truly stupid.

Even if Blue Brook Guild was setting it up, they’d be using open accounts and such accounts had no ties with the guild.

Guild leaders were people capable of thinking quickly and coming up with countless schemes in a single second. Faced with this situation, their priority was no longer the boss, but to hurt Blue Brook Guild as much as possible. This was much more valuable than the rare items and materials dropped by some random wild boss.

What should they do?

Send out their spies in Blue Brook Guild?

Kill those that were aiding the three that stole the Boss, creating a situation where nobody took over the boss, which would be a sign that Blue Brook Guild was guilty?

Ideas after ideas flashed through the minds of the guild leaders, while Excellent Dynasty and Samsara were still fighting. Nobody thought to break up the fight. Deep down, they hated the two victors of the fight for the boss and hoped that both would suffer heavy losses.

“D*mn, I’ve finally stolen the boss, but somebody is tailing me. Are you ready?” At the same time, Wei Chen sent a message to Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

“I’ve been waiting.” Ye Xiu replied.

For those two, the plan was simple. They really hadn’t planned on harming any guilds. Their goal was to kill the boss and get the materials that they direly needed. That was all.

Chapter 537 – Lurkers

Poison Fang Swamp.

Numerous players from the Club guilds were sprinting forward. In their field of view, they could see Swamp Hunter Leipu running in the same direction.

This was the problem with wild bosses. Because of their random spawn locations, they had no fixed area where they resided. The Swamp Hunter could move about in any area of the Poison Fang Swamp. Any aggroing skills could pull Swamp Hunter Leipu to any part of the map.

However, it wasn't easy to do. If a player could effortlessly pull the wild boss all around the map, wouldn't it be easy to kite the boss around forever?

This was why the three Blue Brook Guild players that had managed to steal the Swamp Hunter Leipu were in a difficult situation. It took a lot of effort for them to deal with the boss chasing them from behind. As a result, the speed at which they were escaping wasn't fast either. If the pursuers wanted to catch up, the pursuers could catch up to them in no time. It was just that the guild members had received different orders from their guild leaders. Not one of them had any intention of catching up to the boss. Instead, they stayed behind and observed, while diverting a part of their attention to keep an eye out for players from other guilds.

"If you have the chance, you can try and take them out, but remember, you must stay hidden!" Two players from Herb Garden, Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean, received these orders from their guild leader.

These two characters were named after herbs and were core members of the guild, so the guild leader had placed great trust in them. One of them was an Assassin, while the other was a Ninja. Both classes were adept in ambush and assassination. With the poor terrain of the Poison Fang Swamp, it was the perfect place for their classes to shine. As they tracked down the boss, they set their sights on a Battle Mage from Misty Castle.

Battle Mages wore leather armor and only had mediocre health and defense. Because of the movement speed buff from the Neutral Chaser, the Battle Mage moved quite quickly, but to trigger the buff, the Battle Mage had to constantly attack targets. Thus, the Battle Mage had to attack monsters constantly in an attempt to maintain the movement speed buff from the Neutral Chaser. He exposed himself a lot, possibly because of his guild leader's orders. However, this pursuit didn't require high movement speed, so the movement speed buff from the Neutral Chaser wasn't necessary.

"No good. He's attracting too much attention. If we kill him, he might not notice us, but the others definitely will. That won't be good for us." Octagon Aniseed said to Sword Bean.

There wasn't enough time to deploy open accounts, which was why Arisaema ordered them directly to take up this mission. Even if they hid their guild tag, their names were too obvious. Even if their names weren't exposed, the spies hidden in their guild could easily search up their names. This was why Arisaema specifically gave orders for them to leave the guild if they were revealed.

"Let's go for a different target then." Sword Bean agreed with Octagon Aniseed's opinion. Right when they were about to reposition themselves, a flame appeared in their field of view. It originated from underneath the Battle Mage.

Being veterans, they could tell that the Battle Mage had triggered an Inferno Trap planted by a Thief.

The elites from Club guilds usually possessed extraordinary skills. The Battle Mage immediately reacted by jumping backwards after triggering the trap. Although he still took some of the damage, it was way better than having to take the full brunt of the trap's damage. Inferno Traps didn't have the ability to limit a character's movement, but its continuous damage could be fatal. Even though the Battle Mage avoided the trap, he was still set ablaze after taking the initial damage and his hit points continued to drop.

The damage was far from being fatal though. The Battle Mage immediately became more cautious after setting off the trap. He did a 360 degree sweep of his surroundings, surprising Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean, who hastily ducked under cover.

When they finally popped their heads back up again, the Battle Mage had retreated to the safety of a tree. He had his back to the tree to prevent himself from being flanked. A Ninja suddenly appeared on top of the tree and slowly slid downwards with a Body Disappearing Technique. Just as he was about to reach his target, he abruptly dropped. By the time the Battle Mage noticed the descending Ninja, it was too late. The Ninja knocked him off balance with a Body Bind Technique. At the same time, an Assassin charged out from another direction. Judging from his movement, that was filled with killing intent, Octagon Aniseed immediately recognised the most fearsome technique used by the Assassin class: Life-Risking Strike!

Assassins didn't have much health to begin with. Life-Risking Strike sacrificed the health of its user to deal damage to the enemy. It wasn't capable of one-shotting most classes, but the mage class were worse off than Assassins. Although Battle Mages were famous for their close-combat abilities, they were still fundamentally mages, who were well-known for being squishy targets. The Life-Risking Strike from the Assassin didn't blow the Battle Mage away, but the blood that came pouring out of his back showed the extent of the damage dealt by the strike.

The Battle Mage was still alive after the attack. He managed to turn around, but just as he was about to take a look at the Ninja's name, a gunshot could be heard around the area and a bullet shot through the Battle Mage's right shoulder. The Battle Mage spun around and the visual angle that he was about to gain was lost. The Ninja wasted no time to sneak behind the Battle Mage and threw a flurry of Ninjutsu and blade techniques at his opponent. As for the Assassin, he was under a long period of exhaustion after carrying out the Life-Risking Strike. Strong moves carried great risk.

"Incredible marksmanship!"

Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean knew what was what. Although the Assassin and the Ninja were the main damage dealers, the mysterious gunshot was the one that truly showed skill. The timing and the location of the shot was precisely calculated, but it was still wasted effort. Even though the Assassin and the Ninja weren't seen by the Battle Mage, they had been seen by the duo.

"Someone had the same idea as us." Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean murmured to each other. They sent a message to their guild leader, asking for an investigation on the two characters.

"Should we go after them?" Sword Bean asked Octagon Aniseed after sending the message.

"No, that shooter is still around…" Octagon Aniseed looked, but he couldn't spot anything unusual. They could guess the direction of the gunfire by listening to the gunshot, but they weren't sure if the shooter was still lurking about as they couldn't detect any movements.

"Those two, I don't recognize any of them!" Sword Bean said. Elites of a guild were more or less known. Even if they didn't know them personally, they would still recognize their game tags.

"Neither do I." Octagon Aniseed shook his head.

"Could they be open accounts?" Sword Bean asked.

"Whose open account could they belong to for them to have arrived so fast?" Octagon Aniseed countered.

Sword Bean gave it a thought and agreed with him. They became more cautious after witnessing others having the same intent as them. At the same time, they felt lucky that they didn't make their move on the Battle Mage. That would have exposed them. They were the victors of this incident: a competitor had been taken care of, while they were able to remain in the shadows.

And the other three? They had exposed themselves at the cost of taking out a competitor.

Misty Castle was the first to know when one of their own was killed. The guild leader didn't betray any reaction after learning of the news. He knew that the group that went out to track down the Boss was up to something.

If they could silently eliminate all their competitors, the boss just might fall into their hands.

Misty Lock adjusted his view, sweeping across the players of each guild, and spotted a player sneaking off from the crowd.

"What are you doing!"

What Misty Lock didn't expect was that several guild leaders shouted the same thing at the same time and they were looking in the same direction.

"Huh? What? Me?" The player took awhile to recover from the shock of being shouted at by so many guild leaders, "I'm not trying to do anything!"

"You want to leave?"

"No…."

"From now on, nobody leaves!" One of the guild leaders shouted. From Misty Lock's point of view, these guild leaders must have received intelligence that one of his members were killed. Wasn't it a little too obvious? Despite thinking about it, he was still unsettled. One of his players had died and with so many pairs of eyes watching, he couldn't send any reinforcements out either. He could only depend on the men that he had sent out earlier on, but with one man down, how could he not be anxious?

"Hmm, not bad. I've received some new info, the results were good."

On the other side of the map, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim received news from Wei Chen after assassinating the player from Misty Castle.

"With them restricting each other, our job will be simple." Ye Xiu replied.

"Then move faster." Wei Chen replied.

"You can't hold on any longer?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Shut your f*cking mouth. It's a lv65 field boss, why don't you take it out for a walk!" Wei Chen cursed.

"Seeing that you have the leisure to reply, you seem to have free time on your hands!" Ye Xiu said.

"....." Wei Chen immediately made it known that he was very busy.

"That was a nice kill!" Another discussion ensued in Lord Grim's team.

"Haha, everybody listen to my instructions. Let's continue!" Ye Xiu said in the chat.

"Yes yes." Wei Chen's bros replied in a straightforward manner. They didn't hold a grudge towards Ye Xiu despite their previous conflict. When they learned that Ye Xiu was friends with Wei Chen, they saw him as a friend too. And since they were friends, they had no problems following Ye Xiu's commands. No Glory player would have the confidence to claim that their tactics were better than God Ye Qiu.

"We've taken out one from Misty Castle. Herb Garden is next. Those two move together and they seemed to be quite happy peeking at us just now. Good things should go in pairs. Let's kill the both of them!" Ye Xiu exclaimed.

"Roger that!" The gang shouted.

"This time, the ones from Tyrannical Ambition will do the job." Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 538 – Who Killed Me?

Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean felt ill-at-ease. Although they could still console themselves with the fact that they were the victors, they were still shaken by their opponent’s remarkable shot.

If we have to go up against someone like that, will we be okay?

They didn’t say it out loud, but they gave the question a long thought. At the same time, they searched out all the Gunner experts from the other guilds. With such skill, the person couldn’t be some normal member of a guild unless he was just lucky. He or she had to be a famous core member of a guild.

“Who could it be?” Both of them made wild guesses, but information quickly arrived from their Guild Leader Arisaema.

“We’ve found out the identity of those two. They’re from Blossom Valley!” Arisaema said.

“Blossom Valley...…” With a narrower range, Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean began to ponder over who the Gunner expert in Blossom Valley might be. However, they could name numerous possibilities. There could be many who unknown experts. It wasn’t rare for Blossom Valley to have a lot of Gunners. The famous character Dazzling Hundred Blossom itself was a Spitfire in their pro team, so there would naturally be a lot of Spitfires in the guild. Even though they relied heavily on the special effects of their ammunition, marksmanship was also a fundamental that every player needed to learn.

Herb Garden learned of the identity of the two assailants at the same time as the other guilds. At that moment, only Blossom Valley’s grasp of the situation was different from the others.

“These two don’t exist.”

This was the message obtained from Blossom Valley’s spies in each of the guilds.

“They’ve even dispatched open accounts?” Not knowing that these two characters were from his own guild, Blossom Valley’s guild leader Blooming Blossom was astonished. With tens of thousands of players in a guild, only a few of the experts were well-known. Wei Chen’s brothers tended to lurk in the guilds for their extra bonuses and stats. How would such characters be remembered? When the guilds began their investigation on the two mysterious characters, they started from the other guilds because there was no reason to suspect one of their own.

This resulted in a situation where Blossom Valley wasn’t aware of the situation, while still thinking that the other big guilds were using their open accounts.

Despite knowing the truth, the other guilds remained silent. Even those that didn’t began to do do so. If they used that as an accusation towards Blossom Valley, it would be meaningless.

The rivalry in Poison Fang Swamp continued. With the additional information, Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean’s speculations increased. They still had the boss in sight. After all, it was quite conspicuous! However, with players from the other guilds beginning to operate in a sneaky manner, they soon lost their target.

The sudden realization surprised them.

The situation didn’t look good. The enemies were lurking in the shadows. With this, they had to take on a more passive stance. Were they being targeted? Was there a trap lying in wait for them?

The two hesitated. They didn’t dare carry on their mission separately. They used each other as a source of strength. They crouched and crawled the entire way. They bent their bodies so far down that their heads could almost reach their own crotches.

With all of their attention focused on moving around, they neglected the terrain of the Poison Fang Swamp. During a short moment of absent-mindedness, Octagon Aniseed missed the timing of using his repellent, startling an entire swarm of venomous flies.

“What bad luck...…” The duo cursed under their breath. The flies weren’t organized, so they weren’t afraid, but the flies were still annoying.

The duo failed to notice two other players who had snuck up behind them while they were busy handling the flies. A Grappler skill, Flying Hand, landed on them without warning, pushing them onto the ground.

With their characters buried in the mud, the two could do nothing but watch as their health slowly disappeared. They couldn’t even find out what skills were used in the attack. As they struggled to regain their footing, their opponents were nowhere to be found even after they did a 360 degrees sweep on their surroundings.

Where could they hide in such a short time? Their view shifted to a pile of rotten wood. But even if the enemy players hid themselves, the venomous flies were still continuing their attack. If they chose to deal with those flies, their enemies would attack them from the rear, but they couldn’t ignore the flies either. Those bites could kill!

The two were in a dilemma. They decided to bear with the lesser of the two evils. Players were way more terrifying compared to flies, so they decided to storm the wooden pile after a brief discussion.

There was nothing behind the pile of rotten wood except for a ditch full of mud. With their approach, more venomous flies appeared from within the ditch.

With more venomous flies, they could no longer ignore their damage. Experiencing a sneak attack while fighting against mob was always something unavoidable in the game, but this was exactly what the duo was facing. Moreover, while trying to attack the enemy players, they only attracted more flies…..

They knew that with the huge venomous fly swarm attacking them, they would certainly die if the enemy players made a move. However, the enemy seemed intent on hiding their identities.

Was it necessary to play hide and seek in this situation though? Everybody else had the same plan anyways. There was no point in hiding. Weren’t the last ones standing the ones with the rights to get the boss?

Just when Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean were trying to figuring out their opponent’s intentions on staying hidden, their opponents answered their questions. They attacked without mercy as soon as the duo was swarmed by the venomous flies.

Because they weren’t afraid of being exposed, there was no need to be quick and decisive. Octagon Aniseed and Sword Bean knew that they would die. They did their best and tried to take out at least one of their opponents, but their opponents calmly took advantage of the venomous flies. The duo could do nothing but watch as their characters became two rotten corpses.

The swamp hunting game had begun. Ye Xiu and his gang weren’t the only ones looking for the chance to strike. Even the other guilds were starting to look for others to kill.

Meanwhile, the guilds stayed in a deadlock. All of them wanted to call for reinforcements, but none of them wished to see the opposing guilds getting reinforced as well. This resulted in a stalemate where they could only wait for the reports coming out from the swamp.

Dead.

Dead.

Another dead.

One by one, the players that were sent out to track down the Boss were killed. It was meaningless to even find out which guild did it because everybody was doing it. The more meaningful matter at hand was who would be the last one standing. Nobody knew how many players were sent out and nobody knew who killed the boss in the end. Since nobody knew, they could achieve their means through underhanded means and ignore the proof post.

Five out of eight guilds competed. Apart from these five, Samsara and Excellent Dynasty were still at war and Blue Brook Guild never sent anyone after the Boss. True to Changing Spring’s words, Blue Brook Guild didn’t send any players out. They only watched as the situation unfolded. Each guild had the urge to make the first move, but they kept silent because their actions were being watched closely by the other guilds.

The guilds hadn’t sent many players out, three or five at most. With news of loss after loss coming in, Herb Garden was the first one to lose all four of the players that they had sent into the swamp.

Arisaema was sad! Four of his men had died and not a single enemy had been killed.

His moment of depression didn’t last long though. Arisaema found the perfect opportunity. All of them were moving in the dark and nobody dared to bring it to light. But with Herb Garden players killed, while not killing anyone else, weren’t they the victim? Arisaema could seize the opportunity and make an issue out of it!

Arisaema wasted no time to suddenly jump out and shouted with a face full of anger, “F*ck, which of your despicable b*stards killed all the men that I’ve sent out? What’s the meaning of this? Are you guys secretly preparing to kill the Boss? Was our previous agreement just a joke?”

To be a leader of a guild, one had to have very high levels of the skills “thick-faced” and “deceitful” on one’s skill tree, but Arisaema’s words still shocked the other guild leaders.

There had to be limit to the amount of skill points invested into the skills “thick-faced” and “deceitful”, right? The level of Arisaema’s skill was so high that he must be hacking!

Despite Arisaema’s sudden outburst, the other guild leaders had to maintain their mask of deception. Such matters could be done secretly, but things would get out of hand if light were to be shed upon it because not everybody’s hands were dirty. Excellent Dynasty, Samsara, and Blue Brook Guild didn’t participate in the foul play. If their betrayal came out, the proof post would be seen as a joke. Everyone would look bad. How could they let that happen?

The other guild leaders could only maintain a calm demeanor. “What do you mean? Aren’t we all trying to help track down the boss so that it wouldn’t be stolen?”

“Then how did my men die? Are you telling me that they accidentally fell in a ditch somewhere and died? Can Tyrannical Ambition, Blossom Valley, Misty Castle give me an explanation?” Arisaema refuted. After a thorough investigation, he concluded that players from these three guilds had killed his subordinates.

The leaders of Blossom Valley and Misty Castle remained silent, while Jiang You of Tyrannical Ambition replied, “An explanation? I think you’re the one that owes me and explanation!”

“F*cking explain what?” Arisaema shouted.

“‘Backwards Strike’ and ‘Tiger Sigil’? Which guild killed these two pieces of trash?” said Jiang You, while shifting his sight towards the leaders of Blossom Valley and Misty Castle.

The leaders of the other two guilds, Blooming Blossom and Misty Lock were stunned. They had each taken out a Herb Garden player, but their names were Perfect Milky Way and Hugging Is Healthier.

“Who are those two pieces of trash? What do they have to do with me?” Arisaema was puzzled by Jiang You’s words.

“What do you mean ‘what do they have to do with me’? Are you f*cking blind?” It was Jiang You’s turn to be stunned. He was expecting Arisaema to kick the two players out from the his guild, but according to the spies in Herb Garden, the players were still members of the guild and were still online. Was Arisaema’s “thick-faced” really buffed by a cheat engine?

“What?” Arisaema finally realised that something was wrong. He was able to find the two names after a brief search. They definitely weren’t part of the men sent out by him.

“Ha ha ha ha…. What are you all chatting about?” Changing Spring of Blue Brook Guild suddenly spoke up.

Chapter 539 – Conclusion to the Hunt

Changing Spring laughed coldly. Herb Garden and Tyrannical Ambition had also realized something wasn’t right. The others soon noticed too: not good, not good at all.

“Everyone, haven’t we forgotten something?” Changing Spring asked.

The other guild leaders started to sweat. They obviously forgot something.

The guild leaders immediately exchanged information and regretted not doing this earlier.

There were a surprising number of guild members who hadn’t been dispatched to participate in this hunting game. It was also very clear why these people would be the winners: they had more people.

“Who are these people?” After the guild leaders carefully added them up, they discovered that these people just happened to belong to their five guilds. In addition, they had clearly planned this in advance. They acted in concert with the internal strife between the guilds and killed off all of the deployed hunters in the swamp.

“Hurry up and send back-up. Who still has people left?” Arisaema quickly shouted. All of his hunters had been killed, so he had no information on the situation.

“We still have people.” Jiang You replied. He was just about to send the list of names to his players and tell them to be careful, when the last survivor of his Tyrannical Ambition messaged him in sorrow: dead.

Soon afterwards, the remnants of Misty Castle, Void Walk, and Blossom Valley couldn’t hang on any longer and soon sent reports of their deaths. The hunters dispatched by the five guilds all died. This meant they had lost all hope in finding the Swamp Hunter’s whereabouts. The other side clearly wasn’t going to have the boss stay in one place for them to find it.

“You two are still fighting? The boss has been stolen away!” The guild leaders were depressed. Seeing that Samsara and Excellent Dynasty were still fighting, they didn’t want those two to feel better about themselves. The boss should have belonged to these two. Now that the boss had been stolen, those two guilds should feel extremely bitter, right?

“We’re not fighting for the boss. We fight for justice.” A very normal member of Samsara replied in a cold voice and continued to fight like mad.

“F*ck, Samsara’s crazy! We won’t accompany you!” Excellent Dynasty had originally been incited by Samsara. After hearing Samsara speak, their rationale returned. This fight was pointless. As a result, the guild players began picking up any equipment dropped on the ground and went into a retreating formation.

Samsara had fought a huge battle with Blue Brook Guild and Excellent Dynasty, and naturally suffered heavy losses. If they actually continued to fight, Excellent Dynasty would probably win. However, they didn’t want to continue with such a pointless battle, so they prepared to retreat.

The other guilds hoped the conflict would grow larger. It would be great if Samsara and Excellent Dynasty went to war and splattered the entire Heavenly Domain with dropped equipment. According to convention, such a thing was unlikely to happen, but today Samsara seemed to have gone crazy. Who knew what stupid thing they might do next?

Excellent Dynasty originally had the advantage, but decided to retreat after thinking rationally about it. If Samsara still refused to rest, what would the resulting scene be like?

Full of expectation, the guild leaders almost forgot about the bitterness of losing the boss. If these two Club guilds actually went to war with each other, then losing the boss would have been worth it.

Today clearly wasn’t their lucky day. Right when they hoped Samsara wouldn’t be reasonable, Samsara suddenly became reasonable again. Seeing Excellent Dynasty’s retreat, they didn’t pursue them and continued to put on an appearance. Excellent Dynasty understood tacitly and didn’t bicker. They just picked up their own dropped equipment. Many of Samsara’s equipment also dropped, but Excellent Dynasty didn’t find it appropriate to pick those up.

“Everyone, Excellent Dynasty will take its leave first today. However, I’m going to need an explanation for today’s events.” Excellent Dynasty finished picking up their items. Chen Yehui gave a cold statement and then left along with his guild members.

“Explanation? What the f*ck is there to explain?” The guild leaders felt wronged. They had originally planned on sending players to pursue the boss again, but they didn’t feel like doing it anymore. With that proof post, someone might use the opportunity to cause trouble. As the losers, it would be best not to touch the boss.

“Tch, isn’t it just a Swamp Hunter Leipu? What’s so special about it? We lost. Whoever got the boss can kill it!” Herb Garden’s Arisaema spoke and then left with his players.

The other guilds were in the same situation. They said a few words out of formality and gave up on Swamp Hunter Leipu.

In the end, only Blue Brook Guild and Samsara remained. Changing Springs and Three Worlds stood at the head of their respective teams, facing each other, neither side speaking.

After a period of silence, Changing Spring spoke: “Three Worlds, you must have had a plan when you decided to do your actions today, no?”

“Oh?” Three Worlds answered calmly, completely different from his previous hot-blooded appearance from before.

Deep in Poison Fang Swamps, Wei Chen’s Windward Formation led his team in killing Swamp Hunter Leipu. This wild boss wasn’t easy to beat. Most guilds needed an entire group to kill one. However, even though Wei Chan had retired many years ago, he hadn’t left Glory. He wasn’t like one of those old antiques who couldn't keep up with the times. With his skill level, killing off the Swamp Hunter Leipu with his team could be done. If not, he wouldn’t have arranged this operation with Ye Xiu.

“Pushing Sea, go right. You’re f*cking blocking the mage’s view!”

“Big Head, are you a cheerleader? Go up and attack! If you can’t, just tank it.”

“Shield Attack! Use a Shield Attack! Are you a turtle who only knows how to hide behind his shell?”

Wei Chen’s leading was quite ruthless. Even though his bros played with him a lot, it was their first time against such a boss.

Luckily, Wei Chen was there to control the field. Warlocks were proficient in control skills too. Level 70 was also higher leveled than the wild boss. He might not be able to completely suppress it through his level advantage, but his skills worked effectively, which was exactly what a control mage needed.

In addition, they were all playing in an Internet Cafe, so they could look at each other’s screens. Wei Chen’s shotcalling was like a fish back in water. Slowly, the situation stabilized.

“Go go go! Good, attack while pulling him this way. We can’t keep staying in the same spot. Formation! Stay in formation. Watch the f*cking distance between yourselves. Maintain your position!” Wei Chen never stopped talking. He didn’t dare be negligent. They could kill the boss, but it wasn’t going to be easy.

Suddenly, he saw a few shadows slowly creeping up on them from the corner of his eyes. Wei Chen suddenly became nervous. If they encountered any strangers, let alone experts, even a few noobs could ruin everything.

But when he saw the players, Wei Chen relaxed: “F*ck, you scared this senior to death. You could have at least said something.”

It was Lord Grim and his team.

When Wei Chen saw them, he happily spoke: “Everything’s been resolved?”

“Yeah, I left five people behind to follow behind us from a distance away. If someone pursues us, we’ll notice them. Let’s hurry!”

“Okay, everyone, hurry!” Wei Chen roared.

Ye Xiu’s team joined the battle. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was a pitiful Level 54. Against a Level 65 wild boss, his attacks were worthless, so he didn’t really go up and attack. He just showed up and then disappeared into the background. In any case, with Wei Chen there, he didn’t need to do any leading, so he went to do other work.

With more helpers, the situation stabilized even more. Thinking of materials he would get after killing the boss, Wei Chen became extremely excited.

70%.

60%.

50%.

Swamp Hunter Leipu’s health continued to decrease. No one came to bother them either. Everything seemed to be going smoothly. At this moment, he suddenly received a message.

With the situation stabilized, Wei Chen had some time to reply. He opened it and saw it was from Lord Grim: “Have you killed the boss yet?”

“We’re halfway done. What’s wrong?” Wei Chen immediately became nervous.

“Lower your damage output.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“It’s good for us?” Ye Xiu replied.

“How is it good for us?” Wei Chen asked.

“I’m fighting for it!” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you talking about!” Wei Chen was extremely anxious.

“A guild has come looking for me, they’re willing to pay a high price for this boss.” Ye Xiu replied.

“What? That’s a thing?” Wei Chen was puzzled.

“He he, this boss isn’t as simple as just materials and equipment. This is a rare opportunity. If we get this type of opportunity again, we’ll benefit greatly.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Really? Then I should hurry and get a list out, so they can give me all of the items I need.” Wei Chen replied.

Ye Xiu naturally didn’t pay attention to this message. He turned his camera around to look at two people.

Changing Springs and Three Worlds Six Paths.

“You two should hurry. The boss is about to become enraged. If it becomes enraged, it’ll be difficult for us to hold back. So what do you think of the list of materials I sent you?” Ye Xiu laughed heartily.

Chapter 540 – Extortion

Seeing Lord Grim’s list of materials, Changing Spring realized how Blue River’s helplessness towards Lord Grim in the tenth server was formed.

A god was truly a god. He quickly figured out their weakness. The list of materials that he had received wasn’t impossible to accept, but it wasn’t easy to accept either.

Changing Spring let out a sigh and turned to look at Three Worlds: “Samsara guild leader, your thoughts?”

‘No problem.” Three Worlds replied bluntly.

Changing Spring could only sigh in his heart. Of course Three Worlds would be blunt because for Samsara, they would certainly profit, but for Blue Brook Guild? It was the same as if someone punctured your tire, but there was only one person in the area who could repair it. Don’t repair it? If you don’t repair it, then you can only abandon your car. What else could you do? The only option was to get ripped off.

“If Samsara has no problems with it, then we’re the same!” Changing Spring wasn’t happy, but his tone of voice appeared calm. He turned to look at Lord Grim: “We’ll send the items immediately. What about your side?”

“No problem. We can wait.” Ye Xiu smiled.

Didn’t he just say it would be very difficult to hold back? Now he’s saying we can wait. Changing Spring and Three Worlds rolled their eyes. What else could they do? They could only wait as well!

Ye Xiu wasn’t going to release the hawk until he saw the hare. He needed to receive his payment first before giving them the goods. It wasn’t the same as before. These guilds could easily cheat him. He didn’t have the slightest doubt that, with the guilds’ enmity towards him, they would view him in a different light and wouldn’t treat him in an honest manner.

“Old Wei, persevere!” Ye Xiu encouraged Wei Chen.

“How’s it going on your side?” Wei Chen asked.

“I’ve helped you directly get Swamp Hunter Leipu’s Rotting Ash.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s it? If I kill the Swamp Hunter Liepu, Rotting Ash is practically guaranteed to drop! What else is there? If that’s it, then aren’t we losing too much?” Wei Chen said.

“Of course not. The rest is for me!” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, you’re not nice at all! I worked so hard and all I get is Rotting Ash? Hurry up and give me some more materials. If not, I’ll immediately kill the boss for you to see.” Wei Chen shouted.

“Okay, I’ll try.” Ye Xiu said and then turned to look at the two guild leaders.

“The situation has changed a bit.” Ye Xiu said.

“What? Something’s happened to the boss?” The two were alarmed.

“It’s like this. I feel like the price I proposed to you two is very fair, but you see, my partner is a very bad person. He’s a dishonest fellow. Seeing that you two are in a hurry, he is heartlessly taking advantage of this. Even I feel awfully ashamed to say this, but there’s nothing I can do, the boss is in his hands after all! I can only send his list of materials for you two to see.”

Ye Xiu sent them his list of materials. After hearing Ye Xiu’s first few sentences, they could tell he was just blathering. Their faces darkened. However, they didn’t act immediately. After taking a look at the list, the two were shocked.

“Are you joking!!” The two were relatively blunt guild leaders and directly expressed their thoughts.

“I agree.” Ye Xiu added.

This made the two of them were extremely angry because they didn’t want to face him right now. They wanted to face this dishonest person. As for whether or not this person actually existed, the two had no clue.

Right when they were about to speak, they heard Lord Grim say: “Hm, I’ve contacted the dishonest guy and told him your replies. The dishonest guy asks, aren’t you guys the ones joking?

“We made a deal.” Changing Spring said.

“I want you two to imagine that you have met a despicable and shameless disciple, take out your limit, and fill in his wickedness! If this isn’t enough to satisfy his disgraceful self, then it seems like today’s win-win cooperation will be destroyed in this dishonest guy’s hands.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay…..”

After a long period of silence during, which the two might have been discussing with each other, Changing Spring finally spoke up. While replying to the list of materials, he said: “This is our limit. Please pass this onto your partner. His shamelessness is something we have never seen before.”

“I feel like it’d be best to complete our cooperation before I send this message on.” Ye Xiu said sincerely.

“......” The two had no words to say. The two had privately cursed at Ye Xiu hundreds of times already. They felt like he was playing two roles and cheating them, but from the looks of it, maybe the dishonest guy actually existed?

Lord Grim alone was already enough for them in the Heavenly Domain. Now another evil villain had arrived?! How grim did their future look?

The two guild leaders deeply felt a type of foreboding in the future. Lord Grim replied at this moment: “Congratulations, you two. Through the efforts of both sides, we have finally reached an agreement.”

The two guild leaders cried. Through the efforts of both sides? You didn’t put in any f*cking effort! Or did you mean putting in effort to extort us?

Hearing this response, the two guild leaders didn’t even feel like saying false words out of formality like they usually did towards their competitors. They only spoke coldly: “If everything is set, then you can hand the boss over to us now right? At this point, you’re just wasting our time.”

“I’m very sorry. I trust in the honesty of your guilds, but the problem is…… think about it. For a despicable and dishonest person, if they don’t see the hare, do you think he’ll let the boss go?” Ye Xiu said.

“If this keeps dragging on and something happens, who’s going to take responsibility?” Three Worlds asked.

“If something happens, the losses will be shared between both sides. Speaking of this, our losses would be worse. We would lose all of the materials on that list, but you two? It’s just a Level 65 Swamp Hunter Leipu. You wouldn’t feel worse than us right?” Ye Xiu said.

The two guild leaders wanted to die. For this guy to actually say something like this, a God truly was far above them! According to you, why should we trade all of those materials for a stupid boss? You’re clearly speaking nonsense!

Despite coughing blood, the two didn’t leave. They could only wait, but what were they waiting for? Were they waiting for their people to hurry up and send the materials? It seems like the delay was because of them. Changing Spring understood now. He completely understood why Blue River would have a no resistance policy towards Lord Grim.

Ye Qiu!

God Ye Qiu!

If you only thought of him as a knowledgeable Glory player with incredible skill, then you were wrong, very wrong.

Changing Spring only hoped that the items would hurry up and arrive on time so that he could resolve this problem. He didn’t want to interact with this guy any longer. It would be best if they never had to interact with each other ever again.

But was that possible?

Last time, it was a struggle in Wilderness Town. This time it was a robbery in Poison Fang Swamp. This guy clearly wanted to quarrel with their Club guilds. Hide? How could he hide? Even if he wanted to hide, Ye Qiu was planning on creating his own team. Changing Spring might want to hide, but he couldn’t say it out loud!

Out loud, his words would appear relaxed: that guy Ye Xiu is very arrogant! Let’s go and crush him.

Ugh! Changing Spring thought of this scenario and felt nauseous. He wanted to vomit…...

“Guild leader, the items are here.”

Finally, Changing Spring heard a voice. He turned around and saw a member of his guild carrying the items. Samsara’s delivery person wasn’t any slower. He was about 20 units away from Blue Brook Guild’s runner.

“I have the items.” Changing Spring took the materials and said to Lord Grim.

“Okay.” Lord Grim replied and sent a trade request.

Changing Spring held back his anger and declined the request: “Isn’t it about time you brought us to the boss?”

“Sure. Once I get the items, we’ll go.”

“We’ll pay you, when we see it.”

“That’s not good. It’s too easy for you to cheat me.” Ye Xiu said.

‘Then how can we trust that once you get the materials, you won’t just run?” Changing Spring asked.

“Ask Blue River. When have I ever went back on my word?” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River was the intermediary Changing Spring went to when he wanted to contact Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Ye Xiu had set it so Lord Grim couldn’t receive friend requests, so Changing Spring and Three Worlds had no way of contacting him. However, Changing Spring had an urgent matter at hand and needed to contact Lord Grim, so he found the quickest way to reach Blue River and asked him if he had any solutions.

Blue River actually had a solution. He had interacted with Ye Xiu many times. In fact, he helped manage Guild Happy, so he knew how to reach Ye Xiu.

Blue River contacted Soft Mist, Steamed Bun INvasion, and Chen Guo’s side account. From them, Ye Xiu received messages through Chen Guo’s phone and added Changing Spring and Three Worlds as friends. Once they met each other, Changing Spring and Three Worlds wanted to hide their intentions, but who was Ye Xiu? Without needing too much information, just from seeing their arrival, he linked together their circumstances and quickly figured out their true intentions. Then, he used his extortion technique and the two guild leaders immediately realized they had been seen through. Thus, the transaction took place. They had no way of setting any conditions and could only suffer. They couldn’t even ask to see the goods first.

“We'll trade!” The two discussed with each other and then made the decision.

Chapter 541 – Guarded Secret

“Okay. Please follow me then. Let’s hurry up so you two don’t have to worry anymore.” Ye Xiu added after Lord Grim finished up the deal with the two guild masters. In the meantime, he was already slipping into the depths of the swamp. Taking Ye Xiu’s words seriously, Changing Spring and Three Worlds Six Paths followed him without a moment’s delay, leading their groups away.

They soon arrived at the scene. Wei Chen’s Windward Formation was leading ten to twenty players, who were tangled in a fierce fight. Changing Spring and Three Worlds Six Paths were all veterans at boss fights. With a few glances, they knew right away that Wei Chen’s group was mainly trying to control the boss instead of rushing to kill it. Their worrying hearts finally settled down. Clearly, the other party had been dragging out the fight until the deal could be sealed.

Having roamed Heavenly Domain for so long, Wei Chen knew the big shots from the big guilds better than Ye Xiu did. He saw Changing Spring and Three Worlds Six Paths’ names awhile ago. With a skillful dash, Windward Formation moved through the battlefield and greeted the newcomers enthusiastically, “Guild leader, do you want to take over the aggro? Or do you prefer to have us join your party? Relax, additional service won’t cost you any extra.”

“That won’t be needed.” Changing Spring replied coldly. Taking it as a signal, people from Blue Brook and Samara charged at the boss.

“You two guilds are trying to split one boss? This is going to be intense.” Wei Chen muttered his comment while stopping his people from attacking the boss. The transition that followed went smoothly since everyone was familiar with the process.

At the same time, Changing Spring was starting to believe that the extremely shameless person mentioned by Ye Xiu might actually exist.

Why? Because the person known as Windward Formation was roaming and laughing directly in front of him without feeling any discomfort whatsoever, even though the guild tag of Blue Brook Guild hovered above his character’s head.

Even if he were a spy, he should still feel somewhat uncomfortable right now. Even if this was only in game, as a spy, one should still have trouble calling themselves the police righteously. The guilt of betraying those around them would weigh heavily upon their hearts no matter what, so all the spies had excellent mental strength. The guy in front of him was undoubtedly the best candidate for a spy there was. He was perfectly at ease even when he was directly exposed in front of his own guild leader.

Although the transition finished quickly, when Wei Chen and his people backed down, they still looked very anxious, as if the players from Blue Brook and Samsara would turn and kill them right away to vent their anger.

To Changing Spring, the sight was funny and annoying. For competitions in an online game, killing and fighting was a rather ineffective method. If a battle could actually resolve all the future threat the group in front of him posed, Changing Spring would start a world war without any hesitation. Regrettably, even if he were to beat them here, what could he possibly achieve? If it was a war fought between the big guilds, then victory would win glory for his own guild. On the other hand, killing this group of nobodies would only tarnish his guild’s name.

Being one of the top elites in the game for so long, Changing Spring had long since passed the stage where he still needed to PK to vent his anger, yet people were still weary of him for these kinds of trivial matters. It only made Changing Spring feel that this group’s character was particularly low.

“Hm? What? Aren’t you people going to try to fight us?” Wei Chen exclaimed in surprise when he realized that neither Blue Brook nor Samsara planned on doing anything to him or his group. They had left the battle zone perfectly unscathed.

“Is there such a need?” Changing Spring retorted flatly.

“This is an online game. Scores ought to be settled quickly and directly. Even after such a great loss, instead of fighting it out, you people are still scheming around. What a killjoy! The way you people play is so boring.” Wei Chen lamented.

Wei Chen’s words made Changing Spring fall into a long silence. At last, Changing Spring admitted, “What you say is not entirely false, but we were never here to play in the first place.”

“Haha, apparently you’re quite smart. No wonder you’re the guild leader of Blue Brook.” Wei Chen praised.

“Ha ha, I’ll remember you.” Changing Spring didn’t join the battle himself. His view was pointed at the other party the whole time.

“That’s a must. If possible, I hope you won’t kick me out of your guild though.” Wei Chen replied.

“Why?” Changing Spring asked.

“Because Blue Brook’s benefits are really good and its fame is also quite useful.” Wei Chen answered.

Changing Spring was speechless. He was fully expecting some spectacular reasoning, but all he got was this kind of honesty instead. Thus, when he was moving his view, he kicked those in Blue Brook all out decisively.

“F**k! Shameless! With such a big guild, do you honestly need to empty up a few slots that badly?!” Wei Chen swore as he drifted away with the group. Finally, they all disappeared into the swamp.

“Let me see what goodies you’ve got!” Shortly after they left, Wei Chen was asking Ye Xiu impatiently, drooling in anticipation.

“Here.” Ye Xiu sent an exchange request over and gave Wei Chen the materials he got from the two guild leaders.

“This is it? Why didn’t you use the list I sent you.” Wei Chen was unexpectedly disgruntled with the results, but these were all that the guild leaders could manage with great difficulty.

“Get some standards, why don’t you? Is it even possible for them to accept your list?” Ye Xiu scolded.

“Under that kind of conditions, it was worth a try.” Wei Chen refuted.

“And this is the result of your attempt.” Ye Xiu replied.

“It’s so-so, but it’s still better than what you would have gotten before. Weakling.” Wei Chen argued.

“That’s because I’m not as shameless as you are.” Ye Xiu retorted.

“This is completely shameless? If I had more people, I would have planned an ambush on the way here and kill their delivery person. That would have been spectacular! Could they count that loss on me?” Wei Chen proposed.

“No human can stop you now…” Ye Xiu took a deep breath and lamented.

“Enough already. Give Death Hand back to me. I’m going to upgrade it.” Wei Chen changed the subject.

“Are you sure you won’t destroy it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“F*ck off! Stop cursing me!” Wei Chen yelled back.

“You’re not confident.” Ye Xiu concluded.

“Based on my years of research, I think it should be fine.” Wei Chen answered.

“Clearly, you’ve never tried.” Ye Xiu pointed out.

“But I have experience.” Wei Chen insisted.

“The experience of an antique?”

“F*ck off! I’m not going to argue with you. Hurry up and give Death Hand back to me. Let me upgrade the weapon first. We have to work for the material needed for the next upgrade anyways. I don’t know if we’ll be lucky enough to find another boss.” Wei Chen sighed.

“That’s going to be hard. With all the hidden rules in the game, we’re no better than the big shots from the big guilds. Truthfully speaking, they didn’t pay much attention to us before. They thought that the Heavenly Domain wasn’t like the normal servers. They believe that they have more power here, and we are just a tiny group with no real power, but after this, they will probably start to see us as a threat towards their bosses. If they actually spend some effort on making things difficult for us, we might actually suffer a lot from it.” Ye Xiu explained.

“True! After all, Bosses are different. Just killing one takes a lot of time. Hijacking a boss is more troublesome than hijacking a guild leader.” Wei Chen agreed.

“Actually, killing guild leaders would be nice too, but the problem is that guild leaders only drop equipment, not materials.” Ye Xiu lamented.

“Ai, if only we know who got the material every time they killed a boss, then that would be great! We wouldn’t have to kill the bosses anymore. We just need to kill that player.” Wei Chen added.

“That would still be difficult. Killing the person won’t give you the right thing every time.” Ye Xiu commented.

“If killing them doesn’t drop it, then we’ll just keep on killing.” Wei Chen answered.

“Should we try it next time?” Ye Xiu offered.

“But we need to find out who picked up the material. That’s too hard…” Wei Chen sighed.

“We just need a spy among the higher-ups.” Ye Xiu spoke.

The two turned around and looked at the same time then. Wei Chen’s friends stood behind his Windward Formation. By now, almost all of their guild titles had disappeared. It was not because they were hiding them, but because they got kicked out. There were a few exceptions though: they were in Excellent Dynasty or Samsara. None of Wei Chen’s players from these two guilds had joined the fight, so the spies in these two guilds weren’t exposed.

“We’re probably on their blacklist now. This is problematic.” Wei Chen frowned.

“It shouldn’t be too much of a problem. You can just switch accounts. I checked. Luckily, in your group, everyone has a different class, right? Well, it just happens so that I have a bunch of level 70 empty accounts. I can give those accounts to your people. You can then transfer over your equipment, then that should settle it.” Ye Xiu offered.

“F*ck! Do you know that our accounts all have really high amounts of skill points?” Wei Chen complained.

“Really? How high?”

“About 4700.” Wei Chen answered.

“Why is it so high?” Ye Xiu exclaimed. With the regular leveling and main quests, a character would always end up with exactly 4000 skill points. The additional skill points were gained under random conditions from skill books, hidden quests, and event rewards.

Glory had a long history. Ye Xiu wouldn't be surprised to see some regular characters in the game actually had an amount of skill points comparable to the godly characters. After all, this kind of thing depended solely on luck. However, those around Wei Chen all had around 4700 skill points. Now that was shocking.

This was all the result of good luck? Such good fortune for all 20 or so?

Clearly, this was no longer the result of luck. There must have been some skill involved in it.

“Hehe, this is my guarded secret.” Wei Chen boasted.

“Nonsense! More than 20 people already know this. How can you call that a guarded secret?” Ye Xiu snapped. Speaking about it, skill points had been a headache for Ye Xiu. This was something that could only rely on luck. No one could guarantee how a character would end up. The only solution to this problem was money. On top of that, money couldn’t actually buy skill points. It could only be used to buy the accounts with really high skill points.

Some would say, “All problems that could be solved with money are not problems.” Clearly, those who say that are all rich people. For those who use money to build teams, this is truly not too big of an issue. Even though there are very few accounts with such high skill points, Glory had been established for a long time and it had a large population of players, there are still a decent number of accounts with high skill points.

Still, to Ye Xiu, who was starting over with nothing in hand, this was a very grave issue. The price for accounts with high skill points could be as high as the price of a silver class weapons. Let alone a full team of them, Ye Xiu couldn’t afford a single one. Who would have thought that Wei Chen, who was right in front of him, would have a way to stack skill points? This would not only solve an urgent problem for Ye Xiu, but it would also bring a large amount of fortune to him.

In that moment, Ye Xiu only had one wish: let’s hope this shameless guy isn’t bragging, or that the guarded secret is as worthless as “I bought them.”

Chapter 542 – Follow Up

"Ha ha ha, you want to know? Let this senior think of something for you to do and then I'll consider telling you." Wei Chen raised his eyebrows.

"Old thing, who has your Death Hand?" Ye Xiu laughed grimly.

"F*ck!!" Wei Chen realized that he had been too pleased with himself and had forgotten something so important.

"You win..." Wei Chen clearly valued his Silver weapon. His years of hard work couldn't be faked.

"Hurry up and tell me."

"You should know. In Glory, when certain conditions are met, some items can be dropped 100% of the time." Wei Chen said.

As an experienced expert, Ye Xiu understood what Wei Chen meant: "You're saying kill books can also be dropped in a similar way?"

"Yes, but it's still not guaranteed. At best, it can increase the drop chance." Wei Chen answered.

"Big brother, isn't that just a myth?" Ye Xiu felt a bit confused. Time range, fixed input sequence, fixed kill order, etc. These weren't proven facts in Glory, but rather beliefs of some players. These illogical methods were hard to believe.

On the other hand, setting up certain conditions to hit out equipment had a 100% chance and could be proven through testing. All of these methods made sense too. For example, when Ye Xiu first started playing the game from scratch, the method to guarantee the hidden boss' ornamental sword in the beginner village was to repeatedly hit the sword's belt. This could be explained through logic: if the sword belt broke, the sword would drop.

A lot of these types of methods existed in Glory. However, Wei Chen's method only increased the drop chance. In an instant, his method felt somewhat implausible. How could you know whether the drop chance actually increased or not?

A 5% drop rate didn't mean that you would be guaranteed 5 drops out of 100 kills. Each drop was an independent event after all. Out of a thousand times, you might not get any drops in 950 kills, but you could get 50 drops in the last 50 kills and it would still be considered a 5% drop rate. As a result, for drop rates, apart from 100% or 0%, it was difficult to estimate an exact number. Wei Chen only mentioned increasing the drop chance. His method seemed more like a myth than a fact.

"Myth? Don't all of these characters with around 4700 skill points prove that it's not a myth?" Wei Chen refuted.

"Then tell me, how do you do it?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Okay, we have to start with the relationship between people and Glory."

"Death Hand." Ye Xiu spoke bluntly.

"D*MMIT!" Wei Chen grit his teeth.

"Hurry up and tell me." Ye Xiu held a stick and he didn't have the patience to wait.

"There's a lot of stuff. I'll just send you a doc!" Wei Chen didn't continue stalling. He knew that what he had was very important. If the two of them were going to create a team with the goal of becoming champions, then just having outstanding players wasn't enough. The characters had to be strong enough too.

"Okay, send it to me. I'll study it." Ye Xiu said.

"You don't trust this brother's research? You haven't touched the game very much in these past few years. Glory is an online game, after all. You can still learn a lot from the web. The training methods used by teams are becoming more and more mature, but they're also moving farther and farther away from the game. That's not good." Wei Chen spoke his thoughts.

"It sounds like you've discovered a lot in these past few years?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I have. Definitely things that you guys in the pro scene probably wouldn't know." Wei Chen said confidently.

"So thank me! For giving you a chance to go back on stage." Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen went silent for a long time, but then said: "F*ck off. Hurry up and give me my Death Hand back."

"It's in the city storage. I'll go grab it." Ye Xiu said.

"Wait, something doesn't feel right up ahead." Just as they were about to leave Poison Fang Swamp, Windward Formation suddenly stopped to hear for any sounds of movement.

"Yeah, something feels off." Ye Xiu said. The two experienced players could tell the situation wasn't normal.

"It's probably those guilds from before. They probably left some people behind to see what we're up to." Wei Chen guessed.

"It looks like there are quite a lot of people." Ye Xiu looked around. These people hadn't exposed themselves yet, but they weren't making too much of an effort to stay hidden either. They had clearly completed an encirclement, ready to pounce at any time.

"It seems like breaking out will be a bit difficult." Wei Chen said.

"I agree."

"You go first." Wei Chen said.

"Of course." Ye Xiu logged off.

"F*ck! Can't you say something nice???" Wei Chen cursed in QQ.

"Tch. We still need to play tricks with each other? We all know it's true, so why waste time?" Ye Xiu asked.

"You f*cker. You said you'd give us accounts. Was that for real?" Wei Chen asked.

"Of course. You still have time to chat?" Ye Xiu asked back.

"The enemies aren't moving. I'm not moving. It's not like we need these accounts anymore. In a bit, this senior is going to fight with them and give them a taste of my amazingness." Wei Chen said.

"Seeing that I've logged off, that attack must have hurt them greatly." Ye Xiu said.

"Don't be so happy. They might wait there until you log back on." Wei Chen warned.

"I doubt they'll spend all day waiting for me with so many people. Come rescue me when there are less people." Ye Xiu said.

"Why should I rescue you?" Wei Chen said.

Ye Xiu replied with two words: Death Hand.

"God d*mmit! This time, when you get out, you're going to return my Death Hand immediately. If you don't return it, I won't agree to anything you say ever again. I can't wait another minute." Wei Chen cursed.

"Hurry up and go fight them!" Ye Xiu said.

"Wait for my message!" Wei Chen replied. In Poison Fang Swamp, the battle began.

With Windward Formation at the head, a bunch of half-naked characters charged in a direction. After being kicked out of the guild, they were left half-naked. Half of their equipment had been taken back by the guild storage.

Against these half-naked savages, the guilds calmly concentrated their firepower to kill them immediately.

Who would have thought that this charge would be a fake? The instant the encirclement attacked, the two teams suddenly changed directions and started attacking in a frenzy. At this moment, the encirclement had already let out their attacks and couldn't take them back.

Pu!

It was like a sword hitting a crucial point. However, the sword was too blunt and couldn't kill. It was still enough to injure though. On the other hand, these two teams attacked the encirclement and killed several people.

"Pick up their equipment!!!" Wei Chen shouted. There wasn't many equipment on the ground. With 20 half-naked people scrambling for them, it seemed very uncivilized.

Their scramble made the players making up the encirclement stare dumbly at them. They were all from big guilds and had discipline. It was hard for them to look at such shameless acts. During this period of disdain, all of the equipment laying on the ground had been swept clean. Wei Chen shouted again and the two teams separated with one on the left and the other on the right. Each team forced their way into one part of the encirclement.

This time, the guild players fought back. They wouldn't let these savages pick up their items so easily. Their counterattack killed off several of them.

This was a team battle. With a multitude of attacks coming at once, life and death was only a matter of seconds. Ye Xiu wouldn't be able to remain in this type of battle. A Level 54 character had limited strength.

The battle that took place in Poison Fang Swamp didn't last long. It ended within minutes. All twenty players died.

These players had been cursing the entire time and in a very ugly manner too. Their shouts often had to do with the reproductive system, but from their angry curses, they could also feel that they were happy and having fun.

The enemies had finally been killed, but the guild players didn't feel happy at all. The enemies that they had killed didn't bear any resentment towards their killers, only pure passion for fighting. Right before they died, they often said things like "You're washed clean now. Wait for big daddy to come for you!"

It made all of the guild players feel like they had been ridiculed. They looked at each other and couldn't find anything to be pleased about.

At this moment, a system announcement came: Samsara had killed Swamp Hunter Leipu.

What's this?

When the guild leaders saw this message, their minds suddenly went blank. Hadn't Swamp Hunter Leipu been snatched away by Lord Grim's gang? They even killed off a bunch of guys at Poison Fang Swamp's exit. Even though it was too bad that they weren't able to catch Lord Grim, it was still a small win in their eyes. However, how come Samsara killed Swamp Hunter Leipu?

They hadn't come to their senses yet, when a follow-up to the proof post in the Glory forums.

The follow-up spoke of two things.

One, ridiculing Blue Brook Guild had been a misunderstanding. In reality, this had all been done by the pest Lord Grim. After learning the truth, Blue Brook Guild helped Samsara take the boss and, in accordance to the proof post, the boss was given to Samsara.

Two, Samsara was the main topic. Even if they weren't going to fight for the boss, they had to fight for justice! Blue Brook Guild had proved everything was a misunderstanding, but in this type of situation, Samsara wouldn't cower. Excellent Dynasty wanted to enter by exploiting their weakness. Fine, Samsara would fight. Samsara wouldn't compromise for any reason. No matter the predicament, if they were going to kill, they would slaughter their way to the heavens. They would kill for justice!

These two had videos and images as proof. Samsara's players stood up straight with pride as they watched Excellent Dynasty's players stoop down to pick up equipment and leave. All of it had been recorded.

"Didn't you say you couldn't understand this time's deal? Do you understand now?" Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

Chapter 543 – Spies

Chen Guo looked a bit dumbstruck. She didn’t understand it too thoroughly, but after seeing the two follow-up posts, she got a clearer idea of the whole picture.

Blue Brook Guild’s action had been forced. With the proof post, even if the guilds knew that Blue Brook Guild hadn’t done it intentionally, without any concrete proof to back up their uninvolvement, they didn’t mind putting the blame on Blue Brook Guild. This type of attack was much more valuable than a PvP match in the game. Blue Brook Guild had a Club and a team behind them. Such an existence made up of three entities would be extremely difficult to harm through just PvP alone.

On the other hand, revealing a scandal could weaken the popularity of one of these three entities and could be considered quite a heavy blow to their reputation.

Blue Brook Guild clearly understood this point. As a result, they cleaned themselves of the matter, refusing to let the other guilds use this opportunity to attack them. Blue Brook Guild didn’t have much of a choice.

As for Samsara? Chen Guo saw the chain of shouting and cheering from Samsara fans underneath the post. There were quite a lot of other players praising the manliness of Samsara’s actions too. She quickly realized the significance of the actions that Samsara had taken.

When normal players played the game, they didn’t care about the businesses of these Club guilds. Today, Samsara had been cheated and used this to attract the sympathy of others. Afterwards, they used a battle to show their might. Other guilds might look at such actions with disgust, but it resonated well with the vast majority.

People played the game to have fun. If they were cheated, they didn’t want to go through some lengthy process in order to get revenge. They would rather take revenge immediately. Whether or not revenge was the answer was a completely different matter.

Samsara went with what the people liked. Not only did they rally their own supporters, many neutral players had a deeper impression of Samsara now, especially with Samsara taking the boss. This was a perfect example of a main character taking action to achieve his goals. In the eyes of the people, the only word that could describe this was cool!

However, after looking at it again, she suddenly felt a bit confused about one part: “If that’s the case, Blue Brook Guild needed Samsara as witnesses to clear their name, but Samsara didn’t need Blue Brook Guild to do anything for them? If Blue Brook Guild was still the betrayer, then even if Samsara won the boss in the end, Samsara would look more powerful, right?

“Not bad not bad. You must have improved a lot to think of this outcome!” Ye Xiu praised.

Chen Guo rolled her eyes. She clearly didn’t feel very accepting of his praise. Truthfully, she didn’t have much interest in how the guilds operated. She preferred watching sick plays, killing in a single combo, etc.

“Samsara obviously doesn’t want to be linked with Blue Brook Guild, but if their intents were seen through by Blue Brook Guild, then there’s nothing they can really do about it. Blue Brook Guild refuses to part with them, and they couldn’t take the boss, so to make a trade-off, they helped to clear Blue Brook Guild’s name!” Ye Xiu explained.

“You saw that the two parties urgently needed the boss, so you struck a deal with them?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu laughed bitterly: “I had no choice. In our current situation, trying to compete with these guilds fairly is like asking a tiger for its skin. I don’t have the time to slowly make business with them, which is why I have to resort to such shameless methods like this….”

“You don’t need to explain. I’m not looking down on you for doing it. Keep up the good work.” Chen Guo said.

“With such a shameless guy like Old Wei to help me, it’s like adding wings to a tiger.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“It’s not like you’re very merciful either.” Chen Guo said.

“Don’t say such nonsense, I’m nowhere near Old Wei’s level of shamelessness.” Ye Xiu spoke solemnly.

Chen Guo commented: “You’re really modest when it comes to stuff like this.”

On QQ, Wei Chen reported the death of his gang. All of these characters had to be abandoned, so he decided that they would look around and kill these guild players, so these abandoned accounts would gain some value.

“See, look how shameless he is!” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo, while asking Wei Chen how he should send over the open accounts.

“How are we going to develop after this?” Wei Chen was currently leading his team all over the place to attack the guild players. He was having quite a good time, playing while chatting with Ye Xiu on QQ.

“I have a big plan!” Ye Xiu said.

“What big plan?” Wei Chen said.

“I’ve decided to send you out as a spy.” Ye Xiu answered.

“I can’t though, no? If I were to become a spy, wouldn’t you be wasting my talents?” Wei Chen objected.

“No, for such an unscrupulous guy like yourself, using you as a spy puts your talents to full use.” Ye Xiu honestly replied.

“Wouldn’t you be a better fit then?” Wei Chen said.

“My schemes and foresight aren’t nearly as deep as yours.” Ye Xiu politely refuted.

“No no. I’m older than you in age, but in terms of knowledge in Glory, you will always be the superstar of experience and shamelessness. Even after you retired, you’ve deeply affected the later generation. You’re not like me who stayed silent for all these years. Even Blue Brook Guild’s dog of a leader didn’t recognize this senior. Did Blue Rain not hang up a huge portrait of me in the Hall of Fame for those dogs to worship me?”

“I’m to blame for that. If it weren’t for me, you might have actually been able to win some fame during the two years and earned yourself a portrait in the Hall of Fame, but as the founder of Team Blue Rain, I believe your hard work and passion set the team’s path for the future by becoming the powerful stepping stone for the later generation. One shouldn’t be too unduly humble.”

“Are you f*cking illiterate? When was this senior ever too unduly humble? Flip open the Baidu dictionary and study how to use proverbs properly. Don’t speak such nonsense to me.”

“If you aren’t too humble, then you’ll just have to accept your job as a spy. Trust me. You have the ability to do the job well.” Ye Xiu said.

“What a load of sh*t! This senior is saying this job is too easy for someone like myself. Stop pestering me.” Wei Chen expressed.

“Obviously for a job as a normal spy, but this time, I’m going to be doing something big.” Ye Xiu said.

“How big?”

“What’s the point of having one or two spies? If we’re sending in spies, we’re going to send in a full group of them.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“Look, with your skill, as long as you don’t intentionally keep a low profile, even if you won’t be able to become one of the core members that manage the guild, becoming a core member that leads teams shouldn’t be a problem, right? When this happens, you can add your gang into the guild and we’ll set up a group of spies in the guild. A single spy won’t be able to get much information, but a guild’s elite team should be able to access quite a lot of information, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“You really are too shameless. Not only do you want me to jump into a pit of fire, you even want all of my bros to jump in with me!”

“How can say it’s a pit of fire? Do you know the benefits of being in a guild!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true. Without the extra stats and equipment from a large guild, our strength is too weak. It doesn’t feel good! It seems like taking advantage of these benefits is not a bad idea.”

‘Yeah, it’s like killing two birds with one stone.”

“Okay, I’ll do it. When will those account cards arrive?”

“That depends on the delivery worker.”

“Okay, when I get the account cards, I’ll start. Do you have any recommendation as to which guild I should join?”

‘Which guild do you think would be the best?”

“With this brother’s skill, it doesn’t matter. The guilds will be lining up to invite me. There’s no need to consider whether or not I can do it.”

“Then you decide!”

“What about Samsara? Seeing today’s actions, Samsara has quite the ambition! The guild wants to become more popular and they’ve been doing well in the competitive scene recently too! Samsara’s actions this time might even have been orders from above. They want the attention in game to coincide with their rise to the pro stage.” Wei Chen said.

“Mm, it’s a good choice. With greater ambition, there are more opportunities to join and develop. Samsara is not bad. I approve.” Ye Xiu said.

“B*stard, it sounds like you’re approving my decision. This senior makes his own decisions!” Wei Chen replied.

“This is the last time I’m going to remind you: Death Hand is still with me.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Right, don’t you think that Samsara has a good chance of winning this season?” Wei Chen quickly switched topics.

“Their momentum is strong and they clearly aspire to be champions. This year, they even got to host the All Stars. They clearly plan on cementing their position in the pro scene this year. If you’re talking about chances, all of the strong teams have a chance, but if you’re talking about readiness and conviction, Samsara is looking quite strong!

“Speaking of which, Samsara didn’t seem to be looking too strong for the first half of the split!” Wei Chen said.

“That’s part of their readiness. It’s not easy starting off strong and keeping it up for the entire season. It’s better to start slower, grow, and then burst forth at the end for the playoffs.” Ye Xiu said.

“So what you’re saying is that you think Samsara’s going to win?”

“Yes.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Then should I put some money on it?” Wei Chen said.

‘What are you talking about?"

“Over here, our underground gambling den has opened a spot for Glory. I was planning on placing bets for who would win the playoffs, but I wasn’t sure who to place bets on.” Wei Chen explained.

“......”

Chen Guo’s back was sweating seeing these two talk trash to each other, while discussing their shameless plan to send a group of spies into another guild. When she suddenly saw the two chatting about the playoffs and how Ye Xiu predicted Samsara to win: “Do you really think Samsara will win?”

“If I were the one running the underground gambling den, I would definitely set Samsara’s betting odds low.” Ye Xiu pointed to the screen.

Chapter 544 – Third Follow Up

Blue Brook Guild had kept their name pristine. Samsara had gained more momentum. Overall, Samsara had benefited the most from this transaction.

Blue Brook Guild could only preserve their current popularity, allowing their guild members know just how much they had suffered under Lord Grim and his group’s hand

Samsara’s move had greatly increased their popularity, especially since the Club also made a statement in an interview about the battle spirit Team Samsara had. Even though the Club never referred to the game, anyone would be able to piece the two together.

The Club mostly talked about the performance of the team during the current season. Samsara’s recent achievements formed a backdrop which proved their spirit. Both the guild and Club had made progress together and immediately garnered a great amount of attention. Many people began considering the probability of Samsara winning the championships this season.

At this moment, no one would have thought that after these two follow ups came out, that a third follow up would appear.

The main topic of the post: Who gave you the power to put the boss at stake?

The original poster heavily criticized the eight guilds and their competition that staked the boss as the reward. The poster’s reasoning was very simple: the boss didn’t belong to the guilds. In theory, the boss belonged to all the players of Glory. Why did the guilds get to take the boss as their own and fight against each other with the boss as the reward?

This post gave rise to a huge amount of commotion.

It didn’t matter whether the player was a fan or a supporter, everyone hoped to have the chance to kill this type of boss and obtain its potential drops.

However, wild bosses weren’t beings that could be killed by just anyone. Slightly weaker teams could even die against one. As a result, only the elite guild teams could successfully kill wild bosses with a high success rate.

Club guilds were undoubtedly amongst the top among guilds and also valued wild bosses highly. Over the years, the wild bosses almost always fell into the hands of these Club guilds. In reality, the Club guilds already considered wild bosses as theirs.

As soon as this post came out, controversy erupted. The reasoning was specious though. The Club guilds had never declared that these bosses belonged to them alone. The boss belonged to whoever killed it. They had to care about their own images. If other players came to fight for the boss, they would kill the players or win the boss with higher contribution. In any case, if other came to stop them, they would fight back. They treated everyone equally when it came to wild bosses.

Bosses belonged to all the players of Glory. Because of this, Club guilds obviously had the right to kill bosses as well. Club guilds killed the bosses according to Glory’s rules. If someone else stole the boss away from them, they wouldn’t immediately attack and take revenge.

The proof post hadn’t been well written. It ignored the feelings of many players. The guilds felt that it was completely natural. The players thought so too, which was why no one had said anything about it until now. However, now that someone with a different perspective had come out, it immediately raised a lot of controversy.

The Club guild players naturally supported their own guilds. However, many players criticized the guilds’ inconsiderate conduct towards them.

This post was much more shocking than Blue Brook Guild’s or Samsara’s follow ups. This time, it not only struck a blow towards the eight guilds involved, but also to all of the Club guilds. The post also denounced how the Club guilds only cared about the interests of their pro teams and restricted the freedom of their own players, treating them like slaves.

This denunciation was a harsh statement. In response, the big guilds frantically defended themselves, talking about the benefits of being in a large guild…..

While defending themselves, they conducted an investigation on the original poster. They obviously wanted to know if this attack had been done by someone with other motives. Speaking of which, everyone had already begun suspecting a certain player.

But after conducting their investigation, the poster hadn’t hidden his history. He wasn’t anyone particularly famous. Traces of him could be found all over the forums. It seemed like he was the type of player who liked to spread rumors.

The big guilds didn’t dare to relax their guards though. If it was just some random player talking trash, then they wouldn’t be afraid at all, but if this player had other motives, they had to be ready to respond.

Let alone the big guilds,even Chen Guo began to suspect a certain someone after seeing the ruckus caused by the post.

“Is this your doing?” Chen Guo pointed at the screen and asked Ye Xiu. Then again, she had not seen Ye Xiu typing up anything like this earlier.

Ye Xiu took a quick look and shook his head: “No.”

“Tsk tsk, the guilds are going crazy over this. Look.” Chen Guo went back to the forum home page for Ye Xiu to see. The main page was filled with statements from the big guilds, defending themselves from the criticism they had just been plastered with, especially the part about treating their guild members as slaves. They had to give an explanation.

“Tsk tsk tsk.” Ye Xiu sighed, but didn’t pay too much attention to it and continued to do his own work. He hadn’t played much of the game in these last two days. Instead, he studied the document from Wei Chen on the fastest way to gather skill points.

In this document, Wei Chen listed a huge amount of quests and explained the requirements of these quests in order to get an increased drop rate for skill books.

With Ye Xiu’s knowledge of the game, he didn’t need to do much testing to test the hypothesis in order to figure out the method’s reliability. In the end, he had to admit that Wei Chen’s research couldn’t be considered a myth. The only thing he lacked was hard data that he himself had collected.

In Wei Chen’s research, he called all of these “hidden conditions”. The reason he was so confident was because Glory didn’t seem to be lacking in these types of “hidden conditions”. For example, the vast majority of skills had hidden effects that could be activated upon certain situations playing out. Because players used these skills so often, these hidden effects were eventually figured out. In that case, what other hidden conditions existed in Glory?

This was one reason for Wei Chen’s efforts in researching how to increase the drop rate of skill books. Of course, Wei Chen also considered this as a method of becoming rich. The two had discussed this when discussing the contents of the document.

“I’ve finished looking at the document you sent me.” Ye Xiu hadn’t played the game for the last two days and had spent all his time studying the document.

“What do you think? It’s pretty sound, right?” Wei Chen replied on QQ.

“Yeah, amazing!” Ye Xiu praised sincerely because he knew just how difficult it must have been to research all of this. Wei Chen had studied quests! He had searched through the forums and heard from rumors about the different places and quests with a chance of dropping skill books. Through these quests, he found the hidden conditions necessary to increase the drop rate of said skill books.

Apart from daily quests, most quests couldn’t be repeated. Non-repeatable quests made up most of the results from Wei Chen’s research. What did this mean? It meant that Wei Chen had used numerous accounts in order to test his theory because each account could only try each quest once.

Ye Xiu didn’t ask how Wei Chen had gotten all those accounts, but he could imagine how difficult it must have been. It wasn’t possible for Ye Xiu to not respect such effort.

“Once our team starts using it, make sure it doesn’t leak out.” Wei Chen carefully warned.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu said.

“Come take a look at all the loot we got.” Wei Chen said and sent Ye Xiu screenshots of their regained equipment one after the other. With his gang of bros, Wei Chen wandered around the Heavenly Domain ambushing guild players. They didn’t say a word to them and just killed them directly.

This type of harassment wouldn’t hurt the big guilds much, but they couldn’t let it slide either. The guilds formed a hunting team in order to hunt down Wei Chen and his gang. Wei Chen happily clashed with them, sacrificing their accounts, while continuing to fill up their inventories.

After two days, the stats of their twenty accounts were completely red. Their experience points were negative numbers. They were too lazy to count how many times they had died because they were more interested in the equipment they received during this period.

As they died, their strength declined making it more and more difficult to continue fighting. Even so, they still continued to bite at these guild players. The guilds were completely sick of them, but they learn from their previous mistake. This time, they didn’t dare to release a bounty. Wei Chen’s gang was with Lord Grim. If they offered a reward, what would they do if these guys just killed themselves for the reward?

“Okay, save some strength to help me escape!” Ye Xiu said.

The guilds weren’t having a good time these last two days. Let alone the boss, the proof post was also very troublesome to deal with. A random team was ambushing their players every day. In addition to this, they had a group of players guarding Lord Grim’s log-off spot 24/7, but they had yet to see Lord Grim log on.

This time, they were determined to fight with Ye Xiu though. They had the manpower anyways. If they just made the shifts shorter, no one would be as bitter about it. Whoever killed Lord Grim would get a large reward, so the guild players had fairly high morale.

“Yeah, it’s about time. We should hurry and get you out while our accounts still have enough strength to! If we’re going to be spies, we can’t get revealed yet.” Wei Chen also replied.

“Yeah, I’ll get an account too and help you guys.” Ye Xiu said. He asked Chen Guo to borrow her Chasing Haze. After logging into the game, he headed towards Poison Fang Swamp, where Lord Grim had logged off at.

Chapter 545 – Rescue

The eight guilds involved in the proof post were gathered at the boundaries of Poison Fang Swamp.

Initially, only five of the guilds had hidden themselves to lie in wait for an ambush, but later, they invited the other three guilds to join in. Blue Brook Guild and Samsara had just been extorted by Ye Xiu, so they happily accepted. Excellent Dynasty naturally accepted too.

The guilds arranged the shifts for guarding this area. The method was a bit clumsy, but it was still better than nothing. Against a cunning god-level opponent, having an opportunity to kill him once was hard to come by.

Yes, the eight guilds just wanted to kill him once in order to vent their anger, but how would they have known that he wouldn’t appear for two days? It was quite surprising to them.

Lord Grim won’t log on?

If this was permanent, it would be incredible news, but then again, how could it be possible? Of course it couldn’t be. If he wasn’t logging on, was he perhaps plotting something scary? The guilds thought of the little nincompoop complaining on the forums and suspected that it must have been the work of Lord Grim.

For a moment, they didn’t know if it was better for Lord Grim to be online or not. In any case, they had to hastily explain themselves on the forums and stay in position at Poison Fang Swamp. As for the reward they would receive for killing Lord Grim…… it had already been put up inside the guilds and would never been taken down. Why else had Wei Chen attacked Ye Xiu with his identity as a member of the Blue Brook Guild?

Overall, the deployment of the guilds was a bit sloppy. It wasn’t a very careful formation, but rather more like a desperate action, but in any case, their superiors hadn’t given them any new instructions, so the guild members simply followed orders and changed shifts constantly.

Each of the eight guilds sent a team of players for a total of 80 players. For convenience, they formed a group. As a result, the teams who arrived to take over the new shift would enter the group and then stare blankly into empty space. This sequence hadn’t changed at all for the past two days. The players on shift weren’t too bored though. The guilds had a lot of players. They just needed to randomly switch a few of them out every once in awhile. No one would feel like the task was too repetitive.

The only thing that repeated was Lord Grim never showing up.

At this moment, a team from Misty Castle arrived, ready to take over the new shift. The eight guilds switched shifts at different times to avoid everyone coming at once and making the situation chaotic.

“Are you guys here?”

“Yeah, we’re here.”

“Has Lord Grim logged in yet?”

“No……”

Whenever new players arrived on shift, they would often have a similar conversation.

After some dialogue, the new team entered the group and the old team left. At this moment, twenty players lay in wait, secretly observing the situation.

Wei Chen had already investigated this change of shift already. It wasn’t any different than before.们

“The enemy is quite fierce. By changing shifts at different times, we won’t only be facing these eighty players. There’s always back-up on their way.” Wei Chen said to Ye Xiu.

“Is there always one team coming to change shifts every time?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah, from what I saw this time and last time, this seems to be true.” Wei Chen said.

“Then why don’t we attack this team?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I thought of it, but from the main city to here, the space is very open. There isn’t any place to ambush them from. We’ll catch wind of each other way before we can get close.” Wei Chen said.

Ye Xiu thought of the terrain and agreed.

Afterwards, he said: “Then what about in the main city?”

“It’s a Level 65 city and it’s quite populated too. It would be best if we didn’t go to a place with too many people.” Wei Chen sighed. His team had gone to a city to repair their equipment, but the guilds somehow surrounded and massacred them. It had been a miserable day!

“So the only choice is to break through these eighty players?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It seems like it.”

“Then let’s do it!” Ye Xiu said,

“That’s what I was going to do, but then you started spewing all that bullsh*t.” Wei Chen cursed.

“Let’s go from the six o’clock direction!” Ye Xiu suggested.

“Why six o’clock? Go from the twelve o’clock. We’ll create a small hole. Then, you log on and run deep into the map. As long as you pull some distance from them, how could you not shrug them off with your strict control over your stamina?” Wei Chen said.

“Old bro, I’m only Level 54. I can’t even use insect repellant smoke. Running deeper into the swamp isn’t convenient for me. It would be better to run down the main street.”

“Oh, I forgot about that.” Wei Chen immediately realized. It wasn’t that he lacked experience. There hadn’t ever been a Level 54 character in the Heavenly Domain, so players over here wouldn’t consider things from that sort of perspective.

“Let’s go then!” Wei Chen led his team and changed directions.

“Don’t be in such a rush. Let me cause a small disturbance first.” Ye Xiu was using Chasing Haze. Launchers had the longest range of the classes in Glory, so he dared to provoke these eighty players.

“Hurry up.” Wei Chen impatiently urged.

As soon as he said this, Ye Xiu’s Chasing Haze threw out a lighter, low and level. However, in the dark Poison Fang Swamp, the light attracted everyone’s attention.

“Who is it?” A player on guard noticed the light, but with how Ye Xiu threw the lighter, the lighter didn’t travel far, so it had already landed on the ground by the time the player noticed it. The player could only see light and couldn’t tell what it was.

“What’s wrong?” The unaware players asked, when suddenly, they heard a loud bang and saw several Heat-Seeking Missiles flying towards them.

“F*ck, it’s an attack from above!” Someone shouted. Everyone began to move. The Heat-Seeking Missiles would fly towards wherever the lighter had hit the ground. They hadn’t seen the lighter, so they didn’t know where to run.

“No one move!” The person who saw the light realized that the light was the guiding beacon for the Heat-Seeking Missiles. He didn’t have time to think where the lighter had come from. He only knew that if no one moved, everyone would be safe.

However, at this moment, the one thing that couldn’t be shouted was “no one move”, even something like telling everyone to move in a single direction would have been more believable.

The shout aroused everyone’s suspicion, especially because not everyone here was from the same guild. No one really trusted each other. Thus, it would have been better if he hadn’t shouted anything at all. The shout made the all of the guild teams run around like crazy. Three players pounced directly towards the Heat-Seeking Missiles’ landing spot.

“Not my fault!” The player saw that no one was listening and actually felt happy seeing three players running towards the missiles.

“Bang!!”

By the time the three had noticed that they really shouldn’t have moved, the missiles had already reached them. A mushroom cloud popped up and the three went tumbling away. One player fell on a dried up tree and couldn’t get down.

“Team 1, Team 2 go take a look over there.” Someone spoke. This time, in this joint movement, there was an overall leader. Whoever was the group leader could speak. Because they changed shifts frequently, every guild had a chance to lead the group, so no guild would feel that the system was unfair, so there was no point arguing over it.

Team 1’s captain was the group leader. He gave the orders to personally check and also brought along Team 2.

The two teams hastily ran over with their weapons clanking. When they arrived, the mushroom cloud had yet to disperse. Suddenly, a beam of light descended from the skies and, because of the mushroom cloud covering it, no one noticed it.

This attack was very brave. People had to immediately rush over for the mushroom cloud to cover it, otherwise no would have gotten hit by the light beam and the attack would have been wasted.

But now?

Satellite Beam descended from the skies. The ones in front bore the brunt of the attack.

The other players quickly got out of the way in fright. But then, the Satellite Beam split into multiple smaller pillars, which were controlled manually. The pillars didn’t follow the set pattern and predicted the directions which the players would dodge towards.

“Team 3, perform a flank. Everyone else, search the surroundings!!” The group leader hastily ordered.

The eight guilds dispersed like water. Wei Chen didn’t need Ye Xiu to remind him. He could easily tell that it was a perfect opportunity to act. The enemies scrambled to figure out the situation, which gave them an opportunity to directly cut through them.

“Everyone ready!” Wei Chen typed in the group chat. His gaze was locked onto the numerous players that were heading in his direction.

“Pop out and kill them all for me!” Wei Chen shouted.

“1, 2, 3!”

“There are people here!!”

When Wei Chen finished counting to three, the other side noticed half of Windward Formation’s head sticking out from behind a tree. The distance between the two sides was too close to escape. Wei Chen couldn’t hide any longer, but he timed it perfectly. After counting to three, he shouted a single word: attack.

Twenty players leapt out of their hiding spots and used their strongest moves. All of them were cursing at the same time too, saying things like “F*ck you for ten thousand years!”

One wave of AoE.

Even though Wei Chen’s group no longer had the same strength as other Level 70 characters, their attacks combined together were enough to take down several enemies. The wave of attacks attracted the attention of the enemy. They looked and saw a whole bunch of familiar names. Weren’t they the ones with bounties on their heads? Rumors said they went around bullying stray guild players. Were they hallucinating? Why would they attack such a huge group like them?

“Be careful! They’re here to rescue Lord Grim. Everyone, stay in formation!!” The group leader kept a clear mind and instantly figured out their intent.

As soon as he said this, the dazzling light from the Satellite Beam dissipated. Lord Grim had unexpectedly logged on in the middle of this and had already started running away!

Chapter 546 – Breakout

“You scared me!!” The voice that came out of Lord Grim’s character was actually a female’s voice, who seemed to be grumbling at the person sitting next to her.

Chen Guo hadn’t thought that, as soon as Lord Grim had logged on, her entire screen would be surrounded by light. Lord Grim was completely enveloped by the Satellite Beam. Using this beautiful screen, no one noticed Lord Grim’s appearance. Because of the short period of invulnerability after logging in, Lord Grim didn’t receive any damage from the Satellite Beam.

The reason behind Ye Xiu choosing to control the Satellite Beam’s split pillars manually was to force the surrounding enemies away. When Lord Grim appeared and ran, no one would be able to block him immediately.

However, escaping just like this clearly wasn’t going to happen. Lord Grim’s log off location had been marked as the center of the encirclement. The Satellite Beam descended on this location. The enemy encirclement had only been disturbed by Ye Xiu’s Chasing Haze, as well as Wei Chen’s group. Actually breaking through would require much more effort than just running.

“Hurry up! Hurry up!!!” Chen Guo anxiously urged. She was already standing up, while controlling Lord Grim. Ye Xiu quickly shifted to where she stood. Chen Guo also hastily moved away. The two switched characters, both attempting to escape.

Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze had originally been outside of the encirclement, but the enemy had instructed a team to surround her, but because of Wei Chen’s sudden ambush, this team was instructed to hold their position, so Chasing Haze didn’t have as much trouble escaping.

The challenge was getting Lord Grim to escape. Even though he had logged on cleanly without anyone immediately noticing his presence, he had now been completely exposed. Everyone immediately abandoned Wei Chen’s twenty players and switched to chasing Lord Grim.

When Wei Chen saw that his gang wasn’t even be considered bait and the enemy side completely ignoring them, he couldn’t tolerate it. With an angry shout, he charged at the enemies, along with his gang, to prove their existence.

“Teams 5, 7, and 8 block that side. Everyone else surround Lord Grim!” The group leader could see the entire situation clearly. He had the three closest teams block Wei Chen’s assault and had everyone else continue pursuing Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu hadn’t touched Glory in two days. Now that he had control over Lord Grim again, he was filled with energy. He swiped his mouse and Lord Grim shot his gun at the ground behind him. He flew into the air and onto a dead tree branch. On this dead tree branch hung the poor player who had been blasted into the air by the Heat-Seeking Missiles. The tree branch couldn’t hold the weight of both players and broke. The poor player fell. This attack had been too sudden. The players below were running while they aimed their weapons at Lord Grim, when they heard a cry from above their heads. Before they could lift their heads, their cameras went staggering towards the sky and they tumbled into the mud.

Lord Grim turned around. With a flash, the slash from a Sword Draw flew towards two players who were trying to flank him from the left. The players who were coming from the right were just about to use their own Sword Draws, when Lord Grim suddenly leapt into the air towards them and disappeared from their sight. Ye Xiu had used a Z-Shake in order to slide past these players without slowing down.

The blockade formed by these three players had been broken through, but there were still a lot of players left. Ye Xiu looked around in a circle. Without stopping, he quickly figured out the most optimal pathing. He crouched and rolled forward, dodging an attack from the left. As he got up, he blasted the enemy player away with a Falling Flower Palm. However, because of the over ten level difference, the blow away effect from the Falling Flower Palm was greatly reduced. It couldn’t even be considered a blow away, more like a trip.

Ye Xiu also felt grieved. If Lord Grim had been Level 70 and the Falling Flower Palm worked normally, breaking through this encirclement would be a piece of cake.

This had been within Ye Xiu’s calculations though. He continued running forward past the “tripped” player. Another pincer attack from the left and right came. Ye Xiu accurately predicted which attack would arrive first. He shook his Thousand Chance Umbrella into a spear and stabbed towards the left. Then, with a Circle Swing, he swung the enemy player on the left into the enemy player on the right, slamming both enemies into the ground.

Fast!

Too fast!

The players that were still a distance away from Lord Grim could only become spectators for now. In their eyes, Lord Grim’s attack had been very fast.

Attack speed.

This stat wouldn’t increase as one leveled up. The only things that affected attack speed were the player’s skill, equipment, and the special effects of their skills.

If a player’s skill was the only deciding factor in attack speed, then in theory, attack speed could be limitless. From this perspective, equipment was what restricted one’s attack speed.

However, in reality, this was a misconception.

In Glory, weapons had an attack speed that ranged from 1 to 10. If a player’s skill was poor, they might only be able to utilize an attack speed of 7 or 8, despite having a weapon with an attack speed of 10. If a player’s skill was good, then the player could reach an attack speed of 10, but couldn’t go any higher than that.

However, a player could increase their attack speed with a skill. There might be a limit for speed, but how does one attack in the fastest way possible? By taking the shortest attack route.

Thus, it could be said that in order to increase attack speed through the player’s skill, the player needed to be precise, not quick!

Precise judgement and control was required to perform the attack along the shortest route. Even with similar attack speeds, if one player attacks along a different route, it would take slightly longer for their attack to arrive.

Lord Grim’s attack looked very fast because of this. In reality, all of the forms of the Thousand Chance Umbrella had an attack speed of 5, but that didn’t necessarily mean that this was his limit. An attack speed of 10 couldn’t be considered the limit either. It was simply a limit set by the weapon. Other equipment and the effects from skills could also increase a player’s attack speed. However, because of the mechanics of the game, having higher attack speed wasn’t always better. If a player’s attack speed was too high and the player couldn’t keep up, then the player wouldn’t be able to fully utilize the speed.

The guild players were astonished at the speed of Lord Grim’s attack, but was Lord Grim only fast with his attacks? His movement speed was also the same.

Ye Xiu’s extremely good control over his stamina allowed his movement speed tempo to constantly change, making the pursers unable to properly grasp it. They would predict that Lord Grim would move to a spot, so they would release an attack targeting this spot. However, when Lord Grim actually arrived at that spot, he would always seem to step over their attacks. They felt like Lord Grim wouldn’t reach a spot yet, so they held their attacks, but when they attacked, all they saw was his back.

The guild’s encirclement went from scattered to orderly, but before they could rearrange the troops properly, Lord Grim had already broken through. Along the way were bodies flipped into the ground. No one had been severely hurt, but they lost their chance at blocking Lord Grim. By the time they recovered, they would only see the body of the next person being thrown into the ground.

“STOP HIM! STOP HIM! STOP HIM!!!” The group leader, who could be considered rational and quick-witted, could only resort to this. It wasn’t that he didn’t want a concrete formation. Lord Grim’s actions far surpassed the speed at which he could react. By the time he had thought of a way to stop him, Lord Grim had already gotten past that section.

He tried making predictions, but with Lord Grim’s weird pathing, he had no way to predict how Lord Grim would break through.

Conventionally speaking, the fastest way to break through was in a straight line, but Lord Grim was already halfway out and anyone could see that he wasn’t moving in a straight line. He just moved wherever there was a hole.

Where were the opportunities?

Answering this question and then making the arrangements would require the group leader to think twice as much as Ye Xiu needed to. There was no way the leader could win a mind game like this. Besides shouting “STOP HIM!!”, he didn’t know what else he could do.

In the blink of an eye, Lord Grim had broken past the final layer and rushed out of the encirclement. Everyone was stunned.

What just happened?

Everything happened so quickly. When did he break out of the encirclement?

But after seeing everyone lying on the ground, they felt like a long amount of time should have passed, right?

No one could get a clear understanding of the situation, but they could understand one thing: Lord Grim had successfully escaped.

Their eighty players had been thrown into disarray by an outside force and then broken through just like that.

“Chase….” The group leader shouted. He felt like his voice was very mechanical. He felt like it was what he should shout. As for what he should do after, he had no idea.

“Old thing, I’ll be heading out first!” They heard Lord Grim shout.

“Go! Go! This senior is going to slaughter everyone here!” A coarse voice responded.

Lord Grim ran away, but the twenty rescuers hadn’t. They had been killing the entire time, whether they were against three players, four players, five players, or even ten players…...

In the end, these twenty players eventually turned into corpses. They dropped some equipment, but the guild players couldn’t feel happy at all. Compared to the equipment that they had lost, these twenty players had profited a lot more. They had no way of getting their lost equipment back either.

They had been helpless against Lord Grim’s escape, but these twenty players had killed off 39 of their own players. They had lost almost twice as many people and this was with the opposing side having incomplete equipment and levels.

When the team leaders reported back to their respective guilds, they said this to their guild leaders: we successfully eliminated the rescue team, but Lord Grim escaped.

Chapter 547 – The Wealthy are Aggressive and Powerful

The spawn camp on Lord Grim operation had failed again. Windward Formation and his group of people were still employing guerilla warfare tactics. As these guerillas fought, they became weaker and weaker. Two teams wasn’t considered a lot, but it still surpassed the number of players on a standard team. Their tactics were dirty and nimble too, making the big guilds unbelievable annoyed, but what happened next threw Wei Chen’s little annoyance into the back of their minds.

The post, which the guilds had nervously hoped wouldn’t come, finally appeared.

Heavenly Justice!

This guild had already been officially announced as the guild for the new incoming team and used their identity as a Club to make a statement. For the business structured Club guilds, this action was highly looked down upon. Heavenly Justice declared that they would always put their players first. They definitely wouldn’t be like other Clubs, who prioritized their business and treated their own guild members like slaves.

This statement made the large guilds go crazy. Slaves?! Didn’t we already give a clear explanation? Which guild dared to treat their supporters like slaves? The guilds really obtained a lot of goods and materials from their guild members, but it wasn’t like they completely took it all for themselves! The guilds had a solid guild storage system. Everyone donated items on their own volition and gained corresponding contribution points. The higher the contribution points, the greater the benefits they would receive. This was clearly a win-win situation for both sides. How could this be called slave labor?

But before the guilds could respond, someone posted the guild storage systems of each of the top guilds and analyzed them. The poster picked out a random second-rate Orange equipment from one of the guilds. In order to obtain an equipment of this grade, the player required 15,000 guild contribution points. In order to get 15,000 contribution points and, excluding the points earned from doing daily tasks, according to the guild’s set-up, the amount of items required to be donated would be equivalent to around 30,000 gold coins.

“30,000 gold coins is enough to buy several second-grade Orange equipments. I believe that everyone in the Heavenly Domain should know this.” The poster concluded, “As for the guild, this donation of 30,000 gold coins is theirs to use. In addition, if the equipment traded in is ever lost, there will be a guild contribution penalty. 15,000 guild contribution points can’t get a player a full set of second-rate Orange equipment either. There’s a limit to the number of equipment that can be traded in. For this guild, the limit is four pieces of equipment…….

When the guilds saw this analysis, they went into a frenzy. This analysis made the issue seem very black and white. The other side’s analysis wasn’t wrong, but it neglected a few important points.

Firstly, the other side lightly skipped over the part about compensation from participating in daily activities, but in reality, guilds had a lot of daily tasks and every player who participated in a dungeon run for the guild would receive all sorts of compensation for their work. People who accumulated 15,000 guild contribution points definitely didn’t get all of it through donations.

Secondly, the other side neglected the value of second-rate Orange equipment. How many pieces of second-rate Orange equipment could 30,000 gold coins get? That was hard to say. Even if you had the money, you would have trouble finding even one to buy.

Thirdly, the penalty for lost equipment and the limitation on the number of equipment. These were completely necessary. If not, spies would rack up the necessary guild contribution points, trade it for equipment, and then have others kill him for the equipment to drop. Without a penalty or limit, the spy could rinse and repeat forever…… how could the guilds allow something so stupid happen? Heavenly Justice’s guild storage system must have some sort of similar system to prevent this from happening too!

Lots of intentionally misleading analyses came out. Before the guilds could refute them, Heavenly Justice floated in and spoke frankly of the discrepancies in these analyses. This type of thing was because of this. For example, the limit on the number of equipment and penalties for losing equipment had to be implemented. However, in comparison, our Heavenly Justice requires less guild contribution points and so on.

The guilds were still writing their refutes, when Heavenly Justice jumped out to do it for them. When they took a closer look, f*ck, the people analyzing never said whether or not they were from Heavenly Justice or not. Before anyone could respond, one of the analysts replied, saying how just Heavenly Justice was. Compared to other Club guilds, their benefits were much better. Heavenly Justice was very mighty.

Soon afterwards, Heavenly Justice quickly replied, showing their humbleness. How can our grassroots team even be compared with those powerful pro teams?

One side gave praise, while the other side replied. The other guilds didn’t even have time to reply. Everyone was coughing blood from anger! The two sides were clearly in cahoots! The guilds had been kicked to the opposite of the people’s side. Heavenly Justice seemed to be the leader of the people.

Grassroots team? Grassroots my ass! Heavenly Justice’s guild leader was a famous money warrior in the game. If it weren’t for his money, how could he evenly compete with the Club guilds? How could people like him even be considered grassroots?

Of course, Heavenly Justice’s guild storage system required less contribution. Their guild storage system couldn’t come close to the top guilds. All of the top guilds knew this to be fact. Because the rewards for wild bosses and dungeon records were completely monopolized by the Club guilds. Money couldn’t buy these rewards. If a guild storage didn’t have good equipment, the guild contribution required would obviously be less. Heavenly Justice failed to mention this point. They enticed players by saying they required less guild contribution points and supported it by posting screenshots of the guild storages of other guilds.

Every single big guild madly gave their statements.

Giving a detailed explanation of their guild storage system.

Saying how rare and difficult it was to even find second-rate Orange equipment on the market.

Some even pointed their fingers at Heavenly Justice, daring them to post a screenshot of their own guild storages. Your guild storage don’t even have anything in it, so you obviously would require less guild contribution points for the highest tier of items.

Others directly had their spies screenshot Heavenly Justice’s guild storage. Sure enough, the higher tier items couldn’t compare to the big guilds.

However, Heavenly Justice simply laughed, saying we required less guild contribution points, so a lot of our players already have enough points to rent out those items. Right now, those players were wearing the equipment, so of course you can’t see it in the storage. Unlike you guys, who have such high requirements that all of the equipment is left in the storage, unable to be traded away.

For a moment, the forums heated up. Everyone favored Heavenly Justice’s words. Their eyes opened up, unable to take in everything that they witnessed.

Chen Guo once again discovered the war of words while browsing about in boredom. She hastily pulled Ye Xiu over to see. Ye Xiu looked and praised Heavenly Justice’s powerful move.

“Are they going too far?” Chen Guo asked. This time, Heavenly Justice directly challenged all of the Clubs.

“What’s there to be afraid of? Their previous statement already ridiculed the Clubs. Now, they’re putting themselves and the other Clubs on two different sides. It’s really smart you know. They know that directly stealing fans away from these Clubs is practically impossible. However, by challenging all of the other Clubs, some of the players will certainly waver during this dispute. Even if there weren’t a lot of these players, these players only have one way to go! For the other Clubs, you have so many choices to choose between, but the opposite side only has one Heavenly Justice. With this one move, they made themselves much more popular.”

“But souring their relationship with the other Clubs won’t be good for them, no?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yes, that’s certainly true. But the problem is, think of the other side’s background. You said it before about Loulan Slash. He’s a famous money warrior in Glory. He relied on throwing money at the game in order to compete with these Club guilds and form a pro team. His family background definitely isn’t simple. He has confidence that he can reach the top. Why should he act so timidly in front of them? The wealthy truly are aggressive and powerful!” Ye Xiu sighed.

After saying this, Ye Xiu took a look at the posts and then pointed at some of the content: “Look, something like this isn’t possible for someone like me who’s building a guild from scratch!”

Chen Guo looked. Heavenly Justice made a statement saying that they had a lot of players apply, but because of the player limit in the guild, they decided to create another branch of their guild. The branch’s guild storage would be set up quickly. However, the guild’s level would require the effort of the players.

Chen Guo thought about how it hadn’t been long since Heavenly Justice had announced the creation of their pro team, yet they had already become so popular. On the other hand, their side was faced with numerous difficulties. She couldn’t help but become depressed and hated how powerless she was.

At this moment, Ye Xiu received a message from Wei Chen on QQ. Wei Chen had also seen the war of words on the forums from Heavenly Justice.

“F*ck, this Heavenly Justice is quite aggressive! This senior has heard about the wealth of their guild leader a long time ago, but I didn’t think he was ambitious enough to create his own team. Speaking of this, didn’t your Lord Grim join them? Don’t tell me this guy is going to be our boss?” Wei Chen asked.

Seeing Wei Chen’s message, Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel ashamed, when she saw Ye Xiu quickly reply: “No, our boss is the woman who you ridiculed the other day!”

“F*ck me, what am I doing here then? I should pack up and seek asylum at Heavenly Justice.”

“You want to go to Heavenly Justice to spy on them? No need for that. Didn’t I say our accounts came from Heavenly Justice?” Ye Xiu replied.

“D*mn, you thought that far ahead and already saw the potential in Heavenly Justice so long ago?” Wei Chen was surprised.

“No, no. It was a pure coincidence.” Ye Xiu said.

“Even if it’s just a coincidence, you still have to be able to seize it. I already know how shameless you are, but speaking of this, I had something I wanted to ask you about. I almost forgot.” After mumbling to himself, he was quickly reminded of something and immediately followed: “Right, about the accounts you gave me, why aren’t there any Knights?”

“Oh, I kept the Knight. I have a use for it. You’ll have to make up for this discrepancy yourself!”

Chapter 548 – Unrivalled Super Hottie

“Why do you need a Knight account?”

Wei Chen asked through QQ. Chen Guo, who was sitting beside him, also asked.

Ye Xiu laughed, typing and saying the same thing, “To be a tank!”

“You don't say!”

Wei Chen replied as he sent a “rolling his eyes” emoji. Chen Guo, who was beside him, demonstrated a real life eye roll while repeating the exact same words.

“So what are you planning on doing?” Chen Guo asked again.

“I’ll join a guild and play as a tank.” Ye Xiu said.

“Did you mean to say that you’re also going to be a spy?”

“Pretty much!” Ye Xiu’s reply wasn’t too clear. It looked his role couldn’t just be described as being a spy.

Chen Guo didn’t fully understand what Ye Xiu meant, but she didn’t ask any further. Ye Xiu was still playing on Lord Grim. He was very close to Level 55 and reached Level 55 that afternoon, finally passing the level 50-55 stage, the most difficult stage he would face as an unspecialized character.

“You’ve finally reached Level 55!” Chen Guo felt the barrier had now been passed.

“You’re right, I’m finally level 55. I can start running dungeons to level up from now on. Leveling through dungeons is a lot easier.” Ye Xiu sighed. Chen Guo didn't know whether to laugh or cry. The difference between dungeoning and leveling areas was that you gained more experience through dungeon runs, but you could never say that it was easier. How hard was a dungeon? If you died carelessly a few times, you might lose even more experience than you would gain! However, Ye Xiu was a freak. He was the most hated player in the eyes of the big guilds and had to play cautiously while leveling in leveling areas. He had to leave every time he saw a random stranger. Inside a dungeon, it really would be a lot easier for him than in leveling area.

“You said just yesterday that Loulan Slash isn’t afraid to oppose the other big guilds, but I don’t think you were ever afraid of them in the first place! I’ve never seen you try to maintain a good relationship with them.” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu smiled and replied in a bitter tone, “I don’t have a choice. I don't have much time. I can only take the risky path. High-risk high-reward. Other than that, what can I do to create a whole new team? Our aim isn’t to pass the seeding tournament, but to be a threat to the other teams.”

“I see!” Chen Guo understood, “Let me bring you through a dungeon!” Right after she said this, Ye Xiu logged out of Lord Grim.

“Since I’m already level 55, leveling isn’t priority anymore.” Ye Xiu smiled. Actually Wei Chen’s long year of research about earning extra skill points was now his priority. Along with that research, managing his account became a lot easier, so Ye Xiu had more time to do other things now.

Ye Xiu pulled out the Knight account card, after he logged out from Lord

Grim. Logging into the game, he turned his head and asked Chen Guo, “ Do you have any money?”

“Yes? How much do you need?” Chen Guo reached for her purse immediately.

“I meant in-game money……” Ye Xiu was speechless.

“Oh? Game money, Chasing Haze has about 10,000 gold!” Chen Guo said.

In Glory, 100 or 200 gold coins wasn’t considered rich. 1000 to 2000 would be the starting point and was the amount most players had. 10,000 gold coins was the border between being rich or not rich. Chen Guo used to a member of a Club guild, so she could be considered as a high end player. 10,000 gold coins was a healthy amount of money.

“Give me everything, I’m going to buy some equipment.” Ye Xiu logged into his brand new Knight account. All the accounts that Ye Xiu had won last time had been checked by himself and Chen Guo. They were almost all completely empty accounts. Even if they had equipment, they were at best green mission equipments. Speaking of which, Ma Chengyi not giving them normal server accounts was already considered not being cheap. The difference between level 70 characters in normal servers and the Heavenly Domain was huge. Ma Chengyi’s 24 accounts were all blank, but at least they were Heavenly Domain accounts.

This knight account had 4160 skill points, which was a very common amount. The few items he had equipped were all green recycle equipment. After a short scan, the stats for this character hadn’t been completed either. Apparently, it had yet to finish all the missions that gave stat books. It would be really hard to figure out which quests were missing unless the previous owner was playing. Ye Xiu didn't care about these 5 or 10 extra stat points. It was the previous owner’s ID that truly showed how extraordinary he was.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was its name, extraordinarily not low key.

Ye Xiu couldn’t be bothered by the incomplete stats, however this badass name made him a little uncomfortable deep inside. Ye Xiu had long since passed the age where one would tell others how good looking he was with his ID.

“Come and get your money…..” Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu controlling Unrivaled Super Hottie, causing her to laugh inaudibly, then logged into Chasing Haze to give Ye Xiu the money.

Chasing Haze had 13251 gold coins. She gave Unrivaled Super Hottie 13000 gold coins, keeping the remaining 251.

Ye Xiu was thinking as he walked to the trading center and in a very short while, he walked out in new clothes. Chen Guo quickly ran over because she wanted to know how a pro player would choose equipment for a tank.

She was shocked the moment she leaned forward.

“Click on them so I can see!” Chen Guo said in disbelief.

Ye Xiu opened Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment panel, showing them off one by one to Chen Guo. While saying, “There is still 8000 coins left, you can have them back.”

“You……. Why are you saving so much money? Go get better items.” Chen Guo said. All the equipment that Ye Xiu bought were blue. Who in Heavenly Domain didn’t had a few purple equipment, even if they didn't have any orange ones? Especially for tanks, in a stable team, it was always the first character that was invested in. A purple weapon and purple shield were the bare minimum. Turned out that Ye Xiu gave Unrivalled Super Hottie a very random blue weapon and shield.

To be honest, a tank's job was probably the most important and a tank’s equipment wasn’t expensive. Because playing as a tank was a harsh job and the difficulty was high, ordinary players either misplayed the class or were too lazy to bother. It lead to a small amount of tank players. The fewer players, the less demand and the price wouldn't go up. With 13000 gold coins, players could barely afford a luxury weapon, but if you wanted to get a set of blue defensive equipment, a purple weapon and shield, it was more than possible.

“It’s all right.” Ye Xiu smiled and continue sending a trade request.

“Just keep the money, there’s no meaning in giving it back to me.” Chen Guo waved her hand and rejected.

It was only a few thousand gold coins, so Ye Xiu clearly didn't really put it to mind. Chen Guo didn't want it back, so he just kept it. He then switched to QQ and messaged Loulan Slash.

“Your recent move was very well played!” Ye Xiu started the conversation.

“Haha, I just happened to get the chance.” Loulan Slash was pretty satisfied with his move.

“Seeing how aggressive you were, are you sufficiently prepared?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It’s going so-so!” Loulan Slash replied.

“The reason I wanted to message you is to ask for some information.” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s up?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Do you know which sub guilds belong to Tyrannical Ambition?” Ye Xiu asked.

“God, you don't know ?” Loulan Slash was surprised.

“It’s because I am a God that I don't know.” Ye Xiu said.

“I see…” Loulan Slash suddenly realized the reason. Ye Xiu was at the very top. Low tier jobs, like guild management, wasn’t something he was informed about.

“Let me check.” Loulan Slash had clearly been preparing for a long time. From the guild to the prol team, the had both carefully been planned out. For their future opponents, they were also investigated from the guilds to their pro teams.

“There are a lot of sub guilds in each large guild. Some are very obvious and others are more hidden. You want information about Tyrannical Ambition, right? I’ll send you a copy after I compile a list!” Loulan Slash didn't hide their grasp of the situation.

Although Ye Xiu hadn’t given them any material assistance, but he had helped give them a lot of mental guidance. In particular, he allowed them to see their true position. This alone had greatly helped their chances of survival in the pro scene. If they really thought that they could win the championships like they had in the old days, they would be packing up as soon as they entered.

“Okay.”

Ye Xiu received the document that Loulan Slash sent him shortly after. According to the document, Tyrannical Ambition had 27 branch guilds. Of these 27 branch guilds, 5 were publicly known, 7 of them were hidden and only Loulan Slash knew about them. The other 15 were marked with question marks, indicating that they were still unconfirmed.

Ye Xiu took a look and it was similar to what he had predicted. Although he did not know the exact situation of Tyrannical Ambition, as the former leader of

Excellent Dynasty, a lot of information would flow towards him, even if he didn’t want to know. Tyrannical Ambition and Excellent Dynasty were both old school guilds, so the difference shouldn’t be that huge. Loulan Slash had dug out 27 of them, but he also knew that his list might not be complete.

The reason they hid them was not to hide their overall power. In fact, the real power of each guild could still be directly seen from their main guild. The members of branch guilds were players that might not necessarily fans of Tyrannical Ambition, but the guild was definitely secretly supporting or directly controlled by Tyrannical Ambition. They hoped to expand their control over resources and information through this method. Keeping them a secret was to prevent competitors from causing problems,

And for those guilds that everyone knew, it was the same as the main guild, full of fans. Even if you weren’t one, you had to pretend to be one in order to acquire the benefits.

Chapter 549 – I’m a Tank

“You’re planning on infiltrating Tyrannical Ambition?” Chen Guo had been sitting in front of the computer for the entire day. Fifty percent of her attention had been directed towards seeing what Ye Xiu was doing. If she needed to help Ye Xiu write a daily or weekly report, she didn’t want to miss anything.

“Yes.” Ye Xiu nodded his head. He was used to Chen Guo watching him and asking him questions from time to time.

“I feel bad for Tyrannical Ambition.” Chen Guo said.

“Ha ha, of course.” Ye Xiu laughed. After seeing Loulan Slash’s intelligence report, he immediately began searching for the listed guilds.

The branches of Tyrannical Ambition that everyone knew about weren’t guilds that Ye Xiu could get into because these branches raised Tyrannical Ambition’s banners. Fans of Tyrannical Ambition were lining up to squeeze into one! With Glory’s playerbase nowadays, filling several guilds couldn’t be considered incredible anymore. These branches of Tyrannical Ambition were all full. The big guilds won people over by virtue, so it wasn’t likely for them to kick someone out just to add someone out of kindness.

Besides, who would be so kind to Ye Xiu? Knock on their door, tell Jiang You, ‘I’m Ye Qiu, could you kick someone out and let me in?’ If Jiang You didn’t immediately summon thousands of players to kill him, that would already be considered quite kind.

Thus, Ye Xiu had to choose from the hidden branches of Tyrannical Ambition or the guilds allied with Tyrannical Ambition. Loulan Slash had given him a detailed report. He even had introductions for who controlled these branches. In the end, Ye Xiu chose a guild which someone from Tyrannical Ambition directly had control over. It was a guild called Exterminate the Heavens.

Ye Xiu felt like such an arrogant name perfectly matched his Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Then, there was Exterminate the Heaven’s guild leader: Senior Exterminate the Heavens!

No explanation was needed. Ye Xiu applied for the guild without any hesitation.

If Ye Xiu didn’t have the information given by Loulan Slash, Senior Exterminate the Heaven’s guild would only seem like a normal player guild. Although it was also a max leveled guild, it only had a little over a thousand players. This was pretty much the limit for normal guilds. The guild leader’s charisma could only do so much. Any more players and the guild would be very difficult to manage. The guild would need to use the guild storage as a foundation. However, building up a solid guild storage wasn’t easy for normal players. They would never be able to compete with the money and prestige that a Club guild possessed.

Guild Exterminate the Heavens had 1024 players. For a normal guild, it was quite good. As long as the guild storage system began to circulate, the guild would gradually grow. These types of guilds could indirectly become branches of the Club guilds. The Clubs obviously wouldn’t throw money to build up their guild storage. They just needed to make sure that the guild didn’t fall apart and the guild would naturally grow larger and stronger.

As a normal guild, this sort of business wasn’t something normal players would know about. As their gaming lives progressed, they would unknowingly grow alongside the guild.

After Ye Xiu sent in an application, he pondered over his plan, while waiting for the reply to come.

The reason he had confidence in being accepted was very simple. Normal guilds didn’t have players lining up to join them like the Club guilds did. Normal guilds just added whoever wanted to join them. They might as well add you for now. Besides, Ye Xiu wrote a note when he applied. It was only three words, but these words were very eye-catching.

The three words were: I’m a tank.

Yes, a tank.

Most teams were centered around the tank. It could even be said that the number of teams were restricted to the number of tanks. If a team didn’t have a tank, the team could only go and kill wild monsters. Dungeons and bossing would best be kept as dreams.

Tanks were also high-end classes and difficult to play. Despite being the core of a team, not many people liked to play them. Thus, for most guilds, the words “I’m a tank” was very desirable.

Sure enough, not long after Ye Xiu sent in an application, the guild added him. Someone in the guild greeted him: Welcome, friend.

Ye Xiu looked at the ID: Clove. This player was most likely a girl.

After sending a “Thanks :)”, Ye Xiu opened up the guild player list and skimmed through it. He also saw that the guild leader Senior Exterminate the Heavens was also online.

“Oh? A new member?” Senior Exterminate the Heavens finally spoke.

“Hi guild leader.” Ye Xiu typed. Chen Guo snorted: “So you’re acting polite?”

“Hey!” Ye Xiu said seriously. Then, he saw a bunch of people speak up in the guild chat. The majority of them were just lurking around. There might not be too many people online in a thousand player guild, but there were enough. The chat kept flashing as messages kept on being typed. The guild was quite active.

“Woah, a Knight too! Are you a tank?” Someone saw the new member’s class and shouted it out. Sure enough, the word tank was quite eye-catching. Knights were mainly played as tanks, but they didn’t necessarily need to be. There were quite a few players who used Knights as DPS classes. Of course, more players were interested in PvP. Knights had high defense and health, making them quite a formidable PvP class.

“Yeah, I’m a tank.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? A tank?” The guild leader clearly hadn’t seen Ye Xiu’s guild application, so he hadn’t seen the note. When he heard the new member was a tank, he was very happy.

“What are your stats?” Exterminate the Heavens asked.

‘Stamina 750, Strength 520, Intelligence 414, Spirit 405.” Ye Xiu reported.

The chat suddenly fell silent. After a while, someone couldn’t help but comment: “So weak!”

Knights grew in a balanced manner similar to unspecialized characters. However, tanks naturally chose their equipment in a certain way. Stamina and health were their priorities. The rest would be switched out depending on the situation. Stacking strength would increase their physical resistance. Stacking intelligence, on the other hand, would their increase magic resistance. Stacking spirit would increase debuff resistances. Different equipment could be used against different opponents.

However, the stats Ye Xiu reported didn’t even pass as average. High-end tanks usually had over 1000 Stamina. The passing line for normal Knights was 840 Stamina. Ye Xiu was lower than the normal Knight passing line by 90 Stamina. In terms of stats, he was a legendary squishy tank.

“What are your equipments? Let me take a look at them.” The guild leader Exterminate the Heavens sent a sweating emoji.

“I haven’t played in a long time, so my equips aren’t that good.” Ye Xiu said. He let them have a look at his equipment. The guild veterans looked and sure enough, they were all outdated pieces of equipment. Nowadays, it wasn’t difficult to reach the passing line. After all, tanks played a special role and their equipment wasn’t too expensive.

“How skilled are you?” Exterminate the Heavens asked.

“Look at my name.” Ye Xiu proudly replied.

“Ha…..” Chen Guo laughed.

“Unrivalled Super Hottie…..” Ye Xiu’s name made everyone go speechless. Even Senior Exterminate the Heavens felt defeated. After a long period of silence, he coughed: “Clove, make a team tonight and bring this brother out to get some equipment!”

Clove was the one who had added Ye Xiu into the guild. She clearly had a fairly high position to have that sort of authority. Senior Exterminate the Heavens meant that you’re responsible for the person you added!

Clove didn’t object and replied with an “Okay.” Then, Ye Xiu received a friend request from Clove. He accepted and then received a message from Clove:” When are you free tonight?”

“I’m free anytime.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then is 7 okay?”

“Sure.”

“I’ll message you at 7 then.” Clove said.

“Sounds good. What dungeon will we be running tonight?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We’ll be running Bone Dragon Abyss. The weapons and shields that from there are very suitable for you. The dungeon isn’t too difficult either. Will there be any problems?” Clove said.

“No, I was just asking. I’m going to go take a look at a guide.” Ye Xiu said.

“......” Clove was speechless.

“See you tonight.” Ye Xiu politely replied.

Afterwards, the guild went quiet. The guild members were probably gossipping about Unrivalled Super Hottie. After Ye Xiu joined the guild, he didn’t have much else to do, so he went to a Knight instructor. He reset his skill points and re-allocated them.

A skill reset wasn’t free. The more times you used a skill reset, the more expensive it became. Besides, times when one made a huge mistake and needed to make a big fix, most players would wait until it was time for the game company to announce a special event for skill resets. Any other time, the players would just endure. Who would do a skill reset over a single error?

At 7PM, Ye Xiu finished eating and logged onto Unrivalled Super Hottie. Chen Guo didn’t want to miss it and was ready to watch him play.

As soon as he got on, Clove immediately messaged him: “You came!”

“Yes, I’m here.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Come to Kansas City!” We’ll go together.” Clove typed.

Ye Xiu teleported to Kansas City. This was a Level 70 city. Whether it was a map or a city, the place wouldn’t be as empty as a Level 55 place. One could fully experience the gathering place for all Glory players. No server could compare to the liveliness of a Level 70 area in the Heavenly Domain.

At the north gate of Kansas City, Ye Xiu saw Clove. She was a female Cleric. Around her were nine players with the tag “Guild Exterminate the Heavens”. Bone Dragon Abyss was a ten player dungeon. They had been waiting for Ye Xiu to arrive.

Ye Xiu hastily had Unrivalled Super Hottie run over and turned on his guild tag. When he walked closer, he immediately asked: “Huh? Why is there another Knight? If an equipment comes out, it won’t be easy to split!”

Chapter 550 – You Can Just Be a Leecher

Ye Xiu’s question was normal. When they grouped up for a dungeon, under the given conditions, they would normally spread out the classes This would prevent conflicts between players of the same class when they found a piece of equipment they needed. Many groups experienced great storms and disbanded because of this very reason. It was a problem that had to be considered seriously.

In response to Ye Xiu’s question, someone humphed. “Bro, have you looked at my equipment? Would I want anything that drops from this dungeon?”

When he heard this, it was obvious that the voice belonged to the Knight and pride filled his voice. He obviously felt disdain towards Ye Xiu, a useless tank whose Vitality was only at 750.

Clove also explained at once. “I called Crispy Bean over to help. He’s our guild’s chief tank. 950 Vitality. Physical and magic defense, Intelligence and Strength are all over 760 too. He also has 700 Spirit.”

“If you were going to ask for help, why would you find a tank? There’s me for a tank, right? Wouldn’t it be better to find more DPS classes?” Ye Xiu asked.

Clove felt uncomfortable the moment she heard his question. She originally didn’t intend to find a tank to help, but she felt uneasy when Ye Xiu went to search for a guide for Bone Dragon Abyss this afternoon. A tank couldn’t simply take on the leadership role just by looking at a guide. Driven by responsibility over the whole group, Clove couldn’t entrust the whole group’s life and death onto this tank who reads guides at the last minute. This explained why she specifically found a tank from the guild to help. She didn’t expect Unrivaled Super Hottie was unable to tell good from bad.

Whatever…… All noobs are like this…...

Clove thought this way, but she didn’t want to waste words on Ye Xiu. She gathered everyone to start going into the dungeon. The tank called Crispy Bean wasn’t happy though. “Oh wow, you’re very capable, huh? To be honest, I’m not interested in this small dungeon at all. It’s a total waste of my time! Since I’m not needed, then I shall take my leave.”

“If you leave, we’d be missing a person.” Ye Xiu said.

“What, scared now?” Crispy Bean laughed coolly.

“It’s not possible for you to only have tank equipment, so if you just changed to your damage-oriented equipment, wouldn’t that work?” Ye Xiu asked.

“You… If I become a DPS class, would you be able to hold it?” Crispy Bean was immediately angered. As the chief tank of the guild, of course it would be impossible for him to lack equipment. Apart from tank equipment, he also had a strong collection of combat equipments for a Knight. If he really switched to damage-oriented equipment, he was absolutely confident that he would be able to squeeze into the top ten of Guild Exterminate the Heavens. To be honest, he was looking forward for a chance to present his ability in damage output.

“You can try.” Ye Xiu actually gave him a chance.

“Very well! You said it yourself! Don’t blame me if we get wiped!” Crispy Bean’s last sentence was aimed towards the crowd surrounding him. A flash on his character followed his statement and it became evident that he already changed into his damage-oriented equipment.

“That's enough, stop fooling around!” Clove suddenly yelled out. “Crispy Bean, you’re still the tank.”

As Clove spoke, she also sent a private message to Ye Xiu. “What’s up with you! Everyone grouped up to help you get equipment. This person has no reason to take your equipment. All you have to do is be a leecher. What is there to be unsatisfactory about?”

Ye Xiu saw that this girl even communicated with him through private message, and that she was concerned about everyone’s feelings. Ye Xiu didn’t continue to say anything else. In Crispy Bean’s case, it was obvious that he didn’t obey only because of Clove’s previous yell. Ye Xiu reckoned that Clove also messaged him in private. He soon changed back into his tank equipment. His view scanned over Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie and stepped into the dungeon after giving a cold harrumph.

Other players closely followed after him into the dungeon. Ye Xiu commanded Unrivaled Super Hottie to follow.

Chen Guo wasn’t far away from her game. She looked as if she were watching a movie. When she saw that Ye Xiu had started a conflict the moment he joined the group, she immediately felt that a good show would happen tonight.

“You really are unbelievable.” Chen Guo lamented.

“I’m only speaking of the truth!” Ye Xiu spoke.

Chen Guo deeply agreed with this. Everything Ye Xiu said could drive a person crazy, but it was true. Chen Guo also believed Ye Xiu’s words. Even though 750 Vitality was a little low, who was he? This chief tank of Exterminate the Heavens or whatever guild dared to challenge God Ye Qiu? Chen Guo found it humorous just to think about it. Bone Dragon Abyss itself wasn’t a difficult dungeon. In terms of tanks, a tank didn’t need to have 840 Vitality. The requirement line for 840 was expected of tanks themselves to enter more difficult group dungeons. A mere dungeon with only ten people wouldn’t even be necessary.

What’s more, with God Ye Qiu’s skills, who knew how much those skills could make up for in stats. As an onlooker, she only pitied that she had to watch things unfold from the sidelines.

It should be known that a tank had a busy role. If a professional player like Ye Xiu played one, she didn’t know how fast the screen would move around, though it wouldn’t be the first time she experienced it.

A moment after, the ten people of Guild Exterminate the Heavens was transported into Bone Dragon Abyss.

Bone Dragon Abyss sat in a canyon. According to Glory’s naming style, this canyon was named as Bone Dragon Abyss. The wild boss, dungeon’s final boss, and hidden boss were all bone dragons. According to the background storyline, these three bone dragons were actually brothers…...

Of course, that was when they had been alive, and now that they had become bone dragons, It was evident enough that they had already become imperishable organisms.

Crispy Bean was Exterminate the Heaven’s chief tank, so it could be said that he had gone through all of the dungeons in Glory. With Guild Exterminate the Heavens’s strength, they might have some difficulties in completing difficult dungeons that required a group of 100 people. However, a dungeon with ten people like this was nothing to Crispy Bean.

This explained why the moment he entered the dungeon, he immediately rushed up to steamroll through the monsters. In his eyes, these dungeons only played the part of being thoroughly crushed. Ye Xiu was one of the last of the ten-man team to enter the dungeon. By the time he was transported into the dungeon, the fight had already heated up at the front. A tank normally led the team in the dungeon. However, this was a dungeon that Crispy Bean looked down on, so why would he need to be the leader? Of course it wasn’t needed! All he needed to do was cheer everyone on while they hurried to keep up with his pace.

As a result, the whole group was more or less busy and messy. Ye Xiu was able to spot that at first glance. Crispy Bean was undoubtedly a veteran and Clove wasn’t bad, but several other people in the group had showed themselves to be a little unaccustomed.

They weren’t unaccustomed to the mechanics of the game, but towards the dungeon.

To be able to make it into Heavenly Domain and complete the Heavenly Domain’s Challenge, meant that they wouldn’t have any trouble or unfamiliarities with their mechanical performance. However, when faced with a foreign dungeon, they would obviously be at loss at what to do orwhere to strike.

There were beginners in the Heavenly Domain. Those who had just cleared the Heavenly Domain Challenge would be considered beginners.

There were only two people like this in the tenth server.

But how about the other servers?

Not all players that reached the minimum required level could complete the Heavenly Domain’s challenge on their first try. Ye Xiu and Qiao Yifan were exceptions. They were pro gamers and had skill to back them up, so they could pass the challenge at the mere levels of 50 or 55.

However, towards normal players, the challenge task was most definitely not that simple.

After reaching the minimum required level, a lot of people had to spend a certain amount of time to acquire stronger pieces of equipment. Using strong equipment to face quests and a lot of combat consumables could help in completing in the challenge. Moreover, the PVP Arena could be counted as the easiest part for Ye Xiu and Qiao Yifan. However, it wasn’t so easy for normal players.

When fighting a boss, there was a regular pattern to find, but there was never a fixed pattern in PvP. In particular, the requirement to win consecutively was extremely fatal for normal players.

As a result, newer servers like the eighth or ninth server had a lot of people who had reached Level 70, but had yet to pass the challenge to enter the Heavenly Domain.

On top of this, people didn’t necessarily start from the tenth server. Actually, if a player would like to enter the Heavenly Domain as soon as possible, an older server would be a better choice. There would be high-leveled players to powerlevel your character. The speed in which one could level up would be a lot faster in comparison to those in the new server.

Therefore, there was a constant stream of players entering the Heavenly Domain. Ye Xiu reckoned that the other eight people belonged to this group of players. At the very least least, they hadn’t entered the Bone Dragon Abyss dungeon before. This group wasn’t exactly organized just to assist him in getting better equipments, Clove also grouped up the people so they could come and try Bone Dragon Abyss.

How could a group like this work without a leader? Crispy Bean didn’t care about it, so only Clove could attempt to take charge. However, it was super inconvenient when she had to instruct Ye Xiu.

The reason being the name of Ye Xiu’s Knight.

Unrivaled Super Hottie.

What was she supposed to call him?

If she called him by the full name, it would take too long and be a waste of time.

Call him Unrivaled? Super? Hottie? Clove found it hard to call out any of the words broken apart. She wanted to puke just thinking about how shameless a person had to be to come up with such a name.

In the end, Clove called Ye Xiu “you”. She called the names of everyone else, except when she reached Ye Xiu, she would say “you, you, you” so on and so forth.

After having gone through a little bit of confusion in the beginning of the dungeon, everything finally started to stabilise under Clove’s commands. She was in the Heavenly Domain, so her foundation was already there. Dungeons were pretty much the same. Basic problems, like what to be aware of, was the same in every dungeon. These people obviously wouldn’t make any noob mistakes. There wouldn’t be any major problems if they obeyed the leader.

The group continued killing as Crispy Bean gradually started to talk more, but he was mostly complaining. He was obviously very dissatisfied about their progression speed. In the end, he even cleared his throat and told everyone to do their best to focus on their damage output and not to worry about aggro going off the tank.

Finally, the group reached the first boss. Before they fought the boss, they made some slight adjustments. When Crispy Bean opened up the damage output list, he mercilessly sent it into the group chat at once.

Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie was ranked second to last, just above Clove, who was responsible for the healing.

“You really are a talent!” Crispy Bean taunted.

“Not really. I’m earnestly leeching.” Ye Xiu replied.

Chapter 551 – Proof of Strength

His teammates hadn’t responded yet, but Chen Guo already looked like she was about to cough blood. When she saw the team’s attitude towards Ye Xiu, she was looking forward to the following show! For example, if Ye Xiu didn’t have the tank deal damage, the tank, Crispy Bean, wouldn’t be able to hold the boss and the boss would go out of control. Chen Guo believed Ye Xiu had the ability to make this happen.

But the more she watched, the more doubtful she became. As Ye Xiu controlled his character, he didn’t even touch his keyboard. His left hand only moved to walk, attack, or activate a skill. Otherwise it……rested on the table. Only his right hand moved sometimes. His headphones hung over his neck, sending out noise through the speakers.

“Is he planning on messing up the aggro by playing like a noob?”

Chen Guo originally had faith in this God’s ability, so she continued to patiently watch him play, but the tank Crispy Bean never lost control over the aggro. Chen Guo thought about it. Crispy Bean wasn’t a bad tank and small monsters died relatively quickly, so perhaps there wasn’t enough time to deal enough damage to pull the aggro. If you just went up ahead of the tank and pulled the monster, it would be too obvious. The team would see through your ploy instantly.

Thus, Chen Guo felt like Ye Xiu would show off his godly might when the boss came. However, the first boss went by and only one sentence resulted from it.

“I’m just leeching.”

When Ye Xiu said this sentence, he wasn’t even sitting up straight. His head wasn’t even supported by the back of his chair, and it looked like it would fall off. His mouse clicked a few times as he spoke indifferently.

“What’s wrong with you!” Clover wasn’t happy. Even though she had told him it would be okay to just leech off them, she never thought that he would actually leech. The Heavenly Domain didn’t have noobs. Let alone Clover, the other eight team members could tell just from the numbers from the damage chart that he was leeching.

The ninth place character was only a third of the eighth place character in the damage chart.

Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t have good equipment, but everyone else besides Crispy Bean had low tier equipment as well. In fact, their equipment was of the same tier as Unrivaled Super Hottie’s. Although Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment was meant for a tank, his DPS shouldn’t be a third of the next lowest player’s DPS.

Crispy Bean listened and turned around to look at Unrivaled Super Hottie. He looked as if he had just heard a joke: “What? You’re that petty? Do you really think you leeching will make things difficult for us? How conceited of you! Let me tell you something. With your attitude, even if a Knight equipment drops, you don’t have the qualification to pick it up. Donating it to the guild storage would be more useful than giving it to you!”

“Crispy Bean!” Clove shouted. She clearly felt like Crispy Bean had gone too far, “I don’t think he has those sort of thoughts. If he really wanted to grief, there are lots of better ways to do so. He could just run around randomly and pull a bunch of monsters over, but that’s not what he’s doing. All of you know I’m the leader. He……” When Clover said “he”, she suddenly paused. She originally wanted to say that Unrivaled Super Hottie was following orders and hadn’t made any mistakes, but right when she was about to say it, she suddenly realized, had she even given any instructions to Unrivaled Super Hottie?

She decided to call him “you” after thinking about how to address him, but she had never said “you” besides in the small argument from before.

If she hadn’t given him any orders, then it meant he didn’t need any orders. On the other hand, Clover had been correcting the others the entire time. She only realized this now.

Crispy Bean misunderstood her pause though. He thought Clover had realized Unrivaled Super Hottie had attempted something harmful, but then again, as an outstanding tank, if someone had intentionally tried griefing, he would have definitely known about it. Thinking about this, Crispy Bean spoke: “Isn’t it too obvious if he does it that way? If some sort of hidden opportunity appears, do you think he won’t take advantage of it?”

“He won’t.” Clover said with certainty. She seemed to have discovered something after looking back.

Clover’s confident tone surprised Crispy Bean. For Clover to have asked him for help indicated that their relationship was quite good. Crispy Bean didn’t want to have a dispute with Clover, but he was still very angry with this extremely arrogant guy, so he said: “Fine! Then I won’t say anything, but tell him to stop leeching. If he wants equipment, he has to have the skill to earn it.”

Crispy Bean’s disdain could be heard through his voice. He emphasized the words “leeching” and “skill” in a mocking tone.

“Can you play more seriously? Don’t leech anymore.” Clover helplessly told Ye Xiu. Crispy Bean’s words made sense. For a dungeon run by a guild team, the equipment would usually be split among the team members. When a desirable equipment dropped, there would usually be rules to decide who earned it. Ye Xiu’s leeching would clearly eliminate him from contention.

“Okay.”

The other side had said so many words, but Ye Xiu simply said a single word. He looked like he was about to fall asleep.

He sat up, moved his left hand back to the keyboard, and adjusted his mouse.

Chen Guo was sitting beside him, so she heard the entire conversation. She thought Ye Xiu was about to show these people his might, but all he said was a dull “Okay.” Just like the previous “earnestly leeching”, Chen Guo felt very disappointed once again. Unsatisfied, she spoke her thoughts: “What a letdown.”

“Hm?” Ye Xu turned his head to look at her.

“How can you stand such disdain? You actually leeched off of them? Attack! Grief them!” Chen Guo just wanted to see these guys lose control over the boss and turn the place into a horror scene.

“How boring! If you were playing and the team gave you the chance to leech, would you play seriously?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course! How else can you prove your strength?” Chen Guo said.

“Prove my strength?” Ye Xiu mumbled. He took a worn out piece of paper out of his pocket and threw it at Chen Guo.

“What are you doing?” Chen Guo thought that Ye Xiu had thrown some trash at her.

“Strength.” Ye Xiu pointed at the worn out piece of paper.

Chen Guo uncrumpled it. It said: Glory Pro Alliance Season 3 MVP: Ye Qiu.

This worn out piece of paper was actually a Glory Pro Alliance MVP award certificate. Most people would hang it on a wall and frame it in a conspicuous place, but Ye Xiu had crumpled it up so much, that it looked like a piece of trash.

“You’re so annoying!!!” Chen Guo was mad! She threw the paper back at Ye Xiu, who grabbed it and put it back into his pocket.

She understood what Ye Xiu meant. This piece of paper was enough to prove Ye Xiu’s strength, or perhaps it was to say that he didn’t need to prove his strength. He didn’t need to go all out to prove his existence. He was perfectly content with others calling him a leech.

But now, the others didn’t want him to, so Ye Xiu had to at least put some effort in. However, Chen Guo doubted that he would actually play seriously because if he actually played seriously, the team’s only choice would be to have him be main tank.

“Is everybody ready? If everyone is ready, I’m going to pull the boss.” Crispy Bean asked the team. After hearing everyone’s reply, he charged at the boss.

At the same time, a figure flashed beside him. Crispy Bean turned his head and looked. It was that disgusting name again: Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“What are you doing!?” Crispy Bean shouted. He thought this guy was actually going to grief them.

Chen Guo was getting excited. Was Ye Xiu going to steal the tank position? Ha ha, witness the power of a God! Crispy Bean or whatever, get the hell out of here! It doesn’t feel good to have someone with a name like that be a tank! Crispy Bean? Do bosses roast you to a crisp?

“Damage!” Ye Xiu casually said.

‘Wait until the tank is pulled before attacking. Don’t you understand?” Crispy Bean roared. Not just Crispy Bean, but the others were furious too. Everyone knew that for a boss fight, the tank should be given some time to establish aggro before attacking.

“What? Am I in front of you?” Ye Xiu shook his head.

Crispy Bean turned his head back. He saw Bone Abyss’s boss Guardian Kaiwei raise his humongous axe and charge forward.

The aggro was still on Crispy Bean, but this was because Crispy Bean had walked into Guardian Kaiwei’s aggro range. If Unrivaled Super Hottie attacked, the aggro would transfer to him.

Thinking of this, Crispy Bean immediately attacked!

Almost at the same time, Unrivaled Super Hottie also attacked Guardian Kaiwei.

“KICK HIM OUT OF THE TEAM!!” Crispy Bean yelled at Clover.

Clover clearly suspected Unrivaled Super Hottie’s actions too. She had already opened up the team interface, when she heard him say helplessly: “What are you yelling for? Isn’t the aggro still on you?”

Chapter 552 – Controlling Aggro Through Damage

Boss aggro?

At this moment and time, Crispy Bean had completely forgotten about it because he had also been aggroed by Unrivaled Super Hottie.

He suddenly woke up after hearing his argument. When he took a closer look, he realized Guardian Kaiwei’s aggro was still on him. Guardian Kaiwei’s huge axe hadn’t turned towards Unrivaled Super Hottie despite his attack! The huge axe was still swinging towards Crispy Bean.

Bang!

He immediately raised the shield in his hands. It was a frequently used movement for tanks. The huge axe collided with Crispy Bean’s shield.

The attack clearly wasn’t anything earthshaking. Crispy Bean’s equipment far surpassed the necessary threshold for this dungeon. He didn’t budge a single inch when he blocked the blow. Almost at the same time, he swung his sword and slashed at Guardian Kaiwei. Almost at the same time as him, Crispy Bean also saw Unrivaled Super Hottie swing his shield at Guardian Kaiwei’s head.

Shield Attack!

This skill could induce a Dizzying effect, but all bosses had high resistances to status effects. Bosses couldn’t be controlled by players so easily, otherwise they would be too easy to beat. Guardian Kaiwei was a dragon guardian and natural had immunity to magic status effects. However, the Guardian did not have complete immunity to physical skills like Shield Attack. After taking the Shield Attack, the Guardian’s eyes went blurry and he became Dizzy.

But for bosses, status effects wouldn’t last long. Crispy Bean had to face the boss directly as the tank, so he knew the boss’s stats, skills, resistances, and patterns very clearly. He also had a good understanding of his own Knight class, so he immediately calculated that with Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Strength stat, the Dizzy effect would only last for one second maximum.

However, at the same time, a lot of things happened during this one second window.

Crispy Bean took advantage of this one second window.

Previously, his mind had wandered away because of his enmity towards Unrivaled Super Hottie. After blocking with his shield and striking back, he wasn’t sure what to do next.

This one second window gave Crispy Bean enough time to figure out his next moves. If he didn’t have this one second, he would have been hit by Guardian Kaiwei’s counterattack.

This was only the first mini-boss in the dungeon. Crispy Bean had exceptional equipment too, so eating the counterattack wouldn’t have been the end of the world, but what if this had been a difficult dungeon? What if it was a boss with extremely hard-hitting attacks? One second of rest was especially important.

Even though this one second was insignificant in this case, it gave him time to recover.

One second passed by quickly. After recollecting his thoughts, Crispy Bean began pulling aggro like his usual self. Crispy Bean hadn’t noticed the importance of the one second though. He was even a bit angry at Unrivaled Super Hottie for his Shield Attack because of the same reason as before: he had yet to establish the boss’s aggro. Was this guy trying to kill himself by attacking the boss?

This guy didn’t know how to exercise constraint. Right now, he was actually fighting over the boss with Crispy Bean. The two were attacking Guardian Kaiwei at nearly the same time.

The others hadn’t moved yet. Teams usually waited for the tank to tell them to attack before attacking. Clover healed him from time to time. The healing wasn’t done immediately. After all, healing could also aggro the boss. If she healed him immediately, she might accidentally steal the boss’s aggro away from the tank.

Unrivaled Super Hottie…...

Clover already had the team interface out with her mouse hovering over his name. She was just about to kick him out of the team.

Then, she heard him say “Isn’t the aggro still on you?”, which made her hesitate.

If the aggro control hadn’t been messed up, then there was no need to kick him out of the team. Clover felt like she should teach the new member of the guild rules. She didn’t need to be so strict.

During her moment of hesitation, the two had gone back and forth attacking the Guardian Kaiwei several times already.

Everyone was watching in shock, including Crispy Bean.

Flustered and exasperated, he shouted “Kick him out of the team!” twice. Clover didn’t move though. She simply replied: “Good aggro control!”

Crispy Bean really wanted to shout, “He could steal away the boss’s aggro at any moment!” But he resisted. For a tank, especially the top tank in a guild with exceptional equipment, he felt too ashamed to say such words.

Both people were tanks. His equipment was better and the aggro was still on him. Why did he need to worry about a squishy tank stealing away the aggro?

Crispy Bean felt a bit regretful. He felt like he had lost too much face. Those “Kick him out of the team!” shouts were mostly done in anger at Unrivaled Super Hottie’s actions, but what if the others misunderstood it as being unable to manage the aggro? Wasn’t that what Clover’s reply meant?

He definitely didn’t want to be misunderstood!

Crispy Bean shouted inwardly. He didn’t want to think about whether or not his “Kick him out of the team!” shouts had shown his fear of losing control of the boss.

“You want to steal the boss’s aggro from me? That won’t be possible!” Finally ,Crispy Bean shouted at Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“Senior, I’m DPSing. I’ll control the aggro well.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

DPSing?

Control the aggro?

These words made everyone’s hearts thump.

If he could completely control the boss’s aggro when he was attacking, directly going up to attack the boss wasn’t an issue as long as he had the confidence that he wouldn’t mess up.

Did this squishy tank actually have that type of control?

In Glory, damage, healing, and taking damage could all be calculated. However, aggro couldn’t. This completely depended on a player’s intuition and experience. As a result, they didn’t know how well Unrivaled Super Hottie was controlling his aggro. They only saw him attacking immediately after Crispy Bean. Every time he did it, everyone’s hearts would jump. They felt like any one of his attacks could make the boss go out of control.

“Unrivaled Super Hottie, how about you wait before DPSing?” Clover finally spoke. And for the first time, she shouted out his shameless name.

“No need!” Crispy Bean replied to her. Crispy Bean had entered a full on competitive mode. As the main tank with exceptional equipment, it would be a disgrace to lose control of the aggro to this guy. Even telling others his worries over the situation would be shameful. Right now, Crispy Bean was determined to show off his ability as a tank.

“Yeah, there’s no need. I’ll control it well. I won’t snatch the aggro from you.” Ye Xiu also replied.

“You just try and snatch it from me.” Crispy Bean said. His hands moved like a blur. If he had been taking it easy in the beginning, he was completely serious now.

“Snatch it snatch it snatch it.” Chen Guo urged Ye Xiu. She really wanted to see this type of situation.

“Little kid.” Ye Xiu gave Chen Guo a disdainful look. He ignored her and continued to control his damage output.

After a short moment, Ye Xiu asked: “Why isn’t anyone else coming up? How long do you need to establish aggro before it’s stable?”

Crispy Bean heard this and furrowed his brow. He had been too focused and had forgotten about it. If the tank didn’t say anything, the others wouldn’t dare to attack! He hadn’t said anything, which actually resulted in this squishy tank questioning his ability.

“I forgot.” Crispy Bean explained. It was true, but it sounded bad. Clover heard him speak and, not waiting for Crispy Bean to give the order, she immediately ordered: “Everybody, advance.”

The field became a beautiful sight to behold.

Guardian Kaiwei was only a mini boss. The Guardian only had powerful single target attacks. He didn’t have any strong AoE skills, so with the aggro being controlled well, everyone could safely attack.

How could Crispy Bean be careless? He was afraid the aggro would shift onto Unrivaled Super Hottie. He was taking this originally easy dungeon more seriously than a hundred player team dungeon.

Under everyone’s attacks, Guardian Kaiwei’s health rapidly dropped until it fell.

The Guardian dropped an equip. Clover went up to look. It was a Dragon Guardian Axe.

This weapon could be used by Priest classes: Clerics, Paladins, Exorcists, or Knights. There were currently three Priest classes in the team: Crispy Bean, Unrivaled Super Hottie, and Clover.

Clerics could also use axes, but because Clerics prioritized Intelligence, physical attack weapons like axes didn’t suit them. Crispy Bean already had equipment that surpassed equipment that could be found in this dungeon, so he didn’t need this Dragon Guardian Axe. It looked like Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie was the only choice.

However, as a guild team, there were other options too. For example, the team could choose to donate the equip to the guild storage and then split the guild contribution points later. Another choice was to sell the item for money and then split the money…...

For a team specifically meant to get equipment for Unrivaled Super Hottie, under normal circumstances, no one would object to Clover giving the Dragon Guardian Axe to Unrivaled Super Hottie. However, there was a lot of controversy surrounding this guy. Someone with a leech-like performance was going to be the first to get equipment? Would the others be unhappy with it?

Clover was still hesitating. The others were already asking what she got. Clover showed everyone the Dragon Guardian Axe to see. The suitable classes for it made many disappointed. In the end, that Unrivaled Super Hottie laughed out loud: “Ha ha! It’s mine. Thanks everyone!”

“Do you feel no shame?” Sure enough, Crispy Bean had the same thoughts as Clover, except he spoke his feelings without any hesitation.

“What? You want it too? If you want it, you can have it. Tanks get priority!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why the f*ck would I want this?” Crispy Bean was about to go insane.

Chapter 553 – Damage Output Competition

Crispy Bean didn’t care about any of the equipment that dropped from Bone Dragon Abyss. Just now, this Unrivaled Super Hottie actually thought he wanted to compete for the axe. It made him feel like he was being looked down upon.

“What? You don’t want it? If you don’t want it, then who else would want it?” Ye Xiu asked.

Clover really felt worried! Did this guy really not know the rules, or was he pretending not to know? She didn’t want to say it in public, so she privately messaged Unrivaled Super Hottie: “I told you you could leech and the first equipment that dropped can be used by you, but how am I supposed to give it to you like this?”

“Oh. Don’t worry. I’ll just use it temporarily. Once I get out of the dungeon, I can give it to you. I’m a tank, so why would I need this weapon, but wouldn’t it be better to temporarily use it to raise my DPS?” Ye Xiu replied.

Clover was surprised. She hadn’t thought he would reply in such a way. When an equipment was given to someone, the system would notify those in the team, so she had to say a few words before giving it out. Clover told the rest she would give Unrivaled Super Hottie the axe temporarily. After explaining the reason, she handed the Dragon Guardian Axe to Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Shua!

Ye Xiu immediately switched his Knight sword and shield with the Dragon Guardian Axe. This axe was a dual handed weapon, so he wouldn’t be able to equip both the shield and the axe.

The Dragon Guardian Axe wasn’t anything unique. It was just big and the two blood-red streaks on the two sides of the axe made it quite eye-catching. Right now, it looked very powerful in Unrivaled Super Hottie’s hands. The other players looked at him in envy. Crispy Bean glanced at him and then continued to pull monsters.

The dungeon battle continued. Unrivaled Super Hottie, with his new Dragon Guardian Axe, was no longer leeching. He was on the front lines killing monsters.

Clover, as the rear support, paid more attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie and realized that he didn’t need any instruction from her. His coordination with the rest of the team was solid. When she checked the total damage charts, she jumped in fright.

Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie was still in ninth place, his numbers had increased greatly. Before, he had only been a third of the player in the eighth position, but now, he was already two thirds. And during this time, they had only killed the first boss and cleared three waves of monsters.

Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie had switched his equipment, it shouldn’t have been able to make him increase his damage by so much. Thus, most of the damage must have been from attacking the first boss. The boss’s health was equivalent to several waves of monsters.

However, at that time, Unrivaled Super Hottie was only wearing his original equipment. He didn’t have any advantage over the other players on the team, but for him to be able to catch up so quickly! What skill! His ability to output damage must mean his skill level wasn’t ordinary!

After Clover noted this point, she paid more attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie. With his Dragon Guardian Axe, the current Unrivaled Super Hottie had already caught the eye of the other team members. When Clover looked at the damage charts, she saw that Unrivaled Super Hottie was rapidly rising in the ranking, nearing the player in eighth place.

Once he caught up to eighth place, he wouldn’t be too different from everyone else. The other seven players were all around the same skill level. Even though there were differences, the differences weren’t large. The player in first place was Crispy Bean, the tank. After all, he had the equipment advantage and the tank’s attack couldn’t be too low. Damage was a huge factor in calculating aggro. Only by relying on aggro-inducing skills wouldn’t be able to provide stable control over the monster.

“This person isn’t simple!”

Clover finally concluded. Not just her, but the other players also noticed this. The players, who liked to check the damage charts, saw his huge rise upwards. Even though he had just gotten the Dragon Guardian Axe, it was only a slight advantage. Everyone’s equipment had Level 70 requirements. There couldn’t be a heaven and earth difference between the weapons. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s rise couldn’t be brought about solely because of the weapon.

Everyone else began to raise their damage output. Even though the enemies were NPCs in PvE, players liked competing with other players. The competition in PvE was only slightly different than competition in PvP. PvP was a battle between players, while PvE was a battle of numbers.

The players in the team had started a numbers battle over damage output. No one wanted to lag behind. With the start of this competition, their battle strength soared and they advanced through the dungeon even faster. In the blink of an eye, they reached the second boss in Bone Dragon Abyss.

It was the same as the first boss. Crispy Bean went forward to pull the boss and Unrivaled Super Hottie went forward with him. Crispy Bean already had no more words to say to him, but Unrivaled Super Hottie had already proved that he didn’t have any intention of causing trouble. The first boss battle also proved his ability to control aggro. He wouldn’t be an obstruction to the main tank.

Crispy Bean remained silent and just hit the boss. However, he also paid attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s fighting method. He realized Unrivaled Super Hottie was fighting slightly differently than when he fought the first boss.

The other seven DPS players were very worried. When they reached this boss, Unrivaled Super Hottie caught up from his one third damage deficit. Even though he was still in ninth place, he was very close to the others. He had rushed forward to start putting out damage, but the others could only watch helplessly. If this kept going, wouldn’t they just be watching his damage surpassed their damage?

However, the tank hadn’t said anything yet, so they didn’t dare to move. Unrivaled Super Hottie dared to fight alongside the tank without the tank losing aggro, but they didn’t have the ability to do that. They thought it was probably because he played as a tank and knew the Knight class well, so he had a good grasp over managing aggro. Normal players could also manage aggro, but not as precisely as he could.

The seven others could only watch in helplessness. Having not heard Crispy Bean say anything in a long time, they were starting to look down on him. It’s been so long and he still hasn’t established the aggro?

It had only been five seconds since Crispy Bean had pulled the boss. However, for the seven other players, those five seconds felt like eternity.

Finally, everyone heard Crispy Bean shout “Everyone, up!” The seven impatient players immediately pounced on the boss like tigers and went all out. One of the brothers had charged forward too ferociously and crashed into Crispy Bean. Teammates couldn’t do damage to each other, but it could still mess up his positioning.

The crash had caused Crispy Bean to shift slightly, resulting in his shield failing to block the second boss’s attack.

“What are you doing!?” Crispy Bean roared.

This normal player didn’t have the courage to shout back at the tank. He hastily whimpered “Sorry.” He moved two steps back and then started putting out damage. If he didn’t, he would fall behind.

Their fierce attacks caused blood to constantly spurt from the boss. With a strong tank, the boss battle wasn’t anything difficult. The second boss quickly fell. No one cared about the drops. They immediately pulled up the damage charts.

F*ck! With just one boss, Unrivaled Super Hottie shot past the other seven players. In addition, compared to the slight differences between the seven, the second place Unrivaled Super Hottie was far ahead of them now. He had even shrunken the distance between the player in first, who had a huge advantage in equipment.

“Too amazing!”

The others could only admit their defeat. In the beginning, he had just been leeching, but as soon as he stopped leeching, his damage output immediately soared. In addition to his weapon advantage, they couldn’t compete anymore!

At this moment, Clover picked up the equipment and showed it to everyone. Everyone immediately began murmuring.

Angry Dragon Sword!

It was a Level 70 Greatsword, which Berserkers or Blade Masters could use. In the team, there was a Berserker and a Blade Master. However, this Blade Master used lightsabers, so he didn’t have any proficiency in Greatswords and backed away in tears. The Berserker shouted in happiness and took the Angry Dragon Sword in front of everyone’s envious eyes.

This Berserker placed fourth in the damage charts. His spirit rose after switching equipment. He had more confidence now, but he had completely forgotten that Unrivaled Super Hottie had caught up from a two-thirds damage deficit. He had surpassed them after killing the monsters between the first and second boss. A better weapon clearly wouldn’t account for such a rise.

But in any case, the other seven hadn’t been too far apart in damage output. With a better weapon, his damage output would clearly be shown.

After killing a few waves, the Berserker reached third place and looked like he could compete with the second place Unrivaled Super Hottie.

The other seven players felt somewhat disheartened. At this moment, one of the players who found an item shouted in joy: “Team leader, hurry up and come over here!”

“What is it?” Clover immediately went over. One of the monsters had dropped a golden weapon. When she picked it up, she was surprised. Blue weapon! A mob monster had actually dropped a Blue weapon.

In terms of probability, small monsters obviously had the chance to drop good equipment, but it was a very low chance. If not, why would boss’s be valuable? However, their team had gotten good fortune. A small monster had actually dropped a Blue weapon! They were in the Bone Dragon Abyss, so the equipment dropped would be from the dungeon.

This dagger was given to the Assassin, who found it. Thus, another person began rising up on the damage charts. After several waves, the two with better weapons had pulled a distance apart from the others, but at the same time, they also discovered that Unrivaled Super Hottie had widened the distance even farther. That guy was clearly going after the first place Crispy Bean, but that Crispy Bean had equipment that far surpassed theirs! He had several pieces of Purple equipment. With such great equipment, wouldn’t his damage output naturally be high?

Chapter 554 – Bone Dragon Aldton

Only Crispy Bean wasn’t aware of the huge shift on the damage chart. As a tank, Crispy Bean also had to put out damage, but with his exceptional equipment, it was obvious that his damage output would be greater than the rest of the team. Thus, he had only checked before the first boss and saw his gigantic lead. At the same time, he looked down on Unrivaled Super Hottie’s leeching, and then stopped paying attention to the chart afterwards.

After beating the third miniboss, everyone took a break. Crispy Bean took a look at the damage chart out of boredom and jumped up in surprise. The second to last place Unrivaled Super Hottie was no longer there. Crispy Bean counted from the bottom one at a time, until he saw him in second place. In addition, his damage numbers were about to surpass his own.

“How is that possible?” Crispy Bean wailed. Even if he was a tank, his equipment advantage should put him far above everyone else, but at this moment, he was about to be beat. Crispy Bean had a hard time believing it.

“What is it?” Crispy Bean’s cry had caught the attention of the others in the team. No one except Clove said anything.

“Oh, it’s nothing. I was just looking at some gossip!” Crispy Bean said.

“What gossip?” Clove asked again.

“It’s nothing. It’s nothing. I saw wrong.” Crispy Bean hastily excused himself. He simultaneously looked at Unrivaled Super Hottie and began examining his equipment.

“Could there be some sort of abnormal equipment that I overlooked?” Crispy Bean thought. He carefully checked every equipment on Unrivaled Super Hottie, not neglecting even a piece of jewelry.

Nothing. He had nothing abnormal on him. Crispy Bean was quite experienced with Knight equipment. The equipment on Unrivaled Super Hottie exposed his poverty. Even the Dragon Guardian Axe wasn’t anything in Crispy Bean’s eyes. None of his equipment had any hidden strength.

How is that possible?

How is that possible?

Crispy Bean didn’t dare to express his doubts. He could only mutter to himself. His cry hadn’t disrupted the team’s mood. The third boss had actually dropped another weapon.

Players placed the most value on weapons. In this dungeon, three bosses and a monster had dropped a total of four weapons. Their luck this run was extremely good. Everyone was happily discussing their luck. It was too bad the fourth weapon was a ninjato though. The team didn’t have any ninjas, so no one could use it. In the end, the team decided to donate it to the guild and split the contribution points.

Everyone was doing their best to deal damage. Clove felt like the mood was good and felt happy in her heart. Only Crispy Bean was still pondering over how in the world it was possible for Unrivaled Super Hottie’s damage to be so high.

From then on, Crispy Bean began paying attention to the damage chart and Unrivaled Super Hottie’s moves. He adjusted his pulling method and put more effort into dealing damage.

His adjustment produced results. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s name stayed at second place, unable to pass him. After killing off the last wave of monsters, the team reached the end of Bone Dragon Abyss to face off against the final boss of the dungeon: Bone Dragon Aldton.

Aldton used to be a red dragon, but after dying, it became a bone dragon. Most of his stats had already changed, such as Dragon’s Might.

“Report your Spirit.” Clove asked everyone before the final boss.

As Heavenly Domain players, they knew why she asked about their Spirit. Because as long as one was against a dragon, Dragon’s Might would take effect. If a player’s Spirit didn’t reach a certain level, the player would be affected by Dragon’s Might. According to the game, the player would feel threatened by the dragon and be unable to display his or her full strength. When this happened, the character’s stats would weaken depending on the level of Dragon’s Might and the character’s Spirit.

Aldton was a bone dragon. As an undead creature, it had lost much of its dragon abilities. Even though it still had Dragon’s Might, it couldn’t compare to other dragons. In front of Aldton, players could accumulate enough Spirit to negate the effects of its Dragon’s Might.

The game didn’t announce the data to the public, but players had already figured it out. Heavenly Domain players weren’t noobs. Before running a dungeon, they would look at a dungeon guide. They had known the boss was a dragon. They reported their Spirit stat. All of them had reached a level where they could ignore the effects of Dragon’s Might. This was the benefit of standing on the shoulders of giants. At release, Aldton had been an extremely difficult boss to beat. The bone dragon made every player’s head hurt.

“It looks like everyone prepared well!” Clove notified everyone before the run about this issue. It had only been a reminder though. Actually getting the equipment to meet the requirements wasn’t something that could be done just by thinking about it. However, it looked like everyone had prepared well and worn proper equipment that could ignore Aldton’s Dragon’s Might. Speaking of this, Bone Dragon Abyss was already considered outdated, so their equipment didn’t need to be amazing.

“Of course. Of course.” The team replied.

Clove followed: “However, negating Aldton’s Dragon Might isn’t everything. Be mindful of his attacks. You all might have read the dungeon guide, but I should still talk about it again!”

‘First is his bite attack. It’s a single target attack. Before attacking, Aldton will lower its head. The attack has a range of 12 units and does lots of damage. The attack also has a chance to inflict a Level 70 Bleed. Be careful of his bite, especially Cloth armor classes. If you get bitten, drink a potion immediately.”

“Understood.” The two cloth armor characters replied.

“There’s also his wing attack. Aldton will lifts its wings and attack. The starting animation is very obvious, but it’s not so easy to predict because of the many ways it can use the attack. There are different ways of dodging and different safe spots every time. It’s not easy to describe. Just make sure to be on the lookout for it.”

“In addition, Aldton has a tail attack, which can be used in many ways. It can do a horizontal sweep, whip strike, or a stab. The horizontal sweep has a wide range, making it difficult to dodge. However, if you predict it, you can dodge it. As for the whip strike, it’s more flexible than the horizontal sweep, so be mindful of it. As for the stab, it has a quick starting animation and is difficult to see. The stab is the most difficult to deal with. Try not to stay too close to each other to minimize the damage taken.

“Finally, Aldton has a breath attack. The breath attack covers a reverse triangle area. The area isn’t fixed. The bigger the area, the longer the startup animation will be. However, the power is always the same. Besides the fixed damage, it will also lower your health by 50% and lasts 10 seconds. This effect cannot be dispelled and is very troublesome. If you get hit while at 50% health, it’s possible that you will die in one hit, so if you get hit by his breath attack, immediately leave the range of battle and wait until the effect wears off before going back in.

“This…… what if the tank gets hit?” Someone asked. The tank would certainly be directly facing the boss. It would be difficult for the tank to avoid such a wide area breath attack. If the tank left the battlefield, the boss would follow him.

“Normally, this boss requires a secondary tank. When the main tank is hit by the breath attack, the secondary tank will take the aggro. However, we don’t need one. Crispy Bean can hold on even with half his health, so you don’t need to worry.” Clove said.

“Okay okay.” Everyone understood and paid their respects to Crispy Bean. Crispy Bean had been waiting for this moment and gave his thanks. Afterwards, Clove explained the strategy. Once the team finished resting, they started the fight.

Crispy Bean was naturally the first to charge forward. At the same time, he didn’t forget to look around him. Sure enough, Unrivaled Super Hottie had followed him.

At this point, everyone knew he wouldn’t mess up the aggro, so Crispy Bean couldn’t say anything about his actions. However, the final boss wasn’t a miniboss. It had tricky attacks and besides its bite attack, it didn’t have any other single target skills. When it attacked the tank, it would definitely attack the others at the same time. Right now, Crispy Bean really hoped this guy would be sent into outer space by Bone Dragon Aldton’s tail.

Crispy Bean used a strong aggro skill to pull the boss. A green glow shone from the two black eyes of Bone Dragon Aldton. It lowered its head and chomped at Crispy Bean.

Crispy Bean had prepared. He raised his shield and blocked the giant fangs. Just like this, he blocked the attack. Due to the shield, the bleed effect wouldn’t take effect. This was one usage of a shield.

He took out his sword and attacked the dragon’s head. Metal collided with bone, producing a ear-piercing noise. The sound was so bad, Crispy Bean couldn’t help but furrow his brow. At this moment, a figure came descending from the sky. With two hands holding a huge axe, he slammed the axe into the dragon’s head before it could pull out.

The ear-piercing sound was so loud it made Crispy Bean shiver. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s brave strike was like an attack towards his spirit.

Bone Dragon Aldton pulled back its head and flapped its two wings.

At nearly the same time, Crispy Bean and Unrivaled Super Hottie rushed forward together below the Bone Dragon. This was a safe space, where the Bone Dragon’s wings wouldn’t be able to reach. However, with both Knights running in, the space was a little bit narrow.

“Don’t get in my way!” Whenever Crispy Bean saw this annoying guy and his annoying name, he would feel extremely agitated.

Ye Xiu didn’t reply. After the bone dragon flapped its wings, he immediately rushed out of the safe space.

Aha! You stupid noob! Go die!!!

Seeing this scene, Crispy Bean was delighted. After the bone wings went out, the bone wings would certainly retract and the retraction would also do damage. Rushing out now was still too early. This was a mistake numerous players made against the boss.

“Careful!!” Clove saw the scene and immediately gave a warning.

Chapter 555 – Knight’s Spirit

A DPSer like Ye Xiu, who could attack relentlessly without having the aggro go off the tank, might draw some jealousy from other DPS players, but he was definitely loved by the team leader, tanks, and healing classes. However, in this current team, the one who hated this DPSer the most was a tank. Crispy Bean was dressed in a set of superior equipment. Regardless of whether the aggro went off the tank because of DPS or having another DPS surpass his own damage output, he would find it shameful.

However, this DPS was so outstanding that it caused Crispy Bean heart to tremble. He could already feel that Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t made the aggro go off the tank because of his control. It is only because of that control that Unrivaled Super Hottie’s current output damage was below Crispy Bean’s.

If this was a DPSer whose role was to deal damage…… the two shameful things would have already happened.

An excellent DPSer should have decreased the pressure that would be placed on the tank, but instead Crispy Bean felt as if his pressure multiplied. He wished that Unrivaled Super Hottie would hurry and die.

Now his wish would finally happen!

Unrivaled Super Hottie unexpectedly chose this opportunity to rush out and misposition himself!

Clove yelled out for him to be careful, but Crispy Bean knew clearly that if he reacted to the warning now, it would definitely be too late. Forwards, backwards, left, or right? No matter which way he went, it would be impossible to be faster than Aldton‘s wing attack.

DIE DIE DIE!

Crispy Bean couldn’t express his excitement out loud, so he could only speak it continually in his heart. In the blink of an eye, the retracting wing already covered Unrivaled Super Hottie. He could hear a faint clashing sound.

What a great sound to hear!

Originally, Crispy Bean hated the clashing sound between bones and metal, but at this moment, he found the sound very pleasant.

Aldton’s bone wing finally fully retracted. Crispy Bean couldn’t wait to take a look at the results. The sight of Unrivaled Super Hottie rolling on the ground from the sweep of the bone wing would be humiliating.

After Aldton retracted its wing, it turned its body and swept its tail towards them.

Not bad! Just like this! Crispy Bean was excited.

He knew clearly that with a Knight’s toughness, a wing attack was not enough to instantly kill, but the addition of a tail sweep would be just enough. After all, this was a dungeon for ten people and Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment was poor even with the Dragon Guardian Axe. However, because he used this double-handed weapon, he didn’t have a shield. Speaking of defense, there was a significant difference between having a shield and not having a shield.

At this moment, Crispy Bean was afraid Clove would heal him. However, Crispy Bean already thought about it before. Right at the moment when Unrivaled Super Hottie made a mistake in positioning, Crispy Bean also made a little mistake in positioning. Thus, he also entered the wing attack’s range. Crispy Bean pretended not to notice and didn’t block with his shield.

There was only one Cleric on the team.

For a situation like this, it was obvious whether one should prioritize the tank or the DPSer.

Crispy Bean admired himself for being able to plan so much in a single moment.

When he saw his health gradually recover, Crispy Bean revealed a dark smile. As expected, Clove chose to heal him in this instant.

At the same time, Aldton’s tail swept towards Unrivaled Super Hottie. In fact, the boss’s current aggro was still on Crispy Bean, so its attack was aimed at Crispy Bean. However, Unrivaled Super Hottie positioned himself there, so he became the first person to receive the attack.

Crispy Bean, of course, would hate to miss this scene. His unblinking eyes stared towards the direction of Unrivaled Super Hottie. He even continued to scheme evilly, if this tail didn’t manage to sweep Unrivaled Super Hottie to death, then…...

Just as Crispy Bean reached this thought, his brain suddenly halted for a moment. This was because he saw Unrivaled Super Hottie rolling around. Without any delay, he lay prone and slipped through the only gap as the dragon swept its tail across.

Unrivaled Super Hottie stopped right behind Aldton. As he stood up, he swung his Dragon Guardian Axe in an arc. After straightening up, he continued to use all sorts of attacking skills.

He completed all of the movements in one go. Once everything replayed and connected together, his previous act of continuous rolling became less humiliating. Just from the scene, where he lay prone through the gap under the tail’s sweep was thrilling enough to be recorded, watched, and replayed for a hundred times.

“How is this possible?” Crispy Bean’s couldn’t close his gaping mouth.

This had to be a coincidence!

Crispy Bean thought. This was because under normal circumstances, it would have been too late to use such a method of dodging. However, at that time, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s was already rolling because of the wing attack. The speed of his roll was faster than what could be done by players. He was able to complete such a risky dodge by borrowing the speed generated from being hit by the wing attack.

Crispy Bean hoped it was just a coincidence, but unfortunately it didn’t seem like it.

After rolling, Unrivaled Super Hottie continued to attack. He was absolutely calm. Who would believe that he was able to escape from such a desperate situation through luck?

It was certain that calmness originated from confidence. He was confident that he could dodge the attack, so that chain of rolling wasn’t a coincidence. He deliberately used Aldton’s wing attack to position himself.

A method like this actually existed? Crispy Bean’s mental pressure grew.

How about the others? They were also struck dumb with astonishment by this scene. Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie continued his attacks at once after rolling. The other members froze for a moment in awe. Even Clove, who was meant to quickly heal Unrivaled Super Hottie, was shocked stiff for a second.

“That was so close!” Clove exasperated while healing Unrivaled Super Hottie after she broke out of her shock.

“Haha, it’s good to have a priest.” Ye Xiu said as he continued to attack.

As Crispy Bean watched Unrivaled Super Hottie slowly recover his health, he gnashed his teeth in anger, but he couldn’t come up with any calculations. Don't tell me that I have to finish this dungeon quietly like this? I refuse!

Crispy Bean looked around to see if there were any other chances, but Unrivaled Super Hottie positioned himself behind Aldton. Between the two, one of them faced the dragon’s front and the other faced its back. The bone dragon’s body was not small. He couldn’t even see Unrivaled Super Hottie in person, so how could he make any further calculations?

Crispy Bean continued to fight the boss half-heartedly. On the contrary, other people were passionate like fire. Especially those who had received weapons from Bone Dragon Abyss threw out damage ruthlessly. They wanted to leave the others behind and get closer to their targets ahead.

For a moment, the competition in the damage charts was in full swing as the players competed with one another. Only the rankings of Crispy Bean in first place, Unrivaled Super Hottie in the second, and Clove in last place were stable. The other seven people competed with one another like a race car match. However, two groups formed between the seven people: those with and without dropped weapons.

However, Crispy Bean wasn’t in the mood to care what happened below him on this list, there was only one name in his eyes: Unrivaled Super Hottie.

This fellow’s name continued to hang behind him steadily from start to finish. It seemed as if he would surpass Crispy Bean at any time. Crispy Bean didn’t have any methods to getting rid of Unrivaled Super Hottie, so he could only grit his teeth and try to crush Unrivaled Super Hottie under his name. However, no matter how he fought, he still wasn’t able to pull away from him on the damage charts. Unrivaled Super Hottie was like a cat catching a mouse. The cat wanted to catch the mouse, but would restrain itself and patiently follow behind as if teasing the prey.

Crispy Bean’s eyes were close to spewing fire. His emotions surged as his performance became more and more chaotic. He would only consider which skill’s damage output was greatest and immediately chose to use it.

However, would his total damage rapidly shoot up from blindly using skills with high damage? Of course not! In order to have a higher damage output, apart from optimizing skill cooldowns, one had to take note of random effects triggered by the skill or extending buffs given by skills.

Just standing there and putting out skills? That would be the legendary brainless DPS. True experts at dealing damage might not have it easier than a tank in terms of technique. The reason Crispy Bean had high DPS was because he had good equipment.

But he still continued to grind his teeth and brood about the damage output. He also continued to try making different adjustments. Not only did his damage output become unstable, even his responsibility of keeping the boss’s aggro was influenced.

He was only focused on competing with Ye Xiu. He failed to realize that the other players at this moment were also competing and it became more and more intense. The damage output increased and the boss’s aggro also whirled up. Moreover, they trusted him as the chief tank, so they had completely forgotten about controlling the boss’s aggro.

Crispy Bean was still grinding his teeth and playing as both DPS and a tank though. Suddenly, the bone dragon turned its body. Its pair of pitch-dark eye sockets changed to glare at another target instead.

“The aggro is off the tank!!” Clove turned pale with fright and yelled out continually. The other seven DPSers had already roughly grasped the set pattern of attacking the boss. Amidst their risky thrills with no danger. They had become extremely excited about their competition. They never thought that with Unrivaled Super Hottie so high up, that they would be responsible for causing the aggro to go off the tank.

At this instant, the person who caused the aggro shift secretly felt satisfied in his heart. This was actually the mindset of many DPS players. To cause the aggro shift was something they were proud of instead of feeling ashamed about. They believed that this was a proof of their mighty DPS.

There was nothing wrong with thinking like this. It was true that causing an aggro shift meant having a high damage output, but there was not much else to it. Having high damage output did not necessarily mean that they were an expert in dealing damage. Having a high damage output could perhaps only be because of their equipment. On the other hand, experts in dealing damage could have a high result of damage output, while not letting there be any bothersome problems like causing an aggro shift.

The brothers who chuckled to themselves only had time to feel accomplished for a moment before Aldton turned around. The dragon’s head raised as it tore through to bite towards them.

However at this time, a bright light shone from behind Aldton as Unrivaled Super Hottie already rushed ahead at a fast pace. He raised his hand to beckon and used a Provoke towards Aldton at this crucial moment.

No, this was not a normal Provoke！

This was Glorious Provocation.

At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s body was flooded with white light, he activated the Knight’s level 50 Awakening skill: Knight’s Spirit!

Humility, honour, sacrifice, bravery, mercy, honesty, spiritual, justice.

With the buff from Knight’s Spirit, the Knight would have enhanced skills and a massive buff in stats.

Chapter 556 – Sacrificial Roar

Provoke was considered a crowd control skill. Its effect could generate a huge amount of aggro, while causing the Taunted target to lose its free movement. It could only attack the character who had cast Provoke for the next 3 seconds. Unrivaled Super Hottie activated his Knight’s Spirit, which caused his Provoke to be enhanced to a Glorious Provocation. It generated even more aggro and would increase the forced attacks towards the caster to 5 seconds.

There were many NPC’s that were immune to Provoke, but Bone Dragon Aldton wasn’t one of them. After getting Provoked by Unrivaled Super Hottie, its attention shifted towards him instead of towards the other players.

Using such a skill in the event of an accident was what a MT would usually do. Crispy Bean was very adept with such methods. The problem was that his Provoke was still on cooldown when it had happened!

Provoke wasn’t a skill that would normally be used frequently. It was reserved for dire situations. Crispy Bean had intended to build up aggro while dealing damage. For his own convenience, he used his skills as soon as the skills went off cooldown. The usage of such skills would be able to stabilize the boss’s aggro, but this method overlooked the possibility of an aggro shift and there was no backup plan either.

The problem occurred because Crispy Bean had no intentions of stabilizing the aggro. Instead, his intentions were to compensate the skills, which would generate aggro gradually, with skills that would generate a tremendous amount of aggro in one go to make way for skills that had higher damage output.

This was the main reason he failed to stabilize the aggro, despite casting all of his skills. Even though his high damage generated a large amount of aggro, the calculation for aggro was very complex. Damage wasn’t the only thing that was factored in.

Critical attacks, bleed, poison, and armor break…. Each effect would generate additional aggro. As a result, Crispy Bean’s way of building aggro couldn’t make up for the aggro generated by players that were furiously attacking the Boss. He didn’t have a backup plan either.

He was lucky that Unrivaled Super Hottie had reacted in time.

When Bone Dragon Aldton shifted its attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie, the players let out a collective sigh of relief. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment had also changed. He was facing Aldton directly with a sword and shield in hand.

“Stop attacking!” Clove shouted as she healed Unrivaled Super Hottie at the same time.

Even though the Boss’ aggro had been stabilized after being Provoked, there were still a lot of hidden dangers.

If the aggro wasn’t built up properly during the 3 to 5 second margin that the Boss was Provoked, there was no telling how the aggro would be distributed once Provoke ended.

Under normal circumstances, if the the main tank did his or her work properly and stabilized the aggro within the three to five second window, the boss’s aggro would be reset back onto the main tank. The reason others would stop attacking was to give the main tank a chance to build up the boss’s aggro again.

Crispy Bean was the only one who ignored the orders to stop. He wanted to use his own Provoke to get the boss back to him, but unfortunately, it was on cooldown, so he had to resort to using other aggro building skills and hope that Aldton’s aggro would be onto him once the effects of Provoke wore off.

Who would have thought that when he swung his word, the only thing he hit was air.

Bone Dragon Aldton had actually twisted its body and sidestepped the sword.

Despite its big size, the dragon wasn’t slow at all. It managed to dodge Crispy Bean’s attack.

If it was just this, Crispy Bean would have certainly shouted in anger, but Aldton’s sudden movement not only caused his own attack to miss, but the attacks of the others to miss as well.

These were the players who were unable to stop their attacks when Clove barked out her order. Unrivaled Super Hottie had moved around after casting the Provoke on Aldton and the dragon moved in an attempt to attack him. With that very movement, it dodged the attacks that were aimed at it.

This was undoubtedly a mainstream main tank strategy. When situation got out of hand, the MT would drag the boss out of range from the other players. After all, not everyone was fast enough to immediately stop attacking.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s action was a textbook maneuver. Crispy Bean would have done the same thing himself. Unfortunately, this maneuver had caused his attack to miss, so he was still deeply resentful.

“Bang!”

Crispy Bean’s position was off and his vision was blocked by the Bone Dragon. He couldn’t see the skill cast by Unrivaled Super Hottie. All he heard was a thud, which was the sound of a shield being struck.

Was he defending or was he continuing to build aggro?

Crispy Bean was panicking. As a Knight, he knew that a majority of the skills that required shields could generate a large amount of aggro. This was also a way for main tank’s to build up monster aggro. Was Unrivaled Super Hottie doing all of this in an attempt to replace him as the main tank?

How could that be okay!

Crispy Bean was becoming desperate. He moved forward and hacked away at the Bone Dragon. He really hoped he could see Aldton’s bony skull again after the five second Glorious Provocation wore off.

The five seconds passed quickly. Crispy Bean was so focused on attacking Aldton that he even reposition himself in front of the boss. He had been counting down from five and when the time came….

“Bang!”

Crispy Bean was sent flying into the air. The dragon had caught Crispy Bean in the air with its tail!

Crispy Bean coughed up blood!

The aggro was back on him, but in a very pathetic way! He had been too careless!

The aggro reset meant that the Boss would resume its attack on him, but Crispy Bean forgot that the dragon’s attack range had a 360 degrees reach. It didn’t need to face its target to attack.

As a result, the instant the Provoke off, Aldon lifted its wings…..

The others were already standing far away after stopping their attacks. Only Crispy Bean was standing behind Aldton, expecting it to turn around. In the end he was sent flying away by Aldton’s wing. The dragon followed up with a swing of its tail.

Wing attack, tail whip.

Crispy Bean was helpless against Aldton’s combo. He could only block the attack with his shield and prepared to counterattack as soon as he landed on the ground. With the aggro back on him, he could withstand a few of Aldton’s attacks, especially with Clove healing him.

Bang!

With another dull thud, the dragon’s tail struck Crispy Bean. He had already prepared his shield in front of him, but the impact accelerated him towards the ground. Crispy Bean was well prepared though and had already began Quick Recovering. However, he suddenly heard the DPSers let out a collective curse, “Sh*t!”

Crispy Bean’s eyes began to water.

Aldton finally turned around, but its next animation made Crispy Bean cry.

Dragon Breath!

Aldton was going to use its strongest attack: Dragon Breath.

The dragon ignored Crispy Bean when it was supposed to and shifts its attention to him when it wasn’t. If anybody laughed at an NPC’s intelligence level, Crispy Bean would definitely give that person a heavy slap.

The worst part of the breath attack was that it was aimed in the direction of the damage dealers. The attack would hit everyone else.

If every one of them were hit by the breath attack, they were finished! Aldton displayed a high level of intelligence. With such AOE attacks, wouldn’t it finish the lot of them off in an instant?

Crispy Bean recognized the seriousness of the situation. How could the damage dealers not notice it?

But evasion was impossible.

They was quite a distance away from Aldton, placing them right in the center of its breath, there was nowhere to run...…

As for the Cleric? She was also a target that would be attacked.

As all hope was lost, a roar emanated from behind Aldton. It wasn’t man made. It was a skill called Roar, but with Knight’s Spirit’s buff active at the same time, it was known as Sacrificial Roar. Glory players gave a nickname to this skill based on its special effect: shoot at me.

Roar was a skill of similar nature to Provoke. While Provoke was a single target skill, Roar would often be used on a mob. A Sacrificial Roar, buffed by Knight’s Spirit, had an increased range. With an increase in range, the number of targets affected would also increased. With the concentrated attacks from so many enemies, the Roar was indeed sacrificial.

Roar didn’t have a time limit. It affected its target based on the number of attacks launched. It would force victims to launch a single attack on the caster alone.

In their current situation though, one hit was enough.

Breath was a continuous attack.Despite dealing accumulated damage, it still counted as one hit.

But could Unrivaled Super Hottie survive under the continuous damage of the dragon breath? He wasn’t Crispy Bean, who had superior equipment. With the quality of his equipment, he would need normally need a secondary tank to take the hit.

Everyone of the players couldn’t help but worry for Unrivaled Super Hottie when Aldton breathed towards him.

Sacrificial Roar… Would he really be sacrificed?

Chapter 557 – The Arrogant Youth Whose Face Was Slapped

After being hit by another strong attack, Aldton twisted its neck furiously. Dragon breath continued to spew out like water from a hose. The ashen dragon breath swept past the dumbfounded team of players and headed straight for Unrivaled Super Hottie.

A shadow swiftly dashed out. It was Unrivaled Super Hottie.

He was running away from the dragon breath in a clockwise direction.

As a result, the others looked like they were watching a scene from an action movie. The ashen dragon breath chased close behind him. Four steps, three steps, two steps away….. It was about to swallow Unrivaled Super Hottie, but at this moment, the dragon breath faded away and Unrivaled Super Hottie came out safe and sound.

“D*MN!!” Everyone else shouted.

Before this, they had been crying in despair at Aldton’s dragon breath.

This time, they were crying out in joy, seeing Unrivaled Super Hottie escaping from the dragon’s breath in such a manner.

“He really is unrivaled!!” Someone remarked.

“TOO COOL!”

“What a hottie!!”

Everyone was praising him, completely stunned by Unrivaled Super Hottie’s performance.

Then, they heard Unrivaled Super Hottie yell: “Heal.”

“Oh!” Clove hastily responded and healed him. After the Sacrificial Roar, the boss cleansed itself from the forced taunt, but it was still attacking Unrivaled Super Hottie. Sacrificial Roar clearly had a huge aggro value, so Aldton’s aggro was now on Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Bang bang bang bang!

After a few quick attacks, Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted out again: “Attack!”

The DPS classes replied and quickly rushed forward.

Crispy Bean felt like he had been forgotten…...

No, he hadn’t been completely forgotten. When the others rushed forward, some of them were whispering to each other about him.

The Berserker actually said if Crispy Bean had run like Unrivaled Super Hottie, wouldn’t the problem have been resolved faster?

Crispy Bean really wanted to curse the Berserker “Are you an idiot? I was in the air at that time. Do you think I can just grow wings and fly around?”

Crispy Bean didn’t say it though because he knew that was just an excuse. At that moment, even if he had landed on the ground steadily, there was no way he had that sort of awareness. Even if he had that sort of awareness, it didn’t mean that he could react in such a manner. Even if he were able to react in that manner, it didn’t mean that he would be able to perform such precise moves.

He hadn’t been on the ground, but in the air. During his moment of panic, he had even forgotten to Quick Recover and crashed to the ground. How many of them had laughed at him?

Why couldn’t he do it?

Crispy Bean ground his teeth. His heart was filled with envy and resentment.

Because he had been sent flying far away, Sacrificial Roar wouldn’t be enough to consolidate the aggro. Right now, the aggro had been completely locked onto Unrivaled Super Hottie. However, how could he give up?

Definitely not!

Crispy Bean thought. He chased after the DPS classes and also attacked.

Crispy Bean relentlessly used strong damage skills and aggro skills. However, Aldton refused to turn its head. Crispy Bean’s heart trembled. His gaze had already paused on a few skills several times already.

Provoke…...

Roar…...

Knight’s Spirit. He could use all of these skills too! In addition, if he used them, the skills would be effective. The bone dragon would be forced to attack him for a few seconds.

However, with the aggro already stabilized, if he suddenly used these skills, it wouldn’t be any different than the aggro being dragged from the tank. The others would definitely scorn him.

As a tank, Crispy Bean hated tank-related accidents. If he intentionally caused one, he would be violating the respect he had for his class. As a result, he decided not to use these two skills. Using such methods and using attacks in order to take back the aggro were very different.

With his equipment, he didn’t need to use Provoke or Roar to gain back the aggro.

Crispy Bean’s superior equipment became his pride. He continued to attack Aldon. This time, he was completely prepared and picked a good position. If the aggro returned to him, it wouldn’t matter what attack the Bone Dragon used. None of them would be able to send him flying away.

Come back! Come back! Come back!

Crispy Bean roared. He obviously wouldn’t let Unrivaled Super Hottie tell him to stop outputting damage, otherwise he would lose face.

He could only do his best and hope all the way until Bone Dragon Aldton fell.

What? It died? Just like that?

Crispy Bean couldn’t believe it. It only took that much time? How much health did Aldton have? Why wasn’t it fighting properly? He hadn’t gotten the aggro back, so why did it fall?

He hadn’t accumulated enough aggro. Crispy Bean could only flip open the damage charts.

He had actually dropped down to number two.

What type of joke was this!!

Even though he had initially been prioritizing establishing aggro, Unrivaled Super Hottie had switched out his Dragon Guardian Axe and had to balance between putting out damage and establishing aggro. How did he lose in terms of damage?

Crispy Bean couldn’t believe what was going on. Seeing how happy the other team members were, including Clove, Crispy Bean couldn’t help but feel like he really had been abandoned.

“Leader, what’d we get?” The team wanted to know what the boss had dropped.

“It’s something someone in our team can use. Guess!” Clove began to tease the others.

“Is it a weapon?” Someone asked.

“Yes.” Clove replied.

“Wow, what luck! This isn’t an abyss. It’s a weapon storage!” Someone joked.

Everyone laughed.

“Leader, stop playing with us. Hurry up and show us the weapon!”

Clove stopped dawdling and let everyone see the weapon in the chat. It was a Striker glove. Amidst everyone else’s envious gaze, the glove was given to the Striker.

The atmosphere was very warm.

“Shall we continue?” Clove asked. In the Heavenly Domain, dungeons had a run limit. Bone Dragon Abyss could only be run twice a day.

“Continue! Continue!!” Everyone shouted.

“I have something that came up. I won’t be able to continue.” Crispy Bean suddenly spoke up.

“Okay. Good luck!” Clove didn’t try and stop him. After seeing Unrivaled Super Hottie’s performance, she didn’t feel like Crispy Bean was necessary. Of course, she had good intentions too. For someone at Crispy Bean’s level, this dungeon was a waste of time, so Clove didn’t want to trouble Crispy Bean. As for the mistake at the final boss, Clove didn’t have too many thoughts about it. Everyone made mistakes, no? At crucial moments, the off tank often made up for it.

Crispy Bean didn’t think such simple thoughts though. His arrogance made him unable to accept what had happened. Clove not stopping him suddenly made him feel very unhappy.

Without saying anything more, Crispy Bean left the team and directly left without saying goodbye to anyone. Clove was busy attending to the team, when she suddenly received a message from her guild leader. Senior Exterminate the Heavens: “Crispy Bean says he wants to leave the guild. What happened?”

“What?” Clove was at a loss.

“Didn’t he come help you clear the dungeon?” Senior Exterminate the Heavens asked.

“Yeah!”

“Did something go wrong?” Senior Exterminate the Heavens questioned.

“Nothing went wrong!” Clove was confused. In the eyes of normal players, the run had gone very smoothly, apart from the minor slip-up at the final boss. It wasn’t like anyone died, no?

“Did he get into an argument with anyone?” Senior Exterminate the Heavens asked.

“What did he say to you?” Clove asked back. If that were the reason, then it might be because of Unrivaled Super Hottie. In the beginning, Clove could also tell that Crispy Bean didn’t like him, but she didn’t think he had such a big problem with him. Then again, in the beginning, he had said Unrivaled Super Hottie was a leech, but after playing seriously, he became number in on the damage charts. Crispy Bean had looked down on him as a tank, but Unrivaled Super Hottie later showed incredible skill as a tank. There shouldn’t have been any problems! Clove thought from a bystander’s perspective. She hadn’t thought about it from Crispy Bean’s perspective. Unrivaled Super Hottie took number one on the damage charts and then displayed incredible skill at a crucial moment, which made him feel like he couldn’t show his face.

This was a story of an arrogant youth being slapped in the face.

“I asked what was wrong, but he said he didn’t want to say it.” Senior Exterminate the Heavens sent a helpless reply. A normal guild member didn’t matter, but a tank was different, especially the guild’s chief tank. He was a huge pillar for the guild.

“I’ll ask him.” Clove didn’t feel happy about Crispy Bean’s weird attitude. She was quite close with Crispy Bean too, so she asked directly: “I heard you want to leave the guild? What’s wrong?”

“It has nothing to do with you, so don’t ask.” Crispy Bean replied quickly.

“Everything was good before, but after running a dungeon with me, you want to leave the guild? How does this not have something to do with me?” Clove asked.

Crispy Bean didn’t reply.

“Is it because of Unrivaled Super Hottie?” Clove asked. Even though she didn’t understood Crispy Bean’s thinking, Unrivaled Super Hottie was the most likely reason behind it.

“Yeah…..” Crispy Bean admitted.

“Why?” Clove didn’t understand.

“No reason. I don’t want to be in the same guild as him.” Crispy Bean couldn’t say the truth.

“What’s wrong with you!” Clove wasn’t happy, but was also too lazy to deal with Crispy Bean. She had found the reason, so she told Senior Exterminate the Heavens.

“Because of that? What exactly happened in the dungeon?” Senior Exterminate the Heavens asked.

Chapter 558 – Test

Clove was an honest person. She described everything that had happened between Crispy Bean and Unrivaled Super Hottie without adding in any flourishes. Clover couldn’t understand Crispy Bean’s feelings, but Senior Exterminate the Heavens immediately grasped the problem.

Even so, there was nothing he could do.

This issue was clearly a matter of face and wasn’t something that could be solved through logic. Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t done anything wrong. Even if he had, what was he supposed to do? Call him over and make him apologize to Crispy Bean?

This was a game. Face was even more important than one’s life! At worst, everyone separated. No one wanted to lower their heads to someone else. Even if it wasn’t logical, one should still stand up straight and take it. Apologize? For what reason would he need to? Because he was a tank? Face had nothing to do with being a tank.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens thought about it. If he wanted to resolve this problem, he had to figure out a way to get Crispy Bean out of this embarrassing situation. Unrivaled Super Hottie couldn’t get him out. It seemed like it was all up to him.

How depressing……. Senior Exterminate the Heavens was also troubled. Unless he was a famous money warrior or was backed by a Club, a normal guild leader didn’t have much status in the game. If a conflict came about, the guild leader better get busy! If the guild leader succeeded, then it would be worth it. The worse case scenario would be if the conflict didn’t get resolved. The guild leader would have to find outside help, which would really be quite depressing.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens sighed and sent a message to Crispy Bean: “Crispy Bean, we’ve already played together for so long. You plan on leaving the guild, but you didn’t even give us a reason. That’s not right! When the other members of the guild ask why Crispy Bean left, what am I supposed to tell them? You’re our guild’s chief tank.”

Senior Exterminate the Heavens pretended he didn’t know the reason whatsoever. His words suggested three things. First, he played the emotional card, making Crispy Bean recall his fond memories with the guild. Crispy Bean’s reason for leaving was very simple. If he had to reason with Crispy Bean, his only choice would be strike at Unrivaled Super Hottie, but if Unrivaled Super Hottie became dissatisfied with the guild too, the damage would be irreversible. Right now, it was only because he was unhappy with Unrivaled Super Hottie. As long as his feelings didn’t intensify, Crispy Bean would certainly feel reluctant if he left his guild and his friends in the guild.

The second thing was to tell Crispy Bean about his own problems. This would give Crispy Bean a way out. Crispy Bean was hesitating, but he could excuse himself by saying it was to help him.

As for the third thing, it pointed out Crispy Bean’s status. Senior Exterminate the Heavens completely saw through Crispy Bean’s reason, so he emphasized his status to appeal to him.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens was quite skilled. He wasn’t an ordinary person. On the surface, he was a normal guild leader, but in reality, he was one of Tyrannical Ambition’s core members. He was handling Club matters by expanding their power. In other words, he was on the same level as the tenth server;s Cold Night, an experienced and trusted core member. The only difference was that his relationship with Tyrannical Ambition couldn’t be exposed to the public. He could only protect Tyrannical Ambition’s interests in secret.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens placed great value on an MT, especially one like Crispy Bean. The core of a team couldn’t only have good technical skills. The core had to be reliable. Tanks would usually be trained by the guild and would be treated well. If you just reaped the benefits and then slapped your butt as you left, how sad would that be?

From this point, Crisp Bean being the chief tank was already a form of recognition. Senior Exterminate the Heavens was trying his best to mediate, but if worst came to worst, Crispy Bean would be his first priority.

After Senior Exterminate the Heavens sent his message, Crispy Bean didn’t reply for a long time. Senior Exterminate the Heavens had already reminded Clove not to interfere.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens understood Clove’s personality. If Clove tried to resolve this situation, she would definitely tell Crispy Bean that he was causing unnecessary trouble. This would clearly push Crispy Bean away from the guild, so he told Clove not to reveal the truth. Senior Exterminate the Heavens immediately told Clove to continue playing, while he dealt with the matter.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens patiently waited for Crispy Bean to reply, but at the same time, he saw Clove asking repeatedly in the guild chat if anyone wanted to go to Bone Abyss, but there was no reply from anyone. Senior Exterminate the Heavens suddenly had a thought and messaged Clove: “I’ll go with you guys!”

“Huh? You’re going?” Clove was surprised.

“Isn’t that Knight really good? I want to see for myself.” Senior Exterminate the Heavens said.

“Lower your damage output!” Clove replied.

“Of course.” Senior Exterminate the Heavens said before running over to Bone Dragon Abyss.

The nine players in the team waited and waited until the guild leader arrived. The team was naturally very surprised. Even though normal guild leaders weren’t celebrities or anything, they still had a higher status than a tank. The team members saw that today. The chief tank came to play with them in such a weak dungeon and now the guild leader personally joined them. They suddenly felt like the guild’s future looked very disastrous.

‘If everyone’s here, shall we begin?” Senior Exterminate the Heavens greeted everyone and then laughed.

“Let’s go.” Clove instructed. Even though the guild leader had come, she still led the team.

The team entered the dungeon and began fighting. This time, the tank was naturally Unrivaled Super Hottie. Senior Exterminate the Heavens didn’t care about the others and paid attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s skill.

A tank’s proficiency could be seen through the tank’s ability to pull monsters, but to truly see a tank’s skill required the situation to be messy. The messier the situation was, the more a tank’s ability to control the field would be displayed.

As a result, Senior Exterminate the Heavens planned on making mistakes from time to time. For example, he would “accidentally” pull too many monsters! And then an “accidental” mistake to cause the monster’s aggro to go off the tank! These types of mistakes happened often anyways.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens had an excuse ready for his mistakes.

He hadn’t played the dungeon in a long time, so he forgot how many monsters he should be pulling. He pulled the aggro off the tank because his equipment was too amazing. His excuses were fairly reasonable.

With his plan prepared, Senior Exterminate the Heavens immediately put it into action.

“Ah, my bad! I haven’t been here in a long time, did they change the dungeon? There didn’t use to be so monsters on this side!” Senior Exterminate the Heavens cried as he brought a bunch of monsters with him.

The other team members saw this scene, but he was the guild leader. What could they say? Hurry up and save him!

Unrivaled Super Hottie was the most calm though. He directly ignored the guild leader’s three monsters, allowing the monsters to attack the guild leader. All he said was: “Attack those three. Guild leader, hang on.”

The implication: you become a tank for now!

It wasn’t logical according to common sense, especially because the team only had one Cleric. However, Senior Exterminate the Heavens had good equipment, better than even Crispy Bean. Even though his defense couldn’t compare to Crispy Bean’s, if his equipment far surpassed the dungeon minimum requirement, then who cared? Damage was more important.

Senior Exterminate the Heaven’s health dropped fairly quickly, but the health of the monsters dropped even quicker. In the end, he hung on, while the three monsters all died. Unrivaled Super Hottie had only given them a glance to show his concern.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens was depressed. He was too strong. The monsters he pulled along could be killed with him acting as a tank. If he pulled along any more monsters and even he couldn’t deal with them, then Unrivaled Super Hottie wouldn’t be able to either.

It seemed like this method wouldn’t work. Too few monsters and Unrivaled Super Hottie would have him take the role of a tank. Too many monsters and….. Everyone would die. What was the point then?

If that didn’t work, then on to the second method.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens was a Striker, a pure DPS class, so he began attacking like crazy, but despite his efforts, no accident came about!

Why was it so difficult to cause an accident? Senior Exterminate the Heavens persevered and continued to try and cause an accident, but before he could do so, the boss fell. Senior Exterminate the Heavens dominated the damage charts, but no accident occurred.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens didn’t need to test anymore though. If no accident occurred, it could only mean one thing. Even under his brainless attacking, the tank was maintaining a stable aggro. This Unrivaled Super Hottie had even better skills than Crispy Bean.

“What do you think? Isn’t he pretty good?” After the dungeon ended, Clove messaged Senior Exterminate the Heavens. Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t made any mistakes in the dungeon run. He had done everything an outstanding tank needed to do.

“Quite impressive!” Senior Exterminate the Heavens nodded his head. This Unrivaled Super Hottie had surpassed his expectations. No wonder Crispy Bean felt pressured. If this person developed, he would certainly take Crispy Bean’s position.

Under normal circumstances, he would be extremely happy having such an outstanding player join the guild, but this time, the newly added player had a conflict with the chief tank of his guild. This wasn’t an easy situation easy to deal with. Crispy Bean had replied to him during the dungeon run. Senior Exterminate the Heaven’s words had failed. Crispy Bean had a deep opinion on Unrivaled Super Hottie. It’s either me or him.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens had already made up his mind long ago, but after witnessing Unrivaled Super Hottie’s strength, Senior Exterminate the Heavens felt a little hurt to be losing such a talent. From his guild’s perspective, this person couldn’t be kept, but as a branch of Tyrannical Ambition, it wouldn’t be hard to make arrangements for him.

Senior Exterminate the Heavens quickly contacted Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader, Jiang You and told him of this incredible Knight that had just joined the guild. However, because of a conflict with one of his players, he couldn’t keep him in the guild, so he wanted to see if Jiang You could bring him over to another guild.

“Something like that happened? I’ll make arrangements! What’s his name?” Jiang You asked. If Senior Exterminate the Heavens couldn’t bear to abandon such a talent, then Jiang You wouldn’t either.

“Unrivaled Super Hottie.” Senior Exterminate the Heavens replied.

“This name…… how arrogant!” Jiang You said.

“It really is arrogant, but he has the skills to back it up. I just dungeoned with him. His control over aggro is incredible. I intentionally tried to cause accidents to see his skill, but I couldn’t even do that. My equipment is far better than his too.”

“That good? I’ll hurry and make arrangements.” Jiang You was moved.

Chapter 559 – Tyrannical Ambition’s Four Branches

One could never have too many talents. When Jiang You heard Senior Exterminate the Heavens praise this knight, he also became interested.

Getting him over reasonable was very easy. All he needed to do was send over an invite with Tyrannical Ambition’s name.

Tyrannical Ambition and Exterminate the Heavens were on two completely different levels. A Glory player might not be a fan of the team, but the player definitely wouldn’t reject a Club guild’s invite, unless the player was the type who didn’t want to join a guild. However, if Unrivaled Super Hottie had joined Exterminate the Heavens, he clearly wasn’t that type of person. Jiang You was only worried if this person might have some sort of grudge against Team Tyranny. For example, if he were a fan of Excellent Era, then it was possible he would refuse an invite to Tyrannical Ambition.

“What details do you know about him?” Jiang You asked Senior Exterminate the Heavens.

“I don’t know. He just joined the guild today. According to him, he hasn’t played the game in awhile. Judging from his equipment, it seems to be true.” Senior Exterminate the Heavens said.

Jiang You didn’t have much else to ask. He was just pondering whether this tank, who Senior Exterminate the Heavens thought highly of, had the qualifications for him to personally go out and invite him.

After thinking about it for a bit, Jiang You decided to play it safe. Even though he trusted Senior Exterminate the Heavens, this tank and Senior Exterminate had only played together in one dungeon. Senior Exterminate certainly didn’t dare guarantee this tank’s ability. Without knowing exactly how deep this tank’s skill went, if he invited him into the guild and he turned out to be sham, he would be laughed at.

As a result, Jiang You found a branch guild leader and had him complete the task. Although it was only a branch guild, it was a guild that Tyrannical Ambition publicly acknowledged and could be considered a part of Tyrannical Ambition. The branch guild’s strength couldn’t be compared to the official Tyrannical Ambition, but it wasn’t bad either. Otherwise, Tyrannical Ambition wouldn’t be able to hold onto its image. Publicly acknowledged branch guilds would directly receive help from Tyrannical Ambition, so their resources weren’t lacking. For normal players, jumping from a guild like Exterminate the Heavens to a Club’s branch guild could be considered a huge success.

In-game affairs were always carried out very quickly. Not long afterwards, Unrivaled Super Hottie received a guild invite.

Seeing a personal invite from one of Tyrannical Ambition’s branch guilds, Ye Xiu was quite dumbfounded.

He didn’t think things would develop so fast. He had only just joined Guild Exterminate the Heavens and ran two dungeons. He didn’t think he had made enough of a commotion yet. Who would have thought he would be deemed good enough already?

Even if he had ran a dungeon with the guild’s chief tank and then the guild leader Senior Exterminate the Heavens as well, and received their recognition, Ye Xiu hadn’t imagined he would receive a direct recommendation from Tyrannical Ambition so quickly.

This truly was difficult for someone to imagine.

If Crispy Bean hadn’t made things difficult by showing his intent to leave the guild, even if Senior Exterminate the Heavens witnessed Unrivaled Super Hottie’s skills, he still wouldn’t have immediately asked for a recommendation.

Crispy Bean had forced him to make a decision. He didn’t want to give up on Crispy Bean, but he also felt like Unrivaled Super Hottie wasn’t so simple. In order to not lose either of them, his only choice was to find a different way to get Unrivaled Super Hottie to stay. After all, Senior Exterminate the Heaven’s main goal was to help Tyrannical Ambition.

Ye Xiu wasn’t some godly immortal. How could he have known about all of this? Even if he had seen how unhappy Crispy Bean was towards him, they had only just gotten to know each other. How could Ye Xiu know Crispy Bean had so much pride and actually threatened the guild leader.

“Is this the basis for the saying gold will always shine?” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo was speechless. Ye Xiu truly could be considered as gold, but she really didn’t like how he called himself gold so calmly. Couldn’t you let someone else say those words?

“So you’re in…..” Chen Guo was also surprised. She sighed thinking of how much effort it had taken her to get into Excellent Dynasty. How infuriating!

Chen Guo was still melancholy. Ye Xiu had already begun talking with the inviter. Ye Xiu directly inquired why they wanted him.

This branch player couldn’t say it was because of Jiang You! In the end, he could only say that he had a friend in Exterminate the Heavens who told him of his skill, which was why he hoped to see it for himself.

“Ha ha ha, could I ask who your friend is? He has very good eyes!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Yes, yes.” The other side was speechless. Seeing how arrogant this Unrivaled Super Hottie was, he didn’t want to chat with him any longer. Honestly speaking, he didn’t like this sort of personality.

“Since you look so highly of me, I can’t refuse can I? We have to give each other face! Don’t you think so?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes yes yes……..” The other side really wanted to end this conversation.

"How should I do this? Should I leave the guild first? Have you finished arranged everything on your side?” Ye Xiu asked.

“After leaving a guild, you have to wait five days before you can join another. But it doesn’t matter. You can come dungeon with us during those five days!” The branch player said.

“So there’s something like that. Okay!” Ye Xiu acted like he was reluctant, but then immediately left the guild.

He came and left in a rush. During his time in Guild Exterminate the Heavens, the only thing that he had made an impression of to the guild members was his name. His incredible performance in the dungeon hadn’t spread yet!

No one really said much about him joining and leaving the guild so suddenly. However, the ones who had interacted with him before immediately noticed.

Crispy Bean was naturally bursting with joy. Even though the guild leader never said anything directly, his intentions had been made clear. Crispy Bean acted like nothing had happened and didn’t mention leaving the guild anymore.

As for Senior Exterminate the Heavens? He had received a message from the branch guild saying the transaction had been successful. He was also satisfied.

The only person who wasn’t happy was the innocent girl, Clove.

This girl saw the notification of Unrivaled Super Hottie leaving the guild and immediately became somewhat upset. While complaining to Senior Exterminate the Heavens, she went to ask Unrivaled Super Hottie.

‘I didn’t. I didn’t say anything! I’m still thinking about how to resolve this situation!” Senior Exterminate the Heavens pretended like he didn’t know what was going on.

“Then why did he leave the guild without saying bye!” Clove asked.

“How should I know? He didn’t say bye to me either!” Senior Exterminate the Heavens continued to put on his act.

Clove didn’t reply because she had already received a reply from Unrivaled Super Hottie, who told her someone from Tyrannical Ambition had invited him, so he would be going to their guild.

Clove stared blankly. Had she thought too much? It seemed like he left on his own accord. She didn’t have anything else to say.

“Okay.” Clove only replied with one word.

“If an opportunity comes up, we should dungeon together again.” Ye Xiu replied. He had good impression of this girl.

“Sure.” Clove replied.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything else. The branch guild had already called him over to dungeon together. There were a lot of Level 70 dungeons. It wasn’t possible to run all of them in one day.

The two sides found a place to meet. The branch guild also saw the severity of the situation, when they saw Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment wasn’t any different from before. He had taken the Dragon Guardian Axe in Bone Dragon Abyss, but after running the dungeon, he returned it to Clover and let the team deal with it. In the second run, no Knight equipment dropped, so Ye Xiu hadn’t gained anything from there either. Honestly speaking, Ye Xiu looked down on Bone Dragon Abyss’s equipment even more than Crispy Bean.

Even if he got equipment from Bone Dragon Abyss, so what? Would he appear any different in front of others?

Tyrannical Ambition’s four branch guilds were much more powerful than Guild Exterminate the Heavens. The set of equipment on Unrivaled Super Hottie was even more shocking to the branch guild than to Exterminate the Heavens.

Tyrannical Ambition’s branch guild had directly invited Unrivaled Super Hottie to go into a hundred player group dungeon. They had originally planned on immediately adding Unrivaled Super Hottie to the group to see how he would deal with an extremely difficult dungeon. But now from the looks of it, with his equipment, he didn’t even seem close to being qualified to entering the dungeon.

Before adding Unrivaled Super Hottie to the group, everyone was whispering to each other, when they heard Unrivaled Super Hottie laugh out loud: “Wow, so many people are here to welcome me? You’re all too nice! To tell you all the truth, I haven’t officially joined the guild yet, so all of you should prepare another welcome party five days from now!”

Everyone was speechless. How could a guy with such a set of equipment act so arrogant? It seems like his name wasn’t just for show!

“Uh, everyone is here to run a dungeon. We just happen to only have 99 players and have an open spot. Are you interested in joining?” The person speaking was their group leader, Happy Sheep, a Cleric. He was one of the core members of Tyrannical Ambition’s branch guild. He had been the one to invite Unrivaled Super Hottie over. The branch guild leader hadn’t gone to personally invite him either with the same reasoning as Jiang You. he didn’t want to personally invite over a faulty product.

Knowing this, under the guild leader’s instructions, Happy Sheep was to pull him over to a dungeon and check his skill. As a result, Happy Sheep directly arranged a hundred player group and planned on bringing Unrivaled Super Hottie along. But after seeing his equipment, his equipment wasn’t good enough for the dungeon. At this moment, the team chat was in a heated debate.

“A hundred player group? It can’t get better than that! Which dungeon?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Our group is planning on running the Tomb in the Sky.” Happy Sheep answered.

“Tomb in the Sky? That sounds familiar. Wait one second, I’m going to check a guide!” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 560 – One Hundred Player Dungeon Team

The one hundred player dungeon was undoubtedly the largest scale dungeon type in the game. Naturally, the dungeon’s difficulty would be higher than smaller scale dungeons. There was even a difference in difficulty between hundred player dungeons. For example, Tomb in the Sky, the dungeon Happy Sheep’s group was planning on running, could only be considered moderate when with other one hundred player dungeons. Although it wasn’t too difficult, Happy Sheep’s group had yet to complete it. They were still figuring out how to take down the dungeon.

Equipment from one hundred player dungeons weren’t common because the dungeons could only be run a limited number of times. Compared to smaller dungeons, which could be run three times a day, each person could only enter a one hundred player dungeon once per week. In addition, most couldn’t clear the dungeon until the end. This was because within the dungeon, players only had one life and couldn’t be revived by priests. Within a hundred player team, there’s one less person every time a player died. So more and more players would be taken out gradually until there wasn’t enough manpower. Naturally by then, it would be impossible to clear the dungeon.

However, the rewards for clearing a hundred player dungeon were given out differently than other dungeons, which only gave rewards for finishing the run. The rewards were based on the player’s progress, so even if the whole team wiped out and failed to clear the dungeon, the team could still obtain rewards according to their progress percentage.

This was why many ads to recruit people into their groups included their progress through the dungeon. As long as the player joining wasn’t a first timer in the Heavenly Domain, prospective players would have a good idea of the group’s strength.

For example, Happy Sheep’s team had reached 88% completion for Tomb in the Sky. This percent was good enough to be boastful about for more than 95% of the players in the Heavenly Domain. Even though Happy Sheep was only investigating a moderately difficult one hundred player dungeon, his group’s strength could already be considered amazing. For guilds on a similar level as Guild Exterminate the Heavens, their teams had only just taken the first step at tackling level 70 hundred player dungeons.

As for guildless wild players, forming a random one hundred player team was like buying the lottery. They would run through as much as they could! However, random groups taking down hundred player dungeons might only be possible if the group of players were Level 70 and the dungeon was Level 60…...

As a result, Happy Sheep’s prideful team instantly boiled with anger when faced with a guy who immediately went to check a walkthrough after hearing the dungeon’s name.

“Reading a guide? What does he think this is? A five-man dungeon from the newbie village?” Someone typed furiously in the group chat. If one hundred player dungeons could be cleared by simply reading a walkthrough, then it wouldn’t be so hard. Being able to fight a hundred player dungeon could be counted as a skill. It couldn’t be learnt by reading walkthroughs once. It required hours and hours of practice.These people were able to clear 88% of Tomb in the Sky because they had gone through nine weeks of repetition and hardship. They were only able to exchange their final grade after their skills matured and their equipment improved. Yet this guy just lightly wrote he was going to check a guide. It felt as though he were looking down on hundred player dungeons and felt quite offensive to listen to.

“He’s probably never run a hundred player dungeon before has he? How could a tank like this be any good?” Some people spoke their doubts, blindly shooting off their mouths. In a normal player’s eyes, those who believed that hundred player dungeons could be cleared by reading a simple walkthough were noobs who had never fought in a hundred player dungeon and didn’t know the difference between heaven and earth.

Happy Sheep wasn’t too happy either, but even though he was leading the team, he wasn’t a guild leader level core member. The matter had been reported to Jiang You by Senior Exterminate the Heavens. Then, Jiang You left the task to the branch guild leader, who gave the task to him. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s origin had been lost during this process, so Happy Sheep didn’t really know what responsibility he should take. The guild leader gave him an order and he had just accepted it out of convenience. After hearing Unrivaled Super Hottie say “I’m going to check a guid”, he suddenly felt like this person was overestimating himself.

Guild Exterminate the Heavens? Those who came from such a guild could only be so skilled. Happy Sheep thought, but because he had accepted the task from the guild leader, he couldn’t not do it. Thus, he could only patiently wait for him to look over his guide. At the same time, he looked at the chat to see the others laughing at him. He didn’t intend on stopping them.

The guide for this hundred player dungeon would take a very long time to carefully read. Happy Sheep decided to start the pre-dungeon meeting. The meeting would discuss their mistakes in the previous run and what could be fixed, but not long after starting the meeting, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s voice drifted over: “Okay, I’m done reading. When do we start?”

Happy Sheep checked the clock. It had only been ten minutes. He immediately became furious again. Hundred player dungeons were complicated. First of all, the dungeon itself was complex. Secondly, because the team consisted of a hundred players, the class composition was very complicated. Not a single walkthrough covered everything because all of them used teams with different classes. Because of this, many people compared several guides before considering them as a guide, making the guides even more complicated. So ten minutes? He probably didn’t even get to the first boss, did he?

Happy Sheep didn’t say anything, when the team chat erupted.

“How long have you been looking at a guide? Ten minutes? That’s one minute for each boss!”

“Does he think this is a normal small scale dungeon?”

In normal small scale dungeons, the difficulty was mostly concentrated on the boss, so the important parts for these types of dungeons were the bosses. However, in hundred player dungeons, the mobs were all at a level similar to smaller scale dungeon bosses. When looking at a guide, the player couldn’t only look at the bosses. Unrivaled Super Hottie said he had finished the guide in ten minutes, making many suspicious. Everyone looked down on him again and saw him as being too much of a noob.

“Whatever. Let’s not talk about it anymore. I’ll add him to the team and he can just leech off of us. He’ll understand once we go in.” Happy Sheep said.

“Why not let him be the main tank and see what he says?” Someone suggested.

Everyone laughed out loud. Speaking of this, if hundred player dungeon runs weren’t so limited and precious, they would have certainly agreed so they could laugh at him.

“Don’t joke around. We can let him be a tank when we run a different dungeon.” Someone else refuted.

“He’s just leeching anyways. It’s not like it matters whether he’s there or not!”

“It’ll be more efficient with me!”

Someone suddenly interrupted. Everyone turned. Sweat, it was Unrivaled Super Hottie. This guy had actually joined the chat. They had been chatting too fiercely and didn’t even notice the notification of him joining.

“Cough, what? Brother, you want to be the main tank?” Someone followed up.

“Main tank? I looked at a guide. I might need someone to lend me their equipment for the fourth, fifth, ninth, and final boss.” Ye Xiu said.

Sure enough, this guy had only looked at the bosses!

This guy wasn’t here to cheat them of their equipment, was he?

……

No one knew what to think, but Unrivaled Super Hottie had already joined the team and they felt too ashamed to say anything to his face. This situation was a bit different than when Unrivaled Super Hottie joined Guild Exterminate the Heavens. After all, Ye Xiu had gone to join Guild Exterminate the Heavens himself. He hadn’t needed to show his skill beforehand, which was why Crispy Bean immediately doubted his skill. In his current situation, Tyrannical Ambition had roped him over. Even if everyone doubted his skill, they could talk behind his back, but if they said it to his face, it would make Happy Sheep, who brought him over, feel embarrassed. They might be doubtful of Unrivaled Super Hottie, but at least, they had to give their team leader face.

“How about you be the main tank for now? When we get to the fourth and fifth tank, we can switch?” Someone said half-jokingly.

“Okay, but I don’t really remember much about this dungeon, so I don’t think I would be able to lead very well.” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone cried. He had only just looked at the guide and he wants to lead them?

Happy Sheep couldn’t bear it anymore: “I’ll lead! Are you sure you’re okay with being a tank?”

“I’ll have trouble with the fourth, fifth, ninth, and final boss.” Ye Xiu repeated.

“Okay okay. I understand. Then let’s start and see what happens?” Happy Sheep said.

“Sure.” Ye Xiu said and then went into the dungeon.

“He thought I was serious! He actually thought I was serious!!” Someone spoke in the chat again. This person remembered that besides the team chat, he could speak in the guild chat, which Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t have access to.

“He’s already entered the dungeon!”

“As the tank, he’s going to start pulling monsters. Shouldn’t we hurry up and go in?” Another person sneered.

“What are you guys talking about?” The other guild members were curious.

“A God has come to our guild!” Someone inadvertently said the truth.

“Oh?”

“Yeah, an exceptional God!” The truth continued.

“Who?”

“Unrivaled Super Hottie! Do you see that name!” Someone said.

“How arrogant? How is he a god?” A curious person asked.

“It’s hard to say in a single sentence…….”

“Okay, stop chattering. Let’s go in.” Happy Sheep hastily said. He didn’t think that his team would go to the guild chat to continue this chat. This this……. Wasn’t this equivalent to slapping the guild leader’s face? This guy was the person the guild leader had told him to bring over to the guild, yet his team was laughing at him.

Sure enough, the branch guild leader saw the chat and messaged Happy Sheep privately: “What’s up with this person?”

Happy Sheep explained what had happened to let the guild leader know that his team wasn’t trying to slap his face, but that this person really didn’t seem like any sort of expert.

“Then let him be the main tank and see what happens.” The branch guild leader instructed.

“Fighting in Tomb in the Sky with that equipment?” Happy Sheep felt a scared just saying it.

“What equipment does he have?” The branch guild leader clearly didn’t know the details.

Happy Sheep explained. The branch guild leader furrowed his brows and then said after a short pause: “He should be able to fight against the mob monsters, right? Let's have him fight with the mob monsters first…..”

“Okay!”

Chapter 561 – I Forgot

“Is he actually going to tank for us?”

The players in Happy Sheep’s team entered the dungeon one after the other. Happy Sheep received a message from the true tank in the team. This tank was clearly a kind person. He didn’t want Unrivaled Super Hottie to make a fool of himself and also thought about the safety of everyone else.

“Yeah, we’ll see how it goes first, but be on the lookout. As soon as he slips up falter, hurry and take over.” Happy Sheep said.

“Okay!” The original tank of the team, Seven Blossom Leaves, listened to Happy Sheep’s orders. He didn’t show any unwillingness to do so and didn’t say anything more after agreeing.

Happy Sheep was also very satisfied. Seven Blossom Leaves was truly a good person. He wasn’t like a lot of other tanks, who would curse at the healer for no reason when the team got wiped. As for Seven Blossom Leaves? Whenever the team wiped out, the first thing he would say was: “My mistake……” Then, he would analyze what he had done wrong.

He had just given him the task of keeping watch on Unrivaled Super Hottie. He could already foresee that if an accident happened, Seven Blossom Leaves would say he had made the mistake. A good person like Seven Blossom Leaves would probably act like this, even for someone as arrogant as Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Thinking of this, Happy Sheep was deeply moved. He decided that if an accident actually occurred, he definitely wouldn’t let Seven Blossom Leaves make himself the scapegoat. It would be okay for our own guild’s brothers, but for someone like Unrivaled Super Hottie? He can go kill himself. Why should someone as kind as Seven Blossom Leaves shoulder the blame?

Happy Sheep had been thinking the entire time. When he looked around, he saw that no one was around him anymore. Everyone had already entered the dungeon. He hastily ran into the teleport formation of the hundred player dungeon: Tomb in the Sky.

As the name implied, the dungeon Tomb in the Sky was a tomb in the sky. There were a total of nine minibosses, guarding nine magic-powered engines. After defeating the nine minibosses and destroying the nine engines, the Tomb in the Sky would lose its ability to fly and fall down to earth. At this moment, the Tomb in the Sky’s final guardian would appear and was also the dungeon’s final boss. If this final guardian was defeated, they would clear the dungeon. This dungeon’s hidden boss was the dark soul that resided within the tomb.

Whether or not the hidden boss appeared in the hundred player dungeon depended on luck, just like all of the other smaller dungeons in Glory. The only difference was that in this hundred player dungeon, the hidden boss could be fought after finishing the dungeon and didn’t have to be fought immediately. It wasn’t like normal dungeons, where the boss could suddenly jump out of nowhere. After all, rewards in the hundred player dungeon depended on progress made in the dungeon. If a hidden boss suddenly jumped out and killed everyone, it would be too depressing for the players. If the hidden boss was successfully killed, there would be an additional 20% progress reward, even if the dungeon had already been cleared.

When Happy Sheep’s team entered the Tomb in the Sky, everyone checked if there was a hidden boss or not. Happy Sheep was the last to enter, but he had already seen from the chat that no there would be no hidden boss for this run.

Even though there was no hidden boss, there would be another point of interest in this dungeon run. Currently, Unrivaled Super Hottie was in the front with his sword and shield up, but there was no one around him. All of the other players stayed back, maintaining a good distance from him as if he were the plague. Happy Sheep thought it was funny, but at this moment, Seven Blossom Leaves walked out from the group and stood next to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s side.

“You be the main tank. I’ll be the off tank. If you can’t hold on, call for me. There’s no need to force yourself.” Seven Blossom Leaves kindly advised.

“Oh? We only have an off tank? There’s no third or fourth tank?” Ye Xiu asked.

The third and fourth tank were the original off tank and third tank. Now that Unrivaled Super Hottie had become the main tank and Seven Blossom Leaves took the position of off tank, the other two naturally fell to the third and fourth tank. Unfortunately, the original fourth tank now became the fifth tank…… However, the Tomb in the Sky didn’t need five tanks! What a tragedy!

The original off tank and third tank, or the current third and fourth tank, clearly weren’t as kind as Seven Blossom Leaves. With Unrivaled Super Hottie calling them out and seeing Seven Blossom Leaves look around for them, the two finally stepped forward unwillingly.

“Everyone step it up! Let’s try harder!” Ye Xiu cheered.

“......” Everyone wanted to point their middle fingers at him, but resisted.

“Are the Clerics ready?” Ye Xiu asked again.

“......” No one uttered a word. Luckily, one of the Clerics was Happy Sheep. As the team leader, he had the responsibility of upholding the team atmosphere. At this moment, he stood out and replied, “Ready!” The other Clerics felt embarrassed to not say anything now and also shouted out.

“DPSers……”

“Yes yes yes, we’re ready!”

This time, Ye Xiu had only spoken a single word, when the DPSers impatiently interrupted him. This guy kept on warning them endlessly. Did he think he was a God or something?

“I was just going to say DPSers, don’t be too hasty.” Ye Xiu grinned.

“......” The DPSers fell silent.

“Then I’m going to pull some monsters over?” Ye Xiu asked.

Go kill yourself! Everyone shouted in their minds. The Clerics wanted to pretend they disconnected, while those who weren’t Clerics wanted to tie up the Clerics.

Unfortunately, these weren’t options. The team leader Happy Sheep said, “Pull!” Unrivaled Super Hottie rushed forward. In everyone’s eyes, his posture was disgustingly ugly.

“He’s going to die immediately.” Someone quietly whispered.

“Yes.” It wasn’t convenient for them to say these things in chat, but they could still talk to each other in private. If this Unrivaled Super Hottie only looked at the bosses in the guides, then he would neglect many difficult problems in the dungeon. For example, when entering the tomb…… However, no one wanted to remind him. Everyone wanted to watch him suffer!

“Be careful, there’s a trap at the entrance!” Someone shouted. This voice wasn’t unfamiliar to them. It was the original main tank, Seven Blossom Leaves.

“Sigh……” Everyone sighed. Seven Blossom Leaves was truly too kind.

“Yi?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ha ha ha, look at him. It looks like he got a cramp. Did he get sick?” All they heard was a “Yi?” Then, Unrivaled Super Hottie suddenly started shaking. Some of the players immediately began ridiculing him. However, as soon as they spoke, they saw a cold light suddenly jump out from the side of Unrivaled Super Hottie. A spike had shot out of the ground!

Cheng cheng cheng cheng!

Spike after spike pierced the earth and shot out of the ground, all from beneath Unrivaled Super Hottie’s feet. However, not a single one hit him because Unrivaled Super Hottie kept on shaking. It made everyone feel nauseous, but he just happened to dodge every spikes every time.

“Is he dodging them?”

Everyone was astonished. They were clearly seeing it, but they had a hard time believing it. His movements were too minute and quick to see.

Living through this spike trap wasn’t uncommon. The trap had been completely figured out with the bodies of countless players. All of the players in Happy Sheep’s team knew how to walk through the trap without triggering it. However, getting through the trap in this way was something they had never seen before.

“Oh, there’s a trap here. Right, I totally forgot.” Everyone heard Unrivaled Super Hottie mumble to himself. Then, he turned around and shouted to everyone: “There’s a trap here! Everyone, be careful!”

F*ck, who needs you to tell us!! They once again resisted sending him a middle finger.

“Incredible. You actually dodged all of them.” At this moment, Seven Blossom Leaves had already reached Unrivaled Super Hottie’s side.

“You flatter me! You’re not bad either!” Ye Xiu said.

“You can get past the traps without triggering them. If you forget, then just follow me!” Seven Blossom Leaves walked to the front.

Seven Blossom Leaves, can you not be so kind! Everyone cried. However, they had second thoughts. Someone as arrogant as Unrivaled Super Hottie might say in an arrogant tone: “No need. I can get past the traps even if I step on all of them!”

But in reality, they heard him say: “Really? You can do that? Then let me see how you do it.” Unrivaled Super Hottie followed behind Seven Blossom Leaves, leaving everyone speechless.

As a result, besides the few spikes that Unrivaled Super Hottie triggered in the beginning, none of the other traps were set off. They took the safe route and passed by safely.

“Is everyone through?” They heard Unrivaled Super Hottie asked them with a concerned tone.

“We’re all through.” Only a small number of players replied.

Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t seem to mind. After passing through the traps, he spun around twice: “Two paths? Hm? One second, let me check the guide.”

“Okay okay. You don’t need to look at it. Take the left path.” Happy Sheep said helplessly.

“Okay.” Unrivaled Super Hottie headed the left.

“You……” Happy Sheep only said one word before something happened. The others were elated, but one person still spoke out: “Careful!”

The moment the warning came out, two stone statues on the left path suddenly began moving.

The stone swords didn’t have any light reflecting off of them. As they tore through the air, they headed straight for Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“Woah!” Unrivaled Super Hottie yelled and immediately rolled.

“F*CK!!” This brilliant dodge made Happy Sheep shout in anger. Because he was the team leader, he had been patient with Unrivaled Super Hottie, but at this moment, he was about to start cursing. The reason was because he was the team leader! For someone who kept on making mistakes, he would always curse at them relentlessly.

Unrivaled Super Hottie rolled forward. Even though he dodged the two swords, he rolled into range of another two statues. His one move lured in four statues!

The smaller creeps in hundred player dungeons were all at the same level as normal small dungeon bosses.

For some stronger teams, defeating four statues at the same time was possible, but for Happy Sheep’s team, which seeked safety, they only had high confidence in pulling one statue. After getting familiar with the dungeon, they gradually began pulling two statues. From time to time, there would even be scary moments, but this time, this guy with his ridiculous name actually pulled four statues at once?!

What did he think they were? Tyrannical Ambition’s main team?

Chapter 562 – Gather Around the Tank

It looked like he was underestimating this hundred player dungeon. No one was happy. Pulling four statues at once should have meant that he thought very highly of the team, but they still weren’t happy. That’s why being a tank was difficult.

The four statues were the same class, Blade Masters. They were a bit different from playable blademasters though. They used stone swords, not light sabers, and didn’t posses sword aura. They attacked with plain and simple swordplay. Compared to playable Blade Masters, their attacks had lower range. Playable Blade Masters had a variety of skills, such as Sword Draw or attacked by using their sword aura, allowing them to attack farther than their weapon’s physical capabilities. However, these four stone statues didn’t have these types of methods.

Four statues had been pulled. After Happy Sheep cursed, he immediately raised his voice. He was truly afraid Unrivaled Super Hottie would roll forward once again and pull another two stone statues. Defeating six stone statues at once was a feat that no one had ever pulled off before. Happy Sheep had no intentions on attempting to do so.

Luckily, Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t roll forward again. After another two statues slashed at him, he jumped backwards and dodged another two slashes. However, the first two stone statues had already begun hacking at him again.

A white glow surrounded Unrivaled Super Hottie as if he carried a small Cosmos. He had instantly activated Knight’s Spirit.

He took a step, lifted his shield with his left hand, and swung his sword with his right hand. Under the effects of Knight’s Spirit, this attack was called Heroic Charge!

Unrivaled Super Hottie moved faster than the stone statue and his sword struck the stone statue’s waist.

The stone statue fell, and Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t waste any time.

The Heroic Charge under Knight’s Spirit couldn’t stop!

Bang!

The second stone statue was also sent flying and smashed into the first stone statue.

As for the third and fourth stone statue? They hadn’t been in Heroic Charge’s path. Even so, after two bangs, the third and fourth stone statue were also sent flying.

Everyone was stunned, especially the Knights on the team.

“Was that an…… Arc Charge?” The third tank said to the fourth tank after a moment of hesitation.

“It looked like it……” The fourth tank didn’t dare to believe his eyes.

“It must have been.” Seven Blossom Leaves confirmed. He had seen it clearly. If it hadn’t been an Arc Charge, let alone the third and fourth stone statue, even the second stone statue wouldn’t have been sent flying.

The third and fourth tank had no words left to say.

Arc Charge meant the charge hadn’t been pathed in a straight line and travelled along a curved path instead. Moving in a curved path wasn’t difficult, but the hard part was actually getting the result one wanted and hitting the intended target.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Arc Charge had actually knocked away four targets that hadn’t been on a straight line. This required incredible precision, calculation, and control. Only an experienced Knight could understand the difficulty of this maneuver.

At this moment, the four stone statues had been sent smashing into one another.

Unrivaled Super Hottie flew up. With a Heroic Leap, he swung his sword downwards at one of the four stone statues. However, the damage was passed through each statue and into the next. The Heroic Leap under Knight’s Spirit also had another name, Fair Heroic Leap.

The original Heroic Leap dealt large amounts of damage to a single target, while the remaining targets would receive damage from the shockwave. However, Fair Heroic Leap would deal the same amount of damage to every target. The damage dealt depended on the defense of the target that had been hit by the leap. The others would receive the same amount of damage as well.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attack did the same amount of damage to each of the four statues. The grouped up statues couldn’t stand up for a moment.

“Attack!!” Ye Xiu shouted.

The others saw him fighting the four stone statues alone and were somewhat dazed. When they heard him shout, they finally woke up.

Some attacked, while others hesitated.

Four stone statues? How were they going to win?

The Clerics felt awkward raising their staffs because they didn’t have anything to do for now. When Unrivaled Super Hottie fought the four stone statues, he hadn’t received any damage.

“Everyone, forward!” Seven Blossom Leaves suddenly shouted to the third and fourth tank, while advancing.

“Heroic Charge!” Ye Xiu yelled.

“Understood!” Seven Blossom Leaves seemed like he already knew as he charged forward with a white aura surrounding his character.

Even though he didn’t have the ability to knock down all four statues with a single Arc Charge, the four statues were all in the same spot, so he only needed to charge straight forward.

The first smashed into the second, the second smashed into the third. The third smashed into the fourth. The charge didn’t lose momentum either because this was also a Heroic Charge.

Bang…...

It sounded like there were echoes.

The four stone statues were sent flying to the side by Seven Blossom Leaves, knocking them back into their original stone platforms.

Seven Blossom Leaves had done the charge quite quickly. He leaped into the air and crashed down with a Heroic Leap. The four stone statues had just recovered and steadied themselves, but were immediately slammed back into the ground once more.

The attacks from the DPS classes had already surged forth. The stone platform instantly turned into an eye-dazzling scene. The space was too narrow. Many of the close ranged classes couldn’t get near and could only stay back.

“I’ll send you one!” Someone shouted. One of the stone statues unexpectedly rushed out. Unrivaled Super Hottie was in front, running in an ugly manner. He was waving his sword around in a shameful way, provoking the stone statue.

“This time, you don’t need to learn from me.” Ye Xiu didn’t forget to tell Seven Blossom Leaves.

“I know.” Seven Blossom Leaves laughed, “Third tank!”

The third tank, the former off tank, heard Seven Blossom Leaves’ shout and got ready to take over from him out of habit.

When he saw Seven Blossom’s Leaves’ actions, he immediately understood what to do.

He activated Knight’s Spirit, Heroic Charge, and then Fair Heroic Leap.

The three stone statues were powerless to fight back. They only had enough time to do something, when they were sent flying by another Knight.

The last one had been pulled by Unrivaled Super Hottie over to the close ranged classes that couldn’t squeeze into the space.

The Clerics were also on this side. Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t taken any damage when fighting against the four stone statues. Now that he had pulled one over, that stone statue began doing damage to the other players. It was as if Unrivaled Super Hottie was giving the Clerics work to do.

“Control the field well! Throw a Shururu!” Seven Blossom Leaves directed the battle.

The Witches didn’t dare delay for the true tank in their hearts and immediately threw their Doll Shururus.

“Fourth tank!” When the situation couldn’t be controlled any further, Seven Blossom Leaves called out.

The fourth tank had been prepared. He activated Knight’s Spirit before using Heroic Charge and Fair Heroic Leap.

The original arrangement ended at this moment. The four Knights couldn’t make this an endless loop. Heroic Charge and Heroic Leap didn’t have too long of a cooldown, but Knight’s Spirit wasn’t a shared skill that those under Level 20 could use. It had a very long cooldown…...

However, the team had five tanks.

The fifth tank raised his sword and shield in preparation.

However, another Knight wasn’t enough to make it an endless cycle. The cycle would still fall here, but seeing the health values of the stone statues, the experienced players had already come to a conclusion.

Even though the stone statues were as strong as normal dungeon bosses, the number of players here wasn’t five or ten players. With so many players attacking, they did much more damage than what five or ten players could ever do.

As long as they controlled the battle and attacked freely, they would kill these stone statues at the same speed as killing mobs in normal dungeons.

The fifth tank finally acted.

When he completed his set of skills, complete control over the three stone statues ended. Without Knight’s Spirit, the effects from Charge and Heroic Leap were different. The two skills wouldn’t be able to knock down all three stone statues.

The three stone statues were almost dead though, so it looked like they could still persevere.

Seven Blossom Leaves suddenly felt his head hurt! Because they had completely controlled these stone statues’ movements, they hadn’t kept track of the aggro. After their control over the statues ended, who would they attack?

No one knew.

Confusion over aggro usually resulted in a team wipe out…...

“Everyone spread out!!” Seeing that the three stone statues were still alive, Seven Blossom Leaves immediately ordered and then shouted.

This wasn’t a regular shout, but a skill: Roar!

All three stone statues were within Roar’s range, so all of their attacks were now directed at him.

Seven Blossom Leaves raised his shield to defend against the three incoming sword strikes. Under the heavy blows, Seven Blossom Leaves stumbled and his health dropped to half. With the three stone statues aggroed onto him, if he took another attack from all three, he would die!

At this moment, there was another shout.

The third tank had used Roar too.

Seven Blossom Leaves let out a sigh of relief, but soon discovered that the small amount of time he had rescued wasn’t being used by the DPSers, who were in a frenzy.

“HURRY UP AND ATTACK!!” Seven Blossom Leaves roared. He knew the DPSers hadn’t yet reacted. With his shout, the three stone statues rushed forward and lifted their swords.

They couldn’t waste any time! Seven Blossom Leaves was worried. After shouting, the DPSers woke up and immediately began attacking the stone statues heading towards the third tank.

The third tank blocked the attacks and his health dropped as disastrously as Seven Blossom Leave’s.

The fourth tank was ready too. He stood a certain distance away and then roared. The three stone statues immediately switched targets. This time, the DPSers didn’t need any reminders and hastily chased after the statues.

The fifth tank was eager to try as well. He chose a spot just on the edge of Roar’s range to force the stone statues to run a bit more and win more time.

His time to shine quickly came. The fifth tank immediately Roared, but Seven Blossom Leaves shouted in response: “Not good!”

“What’s not good?” The fifth tank stared blankly. Weren’t the three stone statues coming towards him? He had stood in a good spot.

“Behind you!” Everyone shouted.

The fifth tank turned around. Sh*t. He had forgotten about the fourth stone statue! With his roar, not only had he pulled the three stone statues, but the fourth one as well. The combined attacks of four statues…… The fifth tank’s face went pale. He knew his own stats. His equipment wasn’t as good as the previous three tank's’ equipment. He definitely wouldn’t be able to take all four hits.

But before the attacks came, he heard another roar, followed by someone’s voice: “What’s there to be afraid of? There’s still another tank that hasn’t moved out yet!”

Chapter 563 – Bro, Slow Down

Right when the four stone statues were about to attack the fifth tank, they suddenly turned around and charged towards a different target: the self-proclaimed tank Unrivaled Super Hottie.

In this instant, no one had time to refute his self-proclamation. Everyone knew what was important at this moment.

“Hurry up and attack!” Their accepted tank Seven Blossom Leaves and their team leader Happy Sheep shouted at the same time.

The DPSers didn’t dare to be slow. At this crucial moment, they didn’t care about whether or not their attacks would cause the aggro to go out of control or waste mana. They just fired whatever damaging skills they possessed.

The path lit up with the bright effects from all of the different types of skills. The four statues enshrouded in light could clearly be seen. The stone statues had high resistance, so many of the crowd control skills had no effect on them. It didn’t matter though. They just needed to get rid of their last slivers of health.

Bang!

Finally, a stone statue crumbled and fell to the ground with a loud rumble. Soon afterwards, the second and third also followed. All that remained were bits of stone that no different in size from pebbles on the road.

Only the fourth stone statue was left!

Because the damage output hadn’t been equally spread amongst the statues, the rate at which their health dropped differed. This fourth stone statue still had quite a bit of health left and was still rushing towards Unrivaled Super Hottie.

However, the crisis had been averted. A single stone statue wasn’t anything difficult to deal with. Unrivaled Super Hottie had defended against a stone statue before, so there weren’t any problems. Seven Blossom Leaves had originally planned on using a Provoke to get the stone statue to attack him instead, but he realized it wasn’t necessary. Thus, he decided not to use Provoke and went forward to provide assistance.

Then, he saw a huge storm of skills fly out, engulfing the fourth stone statue and Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Seven Blossom Leaves was startled.

Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie wouldn’t take damage, this type of attack affected the tank’s view and decision making. The tank would usually dodge the attacks anyways. However, seeing how the battle was at its end, there was no point in fussing over trivial matters, so Seven Blossom Leaves decided not to say anything.

The kind Seven Blossom Leaves couldn’t have known that this wave of attacks represented the team’s resentment! The attacks wouldn’t kill Unrivaled Super Hottie, but it would still feel good to see the attacks land on him, no?

Bang!

Another rumble and bits of stone flew out from the light. The bits of stone landed on the ground and crumbled into dust. As the light faded away, the fourth stone statue was already missing its head. It rocked sideways and then crashed to the ground.

Everyone let out a sigh of relief.

When the other three stone statues had fallen, the crisis had passed, but they could only relax after the entire battle had concluded.

After taking a deep breath, they turned towards Unrivaled Super Hottie and glared at him.

Of course, only the people in real life could glare. In game, it just looked like everyone had turned towards Unrivaled Super Hottie. It was also quite a spectacular sight.

“Comrades, good work.” Unrivaled Super Hottie turned to look at everyone and waved his hands.

“F*CK!” Everyone shouted.

“Let’s keep going!” Unrivaled Super Hottie pointed his sword forward and ran out.

Happy Sheep watched him run forward. Everyone was already beginning to turn towards him. If he didn’t say anything, the others would lose respect for him. He immediately chased after Unrivaled Super Hottie and shouted: “Bro, wait one second.”

“Hm? Are you talking to me?” Unrivaled Super Hottie turned to look, but his feet didn’t stop moving.

“Yes, yes. I’m talking to you. Hold on for one second.” Happy Sheep yelled.

“Oh?” Unrivaled Super Hottie stopped. He saw the others weren’t moving either. Their gazes were all on him.

“Did you make a mistake? Were we not supposed to take the left path?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

“No.” Happy Sheep hastily replied, “It’s like this. Bro, slow down. Let’s not pull four stone statues at once. The pressure is a bit too much.”

“Didn’t it go smoothly?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

Happy Sheep was suddenly stumped. From the results, there didn’t appear to be any danger. However, the battle made their hearts jump in fear the entire way through. If they didn’t achieve the ideal crowd control effects, the four stone statues would attack the Knights and the Clerics would have too much pressure on them. For tanks, if they had milk, they were gods. If they didn’t have milk, they were melons. If the tanks turned into melons, the entire team would turn into a melon farm. Anyone could be plucked away at a moment’s notice. This was why when four stone statues had been pulled, Happy Sheep felt like the risk was too big. No, this was what the entire team felt.

“This. If someone makes a small mistake and the statues aren’t controlled well, wouldn’t it be disastrous?” Happy Sheep reasoned.

“There’s me!” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

It’s because of you that there’s so much trouble! Happy Sheep cried in his mind. At this moment, other players interrupted: “You? Can you control all the statues by yourself?”

“With me setting up the foundation, everything becomes quite easy.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

Those who weren’t skilled enough couldn’t grasp the meaning behind his words. Seven Blossom Leaves immediately understood though and asked: “You have confidence in using Arc Charge to gather monsters?”

“A piece of cake.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

Everyone hissed as a sign of displeasure. Only Seven Blossom Leaves honestly said: “Respect.”

“If you just practice a bit, you can get it down too.” Unrivaled Super Hottie encouraged Seven Blossom Leaves. The hissing noise increased in volume. Seven Blossom Leaves was such a good person! His popularity within the team didn’t need to be mentioned. He was one of those guys who, even if you found him disagreeable, you couldn’t hate him. When they heard Unrivaled Super Hottie act like he was giving advice, quite a few felt angry in place of Seven Blossom Leaves. Right when they were about to speak up for Seven Blossom Leaves, they heard him speak first: “I can’t. I’ve practiced for a long time. I still can’t get it.”

“Hm…… there’s nothing I can do then. It doesn’t require intense mechanical skill. It depends entirely on experience and awareness and is executed by relying on intuition. If you need to make calculations beforehand, then you won’t be able to act on time.” Unrivaled Super Hottie explained.

“Yes, yes. It’s exactly so.” Seven Blossom Leaves agreed.

Seeing how Seven Blossom Leaves had a why-couldn’t-we-have-met-earlier look, they could only stare blankly. Happy Sheep wanted Unrivaled Super Hottie to follow their usual strategy. Then, they saw their guild’s accepted tank, Seven Blossom Leaves, move farther away. After a short moment, he brought back four stone statues…...

“F*CK!” Everyone cursed, but in the blink of an eye, the two Knights brought the stone statues to them.

“These four stone statues seem like Battle Mages. They’re different from the previous Blade Masters. This is the troublesome part about using Arc Charge because you must be able to make adjustments according to the target. Actually, the current situation is fairly simple. If our opponents were targets with completely different stats, then using Arc Charge may make it impossible to hit every target. For circumstances like these, if you decide to use Arc Charge, make sure you don’t leave any openings. If there’s an opening and you meet an expert, your opponent will attack and interrupt you right in the middle of it.” The others could hear Unrivaled Super Hottie chattering non-stop.

“Right right right, you’re right.” Seven Blossom Leaves felt moved.

The others were speechless. What could they say? The monsters had been pulled already, they had to attack! Then, they suddenly heard Unrivaled Super Hottie shout: “Not good!”

“What’s wrong?” Seven Blossom Leaves asked.

“I forgot to look at my cooldowns! Knight’s Spirit isn’t up yet!” Unrivaled Super Hottie yelled.

“Uh oh!!” Seven Blossom Leaves immediately understood the severity of the problem. Without Knight’s Spirit, they would just be using normal Charges. Only Heroic Charge would be able to achieve the desired effect. The entire team heard this and felt like crying. F*ck, was the team going to wipe out?

“A crisis has come, comrades!” Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted.

“It’s all your fault!!!” Everyone replied together.

“It’s my mistake. I forgot to wait for my cooldowns to come up.” Seven Blossom Leaves began to take the blame for him.

“Everyone pull one!” Unrivaled Super Hottie said to the Knights.

“Our healing won’t be able to keep up!” Happy Sheep panicked.

“We only need it for a short while!”

“The aggro will shift off the tank easily like that……” Happy Sheep was depressed! Usually, the Clerics would take care of one tank together. This didn’t mean all the Clerics were necessary to protect the tank. This was done in order to control the aggro. Against a boss with high attack, if one or two Clerics rapidly healed the tank, the Cleric might establish enough aggro for the enemy to chain to them.

To put it simply, it was like if a DPSer attacked an enemy with the same strength as a boss. With such a high damage output, it would be strange if the aggro didn’t shift from the tank to the DPSer.

Even though there were differences in aggro for healing and damage, the theory was the same. Boss’ did a lot of damage with their attacks. If the healing class healed all of that damage, the aggro would naturally accumulate, but with many Clerics, the healing and aggro would be distributed among all of them. If a single Cleric had to take responsibility for the healing, let alone being able to heal all of that damage, the aggro would pulled off the tank. With the healer dead, the tank would turn into a melon and the rest of the team would also turn into melons too…… This was a team.

“Don’t be afraid. You just have to hang on for a bit. My cooldowns are almost up! When pulling the monsters, pay attention to their positions. Try to make it easier for me to charge at them.” Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted.

“How about you not go forward?” Happy Sheep saw Unrivaled Super Hottie was about to pull one and immediately called out to him.

“What?”

“Your equipment. If you get hit… the aggro will go off you immediately.” Happy Sheep explained.

“Then isn’t it fine as long as he doesn’t hit me?” Unrivaled Super Hottie grinned. He turned around and attacked a stone statue. This time, the four stone statues were Battle Mages. The one attacked by Unrivaled Super Hottie used Dragon Tooth and stabbed at him with its stone spear. Unrivaled Super seemed to have predicted it. He dodged and slammed his shield into the stone statue.

Chapter 564 – Hold It Steady!

In the previous wave, Unrivaled Super Hottie had pulled one of the stone statues away for the melee classes, who couldn’t squeeze in, to attack. At that time, several Clerics surrounded Unrivaled Super Hottie waiting to act, so they had a good idea of how much damage Unrivaled Super Hottie would take from an enemy attack. This was why Happy Sheep was worried.

Many of the players rolled their eyes when they saw Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attitude, but the Knights had already engaged with the stone statues in battle and several rounds passed in the blink of an eye. For Seven Blossom Leaves and the other tanks, the Clerics supporting them were busy healing. As for Unrivaled Super Hottie, the Clerics that Happy Sheep arranged to support him had their staffs raised, staring blankly at each other.

Why? Because there was nothing to do! The other Knights lost health rapidly while fighting against the stone statues, but Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t even taken a single hit yet.

This scene made everyone rub their eyes. The DPSers hadn’t moved yet. They were still waiting for the Knights to establish enough aggro. However, this allowed them see the distinct contrast between the Knights. Seven Blossom Leaves and the other Knights constantly had a white glow around them; their Clerics were very busy. Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t have any glows around him; the surrounding Clerics could set up a table and start playing mahjong if they wanted to.

“This….. this…...:”

Everyone was speechless. They couldn’t find any words to describe the scene in front of them. What should they do? If he keeps fighting like that, did he even need them? Couldn’t he just kill it by himself?

Everyone was still in awe, when they suddenly heard a thump. Unrivaled Super Hottie had been hit by the stone statue’s spear. Seeing this attack hit the target, everyone unexpectedly let out a sigh of relief. If he actually kept on dodging and didn’t get hit by the stone statue, then he shouldn’t even be playing in the game.

The Clerics around Unrivaled Super Hottie scrambled to begin healing. Even though it had only been one hit, Unrivaled Super Hottie truly had lackluster equipment. A single hit from a hundred player dungeon monster hurt quite a bit, but with three Clerics, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s health quickly rose back to a safe level.

In addition, Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t get hit by the follow-up attack. The next attack was dodged by him. His character was constantly moving; there was never a moment where he stood still. Everyone could see clearly now. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s fighting strategy wasn’t the normal strategy of a Knight. He treated the battle like a PvP match and was trying hard to make the enemy attacks ineffective.

This type of strategy relieved the need for the Clerics’ help. Using three Clerics to support Unrivaled Super Hottie was clearly excessive. The three had gotten into overhealing situations several times. Overhealing meant the amount they healed was greater than the health their target lost, which wasted mana and established needless aggro, so it wasn’t good.

The DPSers on Unrivaled Super Hottie’s side were very depressed too because with Unrivaled Super Hottie constantly moving around, the stone statue wouldn’t be staying still either. The melee DPSers had to constantly move around and the long-ranged DPSers had to constantly predict where the statue’s next move would be.

In any case, it was still easy dealing with the stone statue. No accidents came about, but this strategy relied on the player’s skill.

Because it depended on a player’s skill to work, it meant it had higher risk. As soon as the player made a mistake and the Clerics had to rapidly heal, the aggro might go off the tank. So even though the Clerics didn’t have much to do, they were still very focused.

The rest weren’t sure what to think of the situation.

They were obviously afraid that Unrivaled Super Hottie would make a mistake because a single mistake might get the Clerics killed. If the Clerics died, then the run would be over. They could kill off small monsters, but it would be difficult to beat any of the bosses.

But if this guy didn’t make any mistakes, then it meant that this guy had some serious skill. Most of them didn’t have that type of skill, so the guy that they had been looking down upon, suddenly became far greater than them. This wasn’t a good feeling.

To put it simply, it was a birds of a feather flock together issue.

The weak ones would be looked down upon. The strong ones would be pushed out. Only those at a similar skill level could coexist harmoniously.

The weak ones could be laughed at, but strong ones would leave a sour feeling when being excluded.

Most people hoped that others would be weaker than them, never stronger.

Thus, most of the players in Happy Sheep’s team hoped to see Unrivaled Super Hottie fail. However, their hopes never came true. Nothing dangerous had happened yet for Unrivaled Super Hottie, but the fourth tank had gotten into a crisis.

“We can’t heal enough! We can’t heal enough!!” The Clerics supporting the fourth tank shouted.

With these knights’ skill, even if they couldn’t hang on forever, they shouldn’t have fallen into a crisis so quickly. However, the fourth tank had been distracted by Unrivaled Super Hottie and didn’t block an attack properly with his shield. The spear struck his body. The drop in health exceeded the Clerics’ expectations. Seeing the fierce incoming attacks, the Clerics immediately felt pressured and hastily called for help.

The fifth tank heard the call and went over. The team had a total of five tanks including Unrivaled Super Hottie. At this moment, the fifth tank didn’t have any monster to pull. He originally thought he would need to help Unrivaled Super Hottie, but who would have thought the fourth tank would need it first.

“Pay attention to that side! What are you doing staring at me the whole time?” Ye Xiu spoke. He had three Clerics on him, but they weren’t very busy. In order to prevent overhealing, the three took turns healing. When the fourth tank encountered a crisis, the three were distracted and Ye Xiu had to remind them.

The three Clerics woke up and immediately went to help the fourth tank. This didn’t take them long because they stood in a position where they could cover the entire field and specifically cover the tanks.

The fourth tank’s situation quickly turned around. As for Unrivaled Super Hottie? Nothing happened to him.

Glory had all types of statistics, including healing. Some of the players opened up the healing charts to take a look. The amount of healing Unrivaled Super Hottie had received was actually a bit lower than the other three tanks.

Unrivaled Super Hottie had way inferior equipment to the other three. The amount of damage that he received per attack was much greater than the what the other tanks would take. The amount of healing he received was less than the other tanks too, which meant that Unrivaled Super Hottie had taken way fewer hits. His continuous dodging was very effective, but was used to make up for by his lackluster equipment.

This situation couldn’t last until the stone statues died though. The knights were gradually losing health. If not, why would they be scared of pulling four stone statues at once?

The main purpose was to wait until Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Knight’s Spirit came back up. Then, he could use Heroic Charge to gather the monsters. They could kill off the monsters this way.

However, Unrivaled Super Hottie was using Arc Charge. The problem was exactly what Unrivaled Super Hottie had told Seven Blossom Leaves. Their dungeon run depended entirely on this extremely difficult maneuver. The ones who understood this were very nervous.

How much longer until Knight’s Spirit came off cooldown? This data was available to everyone, so some of the players remembered it. Ye Xiu wasn’t the only one counting down.

“It should be soon…..” Many of the players quietly thought to themselves. Suddenly, they heard a voice: “Pay attention to your position! Pay attention to your position! My Knight’s Spirit is almost off cooldown.”

Seven Blossom Leaves saw Unrivaled Super Hottie’s position and immediately pulled his stone statue over to a good spot. The other Knights originally didn’t think much of Unrivaled Super Hottie, but seeing how he was doing the exact same thing as them with lesser equipment made it so that although they might not like Unrivaled Super Hottie, they couldn’t look down on him either.

Especially when they saw Seven Blossom Leaves act so sincerely towards Unrivaled Super Hottie, there was nothing they could say. After all, Seven Blossom Leaves was accepted by them. If they accepted him and he accepted Unrivaled Super Hottie, what else could they say? It was true that Seven Blossom Leaves was a good person, but even a good person shouldn’t respect such an ignorant idiot right?

As a result, the third and fourth tank saw Seven Blossom Leaves follow Unrivaled Super Hottie’s instructions and even though they didn’t want to, they did so anyways.

“Good good good! That’s perfect. Don’t move.” Seeing the three move, Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted.

Seven Blossom Leaves was trying to improve. When he heard Unrivaled Super Hottie’s approval, he felt puzzled: “Isn’t it a bit off?”

“You guys are good enough. I’m going to go for it!!” Unrivaled Super Hottie yelled and then took over for the other three.

The four knights were all in different spots, but their stone statues were all in a straight line. Unrivaled Super Hottie activated Knight’s Spirit and yelled, “I’m coming!”

In the end, he didn’t need to use Arc Charge. He just charged forward in a straight line. Bang bang bang bang! The four stone statues were hit by Heroic Charge and their situation became the same as the previous four Blade Master statues.

Chapter 565 – A Tank That Makes Others Embarrassed

This time, the DPSers were prepared. As soon as the four stone statues slammed into the walls and started swaying back and forth, the DPSers attacked.

They didn’t need to worry about dealing too much damage and shifting the aggro off the tanks. The purpose of the strategy being employed wasn’t to control their aggro, but rather the field. By chaining their attacks appropriately, the targets would be unable to fight back. Under this type of situation, who cared about aggro? It wasn’t important at all.

After a Just Heroic Leap, Unrivaled Super Hottie pulled a stone statue out. Behind him, Seven Blossom Leaves and the other Knights had their Knight’s Spirit coming off cooldown soon. The tanks lined up, ready to use a Heroic Charge and Just Heroic Leap. The timing wasn’t difficult to grasp. They simply needed to attack when their Knight’s Spirit came off cooldown.

The same scenario repeated itself. Moreover, compared to their first time, everyone knew what to expect. Their execution may not have been completely perfect, but it turned out even better than the previous time.

Unrivaled Super Hottie? At this moment, he was soloing another stone statue. Another bunch of Clerics waited upon him. They didn’t know the first time, but now they knew that Unrivaled Super Hottie could make up for his lacking equipment with pure skill alone, so the Clerics weren’t nervous anymore. They might not have been nervous anymore, but it turned out Unrivaled Super Hottie wasn’t nervous anymore either. Compared to before, he wasn’t dodging like before and just stood there attacking.

Because of his lackluster equipment, the Clerics became nervous again. The Clerics wanted to smash their heads into the wall, but everyone understood Unrivaled Super Hottie’s incredible skill already, so they didn’t dare be negligent. They knew that his previous way of fighting must have been very exhausting. He only needed to dodge at crucial moments. There was no need to waste energy when it wasn’t necessary.

With the Clerics supporting him, Unrivaled Super Hottie wasn’t in any danger just standing there. The other Knights and DPSers grew more accustomed to the strategy and their overall damage output increased. These four statues crumbled faster than the previous four statues. Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t need to rescue everyone with a Roar this time.

The four stone statues crumbled and everyone let out another sigh of relief. This time, the team leader Happy Sheep was in a very different mood than before. After killing these four statues, his impression of Unrivaled Super Hottie became much more favorable.

This was because when Unrivaled Super Hottie went to gather the monsters, he didn’t use an Arc Charge. Instead, he set it up so that the four statues lined up and then simply charged straight at them.

Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t chosen to show off his skill. He chose to coordinate with everyone and executed a safer and simpler method. Happy Sheep appreciated his decision.

A team leader had to consider things from the team’s perspective, not just their own. Team leaders hated people who wanted to be heroes. Unrivaled Super Hottie could have chosen to show off and be a hero, but he chose to use a simpler method instead. Many players wouldn’t have noticed.

Moreover, after fighting this way, Happy Sheep realized that Unrivaled Super Hottie had helped them create a new strategy. This strategy didn’t rely on him either. Lining the monsters up in a straight line and using a Heroic Charge directly at them was something any Knight could do. This type of strategy was very practical.

In the next waves of stone statues, the other Knights became the ones gathering the monsters.

There were a total of 24 stone statues. Every four had the same class, so the players liked to group them together. The six classes that the six groups of stone statues had were randomly determined at the start of each run.

After the initial moment of fear, Happy Sheep’s team smoothly cleared through two groups with a not-so-difficult strategy too. For the next four groups, Seven Blossom Leaves, the third, fourth, and fifth tank each took turns gathering the stone statues together. All of them successfully completed their task.

As the groups of stone statues fell one after the other, everyone gradually realized that Unrivaled Super Hottie wasn’t so simple after all. Whenever Unrivaled Super Hottie said anything again, no one would boo at him. Those who wanted to boo at him could only quietly boo in their heads, because everyone recognized his strength.

After passing through the stone statues and another trap, they finally reached the first boss.

If they touched the gear, the boss would immediately appear to stop them. The player who touched the gear would be designated as the boss’s aggro target. In the Tomb in the Sky, it was extremely easy to set up the nine boss' aggro. The main tank just had to touch the gear and the aggro placed on him would be incredibly high. Simply put, after touching the gear, the main tank would have enough aggro on him for the DPSers to begin attacking.

The Tomb in the Sky clearly wasn’t a difficult dungeon in terms of controlling aggro. The difficulty of the dungeon lay with the mobs, so for normal players, this was a dungeon that ate up equipment. As their equipment became better, this dungeon wouldn’t be too difficult anymore, which was why the Tomb in the Sky was only considered a medium difficulty dungeon.

It was because this dungeon consumed equipment that everyone had initially looked down on Unrivaled Super Hottie’s lackluster equipment.

At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie stood in front of the gear as the main tank, waiting for everyone to finish resting. Even though everyone recognized his skill, some of the players still raised their doubts.

“You’re going to tank it?” Someone asked.

“Of course.”

“Will you be okay?”

“If I’m not okay, someone else can take my place!” Unrivaled Super Hottie lightly said.

Everyone crashed to the ground. Such a happy response made it difficult for them to find a reason not to let him be the main tank.

“Go ahead!” Happy Sheep spoke as the team leader. He also wanted to see just how skilled Unrivaled Super Hottie was by testing his skill with this boss.

Since the team leader had spoken, no one said anything more. After taking a rest, Happy Sheep told him to start the boss fight. Unrivaled Super Hottie touched the first gear.

The first boss appeared and attacked Unrivaled Super Hottie with a powerful strike.

Every player knew the might of the first boss’s first strike, but in front of Unrivaled Super Hottie, the attack had no effect.

Because he dodged it!

As long as one could dodge the attack, the attack would naturally be ineffective.

The boss moved much faster than the stone statues. The players nervously watched. In the blink of an eye, several exchanges passed. During this time, the Clerics raised their crosses and then put them down; raised their crosses and then put them down. In the end, none of them cast any spells.

Unrivaled Super Hottie still hadn’t been hit a single time yet.

It was the same as against the stone statues. When he started the fight, he would be focused and dodge for a good while, but this boss had fiercer and quicker attacks. Even so, Unrivaled Super Hottie was still able to dodge several attacks. This wasn’t just an issue of concentration, but it also meant that his hand speed had reached a certain level.

The Clerics still had to be wary because they knew if Unrivaled Super Hottie were to be hit by an attack, they would need to heal him immediately. With his equipment, there wouldn’t be much time for a breather. As a result, even though they seemed to be having an easy time, they were incomparably nervous. Their crosses repeatedly moved up and down. They didn’t dare to relax for a moment.

“Attack!” Suddenly, everyone heard someone shout out. Only then did they realize that Unrivaled Super Hottie was telling them to begin attacking the boss. Everyone had been watching so intently that they had forgotten again.

The DPSers rushed forward to attack and the Clerics finally started getting busy.

The boss’ attacks wouldn’t only be single target attacks. There would also be AoE attacks. Unrivaled Super Hottie might dodge them, but it didn’t mean that the other DPSers would be able to.

Everyone had originally been accustomed to this, but today, something unprecedented happened.

The Clerics hadn’t healed the main tank before they had to heal the others.

As a result, on the healing charts, the DPSers took the top spots for most healing done on them, while the main tank sunk to the bottom. It made everyone feel very ashamed.

“This really is…” The players in the team didn’t know what to say.

The Clerics who saw the healing charts were also speechless. Because of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s performance, the amount of work to be done decreased. After all, healing the tank was their priority. For the DPSers with light wounds, they could just heal them when they had time.

Because of this, the amount of healing they did was incomprehensibly low. If others looked at it, they would definitely think that the Clerics were slacking, but in reality, it wasn’t that they refused to heal, but that they didn’t have any chances to do so!

What a conflict! This dungeon made them feel very awkward!

“Pay attention!” Happy Sheep was afraid they would relax and reminded the Clerics.

Finally!

Unrivaled Super Hottie had finally been hit by an attack. Everyone cried tears of joy! The Clerics swarmed around and healed him. They truly weren’t used to not healing the tank in a boss fight.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s concentration began to wane and he got hit by more and more attacks. However, he was still dodging most of them, so he still didn’t put too much pressure on the Clerics.

Even against the boss, his skill could make up for his lackluster equipment.

However, unlike against the stone statues, there wasn’t any time to relax. The boss required his full concentration and ability the entire time. Was he going to be able to last for the entire boss fight?

Everyone doubted it.

Chapter 566 – I Won’t Let You Test Your Luck

When the first boss fell, their question was finally answered. Unrivaled Super Hottie had actually tanked the first boss by relying on skill alone to dodge attacks and reduce the damage that he received.

His name didn’t stand out in the various statistics, but the participating players all recognized his skill by now. With Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment, it was already incredible to be in the average group of players.

Moreover, for him to be able to keep dodging for the entirety of the boss fight meant that he still had energy to spare. It wasn’t his limit.

The players in Happy Sheep’s team stood around in small clusters, whispering amongst each other about Unrivaled Super Hottie. Everyone even forgot to care about what the first boss dropped.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was as calm as ever though. After beating the boss, he smashed the gear and turned to face everyone: “Continue?”

“Continue…” Happy Sheep replied. He had quietly picked up the boss drops and showed it to everyone in the team chat, but no one seemed to care. At least three people could use the equipment dropped, but none of them had replied to his message.

On their way to the second boss, no one held anymore doubts about Unrivaled Super Hottie. Right now, they only had one thought on their minds: If he can play the role of main tank in a dungeon like Tomb in the Sky with his current equipment, what would happen if we gave him better equipment? What would he be like then? Would we be able to completely clear Tomb in the Sky?

This was the embodiment of why the tank was the core of a team. With just an upgrade for one player, the entire team could reach a completely different level. As a result, every team prioritized training the tank. The faster the tank became stronger, the faster the team would grow.

Happy Sheep’s team didn’t need to train a tank. A powerful tank directly dropped into their laps. His equipment currently limited his strength, but once he upgraded his equipment, the impact such a tank would provide to the team was unimaginable!

Their path to the next boss verified their thoughts. Even though Happy Sheep still led the team, their strategy would always change a little because of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s performance. The change would initially frighten everyone, similar to their first time fighting the four stone statues, but after getting used to it, their fights became easier and more efficient.

Second boss.

Third boss.

These two boss fights were virtually the same as the first boss. Unrivaled Super Hottie continued to make up for his lacking equipment with his skill. After defeating the three bosses, everyone looked at the time. They finally realized why Unrivaled Super Hottie said “It’ll be more efficient with me.” The time they had used to beat these three bosses was much faster than their previous runs.

After clearing away the mobs, they finally reached the fourth gear.

“How about it? Will anyone lend me some equipment to use?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked after clearing away the mobs.

Everyone was a bit startled. Shortly afterwards, they recalled that Unrivaled Super Hottie had said that he would need to borrow better equipment for a few of the bosses.

“Did he say that for the fourth boss?”

“I think so?”

“He did. I remember what he said. Besides the fourth boss, he also said the final boss.”

“Not just those. There’s more. Didn’t he also mention the fifth boss? I remember him talking about two bosses in a row?”

Everyone muttered to one another. Because they looked down on Unrivaled Super Hottie at that time, they hadn’t paid too much attention to his words. Quite a bit of time had passed and they had long since forgotten his words.

“I’ll lend you my equipment!” Seven Blossom Leaves happily stepped forward. All of his equipment belonged to him. They weren’t borrowed from the guild storage, so it could be traded. Guilds would always invest in their tanks to win them over.

Seeing how Seven Blossom Leaves was once again being a kind person, the players with a good relationship with him were somewhat nervous. After all, borrowing equipment wasn’t a trivial matter. How long had they known Unrivaled Super Hottie? Besides his shameless name and extraordinary skill, they knew nothing else about him. What if he was a scammer? What if he used this type of method to cheat equipment from others?

Many players came to this conclusion. When they thought again more carefully, Unrivaled Super Hottie had only been with them for three bosses. If he cheated them of an entire set of equipment, it would be a low risk, high return plan. Even though they had never heard about this type of scamming strategy, why couldn’t it be the first of its kind?

They couldn’t say this in public, so they privately messaged Seven Blossom Leaves urging him not to trust in this stranger.

But Seven Blossom Leaves objected.

“With his skill, why would he need to scam me for equipment?” Seven Blossom Leaves argued.

“That’s the type of thinking he wants you to have!” His friends warned.

Seven Blossom Leaves stubbornly clung to his belief. His friends continued to warn him, but he had already completed his trade with Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“I’ll give you my equipment for you to use!” Unrivaled Super Hottie handed over his lackluster equipment to Seven Blossom Leaves.

“Okay!” Seven Blossom Leaves took the equipment. In the blink of an eye, Seven Blossom Leaves and Unrivaled Super Hottie looked as if they had traded places.

The doubtful players had their hearts leap into their throats. The trade had already been completed. If he was a scammer, he would directly leave the team to without wasting any time.

But Unrivaled Super Hottie went forward and touched the gear.

Fourth boss, start!

Why did Unrivaled Super Hottie suddenly need better equipment for the fourth boss? No one questioned this issue because, after seeing how he handled the previous bosses, they knew why he wouldn’t be able to for this fourth boss.

The fourth boss was a summoner. The summoned spirits were its faithful servants and prioritized their master’s safety over their own lives. To put it into gaming terminology, these summoned spirits had the same target as their boss. Whoever the boss had aggro on would be whoever these spirits had aggro on.

As a result, the main tank would be surrounded by many monsters at a time.

If Unrivaled Super Hottie continued to use his low-grade equipment, he would instantly fall.

Because these summoned spirits didn’t have their own aggro stat, no matter how fiercely they were attacked, they would still only attack the boss’s target. Thus, in order to pull them apart, only Provoke, Roar, or similar type skills would work.

After using these skills and pulling them away, they would hurry and attack.

This section of the dungeon required a lot of work from every member of the team. The knights had to have fast reaction times. If they were too slow and the summoned spirits attacked too many times before acting, the tank would die. The DPSers had to have fierce firepower. This required a certain level of equipment. When the summoned spirits came out, they needed to immediately send out a heavy barrage. After all, the Knight’s monster-pulling skill would only last a few seconds. In these few seconds, the summoned spirits needed to die.

For such a high requirement fighting method, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s original equipment wouldn’t have been good enough. Everyone would need to play perfectly in order to ensure that he did not die. As soon as the summoned spirits came out, they would need to pull them immediately. When the skill effect ended, the summoned spirits needed to be dead. Otherwise, a few scratches would hit Unrivaled Super Hottie and he would be dead.

But with Seven Blossom Leave’s equipment, there was more room for error. When they pulled the spirits away, they could be a bit slower because he could hang on for awhile longer. Even if not all of the spirits died after the effects ended, he would be able to tank a few hits.

After understanding this point, the players in Happy Sheep’s team felt a bit embarrassed. They felt like the reason Unrivaled Super Hottie needed better equipment to survive wasn’t because of him, but because he didn’t think they would be able to play perfectly…

Even though they understood this, there was nothing they could say because a perfect fight was too difficult. Everyone knew what to do in theory, but actually doing it was an entirely different matter. In the past, when their team didn’t have good enough equipment, they relied on luck for this part. Every time the spirits came out, whether or not they would succeed depended on luck.

As their equipment became better, the tank could survive longer and their damage output increased. This part no longer became a big problem.

But Unrivaled Super Hottie’s originally equipment would be a challenge of luck. Switching equipment was done for their sake!

But they could just switch out the tank! If Seven Blossom Leaves tanked, they would pass all the same. Seven Blossom Leaves lending his equipment to Unrivaled Super Hottie made the more pessimistic players worry. Only when the boss came out did they finally relax.

After wearing Seven Blossom Leave’s equipment, Unrivaled Super Hottie immediately became more carefree. He no longer dodged around as much. He just held his shield up and smashed violently at the fourth boss.

A shriek! After accumulating enough damage, the boss would summon the first wave.

“You guys don’t need me to tell you what to do right?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

“No need!” Seven Blossom Leaves replied.

Seven Leaves, could you not be so nice? Everyone cried.

Chapter 567 – Aquatic Battle? I Know About It

Seven Blossom Leaves didn’t have any complaints about being the secondary tank. He lent his equipment and eagerly cooperated. The kind Seven Blossom Leaves had come across someone whom he truly admired. The others couldn’t watch any longer.

A quick Provoke. The summoned spirits didn’t even have time to attack Unrivaled Super Hottie, when one of them had been pulled away. The third, fourth, and fifth tanks didn’t dare to be slow. Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie had Seven Blossom Leaves’ equipment, his equipment wasn’t so great that he could just ignore the mob attacks and sit there. Others still needed to help him.

The Knights pulled the mobs to one side, while the DPSers attacked madly. The Clerics carefully watched the health of these few Knights.

Usually, Seven Blossom Leaves was the main tank. They hadn’t come across any problems with this strategy. It wasn’t any different with Unrivaled Super Hottie. However, because Unrivaled Super Hottie had borrowed someone else’s equipment, everyone had one thought: if Unrivaled Super Hottie had his original low-grade equipment, they wouldn’t have been able to pass.

The answer was somewhat embarrassing because it seemed to be true.

First of all, the coordination between the Knights wasn’t very good. Seven Blossom Leaves had reacted quickly, but the others were one step slower. Two of the Knights had already messed up and allowed the monsters hit Unrivaled Super Hottie.

They had a clear understanding of their roles though, as none of them Provoked the same monster.

In addition, the DPSers’ attacks were all over the place. Everyone just attacked whatever was close to them. There wasn’t any sort of coordination between them. The Knights were partly to blame. They pulled the summoned spirits away, but they didn’t pull them to a suitable place for the DPSers to attack. Some of the melee DPSers just barely reached their targets, when Provoke’s duration ended…

When Provoke’s duration ended, the monsters would immediately head back to attack Unrivaled Super Hottie.

The Knights hastily Roared one after the other. Their order was quite clear though. None of them overlapped with each other.

Unrivaled Super Hottie watched the events unfold and commented: “How messy.”

Everyone felt ashamed!

This had originally been the place they had previously been stuck on, but after their equipment became better, they could fluster their way through it, so their coordination hadn’t changed. The only thing that improved was their understanding of the order and division of labor the Knights had. When the summoned spirits came out, everyone would be busy. The DPSers attacked freely. In any case, they could beat the boss, so why did they need to be so careful?

Everyone felt their honor disappear when they heard the expert comment “How messy.”

But they didn’t have any problems beating the boss. It might have been messy, but there weren’t any casualties in clearing away the first wave of monsters. However, their hypotheses had been proved: if Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t switched equipment, he definitely would have died.

Besides saying “How messy”, Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t say much else. The players wanted to be less messy, but when the spirits were summoned once more, they returned to their chaotic fighting. After hearing Unrivaled Super Hottie’s comment, they looked at the scene with different eyes and verified it: it really was quite messy.

Everyone wanted to fight more orderly, but they failed to fight in a beautiful orderly manner all the way until the fourth boss fell.

We beat the boss, so it’s fine!

Everyone silently consoled themselves.

“We beat the boss, so it’s fine.” Unrivaled Super Hottie directly spoke their thoughts. When they heard this, they suddenly didn’t feel consoled anymore. Instead, they felt mocked.

Everyone wanted to give it another try to show their true skill. Unfortunately, they could only run this dungeon once a week.

After beating the fourth boss, they continued forward. For the fifth boss, Unrivaled Super Hottie also needed to borrow equipment, but this time, they didn’t know why he needed to switch equipment.

It was only until after they fought for a while did everyone finally understand why.

The fight against the fifth boss took place on several floating stone pillars. There was a limited amount of space on these stone pillars, so Unrivaled Super Hottie would have much more difficulty dodging. More importantly, this boss could freely teleport across these stone pillars. The moment the boss teleported, the boss would reset its aggro counter and freely attack.

This was naturally a difficult test for the team.

The classes, who wouldn’t be on the same stone pillar as the boss, would be the Clerics and long-ranged classes. If the boss suddenly teleported to their position and attacked, it was as if the system ignored the rules and caused the aggro to be pulled from the tank.

The way Happy Sheep’s team dealt with this problem was by splitting the tanks between the stone pillars. When the boss teleported, the Knight in charge of that stone pillar would immediately go up to defend. Provoke, Roar, or whatever would be used to re-establish the boss’s aggro.

But what did Unrivaled Super Hottie do? He chased the boss when the boss teleported. Moreover, he wasn’t any slower than the boss. The task, which had originally been split between the other Knights, was shouldered by him alone.

After teleporting, the boss would attack brainlessly. Unless a player used a skill like Provoke or Roar, no one would know who the boss would attack. As a result, the tanks could really only be meat shields. They would see who the boss was intending to attack and then jumped in front of the target to take the attack for them.

This task wasn’t easy for the Knights.

Because this was more different than normal tanking. Normally, the monsters would attack the Knights. The Knights didn’t need to use any aggro-establishing skills to tank, but in this case, they didn’t know where the boss would attack. They had to predict the boss’s movements and defend. The fifth boss was always a section where Happy Sheep’s team had never been able to pass without any casualties. They wouldn’t lose too many players, but they would definitely lose a few. They could pass the fourth boss without any casualties, but after the fifth boss, their hundred player team would no longer have a hundred players.

But everything changed with the addition of Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Unrivaled Super Hottie closely followed the boss’ steps. He predicted and intercepted the boss accurately too. The majority of the boss’ brainless attacks hit Unrivaled Super Hottie. All of them were blocked by him on purpose.

His low-grade equipment wouldn’t have been good enough for him to be a proper meat shield. Had he been using that equipment, he would have needed to dodge the majority of the boss’ attacks to reduce the incoming damage, but now, he could actively seek to block the boss’ attacks. Even with Seven Blossom Leave’s equipment, the Clerics still felt the pressure.

Usually, a single player couldn’t defend against the boss’s attack. As soon as the boss teleported to another stone pillar, all of the tanks would go up together to act as meat shields. You block, I block, everyone blocks, so the Clerics could spread their healing amongst different players.

But now, Unrivaled Super Hottie was blocking for everyone singlehandedly. In addition to that, he was doing it better than what they could do combined. One or two Clerics on a stone pillar weren’t enough to heal him up properly!

Fortunately, Happy Sheep made appropriate adjustments. The Cleric squad began to chase after Unrivaled Super Hottie. All of them focused their healing on Unrivaled Super Hottie.

When the fifth boss fell, Happy Sheep’s team had made another breakthrough. They had finally cleared the boss without a single casualty with this method. The team still consisted of a hundred players, and not a single one had died yet.

Happy Sheep felt somewhat embarrassed to say this was because of the entire team’s efforts. They had always tried hard on this section, but they had never gotten through without any casualties. It was because of Unrivaled Super Hottie and his outstanding predictions that the team managed to not lose any members.

“Beautiful!” Happy Sheep praised Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“Of course.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

The Knights felt very ashamed. A task that they couldn’t do with all four of them had just been achieved by a single person.

Having created history, the team was in high spirits and swept through the sixth, seventh, and eighth bosses.

Up to this point, there were still no casualties. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s tanking was extremely stable. If an incident ever occurred, he would come to their rescue. With a tank like this, even if someone wanted to die, it would be extremely difficult. An atmosphere of happiness gradually enveloped the entire team. The team killed the ninth boss. Only the final boss was left. At the same time, this was the farthest the team had ever progressed. Up until now, they hadn’t cleared this pass yet.

This time, they had all of their members alive and well, along with a powerful tank like Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“How do we fight it?” Happy Sheep didn’t rashly make arrangements and instead asked Unrivaled Super Hottie for his advice. They had tried to clear this section countless times but had failed, so Happy Sheep didn’t have much confidence in their strategy.

“How do we fight it?” Unrivaled Super Hottie heard this question and repeated the question. After thinking for a moment, he said: “I’ll tank the monsters. The damage dealers will deal damage. The healers will heal.”

The highly anticipated strategy turned out to be something like this. It made everyone want to cry. Wasn’t this the same as normal? As long as it was a game with tanks, healers, and damage dealers, weren’t all bosses fought with this strategy?

Happy Sheep grumbled for a long time, but he didn’t say anything.

“Is everyone ready? Should I start?” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“Wait. Wait.” Happy Sheep hastily stopped him.

“Hm?”

“We’ve died here lots of times before.” Happy Sheep said.

“Oh?”

“Our team’s progress has always stopped here.” Happy Sheep said.

“Congratulations!” Unrivaled Super Hottie exclaimed, “Today will be your first time clearing it.”

“...”

“Should I start?”

“Wait! Wait!” Happy Sheep still wasn’t sure about what his plans were, so he wasn’t prepared. It was their first time reaching here without any losses. They had to grasp this opportunity well!

“What?”

“How are you planning on tanking?” Happy Sheep asked.

“You guys probably weren’t able to tank it before, right?” Unrivaled Super Hottie’s gaze fell onto Seven Blossom Leaves and the other knights.

The Knights couldn’t help but affirm this cruel reality.

“The damage we took was too great. Our healers couldn’t keep up.” Happy Sheep said, “Maybe it’s because our equipment isn’t good enough.”

“Your equipment is good enough.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said, “You’re just not skilled enough. This is an aquatic battle, so there’s a lot of skill involved. It’s a bit more difficult.”

“You know how to engage in aquatic battles too?” Happy Sheep discovered the source of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s confidence.

“A bit.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied modestly, but why did it sound like he was bragging?

Chapter 568 – This Is a Strong Tank

The ninth boss battle in Tomb in the Sky took place in water.

The majority of players were not accustomed to aquatic battles. Due to this reason alone, Tomb in the Sky’s ninth boss was considered even more difficult than the final boss.

Fighting a boss in water was different than fighting players in water.

For PvP, it was fair for both sides. The hindrances from water would affect them equally, but it was an entirely different matter for bosses. For shameless entities like bosses, who had the system’s backing, water would not affect them like conventional logic would entail.

In the water, the movements of players would become slower, but bosses could freely move around, as if they were dragons soaring through the skies. It would be strange if an opponent like this wasn’t difficult to deal with.

Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised Seven Blossom Leaves and the other Knights couldn’t fight aquatic battles well.

Tanking required precise actions. When an attack arrived, the Knight had to raise their shield to defend. It was the whole point of a shield after all. Half of the reason Knights were tanks was because of the damage reduction they would gain from equipping shields.

However, in an aquatic battle, there was a huge difference in speed between the boss and them. This difference in speed made it difficult for players to grasp the timing of the attacks. Even a simple move like raising their shields couldn’t be done easily.

If the Knight couldn’t use his shield properly, the Knight wouldn’t fare much better than the squishies. The healing obviously wouldn’t be enough.

If they had better equipment and could tank without the shield, then they would be able to pass easily, but Seven Blossom Leaves and the other Knights were still trying to beat the dungeon! How could their equipment be at that sort of dominating level? It wouldn’t be quite correct to say that the ninth boss of Tomb in the Sky required exceptional equipment. There was no such dungeon that required vastly superior equipment to beat. In reality, the ninth boss just required skill in aquatic battles.

The skill required wasn’t anything too demanding. It would be enough if the Knight could raise his shield in time to receive the boss’s attack.

But the problem was that players were unaccustomed to aquatic battles. In addition, the boss wasn’t affected by the water in the slightest. Because of these reasons, the majority of players had trouble executing even a simple move like raising their shields.

Of course, for someone like Ye Xiu, this move was well within his capabilities despite only having “a bit” of knowledge in aquatic battles. Difficult and precise aquatic techniques didn’t need to be used. Since all he needed to do was raise his shield at the right time, Seven Blossom Leave’s equipment was more than enough to tank the boss.

If Ye Xiu tried with Unrivaled Super Hottie’s original equipment, Ye Xiu would also feel pressured. It would require him to rely more on dodging the boss’s attacks than to tank. His character’s movements would be restricted in the water, while the boss wouldn’t be hindered, which made dodging much more difficult.

Thus, for the ninth boss, Ye Xiu needed to borrow equipment.

Now, with better equipment, Ye Xiu didn’t feel pressured by the boss at all. The team could just use their normal strategy. He would tank, the DPSers would deal damage, and the healers would heal. Happy Sheep kept asking him how he planned on fighting the boss, but Ye Xiu didn’t know what else to say. Just fight with the basic bossing strategy.

This was also the place where Happy Sheep’s team often wiped out, but they couldn’t find any solutions because this boss didn’t require any specific strategy. The boss didn’t have any extremely powerful moves or anything either. The only difficulty lay in the speed disparity and the players’ inability to fight in the water. If they tried a few more times, the tanks would eventually grasp the timing and they would pass the boss with ease.

“Relax! Just follow along!” Ye Xiu said. He ignored Happy Sheep’s objection and headed straight over to touch the gear.

The gear moved and water poured out from their surroundings. After everyone became submerged in the water, the boss came out and went on stage. Happy Sheep’s team, which had wiped out here countless times, started sweating and nervously stared at the boss. Unrivaled Super Hottie was already heading for the boss though. Initiating with a Charge, he struck the boss.

The battle began.

The boss’s strength was the same as always. As for Happy Sheep’s team? Their tanks’ equipment hadn’t changed. The only thing that had changed was a single person. The bubbles and waves from the exchange between the boss and Unrivaled Super Hottie made it so they couldn’t even see Unrivaled Super Hottie’s name tag. The Clerics fixed their attention on his health bar by using the team list.

This guy sounded quite confident. He’d better not die after a few blows! It had happened before. The tank pulled the monster and before anyone had a clear understanding of the situation, the tank became a corpse.

But what about Unrivaled Super Hottie? The bubbles made it difficult for them to see the situation clearly, but they could tell that his health wasn’t dropping very fast. The waves turned over their heads and the muffled sounds of a shield being struck could be heard. The two sides were fighting and Unrivaled Super Hottie was blocking the boss’s attacks.

“He can tank it!!”

Seven Blossom Leaves immediately figured out the problem. He knew why the boss had been difficult for their team in the past. It was because their shields had turned into decorations. They were never able to block the boss’s attacks. It wasn’t a problem they could fix just by knowing about it. They had tried hard to learn, but today, it looked like someone could finally do it.

“Heal!” Unrivaled Super Hottie gave an order and the Clerics began healing.

“Damage!” Unrivaled Super Hottie gave another order and the DPSers began attacking.

“Done!” Unrivaled Super Hottie stated and the boss floated up as a corpse.

Done?

The team had been stuck here for several weeks, trying all sorts of strategies to tank the boss. Today, it died without any suspense.

No accident or danger even arose. The boss fight hadn’t even been as scary as when Unrivaled Super Hottie almost turned into Swiss cheese from the spear trap in the very beginning.

Happy Sheep’s team was completely silent.

The boss, which had made them ram their heads against the wall, keeled over in such a normal way. They had a hard time accepting it. The boss fight should have been frightening. There should have been constant cries of fear, and dangers all around, accompanied by countless tragedies. Later on, when they stumbled across the topic of this boss again, they should have been able to describe the boss battle for an entire day.

But none of that happened. There weren’t even any orders during the boss fight. Even the mobs had been more exciting.

The incomparably difficult boss died so pitifully.

The boss fell and the gear was destroyed. The water drained out and the entire Tomb in the Sky began to transform. Up until now, Happy Sheep’s team hadn’t ever heard the boss’s roar before. The ground shook like an earthquake, startling everyone awake.

“The final boss.” Unrivaled Super Hottie called out to them.

Everyone followed along numbly. After walking for two minutes, someone suddenly regained their composure: “Team captain, did you pick up the equipment?”

“Oh sh*t!” Happy Sheep immediately turned his head. He had been so lost in thought, he had forgotten to pick up the ninth boss’ drops.

Happy Sheep’s team had never seen the final boss before. It was their first time. They were originally very nervous, but with the supposedly even more difficult ninth boss defeated just like that, wouldn’t the final boss be a stroll in the park?

No one had any expectations for the final boss. After following Unrivaled Super Hottie, they eventually reached the final boss.

“You guys have only gotten to the ninth boss, so that means you’ve never fought against this boss before, right?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

“We’ve never fought it before.” Happy Sheep answered.

“Then have you read the guide for it?”

“Guide…” Happy Sheep was slightly startled. He had read the guide before, but he hadn’t studied this part in detail yet because they had been stuck on the ninth boss for weeks. He hadn’t considered the final boss yet!

“Then should I give a brief summary?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

‘You tank. The DPSers deal damage. The healers heal? I understand.” Happy Sheep said.

“How can it be that simple?” Unrivaled Super Hottie commented in disdain. He described the boss’ problematic points.

“It’s that complicated?” Everyone gasped. They had read the guide before, but they had never gotten this far before, so no one had studied it in detail. They had pretty much forgotten everything at this point.

“How come it sounds like it’s more difficult than the ninth boss?” Someone asked.

“Obviously! Of course the final boss is more difficult to handle than the ninth boss.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“I thought the ninth boss was the hardest boss?” Someone else questioned.

“Those who don’t understand aquatic battles would say that.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“Who knows anything about aquatic battles…” Everyone commented.

“Me!”

“I thought you only understood a bit?”

“I was being modest. Do you know what that means?”

“A bit…” Everyone cried.

“Did everyone remember what I said?” At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie asked if everyone understood what he had just taught them.

“Yes.” Everyone replied, but their answer sounded amiss. F*ck, they were one of Tyrannical Ambition’s branch guilds. Why were they being lectured like noobs?

But then again, for a boss they had never fought before, they really were noobs. The problem was that the person in front of them had just looked over the guide before running the dungeon. He didn’t even know about the spear traps in the beginning. When did he suddenly become an expert that could order them around?

“If no one has any questions, I’ll start the fight!”

Before anyone could give any objections, Unrivaled Super Hottie charged at the boss.

F*ck, so quick and decisive. Everyone could only follow behind.

“Everyone spread out! There can’t be anyone within ninety degrees in front of the boss. Didn’t you guys say you remembered!!” Unrivaled Super Hottie had already begun instructing them.

Everyone cried. They hadn’t even seen clearly what direction the boss was facing? Could you not be so strict!

“That Cleric over there. What’s wrong with you? Are you looking to die, standing behind me? Move outside of the ninety degrees area.”

Everyone looked and went silent. F*ck, that Cleric was Happy Sheep! Even the team captain was being taught like a dog, so this was a what a powerful tank was truly like! Speaking of tanks, the team was too used to Seven Blossom Leaves and his kind personality.

“Do you know what ninety degrees means? The boss and I make up the axis. Move to the areas away from the two o’clock directions on the left and right!”

Everyone silently watched. Team captain, show some pride! Your movements are so slow and your math is so poor. How shameful!

Chapter 569 – The Final Boss’s Three Iron Shovels

Unrivaled Super Hottie very naturally replaced Happy Sheep as the team’s shotcaller. His tone of voice changed too. He just started and he was already scolding the team captain, Happy Sheep.

Quite a few were angry. Even though it was true that they had never fought this boss before, Unrivaled Super Hottie had only skimmed through the dungeon guide ten minutes before starting. How could he be so strict? Reciting words from the guide? Anyone could do that!

Some of the players wanted to say a few mocking words, when they suddenly saw Tomb in the Sky’s final boss, Tomb Guardian Imset, suddenly lift his hands up and slammed his iron shovel, which looked more appropriate for a grave robber, down into the ground.

Numerous cracks suddenly formed on the ground. Rays of light shone through the cracks like magic waves. A fierce storm flew out from the cracks, making everyone, who was about to say something, shut their mouths.

Happy Sheep had reacted too slowly to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s scolding. The magic storm coming out from the cracks in the earth sliced Happy Sheep into bits. Not even a corpse remained.

“Everyone, start moving!!” Everyone was still in shock, when another order came. Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t sway from seeing the team captain dying. When the Tomb Guardian slammed his shovel down, he sidestepped to the right and dodged the flying magic waves.

Since the target had moved, the boss naturally moved along with his target. They didn’t dare be slow and sprinted to behind the boss. They could clearly see that the magic waves covered a 90 degree arc in front of the boss. Unrivaled Super Hottie had given a reminder, but Happy Sheep had been too slow, so of course he got clapped to death.

However, the team captain’s sacrifice hadn’t been for nothing. Everyone now realized the terror of this attack. This kind of feeling couldn’t be felt from watching a video or reading a guide. At best, the guide would mention the attack being an AoE attack and how to dodge it. The reader wouldn’t have any other feelings towards it though. Only those at the scene could discover how fast the attack started and how difficult it was to dodge. Happy Sheep had been warned by Unrivaled Super Hottie to hurry up and get out of the way, but he still wasn’t able to escape the attack’s range and instantly died.

“Melee classes, don’t crowd together! Move back and forth, alternating between using mid-ranged and close-ranged skills. Maintain a distance away from the boss. After using a close-ranged skill, immediately retreat.” Unrivaled Super Hottie continued to direct the team.

For a hundred player dungeon, in order to let many spread out and attack, the boss usually had a big body, so several melee characters could surround the boss at the same time. It didn’t make sense for players to line up and take turns to deal damage. However, this Tomb Guardian Imset had such powerful skills. A quarter of the area instantly became a dead zone, making it so there wasn’t space for the melee classes. Imset was quite big, but he wasn’t a huge dragon, which dozens of players could surround. At this moment, everyone once again realized the terror of this attack. Because it create a 90 degree dead zone in front, they had to head to behind the boss. Everyone rushed to behind the boss. The long-ranged classes didn’t have a problem, but the melee classes had trouble moving.

Even though Ye Xiu had gave them a tip, his tip made everyone somewhat confused. The long ranged classes like the Gunners and Mages were like fish in water, but the melee classes were a mess.

Just as the long-ranged characters were feeling good about themselves, Unrivaled Super Hottie warned: “The long-ranged characters are too far away. If you’re that far away, there won’t be enough time to dodge.”

Ye Xiu had told them all of these pointers before the boss fight. Listening to the theory behind it and actually putting into practice were two very different things though. When the AoE attack came out, everyone had been too busy and had forgotten about his pointers. Hearing the command saying they were too far, the long-ranged characters moved forward.

At this moment, the boss released another attack. The iron shovel in his hands pierced through the ground and began to spin.

“Run counterclockwise! Hurry hurry hurry!!” Unrivaled Super Hottie hastily shouted. Everyone watched as that iron shovel dug a ditch in the ground. Inside the ditch, rays of light seeped out like before, but this time, it sounded louder.

Everyone was scared witless and immediately ran counterclockwise like what Unrivaled Super Hottie said. However, some people thought they were smart and instead of running counterclockwise, they ran backwards. When the iron shovel swung out, the magic waves from the ditch instantly enveloped the players who had run backwards. It didn’t matter what class the player was. The player disappeared.

In just a short moment, Happy Sheep’s team lost another six players. The remaining didn’t dare be slow. Only now did they understand that every single one of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s commands weren’t without reason. If he wanted you to run around in a circle, then you around in a circle. Those who didn’t listen would be like the team captain and the other six who had died!

Happy Sheep had simply reacted a bit too slowly, but the other six didn’t listen because they thought they were smart.

The iron shovel streaked across the ground in a semicircle. At this moment, the long-ranged classes knew why they couldn’t be too far away. If they stood too far away, the radius of the semicircle would be larger and the amount of time needed to get out of range was longer. They might not be able to move fast enough before the boss started the attack. To dodge this attack, they needed to run in front of the boss, the opposite side from their current position. If they moved too slow, the attack would touch them and the death light would envelop them.

Both attacks had killed players in the team. Happy Sheep’s team became more and more nervous with each attack. Even though they knew the final boss couldn’t be beat just by standing there, the difficulty of the final boss exceeded their expectations. For example, if Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t warned them ahead of time to run in a counterclockwise direction, no one would have noticed the boss’s attack and the team might have wiped out right then and there…

“Move away from position three!!! Clerics, pay attention to everyone’s health!!”

Everyone was still trying to catch their breath, when Unrivaled Super Hottie gave another order. The boss was about to cast another powerful spell.

Move away from position three! It sounded like an unclear statement, but Unrivaled Super Hottie had explained it to them before. Position three referred to one of the sides of the boss. The command meant no one could be within that area. Pay attention to everyone’s health gave everyone a vague understanding of the boss’s next move. After all, even those who had never eaten pork before, had seen a pig run.

Right when Unrivaled Super Hottie’s voice fell, the boss’s iron shovel turned and dug into the ground. The boss dug in the position three location.

Even though everyone had received the orders, in that short moment, some of them hadn’t been able to see clearly which spot was the third position. A few even made the mistake of running into position three.

Some of the players were directly killed by the shovel.

Some of the players were scooped up into the air by the shovel and also died.

After a few fearful cries, the dirt scooped up by the shovel fell down. The dirt carried magic waves, but the waves didn’t seem too strong. The dirt flew into the air and rain down all around the boss. The players now knew that it wasn’t possible to dodge the attack. The boss completed the movement in an instant.

When they saw the dirt fall, everyone wanted to run away in panic, but they still vaguely remembered the warning.

“Make sure you avoid position three!” Fortunately, a warning was made and the dazed players instantly became alert. They saw that they were moving towards position three and cold sweat drenched their backs. The warning had been too slow. As soon as they neared position three, more magic waves surged forth and directly killed them.

If the Tomb Guardian Imset was one of the 24 classes in Glory, Imset would be a Thief class. It was a trap! His attack basically set a whole bunch of traps onto the ground! Was this guy a tomb guardian or a tomb robber?

They didn’t have time to think about this detail though. The dirt raining down couldn’t be dodged. Fortunately, the dirt didn’t do too much damage. The Clerics focused and quickly healed everyone back up. At this moment, the Clerics had forgotten about a very basic issue.

The tank!

The tank hadn’t taken any damage, so the Clerics hadn’t paid attention to him. In this moment of tension, the tank still didn’t need help. When the Clerics looked at the names on the team list and healed whoever was missing health, none of them touched Unrivaled Super Hottie.

All of the dirt fell and after this wave was over, everyone’s health returned to full. The Clerics naturally began paying attention to the tank again, but failed to notice this point.

Because they weren’t the only one.

One of the Clerics might not have healed the tank, but the others might have. As a result, when they saw Unrivaled Super Hottie safe and sound, none of the Clerics thought the tank had taken care of himself.

“Stay orderly. The boss only has these three iron shovels. Everyone pay attention to them and this fight will be a breeze!”

After the three iron shovels came out, fourteen players had died including the team captain. But what they didn’t know was that, these losses were considered light for first time challengers.

In reality, any team facing Tomb Guardian Imset wouldn’t have it as easy as Happy Sheep because none of them had a tank at Ye Xiu’s skill level.

When the third attack came out, the Clerics would have to take care of the tank and the entire team. The Clerics had a huge amount of pressure weighing on them. If they messed up, many would die. But Happy Sheep’s team had met a tank like Ye Xiu. For this attack, the Clerics didn’t need to look after him. They only needed to care about the rest of the players, which was how they got through this attack so easily. If Seven Blossom Leaves or the other Knights had been tanks, at least half of the team would have died.

Chapter 570 – Sworn Enemy

The final boss battle continued.

After experiencing Tomb Guardian Imset’s three iron shovels, Happy Sheep’s team didn’t dare to get distracted. Besides focusing on the fight, everyone only had one thought going through their minds. After exiting the dungeon, they were definitely going to look for those people who claimed the ninth boss was more difficult than the final boss and give them a good beating.

That ninth boss couldn’t even compare to even one of Imset’s three iron shovel attacks!

At the teleportation formation for Tomb in the Sky, Happy Sheep waited in worry.

He had a premonition that the final boss battle would be difficult, but he had been the first to die. He had never imagined that would happen. The team had reached the final boss without any casualties, so he had just wanted to share his excitement with someone else, but his typing had delayed him from moving, so when the battle began, he had moved slightly slower than the others. Who would have thought that this boss would be so ferocious and immediately start off by slamming his iron shovel down.

Happy Sheep was upset! The boss battle had just begin. They hadn’t cleared the dungeon yet. Why had he been so cocky?

When a player died in a dungeon, the player wouldn’t drop any equipment, but the player would still lose experience. Besides that, due to the vicious environment known as the Heavenly Domain, when a player revived, the player would be at full health without any loss in stats.

Tomb in the Sky was located in the air and could only be reached through several teleportation formations in the Heavenly Domain. When Happy Sheep revived, he was sent to the formation, which they had used to enter the dungeon. Happy Sheep discovered that he had been thrown into a group of players and immediately took up his guard. This was a basic survival skill in the Heavenly Domain. Being thrown into a group of players was just as dangerous as being thrown into a group of monsters.

Soon afterwards, Happy Sheep saw the names on top of the players in the group and relaxed.

These people were a team from Tyrannical Ambition’s fifth branch. Right now, they were sitting or standing near the teleportation formation. No one said anything. They didn’t seem too energetic.

Happy Sheep was from the fourth branch. These players were from the fifth branch. They could be considered part of the same family, so he didn’t need to worry about them eyeing his equipment. However, after seeing their names, Happy Sheep wasn’t happy either, especially towards one of the Knights amidst the group. When the Knight saw Happy Sheep revive amongst their group, he immediately got up. He swayed over as he circled Happy Sheep several times.

“What are you doing?!” Happy Sheep shouted, but his tone of voice sounded like he was showing strength on the outside, while actually being weak on the inside.

“Did I see wrong?” This Knight circled around a few times and stood still after hearing Happy Sheep’s shout, “Isn’t this team captain, Happy Sheep? I heard that you guys reached Tomb in the Sky’s final boss without losing any players? How come I see you here? Let me see… the time it’s been since you talked to me. D*mn, it’s been half a minute. Did the boss instantly kill the great Happy Sheep?”

Happy Sheep wanted to cry! This was why he didn’t feel happy. Because this guy was the person he had just “shared his excitement with”: Tyrannical Ambition’s fifth branch team captain Wolf Head.

The system might not recognize the fourth and fifth branch as a single guild, but everyone was still under Tyrannical Ambition. They were all fans of Team Tyranny too, so they all treated each other as members of the same guild. However, the teams of the branch guilds liked to compete with each other. It was similar to how different groups in the same company competed with each other. This dungeon progress was one place, where they competed in.

Happy Sheep’s team and this Wolf team had similar progress percentages from the very beginning. Both of them were stuck in Tomb in the Sky, so they had always viewed each other as rivals. Today, with the help of Unrivaled Super Hottie, not a single player had died before reaching the final boss. He felt like this was definitely an astonishing accomplishment, so he had gone and shared the news with his competitor. Who knew that today truly would be a day, where history was created? The team captain Happy Sheep was the first casualty of the team. Even worse, after dying, he dropped right into Wolf’s team.

He didn’t even know if Wolf Head had even finished reading about the excitement he had shared before he landed in their team. Happy Sheep really wanted to logout, but he still wanted to keep up with the situation in the dungeon. He could only grit his teeth and wait for the results!

Facing Wolf Head’s questioning, Happy Sheep felt grim. He coldly humphed and shifted topics: “What are you guys doing? Are you planning on entering the dungeon or preparing to exit the dungeon?”

His words were obviously to prick at Wolf Head’s sore spot. Today was the day before Tomb in the Sky refreshed. Teams would finish their dungeon run and then review it today. If they were gathered at the entrance, it could only mean they had come out after dying. This Wolf team had been Happy Sheep’s opponent for many years, so he understood his style.

“Hmph, don’t be so happy. You died and came out, which means your team is pretty much done for, no? A team reaching the final boss without any casualties, tch…” Wolf Head repeated the information typed out when Happy Sheep “shared his excitement”.

“Tch, it looks like you’ve all been sitting here for a while, no? Besides me, do you see anyone else from my team?” Happy Sheep laughed coldly.

His words were correct. Anyone who died would come out from the entrance they had come in from. Wolf Head’s team had been here for awhile. Wolf Head’s team had failed to clear Tomb in the Sky and were feeling depressed. Then, Happy Sheep came out and acted all cocky. Wolf Head really wanted to curse at him, but then he died and appeared in front of him. In the beginning, he was quite surprised. After collecting his thoughts, he felt incredibly happy.

At this moment, Happy Sheep raised this issue. Wolf Head had no way of answering because no one else had come out besides Happy Sheep, but right when Happy Sheep finished talking, pa pa pa pa pa pa! Six of Happy Sheep’s players respawned.

“Oh!” Wolf Head shouted in glee and immediately welcomed them: “You’ve come?”

The six players came out and were still at a loss. When they heard him asking them a question, they replied back foolishly: “Here.”

Happy Sheep wanted to cry again. What’s up with today? Everything was happening at the wrong time! All the coincidences were going against him! What terrible luck. He must have gotten on the wrong side of the devils.

The six players foolishly replied to Wolf Head and saw their team captain. They immediately waved at him. Happy Sheep couldn’t care about Wolf Head at the moment and hastily asked: “How is it going?”

“How else could it be? They died!” Wolf Head replied in response.

Happy Sheep sucked in a deep breath. Ignore him. The six players nodded their heads and agreed: “We died.”

“No sh*t…” Happy Sheep wasn’t in a good mood, “I can obviously tell that you guys died. I’m talking about the boss. Is the situation stable?”

“They died. How could it be stable?” Wolf Head replied to his question again.

“Those who couldn’t even beat the ninth boss, step aside!” Happy Sheep snorted. He couldn’t say this last week, but he could say it now.

Wolf Head was at a loss for words. They really were stuck on the ninth boss. This time, their dungeon run had been even worse. They hadn’t even gotten to the ninth boss before wiping.

“Tch, how much better could they be? You beat the ninth boss once and now you’re so cocky. You’re still going to fail at the final boss. I say, the ninth boss is even more difficult than the final boss! None of you died on the ninth boss, but the team captain died at the start of the final boss? Something isn’t right! Check your message again. Did you type it wrong? Are you talking about the ninth boss? Did you mistake the seventh or eighth boss for the sixth boss?” Wolf Head chattered.

Happy Sheep was about to die from anger, but reality wasn’t helping him! He really had been cocky and then bang, he died. He argued about how he was the only to die so far and then bang bang bang bang bang bang, six players died. If he bragged again and then the entire team wiped out, he wouldn’t have any more face to hang onto.

Happy Sheep cautiously waited. He didn’t dare to say anything more. Wolf Head’s team didn’t have much to do. After coming out of the dungeon, their experience would be reduced. Most of them would hurry to kill monsters to gain back their lost experience, but seeing that a competitor had come to be laughed at, none of them left. They stood together and watched the spectacle.

They weren’t disappointed. Not long afterwards, more players from Happy Sheep’s team came out. Wolf Head laughed out loud and then said: “I’m just laughing. I won’t say anything.”

Happy Sheep paled. He tried to ignore him again and asked the others: “How is it going inside?”

He could have asked the people inside directly, but he was afraid that his message would hinder the people concentrating inside, so Happy Sheep only asked the people who had died and exited.

“If everyone follows what that guy says, there shouldn’t be any problems.” One of the players who had come out felt like their reply was quite smart, but it made Happy Sheep and the other six roll their eyes. They misunderstood his reply and thought he was making fun of them. They thought it was obvious that he died because he didn’t listen to directions. How could they know that this time, the people had died because they hadn’t listened to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s orders and tried to be heroic.

“At this rate, we’ll only be here for two more minutes. You won’t hold us up!” Wolf Head laughed.

Happy Sheep was just a Cleric. If he wasn’t, he would have challenged Wolf Head to a duel on the spot.

“I say, Big Head, your team wiped out, so how can you be so cocky? Hurry up and go gain your experience back!” Happy Sheep didn’t reply, when one of his team members replied.

“There’s no hurry for that. Once you guys come out, we can do it together and develop our friendship. Ha ha ha ha!”

Happy Sheep was done with the joking. He wanted to cough blood. Reality once again went against him. Another two players came out. Happy Sheep sighed. He didn’t want to ask anymore, but these two happily came over to greet him.

“The situation is looking good! It’s already stable!”

Their reply made him very happy.

Chapter 571 – Dungeon Clear or Wipe Out?

“The situation is pretty good?” Even though Happy Sheep sounded happy, he felt uneasy. He held the same feelings as Wolf Head: if the situation was good, why were people coming out wave after wave?

“Yeah, it’s very good!” Two of the players affirmed: “In the beginning, everyone was a bit new to the boss, but after a few times, we figured it out. That guy warns us very promptly. As long as we follow his orders, we’ll definitely clear the dungeon.”

These words made Happy Sheep red in the face. In the end, he asked: “Then what’s up with you two?”

“It’s hard to avoid accidents from happening……” The two people’s faces also turned red.

“I see, I see.” Happy Sheep expressed his understanding. After all, this was the final boss of a hundred player dungeon. It was their first time fighting the final boss too, so it would have been very strange if no one died. After gaining a grasp of the situation, Happy Sheep straightened up and turned to look at Wolf Head: “Waiting is good. In a bit, you’ll see some equipment that you’ve never seen before.”

“Enough, Old Sheep. Stop dreaming. You’ve bragged long enough. Look at the time. You’ve already reached the final boss? I didn’t even know that your team had the strength to challenge the dungeon record.” Wolf Head spoke with disdain. He felt like Happy Sheep’s lies were too clumsy.

“Dungeon record?” Happy Sheep stared blankly.

This phrase sounded very unfamiliar to him, because for teams who were still trying to clear Tomb in the Sky, setting a dungeon record and passing the dungeon were two entirely different things. When he heard Wolf Head’s words, Happy Sheep suddenly woke up with a start. He checked the time and then checked the dungeon record rankings.

His teammate was faster though and had already finished checking. He sighed in regret: “It’s already too late!”

At this moment, Happy Sheep looked at the dungeon record rankings. He estimated their start time and confirmed that they wouldn’t be able to beat it this time around. However, they had already gotten to the final boss, so they were relatively close to the record! This was quite impressive already! It had to be known that compared to the elite teams of top guilds, which had beaten this dungeon long ago, their teams weren’t on the same level. Even so, they were still able to achieve such a fast time. If everyone had their equipment upgraded by a level, would they have been able to beat the dungeon record?

Happy Sheep was a bit disappointed for a moment. Even though he was the team captain for a branch of a top guild like Tyrannical Ambition, he had never thought that he would ever have the chance to even get close to a dungeon record. Whether it was based on skill or equipment, their team was way too far off! Suddenly, he asked himself how this could have even happened. It was obvious! It was because of a single Knight: Unrivaled Super Hottie.

This Knight, with completely garbage equipment, had actually raised their team’s strength by such a degree. If someone told Happy Sheep this was going to happen before the dungeon had started, even if that person beat him to death, he still wouldn’t believe it, but now reality was unfolding before his eyes. His team instantly became so exceptional. If this transformation wasn’t because of Unrivaled Super Hottie, what other reason could it be?

Happy Sheep had a heap of thoughts in his head. On one hand, he felt happy to have this kind of expert help him. On the other hand, he understood that this expert wasn’t considered a part of their team. Suddenly, he thought of the order that the guild leader had given him. He couldn’t say Unrivaled Super Hottie was trash and then secretly keep him in the team. His lie would be seen through too easily.

In the end, he would need to report Unrivaled Super Hottie’s strength to the guild leader. With the performance that Unrivaled Super Hottie had given, there was no way the guild would let him stay in Happy Sheep’s team. Even the branch guild’s main team might not be enough! He would probably directly join the main team! As for his garbage equipment, if he were chosen to join the main guild’s main team, equipment wouldn’t be an issue. With the main guild’s strength, getting stronger equipment for a tank was something that could be done within minutes.

Happy Sheep thought about this and that. In the blink of an eye, countless thoughts floated around in his head. He could only feel depressed. In the beginning, he had looked down on Unrivaled Super Hottie. After realizing his value, he knew that this would be the only time he would have this experience. At this moment, Happy Sheep had even forgotten to argue with Wolf Head.

“I thought so. You actually thought you could challenge the dungeon record? Could you stop it with your act!” Wolf Head started heating things up.

“Act? This truly is our dungeon time. You’ll see if I’m acting soon.” Happy Sheep regained his composure and immediately retorted. Compared to before, his voice sounded much more resolute. After understanding Unrivaled Super Hottie’s value, Happy Sheep felt confident that clearing Tomb in the Sky today wouldn’t be a problem.

“Ha ha ha, you won’t even admit your lies! Did you not plan out your bragging? Let this brother count how many holes you have in your lie.” Wolf Head said, “First, how long has it been since you started the dungeon? And you’re saying that you’ve already reached the final boss? Old Sheep, do you think it’s my first time running Tomb in the Sky?”

“Second, Tomb in the Sky’s hardest boss is the ninth one. You actually claimed that no one died there, and yet so many have already died on the final boss. How do you expect me to believe that?”

“Ha ha, it’s up to you whether or not you want to believe me. At least, while your team got wiped out, the majority of my team are still fighting in the dungeon.” Happy Sheep said.

“Ha ha, today my team didn’t do so well. I’ll admit it, but your childish lies as attempts to make me jealous are too outlandish, no?” Wolf Head said.

“Today, you really will be jealous. We’re about to clear the dungeon.” Happy Sheep didn’t care about the risk of not actually beating the final boss. Wolf Head’s words had gotten to him and he lost his patience. When he thought about how this incredible Knight wouldn’t be able to stay in his team, Happy Sheep only felt more terrible.

“Oh really? Then I’ll wait. I’ll wait for you to make me jealous.” Wolf Head continued to look at him in disdain.

Happy Sheep ignored him and waited with his teammates for the news.

Second after second passed. Besides the two who had just died, no one else came out. Happy Sheep was naturally joyful. It meant the situation was under control. When Wolf Head saw no one from Happy Sheep’s team dying, he suddenly felt uneasy. He felt like his analysis was completely correct, but after hearing Happy Sheep talk about it with his teammates, why did it seem like Happy Sheep had some sort of expert help him today?

But the problem was Wolf Head knew Happy Sheep’s skill. What type of expert could bring his team up by such a degree? Wolf Head couldn’t imagine it. He still felt like Happy Sheep was only doing well in this run, so he exaggerated a bit. How could he believe that his team really did make a breakthrough!

After a while, players from other teams came out. Only a few were from Happy Sheep’s team. None of them brought bad news. All of them expressed how they died because they had been careless. The situation was stable.

“Unrivaled Super Hottie said the crucial moment is when the boss starts going Berserk at 10% health. Once we pass that obstacle, there won’t be any more problems.”

“What percentage was the boss’s health before you died?”

“We were just about to get there when I died.” One person said.

As soon as he finished, shua shua shua shua. Another ten players of different classes from Happy Sheep’s team came out.

Happy Sheep suddenly felt his chest tighten. Naturally, Wolf Head laughed with glee: “Ha ha ha, what’s wrong? You couldn’t hold on? It seemed pretty peaceful before. Were you guys killing off the small mobs? Now it’s the boss? Are you finally at the ninth boss yet?”

“What’s the situation?” Happy Sheep ignored Wolf Head and hastily asked the ten who had come out.

“Enraged! How fierce!” The ten, who came out, replied. Before the Enraged stated, Unrivaled Super Hottie explained to them in detail what to watch out for, but as soon as the boss became Enraged, ten of them were unable to keep up and died. Because they died too quickly, they didn’t know about the situation afterwards. However, after their wave, no one else came out. It seemed like the situation was stable again.

Happy Sheep wasn’t in the dungeon, but he was more nervous than anyone else. His right hand was drenched in sweat.

“The team has to pass!” Happy Sheep prayed because he knew that after this run, there was no way Unrivaled Super Hottie would continue staying in Happy Sheep’s team. Without Unrivaled Super Hottie, their team would go back to the way it was before. They would probably be stuck on the ninth boss again. With Wolf Head acting so savagely today, he had to slap him back. If it returned to their previous competition, then no one knew who would beat the dungeon first!

A few more players from Happy Sheep’s team died and came out. Happy Sheep immediately grabbed them to ask how the battle was going. These guys told him the team turned into a mess after the boss turned Enraged. They didn’t know what was going on inside.

“Baa~~baa~~baa~~” Wolf Head saw Happy Sheep ignoring him and told his team to start making sheep sounds together to give Happy Sheep’s team some beautiful background noise. This was one of the many ways that they mocked Happy Sheep’s team. Their baa-ing was equivalent to chanting “Die die die!!”

They shouted happily with smiles on their faces, when suddenly white light began to glow around the formation. A whole bunch of characters came out. Happy Sheep looked and saw that it was their players.

Did they pass? Or was it… a team wipe?

Chapter 572 – Who is this Person?

After being nervous for so long, the moment of truth had arrived. Happy Sheep usually pounced on the incoming players immediately, but his nervousness stopped his brain from functioning properly. He didn’t ask. He asked himself a question: pass or fail?

It was only an instant, but it felt like a long time. Happy Sheep was on edge. He wanted to ask, but was too afraid to ask at the same time. He hated how he couldn’t see the expressions of the people controlling their characters.

At this moment, everyone walked out from the formation and saw their team captain. As if the lid to a pot of boiling water had been lifted, they erupted with excitement.

“Did we clear it???”

“We cleared it!!!”

A brief exchange told them all the information they needed to know. Excitement filled Happy Sheep’s heart so much so that it poured out!

“We actually cleared it?” Happy Sheep questioned whether or not he was in a dream. He snatched a person by the arm and asked for confirmation.

“We really did pass! Captain, look!” The person speaking was the vice captain of the team. He allowed him to view the three pieces of equipment that had dropped from the final boss. A hundred player dungeon required the efforts of a hundred players. The rewards would obviously be much greater than the rewards from a smaller dungeon. In a smaller dungeon, it was very rare to get two Purple equipment in a single run, but in a hundred player dungeon, it would be a disappointment. What was two purple equipment? Three or four purple equipment was considered normal. The reward for the dungeon record for this dungeon were two pieces of orange equipment and three pieces of purple equipment! Currently, no one had touched the dungeon record in a long time. Even for a hundred player dungeon, orange equipment wasn’t easy to get. Even more so, two drops? The players thought the system had made a mistake!

Getting two orange drops at the same time usually only happened for once a week wild bosses.

Happy Sheep’s team had also gotten three purple equipment. Their luck wasn’t good, but it wasn’t bad either. For them, the final boss’ drops were secondary. They had finally beaten the dungeon that had plagued them for several weeks. That thrill of success was what made them happy.

“Big Head, do you see it now? Ha ha ha ha!” Happy Sheep raised his eyebrows and laughed. He could finally share his joy with Wolf Head. Before, he had come across some accidents, which ruined his excitement.

“Impossible!” Wolf Head saw the vibe of happiness coming from Happy Sheep’s team and felt extremely envious. No one wanted this type of joy more than the team captain. Even though Happy Sheep’s team really did look happy, Wolf Head refused to believe the truth.

“With your strength, even if you cleared the dungeon, it couldn’t have been that fast!” Wolf Head denied.

“Is it really that fast? It’s only okay, isn’t it?” Happy Sheep grinned. At this moment, he looked at the tie. They were still quite far from the dungeon record. Happy Sheep realized that he had looked down on the final boss too much. They had been pretty close to the record run, when they had arrived at the final boss, but once they began fighting the boss, the record run far outpaced them. Even so, for a first-time-clearing team, this speed was already exceptional. It wasn’t a surprise that Wolf Head had a hard time believing it. If Happy Sheep had been in Wolf Head’s shoes, he wouldn’t have believed it either.

However, reality was reality. After sharing his joy, Happy Sheep didn’t care if Wolf Head actually believed him or not. Only someone lacking in confidence would hastily try to convince a denier. The more he saw how angry Wolf Head was becoming, the better he felt.

This was the truth!

Whether or not Wolf Head believed him, these were the results! One couldn’t deny reality.

“Look, look! Look at me!” Happy Sheep intentionally squabbled with Wolf Head. He didn’t hastily explain the truth to him. He took the boss drops and equipped the,… In Glory, equipment didn’t have class restrictions. It was just a question of whether or not the equipment suited the class. Happy Sheep acted like he was a model and ignored his status as a Cleric. He put on the three pieces of equipment and paraded proudly towards Wolf Head.

“Impossible! Impossible!! Wolf Head mumbled to himself. He couldn’t help but turn to look at Happy Sheep and stare at his three new equips.

“Ha ha ha, face reality, Big Head! Keep trying and maybe after ten more weeks or so, you’ll also get the chance to wear these equips. Okay, I’ve wasted enough of your time. You should hurry up and bring your team to regain the experience you lost. We’re going to need to celebrate here.” Happy Sheep said with glee.

Wolf Head felt wronged! If they weren’t all from Tyrannical Ambition, he would have challenged him to a duel right here and now. He hatefully looked at Happy Sheep’s players, who were about to depart, but he felt powerless to argue with them, but then, his eyes suddenly lit up.

“Wait!” Wolf Head used a Knight’s Charge to block Happy Sheep’s path.

“What are you doing?” Happy Sheep wasn’t scared at all.

“Who is he?” Wolf Head targeted Unrivaled Super Hottie’s head.

“Who?” Happy Sheep immediately felt like he knew who Wolf Head was talking about, but he still asked.

Wolf Head cursed inwardly. His team could see who he was targeting, but Happy Sheep wasn’t in the same team as him. How could he know who he was pointing at?

As a result, Wolf Head personally walked up and stood beside Unrivaled Super Hottie and asked: “Who is this person?”

“Why do you care?” Happy Sheep replied.

“Ha ha ha ha, no wonder you guys suddenly broke through Tomb in the Sky! It’s because you got outside help! Hm, Knight? A tank? You really how know how to look. Where did you find such an expert? What incredible equipment!” Wolf Head felt like he had been enlightened and felt extremely excited, but after his words fell, everyone suddenly became quiet. It was so quiet, it was scary. Not just Happy Sheep’s team, not even Wolf Head’s team helped him.

Wolf Head stared blankly, when he received a message from his own team. After looking more carefully at Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment, he suddenly felt stupid.

He himself was a Knight. He didn’t need to look up the equipment online. He was very clear what type of equipment Unrivaled Super Hottie possessed. With that equipment, how could he have played the role of a tank in Tomb in the Sky? Wolf Head once again refused to believe it.

“We don’t have the time to waste on you. We’re going!” Happy Sheep felt a bit weak. After all, the only reason they passed Tomb in the Sky was because of Unrivaled Super Hottie. It would truly be too embarrassing to say that they had done it all with their own strength. Today, even though they managed to clear the dungeon, next week would be different! Wolf Head’s words saying they had asked for outside help had given him a reminder. Unrivaled Super Hottie definitely wouldn’t be on their team for much longer, but if he could take this chance and get on his good side, maybe he could ask him for help when he needed him. That sounded like a good idea.

Happy Sheep thought in his head. He didn’t have the heart to compete with Wolf Head. However, Wolf Head had been struck by a heavy blow today. He refused to give up, “You wait one moment. You’re not leaving until I understand how you somehow cleared Tomb in the Sky.”

“A pass is a pass? What else needs to be said?” Happy Sheep said.

“Stop bullsh*tting. If this situation isn’t made clear, our Wolf Team won’t be able to act arrogantly in front of your Happy Sheep team anymore. It’s better if we get to the bottom of this right now.” Wolf Head said.

Happy Sheep didn’t think Wolf Sheep would actually say the truth. For a moment, he didn’t know how to respond.

At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie spoke up: “Who is this person?”

“From the fifth branch.” Happy Sheep helplessly introduced Wolf Head.

“Ha ha, what a cute name!” Unrivaled Super Hottie laughed.

‘What an arrogant name!” Wolf Sheep retorted.

“It’s so-so!”

“With your name, no one would be able to forget it. I’ve definitely never seen you in Happy Sheep’s team before.” Wolf Head said. 。

Happy Sheep’s team looked up at the sky and let out a deep sigh. They couldn’t help but agree with Wolf Head. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s name was truly too eye-catching.

“So what?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

“We have to get to the bottom of this! If Happy Sheep really did find outside help to clear this dungeon, then that means they didn’t do it with their own strength. Stop pretending in front of me.” Wolf Head said.

“Oh, if you’re talking about me, I haven’t joined the guild yet, but I guess I count as a part of their team?” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

Happy Sheep was overjoyed and hastily added: “Of course you count. You definitely count. You must count.”

“Hmph.” Wolf Head began to sneer, “After hearing what you said, I get it now. I wonder how many temporary members Happy Sheep’s team has today.”

“What do you mean?” Happy Sheep said.

“What does that mean?! Stop joking with me. You think that you can clear the dungeon now with just one helper? You probably found two or three teams, no? Or did you hide their equipment? At least that, right?” Wolf Head glared in disdain.

“Hm? There are other experts on this team? I didn’t see any!” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked Happy Sheep.

Happy Sheep didn’t know how to reply. Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie had proved Happy Sheep didn’t have any other outside help… what was he implying? For one of Tyrannical Ambition’s branch guilds, their hundred player team should have quite a few experts, no? Why did it sound like Unrivaled Super Hottie denied that there were any experts at all.

“You’d better not tell me that this is the only new person and you beat the dungeon with him!” Wolf Head said.

‘It’s the truth.” Happy Sheep didn’t back down. It really was the truth!

“Really? Then do you have the guts to let this guy spar with me? Let me see whether or not he really is an expert.” Wolf Head suddenly challenged.

Happy Sheep’s heart suddenly thumped. So he was waiting for this moment! He wanted to do a round of PvP for them to see!

Chapter 573 – Natural Knight

It wasn’t without reason that Wolf Head requested a challenge. Happy Sheep was also very clear on his reasons.

If you looked at his character profile, you could clearly see that Wolf Head has fought a total of 50,000 Arena matches with a win rate of 75.49%.

These statistics were enough to show that Wolf Head was obsessed with PK! A 75% win rate was also quite impressive. No one on Happy Sheep’s team had such a record.

Arena records were not hidden. Anyone could see them with a single click. Happy Sheep saw Wolf Head suddenly issue a challenge and immediately remembered that he hadn’t seen Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Arena record yet.

But when he checked, he was very disappointed. Unrivaled Super Hottie had only played 2,000 matches with a win rate of 30%. Compared to Happy Sheep’s team, he would be placed dead last. After all, they were still members of a top guild like Tyrannical Ambition.

A poor Arena record didn’t mean the players was a noob. There were many players who didn’t like PvP and only enjoyed PvE. Truthfully speaking, with Unrivaled Super Hottie’s display in the dungeon, Happy Sheep had a difficult time believing that this was his true Arena record.

Even though PvP and PvE were different, there were similar aspects to them. Those who were good in one area wouldn’t be too far off in the other area. Even moreso, this was the Heavenly Domain! In order to enter the Heavenly Domain, the player needed to pass the Arena portion in the Heavenly Domain quest chain. To complete the Arena part, the player needed to beat a certain number of players. However, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s 34.25% win rate meant his character hadn’t tasted victory after entering the Heavenly Domain. Or perhaps this person had absolutely no interest in PvP?

Happy Sheep tried to estimate Unrivaled Super Hottie’s chances. Compared to Wolf Head’s Arena record, the odds were way too unbalanced. Right when he was about to make an excuse, Unrivaled Super Hottie actually took the initiative to respond: “Spar? That sounds good! PvP is actually my strong point!”

“Are you serious?” Happy Sheep blurted out after looking at Unrivaled Super Hottie’s win rate in the Arena.

“With a name like mine, I can’t have any weaknesses.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied in a modest tone, making everyone speechless.

Happy Sheep didn’t know how to respond. Wolf Head had clearly looked at Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Arena record. This guy’s words and win rate were the complete opposite of each other. Along with this guy’s name, Wolf Head had already judged this person to be a megalomaniac.

He didn’t poke any holes at the contradiction between Unrivaled Super Hottie’s words and Arena record. He simply laughed: “Then, how about we go for a round?”

“No problem.”” Unrivaled Super Hottie immediately answered.

“I have a problem!” Happy Sheep interrupted. Today, he had slapped Wolf Head’s face. He wasn’t about to give him a chance to bite back. Such an obvious risk had to be avoided.

Even if Unrivaled Super Hottie had a reason for his disgusting win rate, Wolf Head’s Arena record wasn’t just for show. His win rate and total matches played clearly showed his skill. No one in Happy Sheep’s team would be an opponent to him. This was one of the reasons as to why Wolf Head had always been so arrogant in front of them.

In the dungeon, the progress between the two teams were about the same, but in PvP, Wolf Head had the advantage. Thus, when comparing the two teams, Wolf Head’s team was slightly better, allowing Wolf Head to always feel satisfied.

It hadn’t been easy delivering a heavy blow to Wolf Head. Happy Sheep didn’t want to give Wolf Head a chance to retaliate.

“Do you have any problems?” Unrivaled Super Hottie and Wolf Head unexpectedly spoke in unison, causing Happy Sheep to turn and glare at Unrivaled Super Hottie. Unfortunately, the other side couldn’t see his glares. Happy Sheep wanted to shout at him, asking which side he was on.

“You just came out of the dungeon and killed the boss, so you must be tired.” Happy Sheep said.

“Not at all. It’s nothing much.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

Happy Sheep suddenly wanted to die, when Wolf Head laughed out loud: “This brother is so straightforward. Happy Sheep don’t be so disappointed. He was the one that said it himself. Those were all trivial matters. What I want to know is how a peerless expert, who sees those as trivial matters, will do against me.

“You misunderstand me.” Unrivaled Super Hottie hastily said.

“Leading a new team to beating the final boss in this hundred player dungeon was quite difficult. What I meant was sparring with you is a trivial matter.” Unrivaled Super Hottie corrected.

“You…”

“Didn’t I say before? PvP is my strong point.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said in a serious tone.

With his character’s Arena record, it was quite hard to believe his claims , but there might be other special reasons for it. Seeing his extremely confident manner, Wolf Head immediately became alert: “This isn’t your account?”

If this wasn’t his account, then of course this character’s Arena record wouldn’t represent his actual skill.

“It’s my account.” Ye Xiu replied, “But I haven’t played on it in a long time and let my friend use it instead. He brought my Arena record way down. My real skill isn’t at this level.”

Ye Xiu explained himself because he suddenly realized that he stood out way too much. He was supposed to be a spy. His background and strengths should be mostly consistent. If his background and strength were too different, it would be suspicious.

“Ha ha ha ha, so it’s like that. Then, I’ll play with you for a bit.” Once Wolf Head heard his explanation, he immediately understood the situation. Unrivaled Super Hottie only had a total of 2000 matches played. Many of those matches were played by his friend, which meant he only could have played a maximum of 1000 matches. If he could get into the Heavenly Domain, his PvP skill shouldn’t be that bad, but the problem was that if one looked at it in the Heavenly Domain, those who could pass the Heavenly Domain Challenge were noobs in the Heavenly Domain.

This guy was probably still looking at matters from the perspective of normal servers. He didn’t realize the terror of the Heavenly Domain! Wolf Head laughed inwardly.

Happy Sheep had been hoping Unrivaled Super Hottie had some sort of mysterious solution. How could he have expected such an answer? He thought the same thing as Wolf Head and started to panic. When he saw how Wolf Head kept on pressing in this matter, he tried to stop him, but Unrivaled Super Hottie was faster: “Okay, should I find you a Cleric?”

Happy Sheep looked up at the sky and let out a long sigh. This name truly represented him, but arrogance should have a limit right?

“Bring a Cleric?” Wolf Head was slightly startled. Originally, he was about to lash out, but he suddenly had a change of thoughts and laughed: “Bring a Cleric? Two versus one?”

“Sure!” Unrivaled Super Hottie exclaimed.

“You’re pretty smart.” Wolf Head said.

“You think so?”

“If I bring a Cleric and I win. Then, there’s no way I can call that a victory, can I? He he, your request looks as if you’re taking a risk, but in reality, you’re putting yourself in an invincible position! Oh, that’s not right. You’ve definitely lost, so you’re putting your team in an unloseable situation. You really care about the team, don’t you!” Wolf Head said.

Happy Sheep also stared blankly for a moment. He hadn’t thought of doing this, but if it was actually true, it was quite a good method. However, Wolf Head had seen through his plan. He probably wouldn’t accept it now, would he?”

“You’re always misunderstanding me. I’m saying the truth.” Unrivaled Super Hottie was helpless.

“Ha ha ha, don’t count on me being fooled. I’m going up alone.” Wolf Head said.

“Your stats were reduced because you just died. Why don’t you get your experience back first?”

“You want to stall for time?” Wolf Head sneered.

“......”

“No need. Let’s go back to the city!” Wolf Head said proudly. He became inspired after hearing the other side requesting a two versus one. His stats were reduced. With this disadvantage, if he beat the opponent, wouldn’t he appear even more powerful? Wolf Head began heading towards the city.

“Where does he get all of that confidence from?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked Happy Sheep.

“What?” Happy Sheep stared blankly for a good while. After a pause, he regained his composure: “Are you talking to me?”

“Yeah!”

“No way?” Happy Sheep couldn’t believe it.

“What?”

“That’s what other people should be saying about you! This “he” is referring to yourself, right?” Happy Sheep cried.

Wolf Head hadn’t gotten very far yet, so he heard them speak. He had misunderstood initially. He thought someone else was trash talking Unrivaled Super Hottie! He had been laughing inwardly, but who would have thought Unrivaled Super Hottie had been trash talking him!

Wolf Head immediately stopped and turned around: “Please! Open your eyes! Look at my Arena record before you continue talking!”

“Oh, got it.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied, but then said to Happy Sheep: “Did you hear him? What he just said is my reason for confidence.”

“What are you talking about?” Happy Sheep was puzzled. Everyone was puzzled. Did Tomb in the Sky’s final boss make him go stupid?

“Fifty thousand matches. 75% win rate. Your skill has probably peaked. Those you can’t beat will never be beaten by you. As for those you can beat, after some time, you won’t be able to beat them anymore.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“Arena! Hurry up! I really want to see what you’re made of!!” Wolf Head furiously roared and stomped off in the direction of the city.

Happy Sheep stood dumbly in place. After a while, he said: “You really are a natural Knight! You’ve got his aggro stabilized perfectly!”

“I’m just saying the truth.” Unrivaled Super Hottie was as calm as ever.

Chapter 574 – 2v2

Mist Earth City was the city closest to the teleportation formation in Tomb in the Sky. As a Level 70 city, this place was bustling with noise. Even though the Heavenly Domain covered a vast expanse of space, it couldn’t hold every player, so every city was packed like a large metropolis. If it wasn’t because players in the game didn’t need living space, it was hard to say if a city could even sustain such a large population.

When Ye Xiu set foot in the city, he also felt deeply moved. Fortunately, he was using an alternate account, otherwise, if Lord Grim had entered this bustling city, who knew what the scene would be like. The Club guilds had enormous influence and power. Not long after entering the city, Ye Xiu saw many characters with these guild tags walking around them. If he had walked in as Lord Grim, would there have been another pursuit all over the city like there had been last time? The Heavenly Domain didn’t have any safe places, which would prove to be quite troublesome. Suddenly needing to use the restroom en-route to some place could make a player very scared and on edge.

However, a player’s wisdom was boundless. In the Heavenly Domain, was there really no way to be safe other than logging off? Of course not. Although it’s a bit ironic, the safest place to be was the PvP Arena.

The inside of the Arena looked similar to a stadium, but in reality, the Arena wasn’t considered part of the game’s scenery. It was more like a platform. In the Arena, players were completely safe because you couldn’t just rush into a huge crowd of players to attack them. If something unexpected came up, going into the Arena was a good choice. Unfortunately, this choice couldn’t be made by players out in the wild. Even though the Arena was a platform, a player could only enter the Arena through a city. Running all the way to the city in order to use the restroom clearly wasn’t worth the trouble. It would be much more efficient to just log off.

Both Happy Sheep’s team and Wolf Head’s team gathered at the Arena. They obviously weren’t there for safety reasons. As teams under the banner of the same guild, they were supposed to be in good relations with each other, so killing each other for equipment wasn’t likely to happen, but sparring in the Arena could be done if they wanted to let off some steam.

Wolf Head’s hostility towards Unrivaled Super Hottie had reached its peak. After leading his team into the Arena, he opened a room and notified Happy Sheep.

Along the way, Wolf Head gradually calmed down and began carefully preparing for the match.

As a player with 50,000 matches in the Arena, Wolf Head had a lot of experience in PvP battles. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s words angered him, but after thinking about it carefully, he also became somewhat fearful.

Because Unrivaled Super Hottie accurately pointed out a problem that he had been facing for a long time.

Wolf Head had reached a 75% win rate a long time ago, but afterwards, the only thing that increased was the number of matches that he played. His win rate was stagnant and stayed around 75% and never increased.

Opponents that he couldn’t beat before still couldn’t be beat by him.

And some of the opponents he used to be able to beat could now beat him. As their win rates went up, they became extremely difficult opponents for him.

Others might think that Unrivaled Super Hottie was taunting him, but this taunt hit too close to home. He had never met this guy before…

The more he felt like this person wasn’t simple, the less confident he became.

A short moment later, Happy Sheep brought his sheep into the Arena. Happy Sheep originally thought Wolf Head would jump on stage and loudly announce the match to everyone, but when he looked, Wolf Head wasn’t even on stage yet.

“What is this guy scheming?” Happy Sheep felt uneasy! With his understanding of Wolf Head, when he looked at this scene, he immediately felt that something unexpected had happened.

“So you’ve finally arrived.” Just as he was thinking about it, Wolf Head spoke.

“Then, let’s start!” Wolf Head continued. Following afterwards, he appeared on stage, but it wasn’t just him. There was another person too!

Wolf Head, Wolf Claw.

“You…... shameless!!!” Happy Sheep immediately shouted.

Happy Sheep recognized Wolf Claw. Wolf Claw was the lead Cleric on Wolf Head’s team and wasn’t any less skilled than him. Unrivaled Super Hottie had asked if the other side wanted to bring a Cleric and Wolf Head responded with ridicule. However, now that it was actually time to start the match, he had actually brought a Cleric?

“Relax, I’m not going to fight two versus one. That wouldn’t count as a victory, so there’s no point. I’m saying that you guys can also send another person up for a 2v2.” Wolf Head said.

“2v2?” Happy Sheep was startled.

“No need. Just me alone is enough.” Unrivaled Super Hottie went on stage, “Let’s start!”

“Ah, you…….” Happy Sheep couldn’t stop him in time. Happy Sheep didn’t even have confidence in a 1v1, let alone a 1v2. In fear that they would actually start the match like this, Happy Sheep didn’t have time to think and immediately went on stage as well.

“What are you doing?” Unrivaled Super Hottie actually complained.

Happy Sheep was speechless. He had never met someone who didn’t know the difference between good and bad.

“Okay, if it’s a 2v2 fight, then it’s fair. No matter who wins or loses, there shouldn’t be any objections.” Wolf Head said.

“Sigh, whatever.” Unrivaled Super Hottie sounded regretful.

Happy Sheep was nervous though. He felt like Wolf Head probably had some trick up his sleeve, but he couldn’t figure it out at this moment. This Unrivaled Super Hottie probably had one too. He had actually gone up by himself without hesitation. Even though winning a 2v1 wasn’t anything worth noting, the problem was that Wolf Head had analyzed this issue before. If he still planned on sticking with it, he must have some sort of other plan in mind too, right?

Happy Sheep felt like if he didn’t follow along with the other side’s plan, then it meant that he was ruining the other side’s plan, so he quickly joined.

“Good, then shall we begin?” Wolf Head said and then clicked the start button.

The map chosen was the commonly used boxing arena. It was a rectangular map without any obstructions, but because it was a 2v2 match, the boxing arena expanded to accommodate, so it appeared a lot larger than normal.

“What is he scheming?” Happy Sheep’s mind was still occupied by this question. The scene changed into the boxing arena. Wolf Head made the first move and directly charged at him.

It was a 2v2 and both teams had a Knight and Cleric. Without a doubt, the first priority target would be the Clerics. Wolf Head didn’t even give a greeting and directly rushed at him. Right when he thought he had seized the initiative, he heard someone curse from behind him: “F*ck!”

“What?” Wolf Head couldn’t turn his head around while charging forward, but up ahead, why was it only Happy Sheep in front of him?

Could it be…… that guy started moving towards Wolf Claw before he started moving?!

Right when Wolf Head had this thought, his character reached Happy Sheep. Happy Sheep was also distracted and was unable to dodge. He was hit by the Charge and sent flying.

Wolf Head hastily looked back. Sure enough, Unrivaled Super Hottie had also charged at the Cleric, even faster than he had. Happy Sheep had only just been sent flying, but Wolf Claw was already on the ground......

How did he do it?

Wolf Head was experienced though. As he thought about this question, he paid attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s and Wolf Claw’s positions.

It wasn’t a distance that Charge could cover! Wolf Head was familiar with the equipment that Knights used, so he knew that Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t have any equipment that increased Charge’s distance. If he started his skill from his initial position, Unrivaled Super Hottie must have moved a distance after using Charge. When he saw Wolf Claw crashing into the ground, Wolf Head immediately thought: could he have used a Charge and then followed up with a small jump into Heroic Leap??

Heroic Leap…… To leap such a small distance, his hands must be extremely nimble!

Wolf Head knew what was what. It was the class he played, after all. This detail immediately made him understand who was better, confirming his thoughts.

As expected, he wasn’t simple!

From this one move alone, Wolf Head lost all disdain for Unrivaled Super Hottie. Happy Sheep had fallen under his hand, but Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t even blink in their direction. He just continued to attack Wolf Claw. Wolf Head turned around and headed over to rescue him. Happy Sheep, who had been thrown to the side, wanted to cry! He was the Cleric, so why didn’t he feel protected? Unrivaled Super Hottie had left him to die as soon as the match started and didn’t even look in his direction when he was being attacked. Did Unrivaled Super Hottie really think that his existence was unnecessary?

But Happy Sheep’s goal was still victory. After healing himself, he prepared to help Unrivaled Super Hottie out.

Wolf Head quickly dashed back and used a Provoke in order to force Unrivaled Super Hottie to stop attacking Wolf Claw.

A white glow surrounded Unrivaled Super Hottie. He actually activated Knight’s Spirit at this time.

Wolf Head was surprised. He didn’t quite understand. If he didn’t want to be influenced by Provoke, he simply needed to activate Calm Like Water. Under Calm Like Water’s effects, he could dispel Provoke as well as status effects, such as Fear and Confusion. However, Knight’s Spirit didn’t have any effect.

Just as Wolf Head was puzzled, he saw the Provoked Unrivaled Super Hottie turn around and head towards him. Provoked players couldn’t attack in any other direction except towards the provoker. However, the player could still move around freely. As a result, Provoke stopped Unrivaled Super Hottie from attacking Wolf Claw, but Wolf Head would need to face the enemy’s unknown attack. Because the enemy was locked on, the enemy didn’t need to waste the efforts of looking around. Sometimes, Provoked players wouldn’t try and dispel the effects and simply go along with the flow. It wasn’t a bad choice.

Chapter 575 – Rough Coordination

With Wolf Head’s experience, he knew that Unrivaled Super Hottie only had two options. He would either activate “Calm Like Water” to get rid of Provoke’s CC effect or he would take the opportunity to attack him. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s choice in using Knight’s Spirit had puzzled him, but he could see Unrivaled Super Hottie turning his head and charging at him, so Wolf Head immediately prepared to meet his attack.

Wolf Head’s goal had been to stop Unrivaled Super Hottie from attacking Wolf Claw. From the looks of it, he had reached his goal, so now he needed to proceed to the next step.

What he hadn’t thought of was that when Unrivaled Super Hottie turned around and took a step forward, Wolf Claw was suddenly swept along as Unrivaled Super Hottie’s rushed forward! Without giving Wolf Head any time to think, Unrivaled Super Hottie sped up.

Charge!

When Wolf Head saw this skill, he immediately realized why Unrivaled Super Hottie had activated Knight’s Spirit.

Apart from buffing many of the Knight’s skills, Knight’s Spirit had another usage. When Knight’s Spirit was activated, it would refresh the cooldown of all Knight skills.

In other words, his Charge and Heroic Leap skill had originally been on cooldown, but the instant he had activated Knight’s Spirit, those skills would be up for use again.

And at this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie was using a Heroic Charge to rush over. Under Provoke’s effects, his skill was locked onto Wolf Head. However, when he charged over, Wolf Claw was swept along. This wasn’t something that Provoke could stop.

When Provoke came out, Unrivaled Super Hottie had already begun moving towards him. He instantly activated Knight’s Spirit, grasped the angle between him and Wolf Claw, charged, and and brought Wolf Claw along with him........

Wolf Head felt dizzy just thinking about it and Unrivaled Super Hottie had actually done it all?

Heroic Charge was too fast! Hitting Wolf Claw hadn’t slowed him down at all. Wolf Head suddenly woke up with a start. It was too late to dodge, so he hastily lifted up his shield in an attempt to defend and prepare to counterattack.

When Unrivaled Super Hottie arrived in front of Wolf Head, he didn’t slam into Wolf Head’s shield. Unrivaled Super Hottie, as well as his sword, came crashing down from above.

Heroic Leap!

It had also originally been on cooldown, but because of Knight’s Spirit’s activation, it could be used again.

He had cancelled his Charge and switched to Heroic Leap to bypass the shield’s defenses.

His timing and jump height had been executed perfectly. Wolf Head could see the attack coming, but he couldn’t react in time.

The knight sword swung down!

Heroic Justice Leap wouldn’t only dealt damage to Wolf Head, but also Wolf Claw.

During the few seconds that Provoke had been active, not only did Unrivaled Super Hottie give him a good beating, even Wolf Claw couldn’t escape. Knight’s Spirit had buffed the attack, so the blow did even more damage than usual......

However, Wolf Head was someone with thousands of matches under his belt. He wouldn’t panic so easily.

He had failed to dodge Heroic Leap’s attack, but he immediately Quick Recovered, rolling away at a strange angle. He wanted to leave his opponent’s attack range.

But before he could stand up, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s shield slammed into his head with a Shield Attack.

His roll didn’t have any effect. Unrivaled Super Hottie had caught him once again.

This was because Unrivaled Super Hottie was still Provoked! With the system helping him guide his attacks, it didn’t matter where Wolf Head rolled towards, because he wouldn’t be able to escape!

Thinking of this reason, Wolf Head wanted to cry. His own Provoke caused him to become depressed, but right now, he could only stand there in a daze because of the Dizzy effect from the Shield Attack.

Provoke’s effects wore off at this moment. Unrivaled Super Hottie ignored the stunned Wolf Head and immediately charged back towards Wolf Claw to attack him.

Another skill was used. Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t waste his Knight’s Spirit. He was always attacking. Any skill with a buff was used on Wolf Claw. Wolf Claw wanted to clear Wolf Head’s Dizzy effect, but at this moment, he didn’t even know how to survive.......

The spectators were dumbstruck.

It was supposed to be a 2v2 match, but apart from the beginning of the match, it was a complete 1v2.

Happy Sheep had already been forgotten.

He had rushed forward to help, but he didn’t know where to start. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attacking methods made him unable to coordinate with him at all. Whenever he thought of what he could do to help, the opportunity to do so had already passed.

Not only were Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attacks difficult for the opponent to deal with, but it was difficult for his own ally to keep up with.

This was what Wolf Head had initially been hoping for.

Why did he suddenly ask for a 2v2? Because of this exact reason.

He was worried about Unrivaled Super Hottie’s skill and didn’t have much confidence in a 1v1. Thus, he proposed a 2v2. It seemed fair, but since Unrivaled Super Hottie had only just joined Happy Sheep’s team. It didn’t matter who he partnered up with. There was no way they would be able to coordinate with each other well, but for his side? He and Wolf Claw were known for their synergy with each other. One side had a one plus one is greater than two duo, while the other side had a one plus one is less than two duo. Since that happened to be the case, wouldn’t his chances of victory be much higher?

Wolf Head’s calculations had been correct. Right now, Unrivaled Super Hottie and Happy Sheep didn’t have any sort of synergy with each other, but what he hadn’t expected was that Unrivaled Super Hottie could crush the two of them single handedly.

Letting him bring a Cleric for a 1v2...... he hadn’t been joking?

After the Dizzy effect wore off, this notion was firmly rooted in Wolf Head’s mind. Unrivaled Super Hottie continued to attack Wolf Claw, as if he had forgotten the duration of the Dizzy status effect from Shield Attack.

Wolf Head just stood on the sidelines in a daze. If he tried to go after Happy Sheep, he wouldn’t be able to kill him before Unrivaled Super Hottie killed Wolf Claw and it would become a 2v1 situation.

Wolf Head could only charge towards Unrivaled Super Hottie in an attempt to rescue Wolf Claw from death.

He activated Knight’s Spirit and prepared to launch a chain of attacks. Soon, his first attack hit Unrivaled Super Hottie’s body. He felt a bit surprised at how smoothly everything had gone.

Wasn’t it a little too easy?

Against such a skilled expert, Wolf Head’s first attack had been a cover up. He was thinking about how he should react to his opponent’s retaliation. Then, he thought about how he should chain his attacks and gain control the situation to rescue Wolf Claw.

However, Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t do anything. He just took the cover up attack, which didn’t deal that much damage.

Could this guy not care about defending???

Wolf Head suddenly felt like this might be the case. It was a common bad habit for PvE players. In PvE, players held the initiative. If the player couldn’t solo the boss, then they would bring a team next time, but in PvP, a player could only rely on his or her own efforts to beat the opponent.

With new found confidence, Wolf Head immediately attacked again.

Sure enough, Unrivaled Super Hottie let the attack hit him.

“Ha ha ha ha, so it’s like this!” Wolf Head was delighted and threw out skill after skill.

The scene suddenly looked very strange, which made all of the spectators confused. At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie suddenly yelled: “The one over there. What are you doing standing there doing nothing? Do you even know how to heal?”

“Huh? Oh!” Happy Sheep had just been standing there, watching dumbly. He had already considered himself as one of the spectators and had forgotten that he was one of the participants.

A holy white light surrounded Unrivaled Super Hottie’s body and the health he had lost from Wolf Head’s attacks quickly came back.

Wolf Head was startled.

This was a PvE strategy. It was a very rough and simple strategy. The Knight would tank the monster, while the Cleric healed the Knight’s health back up.

Who could have thought that such a strategy would appear in a PvP match? Happy Sheep’s healing completely negated Wolf Head’s damage.

What’s going on? The experienced Wolf Head felt a bit stupid. He quickly reassessed the situation.

Wolf Claw kept on being pounded by Unrivaled Super Hottie. His first priority was to rescue Wolf Claw, but Unrivaled Super Hottie was completely ignoring his attacks. Whenever he dealt some damage, Happy Sheep would immediately heal him back to full. If this continued, Wolf Claw would fall and the two would do the same to him, no?

F*ck!

How could such a stupid and simple strategy work?

But the problem was how he would resolve the situation?

He had to interrupt Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attacks! Damage was secondary. The important part was interrupting his attacks, so he could let Wolf Claw escape.

Wolf Head came up with a plan and immediately slammed his shield forward. He wanted to CC Unrivaled Super Hottie with a Dizzy.

But this time, Unrivaled Super Hottie suddenly turned a little bit and lifted his shield.

Bang! The two shields hit each other.

The attack still did some damage, but the shield blocked the Dizzy effect.

Pu!

Unrivaled Super Hottie had blocked Wolf Head’s attack, but he didn’t stop attacking Wolf Claw either.

“F*ck!” Wolf Head cursed and used another attack that could interrupt Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attacks.

Chapter 576 – Tree Trunk PvP

Clang! Clang! Clang! Clang! Clang! Clang!

Repeating ceaselessly, the same sound evoked different emotions in the spectator’s ears.

To the players from Happy Sheep's team, this sound only brought joy to their hearts. For the players from Wolf Head’s team, they could feel their hearts breaking with every strike. Wolf Head attacked over and over again. Unrivaled Super Hottie ignored all of the strikes that only dealt damage. However, every attempt to interrupt his attacks was blocked by his shield.

As a result, all of Wolf Head’s efforts were wasted. With Happy Sheep healing from the side, Wolf Head’s attacks were nothing to Unrivaled Super Hottie. On the other side, Wolf Head’s partner, Wolf Claw was barely hanging on. His health was slipping deeper and deeper into the danger zone.

This… Is this the true power of a top-tier tank?

All of the spectators had this sort of thought.

This was indeed a PvP match, but Unrivaled Super Hottie’s dominating strategy screamed PvE. A top tier tank’s control over their shield had to be perfectly skillful like this. The scene in front of them clearly conveyed that: all of Wolf Head’s problematic attacks were deflected by Unrivaled Super Hottie’s shield. Everyone agreed that this type of skill must have been forged through countless fights with monsters.

A usually unpredictable PvP match had been molded into a PvE style battle. On top of that, Wolf Head and Wolf Claw could do nothing about it.

Among the two, one of them was doing everything he could think of, but nothing worked. The other one had thought of countless ideas. However, since the beginning of the match, what could he do?

Nothing, absolutely nothing. Since the moment the match began, the only thing Wolf Claw could do was get beaten down.

Was it going to end just like this?

Wolf Head found it harder and harder to believe as he watched Wolf Claw’s HP continue to fall lower and lower. He never imagined that a match could end in such a way. Could this Unrivaled Super Hottie’s skill be forged solely through his battles with monsters? Not necessarily! PvE could develop mechanical skill, but it could not nurture such awareness. To defend with a shield, one must be able to predict the opponent’s attacks. Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t made a single mistake regarding such prediction so far. This alone was enough to prove the vast amount of PvP experience he had.

The problem was that he only had around 2000 Arena matches! Some of those were even fought by other people! How could he possibly have gathered any experience?

Or did it mean that his PvP experience was accumulated in the wild?

The battles in the wild were undoubtedly more chaotic than the ones carried out in the Arena. Because if the player didn’t bet in the Arena, then the match would simply be a matter of victory or defeat. However, every fight in the wild was a gamble. The loser could lose experience and equipment. Therefore, battles in the wild required more mental strength than fights in the Arena. In the Arena, after many matches, the player would eventually grow numb towards the result. On the other hand, in the wild, under such pressure, the player would never grow numb towards the result. As a result, there were quite a number of players who had lost all interest in the orderly battles in the Arena. Instead, they would go around the wild to “hunt”.

Was this person one of those experts?

Wolf Head was scared now. In contrast with the Arena matches, fights in the wild usually involved more complicated situations. In addition, these fights rarely started fairly: you could start at an advantage or at a disadvantage. In general, players who preferred fights in the wild were much better at dealing with complex and disadvantageous situations than regular players, who liked the Arena better. Compared to the wild, the Arena seemed more like delicate flowers.

After figuring out that Unrivaled Super Hottie was an expert of the wild, Wolf Head, who knew his own skills were inferior to his opponent’s, became even more afraid. His attacks weren’t as fierce as before.

Watching from the sidelines, Happy Sheep was a bit confused. He found it strange that a PvP battle could develop into such a situation. Even though he wasn’t as experienced as Wolf Head, as a long-time player, Happy Sheep still knew that this situation was created entirely by Unrivaled Super Hottie. But did this scene prove Unrivaled Super Hottie’s expertise in PvE or PvP battles? Happy Sheep could hardly tell the difference. Nonetheless, the situation in front of him was undoubtedly the most classic scene of a PvE monster fight......

The scared Wolf Head didn’t even have thoughts of going all out. He continued to whack Unrivaled Super Hottie sluggishly. His attacks were becoming automated and he practically transformed into a stationary attacking tower. As the repetitive metallic sounds of shield and armor continued to clank, the match reached its peak.

This kind of stationary battle was the simplestt, but also the most boring. Clearly, it was very unlikely for the current situation to change much now. Everyone was waiting for the moment Wolf Claw fell. Once that happened, then this match would be set in stone.

The audience didn’t have to wait for long. Wolf Claw, who did nothing but get chopped since the beginning of the match, finally fell. In that same moment, Wolf Head gave up all hope and stopped attacking. He directly surrendered and left the match.

The atmosphere was somewhat cold.

Despite the quick pacing at the beginning that ignited the audience’s excitement, this match ended rather unexpectedly.

There were no up and downs, no excitement, nothing. It couldn’t have ended more dully.

The start had everyone’s hearts in their throats, but the ending didn’t even allow their hearts to fall back down. The match steadily trapped their hearts there uncomfortably. Everyone felt that the match hadn’t been good. Regardless of which side won, neither side felt satisfied.

“Leader! Let me try!”

This person was from Wolf Head’s Party. Some had found their defeat unreasonable and humiliating. For the sake of their pride, many were demanding a rematch. As for Wolf Head? Only he, who had experienced the battle for himself, could understand the helplessness that he felt. Even though he had analyzed the situation, even though he knew how to change the situation and attempted to do so… the result was the same: not the slightest thing changed. If he would have known, then he would rather have attacked Happy Sheep. Even though that would have gotten the same result, at least he wouldn’t feel like choking on bitterness now.

Wolf Head didn’t know what he could say to the eager players who wanted a match. He understood how they felt. If he had watched such a match from the sidelines, he would definitely want a match to turn the mood around. The was because, from the views of the spectators, they thought of many ways of disrupting Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attacks. However, only by being there in person would they discover that all of these ideas would have been useless. Didn’t Wolf Head try? But the crucial strikes would always be blocked by the opponent’s shield.

“No need.” Wolf Head sighed, “It’s useless.

“Leader, you and him are of the same class. He knew Knights too well. If it were any other class, then it definitely wouldn’t have been the same!” Someone cried out.

Upon hearing this, Wolf Head’s heart shook with realization.

Right! He himself had been wondering how Unrivaled Super Hottie saw through every trick of his, but now he knew. He had overlooked such a fundamental factor: they were of the same class. Due to the extreme familiarity both parties possessed regarding the other, matches between the same class tended to be boring and have little entertainment value. The result of this particular match was an extreme example, but… Wolf Head suddenly found the excuse “because we are of the same class” quite plausible.

“Let me try!” The players of Wolf’s Party were fairly upright. Without the words of their leader, none of them would go up and challenge Unrivaled Super Hottie on their own.

Meanwhile, on Happy Sheep’s side, things were unusually quiet. Although they had won the match , it had not been a glorious victory. WIth no dramatic ambience to speak of, it was as if all that happened was a weak monster that guarded the gateway of a dungeon had been killed. If everyone started cheering in delight, the scene would be rather weird.

After all, Wolf Head’s team and Happy Sheep’s team both belonged to Tyrannical Ambition, so the competition between them had always been constructive. They weren’t actually enemies, so they didn’t only seek the end results, but rather mutual benefit. What they needed was the process. As of now, the overly mundane process left them unsatisfied. Even the act of bragging about their victory felt hollow. Therefore, despite being the victors, no one from Happy Sheep’s Party went over to Wolf ’s Head Party to laugh at their failure.

“Unrivaled Super Hottie, do you dare to have a match with me?”

At this moment, someone from Wolf Head’s Party issued a challenged.

The victory didn’t bring much joy to Happy Sheep’s Party, but it brought much bitterness and discomfort to the Wolf Head’s team, so they were eager to prove themselves.

“What? After seeing the last fight, you still want to fight me?” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“Useless words.”“Is there a need?” Unrivaled Super Hottie gave an unexpected answer. Happy Sheep and the others thought he would jump in again without asking for the team’s opinion.

“Are you trying to run after taking a victory?” The opponent started to mock him.

“Is it because you thought the match was too boring and the victory wasn’t beautiful?” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“Exactly! If it were me….”

“If it were you, it would have being the same.” Unrivaled Super Hottie interrupted.

“Come on! Show me!” The player had already entered. He was a Launcher. Similarly, he brought a Cleric with him.

“Last one!” Unrivaled Super Hottie said and entered. Then he asked Happy Sheep’s team: “I need a Cleric.”

“I can do it!” Happy Sheep entered by himself.

“Ready?” The opponent asked coldly.

“Start!”

As soon as the match started, the Launcher began attacking, but with a slight sidestep, Unrivaled super Hottie easily dodged the attack. Immediately, the latter followed up with a Knight Spirit. This was a rule within the Arena:, all cool downs would be reset at the start of a new match.

Right after Knight Spirit was activated, Unrivaled Super Hottie charged forward. The Launcher was expecting it. He jumped and tried to avoid it with an Aerial Cannon, but who would have thought that Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Charge would curve instead of go in a straight line? The Heroic Charge came in from a strange angle and slammed the Launcher back into the ground. The skill hadn’t finished yet. Pushing the Launcher along with him, the curved continued to stretch around the Arena. The Cleric had never imagined that the Charge would even come close to him. Unable to dodge in time, the Cleric was hit!

The Heroic Leap that followed smashed into both of them. Unrivaled Super Hottie then stunned the Launcher with a Shield Attack and focused on the Cleric.

“This is…. he’s finished rounding up the monsters already?” Those familiar with the scene couldn’t help but make a comment.

Chapter 577 – Replicating Victory

The Launcher had planned on taking the initiative from the beginning, but after just a single skill, the last match repeated itself again. As a matter of fact, it was worse since he had fallen into hot water right away. Wolf Head had at least thrown out a Provoke against Unrivaled Super Hottie and attacked Happy Sheep at the beginning of the match.

However, players weren’t NPCs. Even though the Cleric was entirely powerless under Unrivaled Super Hottie’s control, the Launcher would be cleared of the stunned state eventually. Wolf Head’s players were brainstorming on how to deal with this type of situation. Meanwhile, the Launcher was preparing for his next move.

The moment the stun duration ended, the Launcher retread by using an Aerial Fire. As expected, Unrivaled Super Hottie paid no attention to him. Then, the Launcher propped his cannon on his shoulder. With a blue flash, an X-1 Extruder missile came flying out from the cannon’s barrel some distance away.

Glory had numerous skills with various CC effects, and blocking with a shield could negate many of those effects, but not all of them. X-1 Extruder’s effect of attracting the target then dragging the target away was one of these spells. The Launcher clearly knew this, so he started off with this move that would render the shield’s block ineffective, wondering what Unrivaled Super Hottie could possibly do to counter it.

Nonetheless, Unrivaled Super Hottie seemed to oblivious towards the impending missile as he did completely ignored it. Only when he was about to enter the suction effect’s range did he swing out his sword horizontally: a Repel. He obviously manipulated this skill a bit since the Cleric wasn’t pushed the maximum distance away. While the Cleric slid away, Unrivaled Super Hottie also shifted forward, along with the Cleric.

The scene looked like two ghosts drifting. Everyone soon realized that Unrivaled Super Hottie had entered the X-1 Extruder’s effect range and was being dragged by the missile. Facing the incoming missile, Unrivaled Super Hottie swung out his shield, not in an attempt to block, but rather to attack. He didn’t activate a skill though. This attack wouldn’t have any special effects. It would only deal small amounts of damage, but it still successfully detonated the missile.

At such close distance, the explosion would obviously hurt Unrivaled Super Hottie, but with his shield in front of him, the shockwave caused by the explosion wouldn’t push him away. As for the damage taken… wasn’t Happy Sheep starting to chant with his cross in the air?

The Cleric remained within Unrivaled Super Hottie’s grip. All the possible interference caused by the X-1 Extruder were completely negated by Unrivaled Super Hottie’s maneuvers. Even though the attempt had done some damage, hadn’t Unrivaled Super Hottie also been taking damage from Wolf Head in the last match, but then healed by Happy Sheep?

The Launcher was clearly surprised, seeing his plan being dealt with so easily. But the Launcher had more tricks up his sleeves. Roaming, Mechanical Seeker, Demolition, Satellite Beam… Skills activated one after another, each with a thoughtful plan laid out. Finally, this match was no longer dull in the eyes of the spectators. Everyone wondered how Unrivaled Super Hottie would nullify all of these powerful attacks.

In the end, whether it was by dodging, blocking with his shield, running around, standing still, taking the attack, or not taking the attack, Unrivaled Super Hottie dispelled every attack. The only thing that didn’t change was the fact that the Cleric remained standing there, getting beaten up.

“Impossible!” The Launcher finally ran out of ideas, but the situation hadn’t changed in the slightest. The only thing that changed compared to the previous match was the helplessness of the close quarter fighter had turned into that of the long-range combatant’s.

The Launcher had no more plans. If he were to attack again, he could only employ his previously used strategies. Unrivaled Super Hottie might make a mistake, but would a single lucky chance be able to solve the fundamental issue? That chance could only allow the Cleric to heal himself a little before falling back into Unrivaled Super Hottie’s grasp again. If the Cleric could truly get out of this crisis, then the battle wouldn’t have been like this from the start.

The Launcher knew that this time, he hadn’t become the savior of his team. Instead, he stood shoulder to shoulder with his team leader Wolf Head in another embarrassing defeat. The Cleric eventually died, but during that time, the Launcher didn’t stay idle. He pointed his cannon at Happy Sheep. Poor Happy Sheep dashed around all over the Arena field, but Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t show the slightest bit of interest in rescuing him. On the other hand, this Launcher was desperate to kill him to save himself some face before Unrivaled Super Hottie killed off his Cleric.

However, he had switched targets too late. Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment was weaker, the Launcher still couldn’t catch up. In addition, the Cleric of Wolf Head’s team was much more obedient than Happy Sheep. He looked like he was just standing there, taking the attacks.

Was the Cleric doing this on purpose? Of course not! His current sorry state was entirely because of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s manipulations.

In that moment, Wolf Head finally came to this realization.

Everyone focused on how Unrivaled Super Hottie nullified all of the Launcher’s attempts to disrupt him. However, all of thom overlooked how Unrivaled Super Hottie’s endless strikes suppressed the enemy Cleric into obedience.

Clerics didn’t have many offensive abilities, but turning a player-controlled character into a ragdoll was still a difficult task.

“Is this… also developed from PvE?” Wolf Head, who was very familiar with Knights, observed Unrivaled Super Hottie’s maneuvers attentively. Unfortunately, the Cleric had long since given up, so Wolf Head couldn’t figure out how Unrivaled Super Hottie dealt with the Cleric in detail. Thinking back now… all he remembered was how Unrivaled Super Hottie had cancelled the Launcher’s attacks.

Up until the Cleric fell, Wolf Head wasn’t able to get much information. Right after the Cleric fell, Unrivaled Super Hottie changed direction and charged straight at the Launcher. The Launcher tried to maintain some distance, but Unrivaled Super Hottie caught him after a few attempts.

“Hm? This could be a good chance to watch too!” Wolf Head suddenly thought, wondering if Unrivaled Super Hottie would turned the Launcher into another sandbag. At the same time, Wolf Head regretted quitting right after Wolf Claw’s defeat. If he had fought with Unrivaled Super Hottie himself, he would know his capabilities much better.

Unfortunately, the Launcher replicated the entire last match, even Wolf Head’s decision at the last moment. Upon seeing the defeat of the Cleric and that the match had turned into a two versus one battle, the Launcher surrendered. Gloom loomed over Wolf Head, but he couldn’t say anything. After all, he had been the one to set this example.

For this kind of match, one victory felt awkward and dull. However, there were two victories now and the second match was an exact replica of the first one. During both matches, the opponents were completely powerless. This demonstrated the true power of the victor. After the second victory, cheers, applause, and congratulations exploded out of Happy Sheep’s team. Quite a number of them shouted, “Do you accept it now, you wolves?”

How could the wolves accept such infuriating matches so easily? But what would be the point of objecting now? The other side would just say “then try again” and Unrivaled Super Hottie would slap them to death again.

Everyone in Wolf Head’s team was unhappy. Wolf Head was powerless to do anything. In the end, he could only say “Let’s go,” and all of the players in Wolf’s Party left dejectedly.

“Bro, incredible!” Upon seeing Wolf Head’s team taking their leave, Happy Sheep’s anxiety finally disappeared. His heart was filled with joy.

Today, not only did they surpass their long time rival in terms of dungeon progress, but they also beat them in the Arena, which had long since been their weak spot. Even though these had only been possible because of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s presence, today was still a day to remember.

“Incredible!!” There was not a single player in the team who was unhappy with Unrivaled Super Hottie. Everyone praised their hero with joy.

“Haha, didn’t I say it earlier? This is what I’m good at.” Unrivaled Super Hottie responded.

“Yes, yes.” Everyone nodded in agreement.

“If there isn’t anything anymore, then shall we call it a day?” Unrivaled Super Hottie said, preparing to leave.

Happy Sheep sighed, “Bro, you’re so skilled. Once you join the guild, you’ll quickly be put into the elite team. When that happens, don’t forget about us!”

“Of course.” Unrivaled Super Hottie laughed.

The players of Sheep’s Party flocked over one after another to add Unrivaled Super Hottie on their friend list, bidding their goodbyes unwillingly. The hundred-player dungeon was rather time consuming. Despite having maintained a pretty normal schedule for the past few days, Ye Xiu still dragged it well into the night. Chen Guo and Tang Rou had left awhile ago. Even though Chen Guo was still curious about Ye Xiu’s intention for joining Tyrannical Ambition, she still couldn’t find any interest in watching, seeing that they were still running dungeons. Although her skill wasn’t that high, she had been one of the members of the main force in Excellent Era back then. The team that she was in had a much better progress in the dungeon. In Chen Guo’s eyes, these people’s skill levels were on the low side.

After saying goodbye to the players of Sheep’s Party, Ye Xiu called it a day. However, the players of Sheep’s Party had no such plans. They were obviously planning on pulling an all-nighter. As of now, they were still together chatting. The focus was none other than the expert Knight that they had met today.

The majority of the conversations were about how incredible this person was.“I can’t see it. All I know is that there is no way for me to become that skillful.” The main tank, Seven Blossom Leaves, replied after being asked.

“I played once with the guild’s main force once. I think his skills are on the same level as our branch guild’s number one Knight, Flight.” Happy Sheep said.

“That’s the main tank of the elite party! He’s that good?!” Someone exclaimed. Flight, the number one Knight of the fourth branch guild, was already an unbelievable existence to the players in that guild.

“He might even be better.” Happy Sheep spoke.

“Oh? Why would you say that?” Seven Blossom Leaves asked.

“Clerics are the ones who can understand the main tank’s strength the best. Even though we were really worried when we had to heal Unrivaled Super Hottie, that worry mainly came from our distrust in him. Now that I look back at the big picture, he didn’t make any mistakes that we needed to compensate for. All we had to do was our most basic job.” Happy Sheep pointed out.

Chapter 578 – The People from Tyrannical Ambition

Happy Sheep’s analysis received the approval of the other Clerics on the team. They all expressed that, if their team had such a tank, then running dungeons would be very easy. Praising another tank in front of the team was usually considered offensive to the other tanks, but Seven Blossom Leaves himself was also completely convinced by Unrivaled Super Hottie’s skill, therefore, no one in Happy Sheep’s team had any misgivings. As for the second, third, and fourth tank, if even the main tank was neglected, then nothing needed to be said about them.After discussing everything, everyone gasped in admiration. Happy Sheep didn’t want to dampen the mood, but in the end, he found it uncomfortable to hold these words within his heart. Thus, Happy Sheep called for everyone to recognize that it would be hard for such an expert to a permanent member of their team.

Many of the players in the team had been worried about this fact earlier. Now that they heard their team leader say it himself, they all felt that it was a pity. In the first half of the night, they were pushed to the peak of excitement in waves, but after hearing this news, everyone couldn’t help but feel somewhat disappointed.“Sigh……” Someone sighed and the conversation ended.

However, the news of Happy Sheep’s team completing Tomb in the Sky spread throughout the guild. There were many hundred-man teams in the guild and many of them had also been stuck on Tomb in the Sky, just like Happy Sheep’s team had been. The fourth and fifth branch guilds would often compete against each other. Being in the same guild didn't mean that there was a lot of teamwork and friendship. Games are more fun, when there’s competition. Levels, skill, equipment, anything that could be compared would be compared.

Now that Happy Sheep’s team had reached a completely new height in the dungeon, the players on his team were naturally very willing to share their joy with others. There were all sorts of responses in the chat. Some congratulated them, while others asked for help. Some were envious, and so on.

At this moment, Happy Sheep received a message from his guild leader: “You’ve cleared Tomb in the Sky?”

“Yeah……” Happy Sheep couldn’t help but reply. He wished that the guild leader wouldn’t notice what had happened and would just forget about Unrivaled Super Hottie’s existence for the time being so they could spend a few more days with the pro. It was a pity that passing the dungeon was considered a big deal, so the guild leader came to ask him the moment he received the notice.

“How did Unrivaled Super Hottie perform?” The guild leader asked.

Happy Sheep took a deep breath and spoke honestly. “It was only thanks to him that we cleared the dungeon. It would have been impossible otherwise.”“Oh?”Upon that, Happy Sheep informed the guild leader of all of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s spectacular performances, including his PVP performance after the conflict with the fifth branch’s Wolf Head.

“How good do you think his skills are?” The guild leader then asked.

“No lower than Flight.” Happy Sheep replied.

The value of this appraisal was not light at all! Flight was the head knight of the fourth branch, and Tyrannical Ambition's fourth branch was considered a top tier guild in the view of Heavenly Domain players. It couldn’t be compared with guilds created by normal players. The only guilds that were stronger would be the main guilds of the different Clubs. A top Knight of such a guild in the Heavenly Domain was very impressive.

“Oh.” The guild leader was unsure as to how to react towards Happy Sheep’s high appraisal. “Is he still on?”

“He’s offline.” Happy Sheep replied.

“Then let’s talk about it tomorrow!” The guild leader spoke.

Ye Xiu slept very late that night, but he didn’t get up too late in the morning. He met Chen Guo when he woke up, who instantly asked about yesterday’s final result.

“Cleared!” Ye Xiu said..

“How did those guys act afterwards?” Chen Guo asked.

“Probably kneeling on all fours out of admiration?” Ye Xiu guessed.

“......”

After breakfast, they headed to the private room to game. When Unrivaled Super Hottie logged on, no one on his friends’ list was online. Happy Sheep’s team hadn’t slept all night yesterday, so they were still offline and had stopped work for the day. Ye Xiu logged onto his Unrivaled Super Hottie’s account, but he didn’t play on it. He found a computer besides Tang Rou and logged onto Lord Grim. “Are you just going to stand there and wait for your death!” Chen Guo was able to roughly guess Ye Xiu’s intention. If the two accounts were logged in at the same time, it would prevent people from associating Unrivaled Super Hottie with Ye Xiu! If this were in the past, no matter how good a player was in the game, no one would ever imagine this player would be a God. But now, a God mingling among them was not a secret anymore between the big guilds. Now that the major guilds had been tossed around multiple times, they had to be more cautious. Even though it wasn’t hard to log onto multiple accounts at the same time, it was necessary. It wouldn’t be too hard to connect the dots if two experts with supposedly no connection would, coincidentally, never appear online at the same time.

After Chen Guo finished dumping Unrivaled Super Hottie in the Arena, she paid no more attention to him. She went over to ask what Ye Xiu was planning to do with Lord Grim.

“Leveling up through dungeons!” As he spoke, Lord Grim had already logged online. He scanned his friends list and to his surprise, he found One Inch Ash online. Ye Xiu was about to message him, but One Inch Ash was already one step ahead: “Good morning, senior.”

“Good morning, good morning, are you free?” Ye Xiu asked. Pro-gamers also had work to attend to. Even though he would also be playing, it was a different type of playing. Killing time in the game counted as being quite free.

“Yes……”

“Want to enter a dungeon?” Ye Xiu asked.“Sure!” Qiao Yifan wished to follow God and get some advice. Playing together was exactly what he wanted.

“Do you want me to come along?” Chen Guo also responded to Ye Xiu’s “Leveling up through dungeons.”

“Sure!” Ye XIu agreed.

Upon hearing this, Chen Guo didn’t log into her tenth server account, but logged onto Chasing Haze instead. Ye Xiu invited her into the team and called for Qiao Yifan. He gave him a location and the three people went there to meet up.

Level 55 was Heavenly Domain’s lowest-level dungeon, but it was definitely not beginner friendly like the beginner village in the normal servers. However, Chen Guo was on her Level 70 main account and there were two pro level players. It went without saying that the three could easily complete a small five-man dungeon.

Chasing Haze had strong equipment, so she naturally became the main DPS unit. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash assisted Chasing Haze, while he paid attention to controlling the battlefield. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, on the other hand, ran back and forth like a fireman, doing everything. As the three people worked together, they advanced through the dungeon fairly quickly. Chasing Haze was more than capable of soloing this Level 55 five man dungeon. It goes without saying what would happen with the addition of two experts helping her.

“How is it? What knowledge have you recently gained as a Phantom Demon?” The dungeon wasn’t difficult, so Ye Xiu started a conversation with Qiao Yifan.

Wasn’t this why he was following Ye Xiu? He instantly reported to Ye Xiu about what he had experienced for Ye Xiu to advise him on.

Ye Xiu gave him some tips, while letting Qiao Yifan experiment on the dungeon’s mobs. Even though Lord Grim could only use Sword Formation, he could still demonstrate it.

“Good good, not bad, not bad.” Ye Xiu watched Qiao Yifan’s performance and complimented him. “That’s the general idea. However these dungeon mobs are brain-dead. In a real competition setting, it will definitely not be as easy as it is now. The NPC doesn’t know your intentions, so they can easily be manipulated by you. However, it’s different with players. They can predict your intentions and will naturally try to interfere. They might even beat you at your own game. Therefore, your thoughts must not be set by this training. The changes that occur in competitive matches are always more than you can ever imagine.”

“I understand.” Qiao Yifan responded.

As a result, the trio continued to clear the dungeon until they couldn’t anymore. All the questions Qiao Yifan had piled up were all answered. Also, it was obvious that he didn’t just leave the questions there to wait for Ye Xiu to answer. He always had his own thoughts too like a pro. Qiao Yifan was unlike Tang Rou or Steamed Bun Invasion who needed Ye Xiu to specifically guide them every step along the way. Sometimes, Ye Xiu only needed to say a few words and Qiao Yifan would be able to locate the problems. In fact, Ye Xiu didn’t teach him much on the mechanical side. Ye Xiu mostly taught him his own experiences and have Qiao Yifan learn about them. Experience couldn’t be gained through just through talking about it, but this method would tell him what to be aware of, so when Qiao Yifan experiences these circumstances himself, he’ll have an idea of what to do.

The morning passed like this. Qiao Yifan obviously couldn’t play forever. He had to log off in the afternoon. After Ye Xiu returned from lunch, he continued to use Lord Grim, until Chen Guo noticed that someone had messaged Unrivaled Super Hottie. She called out to Ye Xiu, who decisively dumped Lord Grim aside and sped to her side.

“Hey, what do I do with this?” Lord Grim was in middle of a dungeon, but was then just thrown to the side.

“Just leave him! I can continue afterwards.” Ye Xiu said.

Heavenly Domain’s second safe place: the dungeon.

“Then I’ll just leave him here.” Chen Guo spoke as she logged off Chasing Haze. If she logged on again, she would appear in the same place in the dungeon. If a player entered a dungeon, there were no other way to leave apart from dying or clearing the dungeon.

As for Unrivaled Super Hottie, he received a message from Happy Sheep. Ye Xiu looked and saw that Happy Sheep was asking where he was.

“Mist Earth CIty。” Ye Xiu replied.

“Okay. Our guild’s boss would like to meet you!” Happy Sheep replied afterwards.“Where?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We’re at Luxuriant Mountain City.” Happy Sheep said.

“Ok, I’ll come over.” Ye Xiu replied and had Unrivaled Super Hottie leave the Arena. Luxuriant Mountain City was also a Level 70 city. It shared a teleportation array with Mist Earth City, so it saved a lot of trouble traveling there.

After being transported to Luxuriant Mountain City and asking Happy Sheep for his location, he saw a team of players bearing the Tyrannical Ambition fourth branch title. Happy Sheep was among them. When he saw Unrivaled Super Hottie coming over, he hurriedly called out. After coming to the front, Ye Xiu scanned the team of people’s sparkling equipment. With just a glance, he instantly knew that these players were not like Happy Sheep’s group who aimed for moderately difficult dungeons. These people were probably the elite members of Tyrannical Ambition’s fourth guild.

“Loyal Hear, Flight, Burning Mountain......” Chen Guo clicked her tongue as she watched Ye Xiu’s screen, already sighing.

“Oh? You know them?” Ye Xiu asked.

“All of them. They belong to Tyrannical Ambition!” Chen Guo spoke. She originated from

Excellent Dynasty and Tyrannical Ambition was their sworn enemy. Wasn’t there a saying? The people who understood you the most were your enemies.

“Woah！It’s Wandering Peak” When Ye Xiu tilted his camera, it caused Chen Guo to see another person, which made Chen Guo exclaim.

“Huh? Who’s that?” Ye Xiu looked at an Elementalist.

“You don’t even know him? He’s the guild leader of Tyrannical Ambition!!” Chen Guo spoke.

“Oh……” Ye Xiu paused. “How incredible! I’m only familiar with the tenth server guild leader.”

Chapter 579 – Starting at the Top

Wandering Peak was Jiang You’s main account in the Heavenly Domain and Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader. Ye Xiu had interacted with him in the tenth server before, but he hadn’t really cared. In his eyes, there was no difference between Cold Night or Jiang You.

A famous name like Wandering Peak didn’t need any tags next to his name. For Glory’s players, in terms of reputation, the guild leaders of these top-tier guilds weren’t any less renowned than pro players. All of them could be considered public figures. Wandering Peak didn’t need a “Guild Leader” tag for people to recognize him.

As Ye Xiu moved Unrivaled Super Hottie forward, Happy Sheep introduced who was who. Besides their IDs, Happy Sheep also told him their titles in the guild. It’s like how in real life, whenever people introduce someone else, people always tells others about that someone else’s job. However, several of the titles sounded kind of funny to Ye Xiu. For example, Tyrannical Ambition fourth branch’s number one Knight and so on. There were just too many adjectives attached to the title. However, none of the adjectives could be removed. Get rid of Tyrannical Ambition? Then, the title wouldn’t seem very impressive. Get rid of fourth branch? It wouldn’t be the truth......

“Oh oh oh oh oh......”

Ye Xiu responded with an “Oh”, after each player’s introduction. After the introductions were finished, he concluded: “Hi, everyone.”

With Jiang You’s status, his character’s equipment was naturally top tier. Equipment was a symbol of status. Whether it was Tyrannical Ambition’s great guild leader or the branch guild’s number one Knight, if they walked out with Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment, it would practically be the same as walking out naked. No one would take their title seriously.

“Unrivaled Super Hottie? What an interesting name. Speaking of your name, I once knew someone called Unrivaled Silence, but I haven’t seen him in a long time. It seems like he really did go silent.” The first person to speak was Tyrannical Ambition fourth branch’s number one Knight, Flight. It sounded like a joke, but it clearly showed his hostility towards Unrivaled Super Hottie.

This wasn’t unexpected. Very few players were as kind as Seven Blossom Leaves. Online games were competitive in nature.

In the normal servers, everyone compared their levels to other players. In the Heavenly Domain, everyone was max level, so they compared their equipment, stats, skill level, experience, dungeon progress, Arena record, and so on. Anything could be compared would be compared. The competitive environment didn’t differ from real life too much. Very few were willing to admit their inferiority.

Like Flight, Seven Blossom Leaves, or even Crispy Bean. They were their team’s number one Knight. Relatively speaking, they were at the top of their respective teams. Honest and kind players like Seven Blossom Leaves were the exception. Most players were like Crispy Bean, who looked down on experts of the same class.

However, everyone showed off their feelings in different ways. Crispy Bean was more childish. Flight handled things more maturely. He clearly knew that Unrivaled Super Hottie was someone the guild leader wanted to rope into the guild. Moreover, the guild leader personally came over to invite him, showing the importance of this matter. If he made things too difficult for Unrivaled Super Hottie, he wouldn’t be giving face to the guild leader.

The enormous guild had an almost corporation-like management. The higher a guild member’s status, the more the guild member wouldn’t be able to look at things purely from a gaming perspective. A lot of matters had to be handled responsibly. Guild leaders weren’t mothers to the guild members. Even though they often acted like one, everyone knew how much power these guild leaders possessed.

“Unrivaled Silence? What class?”

Ye Xiu responded to Flight’s words.

“Class? It’s been too long. I forgot.” Despite being startled, Flight responded quite calmly.

“Oh, is that so!” Ye Xiu said and even added a “Ha ha” emoticon.

Flight suddenly felt dejected. Unrivaled Silence? He didn’t know anyone like that. He just saw Unrivaled Super Hottie’s name and then fabricated a person to mock the other side’s arrogance. But then the other side asked for this imaginary person’s class and he couldn’t give an answer. The “Ha ha” emoticon seemed to be laughing at him.

“I’ve heard how skilled you are. Today, I’ve finally gotten to see it.” Happy Sheep did the introductions. Flight opened up the meeting. Now, it was Jiang You’s turn to speak up. The fourth branch’s guild leader didn’t get a chance to talk though. This simple exchange showed the complexity of the relationships between guild members.

“Ha ha, the rumors are true.”

“Of course, of course.”

Normal people would hear his arrogance and explode in anger. Jiang You didn’t have the best temper either, so it made Flight quite puzzled, when he saw how friendly Jiang You was being. Even though he wasn’t a part of the main guild, he still had some understanding of the overall guild leader. Jiang You wasn’t as cold and strict as Hang Wenqing, but he still leaned towards that side. Flight had never heard of him being so friendly before. What was going on today?

Someone’s personality couldn’t suddenly change in an instant, which meant the reason lay with Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Was he really that good?

Flight muttered to himself. He didn’t look down on Unrivaled Super Hottie because of his equipment. After all, equipment was external. If his skill was truly up to mark, then his equipment would immediately be switched with equipment that might even be good as his own.

Seeing the overall guild leader’s attitude, Flight felt a bit of regret towards his initial remarks.

Speaking of which, it didn’t matter who this person was. What was the point in competing with him? Today was a rare opportunity to interact with the main guild leader. It was more important to show his worth.

Flight had his own plans.

Even though their branch guilds were also a part of Tyrannical Ambition in name, in everyone else’s eyes, the main guild was the true guild. The branch guild players all hoped to enter the main guild.

The main guild had obviously reached its max capacity a long time ago. According to the guild’s rules, the guild wouldn’t kick someone out for no reason. But everyone knew that the rules weren’t rigid. If a truly outstanding expert came, the main guild would certainly find some way to get someone out of the guild. As for Flight? He didn’t think being the fourth branch’s number one Knight was good enough. Speaking of this, he hated how others always added “fourth branch” after “Tyrannical Ambition”, when being introduced. He felt like these two added words made it sound like a joke.

He hoped to get rid of these two words! The only way to do it was obviously to join the main guild.

This was why enough he hoped his strength would be enough to garner the attention of someone with power in the main guild. Unfortunately, he had held the title of number one Knight in the fourth branch for a long time, but the main guild hadn’t given him any offers. Today, the overall guild leader had personally come, making Flight feel like it was a good opportunity to display his value. However, the reason for the personal visit was because of another Knight. Flight couldn’t help but feel jealous, so he intentionally showed hostility towards Unrivaled Super Hottie. If Unrivaled Super Hottie was truly acknowledged by the overall guild leader, then didn’t that mean he would directly enter the main guild?

He needed to perform better than him!

Flight had made the decision a long time ago, but now that he was reflecting on his previous actions, using words to compete against him felt somewhat childish. He immediately criticized himself. He already knew what he needed to do today. He needed to show that his skill surpassed Unrivaled Super Hottie’s. That was the only true way. A word battle was pointless.

Flight arranged his plan, while Jiang You and the others told him their purpose in coming here.

“A wild boss?” Ye Xiu stared blankly.

“No way?!” Even Chen Guo was astonished. It might be a game, but wasn’t this spying progressing too quickly? Other spies took three years and then another three years to get this far, but Unrivaled Super Hottie had only just joined a small support guild only two days ago and he was already going to join the elites in a fight for a wild boss?

Normal guilds didn’t pay too much attention to the rules. Experts would immediately be put into the top team, but for a Club guild with such a complicated competitive environment? Wild bosses were very important and dangerous matters. If there was a spy from another guild, it would be disastrous. Strategies, plans, and so on would be sold out by the spy. It would be impossible to steal the boss if that happened.

“Yes, Sword Peak Ravine’s Blade Master Lan Rui has spawned. Our people are already heading over. We’re going over to support them. You just happen to be online. Why not come with us?” Jiang You said.

“Sure!” Ye Xiu happily accepted.

“Good. Brother, your equipment.......” Jiang You looked at him and had to say it: “Brother, you can’t join our guild yet, so I can’t give you contribution points to use. You’ll just have to make do with this for now!”

Jiang You had clearly been prepared. If not, why would an Elementalist carry a full set of Knight equipment?

Ye Xiu wasn’t polite and accepted the trade from Wandering Peak. It was a complete set from accessories to weapons. It was far better than his current equipment. For a normal player, his equipment went up to grades. It was enough to feel moves. As a result, Ye Xiu expressed his thanks and quickly put them on. Then, he requested for a trade with Wandering Peak and offered his trash equipment: “I’ll have to trouble you to donate these equipment for me. Ha ha ha ha ha.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah...... this.....” Jiang You was sweating! He was an Elementalist. With his Strength, carrying a Knight’s armor, weapon, and shield would definitely impact his movement heavily. The equipment he had brought with him were for Unrivaled Super Hottie. Now the other side was giving him back equipment. It wouldn’t be good to carry it in an intense battle.

But the other side said he was donating it to the guild. How could he refuse? It wouldn’t be appropriate to say “You can keep it.” With new improved equipment, why would he keep his old trash? Most players would donate their old equipment to the guild. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s actions weren’t weird. It was just that this guy was telling him to donate it for him, leaving Jiang You at a loss for what to do.

Chapter 580 – On Equal Footing

It wouldn’t be good to accept the equipment, but it also wouldn’t be good to refuse the equipment. These situations were a test of the perceptiveness of his subordinates. Sure enough, the fourth branch guild leader wasn’t just a guild leader in name. He had heard their conversation and immediately interjected: “I should probably be the one to donate the equipment! After all, you’re still a part of the fourth branch!”

The awkwardness was easily resolved. Even Flight felt happy. When he heard that Unrivaled Super Hottie was still a part of the fourth branch, how could he not be happy? Entering the main guild was his goal. At this moment, his competitor was Unrivaled Super Hottie. He didn’t want to be beat by his competitor.

Soon afterwards, Jiang You parroted the fourth branch guild leader’s words and cancelled the trade. The fourth branch guild leader traded with Unrivaled Super Hottie and received the trash equipment full of tears. He was a Berserker, a physical class. Carrying a set of equipment wouldn’t affect his movements as much as an Elementalist. His movements would still be affected, but he had to take the burden at this moment.

“There’s no time to lose. Let’s go.” Jiang You said.

Everyone said okay. All of them were elite core members of the guild. The elite core members in the main guild were closer to Jiang You and seemed like good friends of his. But for the fourth branch guild players, their relationship with Jiang You wasn’t as close and they seemed more like underlings.

Jiang You’s Wandering Peak led the way. Not a single player moved ahead of him. The group of players followed after Wandering Peak and quickly left Luxuriant Mountain City.

Luxuriant Mountain City was a city on the mountains. After leaving the city, it would be similar to going down a mountain. Sword Peak Ravine, where the wild boss was located, happened to be the neighboring Level 70 area.

Sword Peak’s Blade Master Lan Rui was a drifter. Consistent with a boss’s style, even though he was a Blade Master in name, his skill set wasn’t as simple as just a Blade Master’s skill set. Lan Rui mainly used Blade Master skills, but he could use skills from the other three Swordsman classes as support. Besides that, he could also use a few Striker moves and a few Grappler throwing skills.

The more skills a boss possessed, the harder the boss. A boss’s difficulty wasn’t simply determined by its health, defense, or attack. A boss’s complicated move set and excellent AI made a boss less predictable and harder to deal with.

Level 70 wild bosses were the hardest bosses in Glory. Their settings were naturally at their highest. The Level 70 cap had been added to the game for three years already. Even so, up until now, no one had figured out the system’s AI for Level 70 wild bosses in the Heavenly Domain.

Wild bosses only spawned 52 times in a year and there were always huge crowds of players fighting over them. It wasn’t possible to do any tests on them. In addition, these wild bosses had numerous skills available to use, making it nearly impossible for players to determine any patterns from one.

At this point, players had figured out the skills for each boss and how to suppress them. There were a few guides out there, but these guides were very theoretical and lacked practicality. Level 70 wild bosses were the targets of the all the top guilds and most of the fighting revolved around the players. Under these circumstances, what was the point of a guide?

Level 70 wild bosses were absolutely events that the guild leaders of the Club guilds personally led. However, just a team from a branch guild wouldn’t be enough. For this type of difficult war, the main force would be comprised of the elite guild members. The only reason that Jiang You’s Wandering Peak even came here was because of Unrivaled Super Hottie.

When they arrived at Sword Peak Ravine, the team didn’t stop for a break and continued running towards a certain direction. Leveling areas naturally had a lot of small monsters scattered around, but for these elite guild members, they were familiar with all the major areas in the Heavenly Domain. These monsters wouldn’t obstruct them. After going deep into Sword Peak Ravine, the team joined together with Tyrannical Ambition’s main force. Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu’s screen and swept across all of the IDs lined up. Nearly all of them had some reputation in the Heavenly Domain. She clearly knew that these players were all a part of the upper class in Glory. She had been with Excellent Era for so many years, yet she had never been able to join their circle. Ye Xiu and his Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t even been in the guild for two days yet and he was already a member. Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel somewhat upset.

Apart from the elites of the main guild, all of the branch guilds had a team too for a total of around two hundred players. The main guild was the main force, while the branch guilds were for support.

Tyrannical Ambition was only a part of the forces in the Ravine. Ye Xiu had Unrivaled Super Hottie look around and quickly saw two other guilds in formation.

Hundred Blossom Valley, Samsara.

Samsara again. Ye Xiu noted. Samsara’s momentum in the competitive scene was growing. In the game, their guild was also making movements everywhere. They almost always participated in every event possible. It was the bearing of a top guild. Hundred Blossom Valley was a bit weaker, but a Level 70 wild boss couldn’t be missed. Even if they were slightly weaker, it didn’t mean they had no chance. Wild bosses hadn’t gone to the point where the old titans had a completely monopoly over them.

The forces from these two guilds were also led by their guild leaders.

Hundred Blossom Valley’s Blooming Blossom and Samsara’s Three Realms Six Paths were both standing next to their forces. Along with Tyrannical Ambition, the three forces stood as three competing rivals. At this moment, Jiang You’s Wandering Peak arrived at the scene. Tyrannical Ambition’s players naturally gave a greeting and Wandering Peak went forward to stand. The heads of these top guilds began glaring at one another. Afterwards, Blooming Blossom and Three Realms Six Paths, along with everyone else, turned their attention to the person next to Wandering Peak.

Unrivaled Super Hottie. What an eye-catching name. At this moment, he stood casually next to Wandering Peak.

The three guilds showed good sense. In order to let their guild leader stand out, the rest of the troops stood behind the guild leader. But someone unexpectedly had no eyes and stood alongside Wandering Peak. He didn’t have any guild tag next to his name and his name was so arrogant too.......

Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie only needed to stand there in order to instantly capture everyone’s attention.

The Ravine was completely silent. Only the faint noise of grinding could be heard among Tyrannical Ambition’s players.

Flight felt regretful! With all of these heroes of Tyrannical Ambition in front of him, his title of the number one Knight in the fourth branch felt worthless. Even the fourth branch guild leader probably didn’t have a higher status than these elites from the main guild. In the end, Flight and the other branch members stood at the back. But this Unrivaled Super Hottie actually followed Wandering Peak to the front and even became the focus of everyone’s attention. Flight didn’t feel good! For one, this guy was such a disgrace. At the same time, he also felt a bit jealous. However, Flight knew very well that he would never have the courage to just casually stand alongside the guild leader.

“Who’s this idiot?” Tyrannical Ambition’s players held themselves back, but the players from the other two guilds were already laughing in ridicule. They spoke in very loud voices, so the other side could hear them.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was perfectly composed. He ignored all of the insults and went straight to the main subject: “Where’s the boss?” His words switched the topic to a very sensitive subject.

The two guild leaders naturally had to appear calm, but they couldn’t help but feel somewhat uneasy seeing this guy standing with Wandering Peak,

To put it plainly, no one in the game besides another Club guild leader could stand on equal footing with a Club guild leader. Could this person be a pro player from Tyrannical Ambition?

Zheng Chenfeng?

The two guild leader immediately made a guess. Zheng Chengfeng was a Knight pro player from Tyranny. His character was called Mountain Split and he could be considered a top player, who was a part of the main roster. Even though he wasn’t a God, he was more than good enough for players in the game to worship him.

“Who is this?” The two guild leaders hesitated. The first to speak was Three Realms Six Paths.

Unrivaled Super Hottie actually walked up with him. Even Jiang You jumped up in fright. He had walked up loftily to the other two guild leaders, showing his imposing manner as a guild leader. He really hadn’t noticed someone was next to him.......

Now that the other side suddenly asked him a question, Jiang You didn’t know how to respond. What should he say? He found an expert? The problem was that he hadn’t personally seen his skill before. What type of entity was Tyrannical Ambition? No matter how great of an expert one might be, one still wouldn’t qualify to stand on equal footing as him. If he really did say that, he would feel quite ashamed. For a moment, he didn’t know how to explain the situation. He truly wasn’t happy, seeing this guy next to him. Couldn’t you have given me a notice beforehand so I could prepare? Now you’ve put me on the spotlight with no explanation to give. He really hadn’t noticed that someone had been walking with him, but how could he say that?

“Are you talking to me?” Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t make him worry and replied: “I’m an expert passing by. It seemed like there was a lot of people here, so I came over to help out. Where’s the boss? Let’s hurry up and start! You’re all wasting time. What if another boss spawns?”

His words hit the nail on the head. This was one issue among the guilds. Wild bosses didn’t spawn at a set time. They might not see a wild boss for one or two days. Sometimes, multiple wild bosses would spawn at the same time. The guilds all wanted the bosses for themselves. If multiple wild bosses spawned at the same time and they were too greedy, they might not even get one. But if they just focused on one, they felt too unwilling to part with the other ones.

All of the guilds knew which bosses had spawned already this week and which ones hadn’t. Several of them hadn’t spawned yet, so it was possible that another could appear at any time. They had to hurry. His words weren’t wrong! But the problem was how did a random passerby get to say these words?

But for the two opposing guild leaders, the situation had changed. This person was so calm and decisive. He covered up his identity very casually. Could he really be Zheng Chengfeng?

Chapter 581 – Pleased Knights

The two guild leaders were suspicious. They didn’t dare make any rash movements.

Where was the boss? This question didn’t need to be answered. Everyone was gathered around here. Who would let the boss out of their sight? It was just that because there were so many players, some of the players such as Unrivaled Super Hottie would have their line of sight blocked by others. After this question was asked, a few players couldn’t help but turn around and look in a certain direction. Ye Xiu noticed their actions and naturally adjusted his position, so he could see the boss.

No one else moved. Unrivaled Super Hottie jogged out of the crowd alone, alarming everyone else.

“What are you planning on doing!”

Quite a few players yelled. They were still in the stalemate stage.

The boss needed to be fought over, but according to convention, everyone was supposed to spend some time talking to each other Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader had just arrived, so it should be time to have some small talk with each other, but Unrivaled Super Hottie had taken away the spotlight. The small talk hadn’t even finished yet and he was already moving! What was he doing? Was he trying to take the initiative to show his power?

Who held the boss’s aggro was an important deciding factor in who ended up winning the boss. At this moment, a Knight was moving towards the boss, causing everyone to be alarmed.

The hearts of Blooming Blossoms and Three Realms Six Paths started to thump. They suddenly remembered that today’s wild boss, Blade Master Lan Rui, had an aggressive personality, so Knight skills with taunting effects were twice as effective than normal. Knights already had the advantage in grabbing aggro, even more so against Lan Rui. If the outcome of today’s battle came down to aggro, Knights would undoubtedly be extremely crucial. Was this why Zheng Chengfeng personally came out to help?

It wasn’t impossible for a pro player to occasionally came out and participate in this type of battle. For example, if the Club needed a certain material from a boss, then they would send a pro player over to ensure they obtained that material. The two guild leaders immediately thought of this possibility. If that really was the case, then competing against him head on would be hopeless. They needed to kill the pro player first in order to have a chance at victory.

In a chaotic battle between hundreds of players, a pro player could be killed too. The existence of a pro player added pressure to the two guild leaders, but they didn’t need to go so far as to retreat. A pro player could increase that side’s chances of winning, but it didn’t mean a guaranteed victory.

Also, wasn’t this Zheng Chengfeng too confident? Did he really think just the addition of himself would allow Tyrannical Ambition to easily swipe up Blade Master Lan Rui?

The two guild leaders gave out orders for a team of their players to sneak out and directly attack Unrivaled Super Hottie to turn the momentum around. Jiang You noticed their actions and couldn’t just ignore it. He also gave out an order. Tyrannical Ambition sent out two teams seemingly to protect Unrivaled Super Hottie.

The two sides hadn’t even used a tenth of their total troops yet. They clearly wanted to probe out the situation first. But to have already reached this step without even saying some words first indicated how quickly today’s battle was progressing.

At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted: “Everyone, don’t panic. I’m just taking a look.”

“Looking at what!” Someone responded.

“Looking to see where the boss is. I couldn’t see it from where I was standing before!” Unrivaled Super Hottie told the truth.

The reason was too plain and simple. The two guild leaders didn’t have time to analyze it in detail and directly expressed that they didn’t believe him. They immediately gave out an order: the other Tyrannical Ambition players don’t matter. Unrivaled Super Hottie cannot be allowed to get close to the boss.

When the order came out, the two guilds each sent out a team. They went over to the previous team that had been sent out before and firmly stood in front of Unrivaled Super Hottie, blocking his path to the boss.

Seeing that a fight could start at any moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie halted and asked incredulously: “I’m not even allowed to look?”

“Look? How do you plan on looking?” The players blocking his path questioned him.

Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t reply, but then suddenly ran to the side and rolled. Several magic spells and bullets landed on the spot, where he had just been standing. These two guilds actually decided to first get rid of this hidden danger before doing anything else.

But they didn’t think that this guy was actually so alert. The sneak attacks from these two guilds missed.

In a situation with swords drawn and bows bent, any movement could be the trigger, let alone such a frightening wave of attacks. The two Tyrannical Ambition teams that had come out to protect Unrivaled Super Hottie counterattacked out of reflex, but since they didn’t know where those sneak attacks had come from, they simply attacked the most convenient target around.

The two teams attacked with a bang. In any case, the other two guilds were their opponents. It didn’t matter who was who.

In this battle, the players from Samsara and Hundred Blossom Valley were the first to fall.

This was a group battle! The weak characters wouldn’t be able to survive under concentrated fire even with help from Clerics. This battle had begun too suddenly. None of them had been prepared, so it wasn’t a surprise some of them died.

When the two guilds saw that they had lost a few players, how could they be nice anymore? They immediately returned fire and the three sides immediately began fighting each other.

These players completely reacted out of instinct. None of them had received orders from their superiors. Their minds were clear though. A fight was a fight! They were going to fight sooner or later anyways. But the important part was not to kill off any one side, but to get a hold of the boss within this chaotic mess!

Blooming Blossoms and Three Realms Six Paths immediately thought of Unrivaled Super Hottie. Was he going to use this opportunity to get close to the boss? However, because of the chaos, it was difficult to find a specific person. They couldn’t see where Unrivaled Super Hottie had gone to, alarming the two guild leaders. This pro player couldn’t be allowed to make a sneak attack!

Where was Unrivaled Super Hottie right now? He was just standing on the side in a daze. He really hadn’t done it intentionally. Ye Xiu didn’t think he made any weird moves. How did it turn out like this? He couldn’t understand why......

Blooming Blossoms and Three Realms Six Paths couldn’t find Unrivaled Super Hottie, so they passed down orders to find him. With so many eyes looking, Unrivaled Super Hottie was quickly found.

“He’s over here!!” Someone reported.

“What’s he doing??” The guild leaders asked anxiously.

“He’s doing nothing!” The player replied.

What...... the minds of the two guild leaders froze. This...... this was completely different from what they had anticipated. Did this mean the plans that they had prepared could only be tossed away now?

At this moment, Ye Xiu had nothing to do, but he didn’t wasn’t alone for too long. Jiang You came over to him.

“Brother, could you secretly pull the boss over? Will that be a problem?” Jiang You asked.

“I’ll try.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Okay, we’ll do our best to give you cover.” Jiang You said.

As a result, Unrivaled Super Hottie immediately headed over to the boss’s location. The players from the other two guilds had received similar orders. After all, this battle was for the boss. They had already started fighting with each other. It wouldn’t be right to just let the boss stand there and watch them.

The three players sent out to secretly pull the boss over met together in this way. Everyone else was surprised to see them as they saw as the three Knights rushed out at practically the same time. The three Knights used a Charge and instantly closed the distance with the boss. Then, the three Knights went into a pose together, but stopped there.

None of them moved.

The three Knights were surprised, but they understood the reason.

Against Blade Master Lan Rui, Provoke would definitely work, but the effects didn’t overlap. In other words, the last person to use Provoke would cover up the previous user’s Provoke. Thus, in order to use Provoke to aggro the boss, the player who used it last would be the winner. The three Knights were all experienced, so they were waiting for the other Knights to act first. But because of this, none of them acted, so they just stood there.

“Ha ha!” Only Ye Xiu could laugh in this comical situation. He was the first one to understand, so he made the second step the fastest. Since they were stopping each other from using Provoke, it essentially meant that Provoke couldn’t be used to start the fight. Thus, it would just be better to be the first player to deal damage to the boss.

Unrivaled Super Hottie stepped forward, while laughing. Only then did the other two Knights react. Their slower response made them very annoyed.

Since it looked like they wouldn’t be able to reach the boss before Unrivaled Super Hottie could do so, the only other option was to stop Unrivaled Super Hottie from getting closer. The two Knights had the same thoughts, but neither of the two attacked.

“Ha ha.” Another laugh. Unrivaled Super Hottie was the first to enter the boss’s aggro range. Blade Master Lan Rui was already heading towards Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s laugh made the two Knights feel like crying.

Why did he laugh again? Because they repeated the previous scene.

Before, because they wanted to cover up the other person’s Provoke, none of them acted. But this time, both of them wanted to stop Unrivaled Super Hottie, but then they immediately thought: I’ll let the other guy attack him, while I go and take the boss. Thus, the two Knights didn’t move.

There was nothing they could do...... the two Knights weren’t partners, but competitors.

Bang!

The first clash finally happened and it was between Blade Master Lan Rui and Unrivaled Super Hottie. This sound made the hearts of many players shatter. The two Knights from Hundred Blossom Valley and Samsara turned in distress to look at their respective guild leaders. They failed to complete their guild leader’s orders and let Unrivaled Super Hottie take the first victory.

Suddenly, a player from Hundred Blossom Valley rushed out. He jumped high into the air. His equipment clearly added to his jump height. While in midair, he carried his gun in one hand, while throwing stuff out of his pockets with his other hand. In an instant, all sorts of bullets and grenades rained down from the skies. Tyrannical Ambition’s guard team was completely enveloped by the air strike.

They cried out in fear and scattered, but were unable to escape from the attack’s range. The noises from the gunfire and explosions linked together like a song from a symphony. In that short moment, the chain of skill effects looked like a hundred flowers blossoming.

This Spitfire landed on the ground as the smoke from his surroundings faded away. Only then did Tyrannical Ambition’s players regain their composure. They shouted for heals, but didn’t receive a response. They suddenly realized: where were the Clerics? Their Clerics had unexpectedly disappeared.......

Chapter 582 – Under Attack

All the Clerics were already dead on the ground.

There were three Clerics in the team that was assisting Unrivaled Super Hottie to steal the boss. No one thought that all of them would die together after that flashy attack.

Everyone had a hard time believing it. When the people who were yelling “Heal! Heal!” looked at their own health, they realised that they had only taken a small amount of damage. These small scratches probably resulted from being accidentally grazed by some skills when they were dashing about in a panic.

That air strike had clearly been targeting the Clerics, but the garish skill effects made them feel like it was the end of the world, spreading fear into the hearts of all.

It was only when the panic subsided did people notice that the Spitfire was still among them. At this moment, the Spitfire stood up, fired again, and tossed out grenades. The panic immediately resumed. The flying bullets and roaring explosions created an illusion of an all-out assault. He fought his way out of the crowd effortlessly.

“What are you doing?! Stop embarrassing yourselves!” The guild master of Tyrannical Ambition, Jiang You, watched the entire mess take place. Although he hadn’t come over, the boss was still his top priority. Seeing his elite team being devastated by a single person, Jiang You yelled out right away to calm down his guild members. At the same time, his heart shook in fright over the astonishing abilities of the unexpected troublemaker.

Initially, Jiang You didn’t notice that all three Clerics were dead. After all, he was not there amidst the chaos, so his observations weren’t as thorough. With a closer look, Jiang You finally noticed the problem, much to his own shock. While everyone else was still wondering how all the Clerics had died, as the guild master, he already realized the more immediate crisis at hand — Unrivaled Super Hottie.

That’s right.

Truthfully speaking, three Clerics were no where near enough for a Knight going against a level 70 wild boss. This group was only the first team in the rotation. Jiang You was currently organizing people to provide further support, but who would have thought that all three Clerics of the first team would die so fast? Could Unrivaled Super Hottie endure during this period of time? Not only did he have to face the attacks of the wild boss, he also had to deal with the treachery of the other guilds!

Ignoring the first team, Jiang You turned his view around frantically to check the situation on the frontline. Meanwhile, he ordered the second team, which was still preparing, to start providing support right away.

As expected, things were not going so well for Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Blade Master Lang Rui had already unsheathed his sword. The two Knights from Samara and Blossom Valley turned around with both of their swords pointed at Unrivaled Super Hottie instead of the boss, because Unrivaled Super Hottie had secured the boss’s aggro.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was alone in this three-directional siege. Besides death, Jiang You could not imagine any other fate for Unrivaled Super Hottie.

In the blink of an eye, icy flashes blossomed off the enemy blades like dazzling strands of silk, each intertwining, weaving into a deadly net that descended upon Unrivaled Super Hottie.

In the end, the boss was the fastest and started with the Blade Master ultimate: Formless Phantom Blade.

This was a level 70 wild boss. Without the help of the Clerics, even the best knight would be jumping to his own death if he tried to block the skill with his shield. On top of that, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipments were far from the best.

Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t try to block the boss’s skill. He seemed to have already noticed the absence of the Clerics. But if he wasn’t going to dodge it, was it even possible to dodge an ultimate from a Level 70 wild boss?

The answer soon revealed itself. Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t raise his shield. Instead, he chose to run. He jumped backward several times. Lang Rui obviously wouldn’t let Unrivaled Super Hottie escape so easily and gave chase at once. Hie huge strides made his movement much faster than that of Unrivaled Super Hottie’s.

Just when it seemed as if Unrivaled Super Hottie could not outrun this strike no matter how hard he tried, a figure rushed in front of him fearlessly in self-sacrifice. The gleaming net of metallic flash swallowed the player up instantaneously. While the white light of the strike still dancing around him, the unfortunate soul fell in a heartbeat. In his last moment, his body struggled to twist around, trying to catch a glimpse of Unrivaled Super Hottie.

It was Samsara’s Knight who fell!

His death wasn’t on purpose. He became Unrivaled Super Hottie’s shield entirely by accident. When he saw Unrivaled Super Hottie in a pinch, he activated Knight’s Spirit and rushed in towards Unrivaled Super Hottie with a Charge.

He never thought that Unrivaled Super Hottie would have the confidence to dodge. He never even imagined that Unrivaled Super Hottie could flee so quickly. By the time he had charged in front of the boss, Unrivaled Super Hottie had already left his original position. When he tried to change directions again, it was already too late. The boss’s blade was already upon him. In the end, he turned himself into the ultimate shield and saved Unrivaled Super Hottie’s life.

The Knight from Samsara was dead, but what about Blossom Valley’s Knight? He threw out a Provoke at the boss with ease. To Blade Master Lang Rui, their was an extremely powerful skill, and it grabbed its aggro right away. Lang Rui swirled around with his blade pointed at Blossom Valley’s Knight.

The Blossom Valley’s teams were all well-prepared, so the Knight was in no hurry. He had thought about it: as of now, Unrivaled Super Hottie wouldn’t dare to use another Provoke to nullify his Provoke if he didn’t want to die. He wouldn’t dare seek his own death yet.

Nonetheless, Lang Rui, stopped abruptly on its way charging towards the Knight and turned around, rushing towards Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Blossom Valley’s Knight froze in disbelief. He turned around and found Unrivaled Super Hottie, whose gesture proved that he had just used a Provoke.

He had used Provoke!

Surrounded by enemies, without a single Cleric, this guy actually used a Provoke as if he were seeking his own demise.

Fine! If you want to die, then die!

The Knight from Blossom Valley watched coldly, not planning on doing anything. If he became too impatient, then he would end up just like the Knight from Samsara - rushing to his own death without even understanding what had taken place.

Lang Rui rushed over with large strides, but Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t stand his ground. Instead, he swirled around and tried to run away. However, he was stopped short in his track by none other than the Spitfire that had turned the entire first team of Tyrannical Ambition into a mess.

“Who is he?!” Jiang You roared in rage. Competing with each other for so many years, all the guild knew each other’s experts. Still, no one had heard of this Dazzling Spring. Where did these hidden experts come from? On top of that, thinking back to his skillful feat of disrupting an entire team and killing all three Clerics in a single move, Jiang You felt a shiver running down his spine.

Those in the first team were all members of the elite main force of the main branch guild of Tyrannical Ambition. Every one of them was an unmatched expert in the game by themselves. How skillful did one have to be to trash all of them in one go? The Spitfire must be at a pro level!

Since team Hundred Blossom’s ace was none other than Spitfire Dazzling Hundred Blossom, Blossom Valley was also filled with Spitfires. However, this particular Spitfire’s skill level seemed to reign over regular players considerably.

Could he actually be … a pro player?

Blossom Valley was so determined to get this boss that they even sent out a pro player for this?

Jiang You didn’t know that, just moments ago, the guild leaders of Blossom Valley and Samsara had the same doubt about Unrivaled Super Hottie. In a way, this competition was very fair.

“Go die!” The intercepting Spitfire threw out his declaration coolly. His hands moved simultaneously. The speed at which the skills the skills were released fully demonstrated the player’s incredible hand speed.

Lang Rui still chased after Unrivaled Super Hottie, who clearly had no time to respond. Activating Knight Spirit, followed by a Charge, he rushed straight into Dazzling Spring’s attacks with his shield in front of him.

Trying to avoid a frontal collision with the Charge, Dazzling Spring jumped hurriedly to the side. Unexpectedly, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Charge twisted around after Dazzling Spring right away.

“Arc Charge!!!”

Someone among the crowd watching this sideline battle exclaimed in shock. Among all the players present, none of them were noobs. All of them were the top experts in the Heavenly Domain.

“Ha ha.” Dazzling Spring laughed as if he didn’t care about the Heroic Charge. He had enough reasons to do so: this jump of his was not only fast, but also extremely high.

The status enhancement of the equipments were being utilized to their fullest. Dazzling Spring’s jump height was significantly higher compared to that of the normal players.

Despite having used an Arc Charge with a curve of the just right angle, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Charge seemed to have became inevitably fruitless. Yet in that moment, his sword sung up with his shield. He somehow started to ascend.

“Aerial Curve!!!” Someone cried out in shock.

What is an Aerial Curve? An Arc Charge that didn’t only move around on the ground, but curved into the air. That is an Aerial Curve. The mechanics behind it were actually pretty simple: just jump when you activate Charge. However, similarly to Cursive Charge, it’s easy to perform Aerial Curve, but you have to make it effective and hit your target. Because of this, both skills are considered as “easy to learn, hard to use” skills. At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s Aerial Curve curved upward with perfect timing, shooting straight towards Dazzling Spring.

“Not good enough!” Dazzling Spring laughed. A grenade tumbled down from his hand.

With Knight Spirit's skill effect, Heroic Charge wouldn’t be stopped by anything. The grenade was entirely just there to create some damage. Unrivaled Super Hottie clearly didn’t try to dodge in midair. The flames of the explosion swallowed his silhouettes in the blink of an eye. Then, within the flames, his figure shot out upward. His height surpassed that of Dazzling Spring in the next second. Still with the shield in the front, Unrivaled Super Hottie raise his knight sword high into the air. As he dove upon Dazzling Spring, his sword slashed towards its target.

“What is this? Heroic Leap???” The exclamations continued.

“What kind of joke is this? How is that possible?”

Heroic Leap could not be performed in midair. This was a rule set by the game. It could not be changed. No one can violate the system’s rules. However, this Unrivaled Super Hottie had accomplished this violation of the system’s rules, causing all the spectators to fall into confusion.

“Who are you?!!!” Even Dazzling Spring shouted in surprise.

“Unrivaled Super Hottie!” Unrivaled Super Hottie shout out his name as if it were some kind of move. The falling Knight swung out his sword, smacking Dazzling Spring out of the sky and into Blade Master Lan Rui.

Chapter 583 – Flashy But Ineffective

After being hit by Heroic Leap in the mid air, Dazzling Spring fell like a meteor. Sensing the approaching player, Blade Master Lan Rui pointed his sword and started another sword dance. Seeing the familiar scene, everyone soon remembered the Knight got killed in the same manner before. It looked like this Spitfire could only die faster than that Knight.

Who would have expected the Spitfire to actually fire twice during his fall despite going as fast as a meteor?

As the gun roared, the falling figure took on a different trajectory, twisting towards the side. As soon as he landed, he rolled away, successfully dodging Lang Rui’s dancing blade.

Who are these two players!!!!

All the players watching felt like going crazy.

One defied the system’s rules and used Heroic Leap in mid air. The other was able to use Aerial Fire to dodge the boss’s attack while rapidly descending. Only a perfect amount of experience, judgement, and speed would have made both feats possible: just the slightest insufficiency in any of the three would have spelled failure. Even up until now, the audience still had no idea how Unrivaled Super Hottie had accomplished that impossible Heroic Leap.

The brilliance wasn’t over yet. Dazzling Spring’s Aerial Fire, landing, and rolling linked together flawlessly, allowing him to dodge Lang Rui’s flashing blade. Still, the descending shadow above his head was still locked onto him. Heroic Leap hadn’t ended yet!

Bam!

Heroic Leap hit Dazzling Spring again. There weren’t a lot of changes, but to be able to deal damage again under these circumstances was truly unbelievable for the viewers.

Heroic Leap was used under Knight’s Spirit. This Just Heroic Leap hit Dazzling Spring as well as the boss. The special effect of this skill was to deal equal damage to its targets. There was no way to avoid it, even the boss was no exception. After being hit, Lang Rui’s steps paused, unlike Dazzling Spring, who got flattened on the ground. After all, a boss is still a powerful existence.

Knowing that the boss was more dangerous than Dazzling Spring, Unrivaled Super Hottie rolled away immediately after landing.

The boss soon got out of the stun from Just Heroic Leap. Lang Rui’s blade chased after Unrivaled Super Hottie without a moment’s delay. Expecting the attack, Unrivaled Super Hottie avoided all of the strikes as Dazzling Spring cursed aloud, “F***!” on the side while scrambling away towards safety.

All the players who saw it were stupefied. What an evil scheme! He could have run anywhere to avoid the boss’s blow, but he just had to run in Dazzling Spring’s direction so that the boss’s attack would also be pointed at the Spitfire. Had Dazzling Spring not been an expert player with outstanding reaction speed and mechanics, he would have died right then and there under Lang Rui’s blade. If it were any other normal player under the same conditions, it would have being a certain death. Even though the boss’s sole target was Unrivaled Super Hottie, the boss’s slashing sword covered a significant amount of area. If Dazzling Spring hadn’t reacted fast enough, he would have been smashed to pieces on the spot.

“Second tank, take over!” Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted.

At that moment, almost half of the players had abandoned their tasks to watch the commotions on the sideline. This shout snapped Tyrannical Ambition’s Knight back to reality: Blade Master Lang Rui was really close to him right now.

Was this his true intention?

Everyone was confused: was Unrivaled Super Hottie trying to lead the boss towards Tyrannical Ambiotion’s troops, or was he trying to killing Dazzling Spring indirectly, or was he trying to kill two birds with one stone?

Tyrannical Ambition’s Knight immediately threw out a Provoke, forcing Lang Rui to turn, while making Blossom Valley’s Knight very sad.

Blossom Valley’s Knight thought Unrivaled Super Hottie was dead for sure, so he didn't rush in to fight over the boss. Who would have thought that Unrivaled Super Hottie would be able to survive through all that? He knew that Unrivaled Super Hottie was too busy to take on the boss, but he had forgotten that there were still people from Tyrannical Ambition present. Right now, the second team, which had a good number of Knights and Clergy and plenty of time to prepare, easily dragged the boss away.

“Get it back!!” With the Knight’s shout, Blossom Valley’s troops rushed forward. The second, third, fourth, and fifth tank gathered around the main tank to start a war of Provokes. Blossom Valley’s Clerics all tensed up right away. They knew soon that the battle would soon fall into chaos as the ownership of the boss’s aggro becomes a total mess. That would be the hardest time for the teams, especially the Clerics.

Provoke!

Provoke!

Provoke….

Both sides started picking fights with the others. They were provoking each other to see which side had the better skill.

Meanwhile, despite being pushed around earlier, Dazzling Spring had already jumped back up and was chasing after Unrivaled Super Hottie. Both of them had no helper now, so the battle turned into an one on one death match. Dazzling Spring’s embarrassing state was nowhere to be seen now. His gun roared in his right hand while grenades rolled off his left, churning up a fiery storm of explosions.

Under Ye Xiu’s control, the Knight moved nimbly in spite of its usual clumsy impression. Unrivaled Super Hottie dodged all of Dazzling Spring’s offensives narrowly with skillful pathing.

But because of the fast pace of the fight, no one was able to tell how many skills Dazzling Spring released nor how many times he had attacked. All that people could be heard were the endless roars of explosions and gunshots. In the blink of an eye, the colorful visual effects of the skills had swallowed up a large area on the map.

“So flashy!!” Someone exclaimed.

“But they seem ineffective though? None of them hit.” Someone followed up after noticing Unrivaled Super Hottie’s expert positioning.

Flashy, but ineffective….

When this comment came out, many players paused in realization, especially the players from Blossom Valley. Although Dazzling Spring had whipped up a lively battle for the sake of Blossom Valley, the players from Blossom Valley had no idea where he had come from. Amidst the discussion, one thought suddenly came up, reminding these Blossom Valley’s players of one person.

That person was none other than Hundred Blossom’s former captain, Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s owner: Zhang Jiale.

Zhang Jiale’s style was extremely garish, just like his character’s name: Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. However, because he overly pursued the flashy effects in an onslaught of skills, his style's effectiveness had became the target of many’s criticism. Especially when his opponent had managed to analyze his fighting style thoroughly, comments like "Cool, but you aren't able to hit him" started to appear more and more frequently on Zhang Jia Le's commentary.

Right now, the same critique appeared on Dazzling Spring. It sparked that feeling of familiarity almost instantaneously among the fans of Team Hundred Blossom.

Dazzling Spring grabbed everyone’s eyes since the moment he got on stage. His style had been garish enough. It was so excessively flashy that even the issue of being effective had surfaced. Could this person truly be Zhang Jiale? If not, then the player behind Dazzling Spring had perfected a truly unbelievable imitation.

However, if Dazzling Spring was indeed Zhang Jiale, then the player who was able to dodge every attack of his had to be a pro player too. Could he be Zhen Chengfeng? While everyone was having a headache just to figure out the situation at hand, Jiang Jiale suddenly exploded as if being triggered.

That person really is Zhang Jiale!!!

The players of Blossom Valley were incomparably familiar with their team’s former God and immediately came to this conclusion. Even the players from other guilds quickly had the same thought. In this instant, Dazzling Spring’s hand speed rampaged freely. Knowledge, decision-making, and reaction speed could occasionally be made up for with luck, but hand speed was a rigid physical factor. It wasn’t something luck could bring about. This person wasn’t randomly mashing his keyboard either. His character’s movements were clean and crisp like a famous star singing. No matter how fast he or she sang, each and every word could be heard clearly.

Dazzling Spring gave the audience this type of feeling. All of his moves had some purpose to them. What about Unrivaled Super Hottie? It looked like he could no longer dodge any more. The brilliant array of attacks enveloped him. Was he dead or alive? No could tell.

Probably dead, right?

Most of the players made this guess. The wave of attacks had been too frightening. However, Dazzling Spring didn’t seem to share their thoughts. Although he stopped attacking, it was because even he couldn’t see the situation from all of the attacks he had released. Even so, he prepared to attack at any moment. His gun didn’t lower and his left hand had a grenade prepared. He was waiting for the moment the field cleared up.

Suddenly, more than half of the players stopped whatever they had been doing. Only those fighting the boss couldn’t do so because they simply couldn’t. Though at this moment, no one cared about the boss. Everyone focused their attention onto the duel between these two mysterious guys.

The light dispersed and everyone saw that Unrivaled Super Hottie had fallen.

Dazzling Spring lowered his gun and turned around. His attention was already on the boss. At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie’s corpse suddenly glowed with a white light. Unrivaled Super Hottie leaped up and headed straight for Dazzling Spring with a Charge.

This unexpected revival was undoubtedly the best kind of ambush there was. Dazzling Spring had no time to prepare against it. Among the shocked cries of many, Unrivaled Super Hottie charged directly into him.

“I know picking on noobs feels good, but you don’t have to look for superiority in this way, right? You’re better than this!” As Unrivaled Super Hottie spoke, Dazzling Spring was already being sent away flying.

Chapter 584 – Creating an Environment

Even though everyone saw the scene clearly with their own eyes, not many of them apart from Unrivaled Super Hottie’s helper team understood what exactly had happened.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was obviously in a team. He had come over with Tyrannical Ambition. Although he wasn’t officially a part of the guild, he still joined one of their teams. When Dazzling Spring’s brilliant attacks engulfed him, everyone felt like he was definitely dead. At this moment, a message appeared in Unrivaled Super Hottie’s team.

One word: Revive. Next to the word were detailed coordinates of his position.

With these instructions, the team’s Clerics cast a Revive. As for Unrivaled Super Hottie? He might have died, but he had sent out the message. After being revived, he didn’t hurry and get back up. He lay there, acting dead, waiting for Dazzling Spring to turn around before launching a surprise attack.

“How despicable......”

The team members who knew the truth couldn’t help but give this remark in private, despite their bias towards their teammate.

Charge, Heroic Leap, Shield Attack, Upward Slash......

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s movements were very quick. He chained his attacks in an instant, striking down the target, who had been sent up into the air by the initial Charge. These moves weren’t things most Knights could do.

Dazzling Spring wasn’t worried about the damage from this combo. He had a stronger reaction towards those words.

“Who are you?” Dazzling Spring made all sorts of guesses, but he wasn’t certain about any one of them.

“What have you been busy with this year? Could you really have been preparing to leave just to run to the game and bully noobs?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked. His voice wasn’t loud, just enough for Dazzling Spring to hear. Otherwise, if these top elites in the game heard themselves being called bullied noobs, who knew how angry they would be.

Dazzling Spring didn’t answer. He suddenly focused and amidst Unrivaled Super Hottie’s continuous attacks, he dodged and actually escaped from the combo.

“Tch.......” Unrivaled Super Hottie clicked his tongue. He immediately fell back and Dazzling Spring chased after him.

Dazzling Spring immediately won back the upper hand in that instant.

The players from the three big guilds were even feeling slightly annoyed at the boss’s existence right now. The boss was interfering with this incredible show. If they couldn’t determine the skill levels of these two players, they weren’t worthy of being players in the Heavenly Domain.

“This Unrivaled Super Hottie, could he be......” Someone moved close to Jiang You and whispered to him.

“Yes, I have an idea. Don’t worry.” Jiang You appeared to be becoming more and more calm.

“Heal, heal, heal! Why aren’t there any Clerics healing!!!” Everyone heard Unrivaled Super Hottie shout loudly as he dodged Dazzling Spring’s attacks.

Everyone had heard these sort of words coming from Knights countless times. No one gave much thought to them. Knights were tanks. Wasn’t it normal for them to tell the Clerics to heal? But the problem this time was that it looked like a 1v1 duel. This Knight was actually telling them to help. Wasn’t that too disgraceful? Many of them were disappointed.

“Heal him.” Jiang You decisively gave the order.

Unrivaled Super Hottie soon began to glow with white light. He immediately stood still and stopped dodging Dazzling Spring’s attacks. He was about to go forward and trade blows.

“How shameless!!!” The players from Blossom Hundred Valleys shouted angrily.

With several Clerics healing him, this guy wanted to trade blows with a Spitfire? Wasn’t that too shameless? In theory, for team battles, supporting a tank while having him charge through the troops was a very common strategy, but the confrontation between Dazzling Spring and Unrivaled Super Hottie clearly indicated that these two certainly weren’t ordinary players. As soon as everyone saw them as being on a higher level, everyone’s requirements went up another level too. Wasn’t asking others for help in a PK very normal? But everyone felt like it was too unstylish for someone so high class.

“F*ck!” Dazzling Spring shouted. He clearly despised his opponent’s action, but he could only run away. No one could directly win over a tank with a bunch of Clerics healing him. When he saw this action, Dazzling Spring was now very certain who this person was! He he originally thought it was highly probable it was this person, after all, no one else had the spare time to run over to the game to fight a boss.

“Don’t run. Let me give you a good lesson. Did you really think you could go on a rampage without any fear in the game?” With help from the Clerics, Unrivaled Super Hottie clearly became more arrogant.

Everyone was speechless again. If you’re that capable, then don’t bring Clerics with you. If you hadn’t brought Clerics, wouldn’t you have been the one to get cleaned up? Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie had put Dazzling Spring into a difficult situation too, Dazzling Spring clearly had the upper hand. Previously, Dazzling Spring had directly killed off Unrivaled Super Hottie, who had to be revived to fight back.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s equipment had been worse than Dazzling Spring’s to begin with. After dying, his stats would be reduced. If they fought head to head again, he would just die again. Who would have thought that this guy would directly call for a bunch of Clerics to help him. How could he shout like he was in the right?

Dazzling Spring looked quite patient. With Clerics helping the Knight, he obviously couldn’t contest him directly. At this moment, he was relying on his fast movements to circle around Unrivaled Super Hottie and target the Clerics helping him.

“Clerics, protect yourselves!” Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted. The Clerics suddenly started to get flustered. Protect ourselves? More like you should be protecting us...... and he wants us to protect ourselves against such a terrifying enemy? Are you joking?!

As proof that he wasn’t just saying this, when Dazzling Spring directly went for the Clerics, Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t show any attempts at stopping him. It seemed like he was using the Clerics as bait, so he could use the opportunity to inflict heavy damage onto Dazzling Spring.

Dazzling Spring open fired!

With his high speed actions, he immediately engulfed the Clerics with a dazzling array of attacks.

The Clerics immediately acted to protect themselves: run.

The Knight didn’t have any intentions of helping them. It made the Clerics feel very angry. If he wouldn’t help them, then they wouldn’t help him. All of them sprinted towards their other teammates. Those guys would care for them, unlike Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“What are you running for...... heal each other. Do you really think he can instantly kill all of you?” Unrivaled Super Hottie said helplessly. But previously, a squad of Clerics had been killed instantly. Everyone saw it very clearly. How could the Clerics not be scared?

Dazzling Spring didn’t chase after the Clerics. He turned around and aimed at Unrivaled Super Hottie.

‘Hurry up and kill the boss!” Unrivaled Super Hottie immediately backed away. He looked like he was heading back to Tyrannical Ambition’s troops for protection.

Dazzling Spring saw through his intentions and quickly stopped Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“How much movement speed does your equipment add!” Unrivaled Super Hottie complained. He saw Dazzling Spring’s equipment. Apart from a bunch of jump height, the rest was a bunch hfo movement speed. Compared to a heavy Knight, who knew how much faster he moved.

Dazzling Spring didn’t know either and attacked in a frenzy.

Blossom Valley’s guild leader Blooming Blossom felt like he should do something. With a shout, Blossom Valley’s players joined the fray.

They had no doubts about the identity of Dazzling Spring. He was the former team captain and ace player. It was an honor to play with him shoulder to shoulder. Who knew how many Blossom Valley players hoped to have the opportunity to interact with a God-level player like him.

Zhang Jiale had already retired, but he definitely still had influence because no one in Team Hundred Blossoms was able to replace him yet. Tang Hao was a promising rookie, but according to Blossom Valley’s traditions, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms should be the core. Right now, the ace player was a Brawler. No one was used to it. Everyone hoped Zou Yuan could hurry up and become the core with Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, but Zou Yuan’s performance this season made them give up. He was pushed to do something beyond his abilities. He truly didn’t have the temperament of an ace player or at least he didn’t show it. It made it seem like Team Hundred Blossoms was being held up by Tang Hao. According to rumors, next season, Team Hundred Blossoms was trying to buy Team Wind Howl’s top Brawler character, Three Hits. Was Team Hundred Blossoms really going to become a team with a Brawler as the core?

This was an issue that made Team Hundred Blossom fans very conflicted. Among them included elites from the guilds. Seeing the former captain Zhang Jiale in-game gave them hope again because at least they knew that Zhang Jiale hadn’t abandoned Glory. Or perhaps he was going to come back? They didn’t know, but they wanted to give this former captain of theirs an environment for him to fight in. It didn’t matter if it was in the game. Their original goal of the boss had been somewhat forgotten by Blossom Valley.

None of the Blossom Valley players that rushed out went to attack Unrivaled Super Hottie. They immediately headed to stop Tyrannical Ambition from helping him.

“Kill him!!!” The players from Blossom Valley suddenly shouted in unison. They cheered on their captain as if they were watching a pro match.

Dazzling Spring’s movements clearly paused. He was clearly moved by actions from Blossom valley.

For an enemy, this pause was an opening. Unrivaled Super Hottie instantly activated Knight’s Spirit and rushed at him.

Chapter 585 – Starting Place

Dazzling Spring attacked with an extremely quick pace. In order to dodge these types of attacks, Unrivaled Super Hottie had to make lots of movements. This caused Chen Guo, who was beside Ye Xiu, to stare at his screen, but be unsure of what was going on.

Despite this, she was still immensely excited.

This was because she was the only person who could actually confirm the two’s identity.

Ye Xiu, that naturally goes without saying.

Zhang Jiale. His flashy Spitfire’s Hundred Blossoms style was too noticeable. Even more so, Ye Xiu quietly spoke to Dazzling Spring so that no one else besides Dazzling Spring could hear him. However, Chen Guo was next to Ye Xiu, so she could hear him speak. Chen Guo didn’t need further confirmation. She had already made an accurate guess on this person’s identity.

Chen Guo was extremely excited. She was too busy to even look down on Ye Xiu for telling the Clerics to support him, so he could just tank the hits to fight.

Zhang Jiale was a God!

In terms of age, he had been a pro for six years. Right now, the Glory Pro Alliance was on its eighth competitive season, so he would be considered quite old.

Within these six years, he participated in three finals, which was quite an accomplishment. Amongst all the Gods in the pro scene, only Ye Qiu and Wang Jiexi had similar achievements. Ye Qiu had participated in four finals and became the champion three times. Wang Jiexi had participated in three finals and became the champion two times. Zhang Jiale had participated in three finals, but won the championship zero times.

This tragic comparison was honestly very depressing. Especially for those three finals, Zhang Jiale’s opponents just happened to be Ye Qiu and Wang Jie Xi. When the three were compared together, it only made Zhang Jiale look even more tragic.

Last season or the Pro Alliance’s seventh season, Team Hundred Blossoms led by Zhang Jiale lost to Team Tiny Herb led by Wang Jiexi. Zhang Jiale’s heart completely died. After the long holidays, he suddenly announced his retirement, completely catching Team Hundred Blossoms off guard. Because Team Hundred Blossoms wasn’t able to prepare well enough during the summer, their performance this season fell sharply. It was only because of Team Excellent Era’s downfall that Team Hundred Blossoms was able to escape from criticism.

Then again, Team Hundred Blossom’s decline wasn’t unreasonable like Team Excellent Era’s. The sudden retirement of their ace player and captain resulted in the team not having anyone to take his position. Their decline wasn’t a surprise with such misfortune falling upon them. However, a team that had participated in three finals couldn’t be ordinary. Team Hundred Blossom’s second year rookie Tang Hao had risen abruptly this season. But their best character and the responsibilities involved were pushed onto Zou Yuan, which was way beyond his ability. On the other hand, Tang Hao was outstanding player, but the Brawler character in his hand wasn’t good enough to be considered a trump card. In the end, Team Hundred Blossom’s performance was shaky. At this point in time, it would be natural for a person to think: if Zhang Jiale and his Dazzling Hundred Blossoms were still playing, along with the aid of the rising Tang Hao, Team Hundred Blossoms would undoubtedly be a power to be reckoned with this season.

Harsh critics would say Zhang Jiale was worthy of being called the Number One Unlucky God. He couldn’t take it anymore and retired after suffering through so many years, but then an outstanding helper immediately popped up in the team. Originally, he could have had another chance to win the championships, but the chance was missed just like that.

But the majority of the people were lenient and felt sorry for Zhang Jiale. Hundred Dazzling Blossom’s performance during last season’s final was still as splendid as in the past. Zhang Jiale hadn’t aged to the point, where he needed to retire yet. It was just that he was unable to get any return from all of his struggling for so many ears. Although he wasn’t old, his heart had been grinded by time. His heart had given up. His sudden announcement of his retirement felt a little bit irresponsible and impulsive.

Topics related to Zhang Jiale continued for the whole competition season. Even if Team Hundred Blossoms had the upcoming Tang Hao, it couldn’t stop the fans’ reminiscence of Zhang Jiale. Some people suggested that in the All Star Weekend’s Rookie Challenge, Tang Hao’s prideful “junior succeeds the senior” might have been because Team Hundred Blossoms constantly talked about their retired team leader, which irritated him and caused him to want to rise like the devil. If one thought about this more carefully, the explanation would feel a bit far-fetched, but it was truly hard to say why Tang Hao issued the challenge.

A God had just risen in the team, but the only thing people talked about was the previous leader. What could he be feeling in his heart? Tao Hao was only a God because of his skills. In terms of age, he was only a second year rookie. He was turning eighteen this year, an age where it’s easy to be proud. How could anyone expect such a youth to be mature and reserved?

Everything that had happened to Team Hundred Blossoms this season could be attributed to Zhang Jiale’s retirement. His leave was straightforward, but was he truly willing in his heart? If there really was another chance, would he return again? With the rise of Tang Hao this season, many Team Hundred Blossom fans wanted Zhang Jiale to come back.

But now, in the online game, Zhang Jiale’s Spitfire had appeared. Combined with the encounter with Wei Chen from before, Chen Guo immediately became excited.

Chen Guo was obviously a bit uneasy about their future new team. But another powerful God had come. How could Chen Guo stop herself from being excited? She hoped to see a repeat performance of Wei Chen’s encounter.

“Did you become a spy in Tyrannical Ambition for this to happen?” Chen Guo was so enthusiastic that her voice was shaking.

“For what to happen?” But Ye Xiu was puzzled.

“Him! Zhang Jiale.” Chen Guo pointed towards Dazzling Spring on Ye Xiu’s screen. Chen Guo felt dizzy seeing a fight between two Gods from a first person point of view.

“I became a spy in Tyrannical Ambition to find Zhang Jiale? Could you please analyze how that makes any logical sense.” Ye Xiu spoke helplessly.

“It’s not?” Chen Guo asked with uncertainty.

“Of course not! This is a pure coincidence! If I knew he were here, wouldn’t I be seeking death by coming in my current condition?” Ye Xiu spoke.

“What about your condition?”

“With only my current equipment, no guild, and lacking 160 stat points.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Do you mean to say that you can’t beat him?”

“I just died a moment ago. Did you not see that?” Ye Xiu asked, puzzled.

“I thought that was one of your despicable tactics.” Chen Guo was dumbstruck.

“What type of tactic is that? When I get revived, my experience is still deducted. I was level, so a loss in experience means a reduction in stats.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying…… it’s a tragedy?” Chen Guo asked.

“Didn’t you see me calling for the Clerics to come help me?” Ye Xiu said. “What exactly have you been doing this entire time?”

“I…… I……” Chen Guo was at a loss for words. She really didn’t think that the reason for Unrivaled Super Hottie’s death and Ye Xiu’s call for help was actually so simple and plain: he couldn’t beat his opponent. She had been thinking about what sort of despicable scheme Ye Xiu was hiding. The truth rendered her speechless.

He died because he couldn’t beat his opponent.

He called for help because he couldn’t beat his opponent.

F*ck, those actions were so logical! But Chen Guo didn’t even spend a second to think about the possibility of this happening to Ye Xiu and regarded it as illogical.

Chen Guo was still in a daze, when Ye Xiu shouted again: “Is anyone going to come help me??”

Now Chen Guo finally understood. This was no scheme nor was it a trap. It was because he really couldn’t beat the opponent that he had to ask for help.

Even though Ye Xiu managed to take advantage of the opening, while Zhang Jiale was in a daze, and attacked a few times, but just like what Ye Xiu had told Chen Guo, his character’s was too weak. Even though the equipment was provided by Jiang You, it was only bit better than his previous out-dated equipment. It was nowhere near Dazzling Spring’s equipment. Nowhere near didn’t just mean the stats. For Unrivalled Super Hottie, it was a set of equipment casually provided by Jiang You. But for Dazzling Spring, it was obviously matched and designed meticulously by Zhang Jiale according to his own habits and style. It could be likened to a scuffle between two people. One fellow would be improvising with a randomly picked up brick, while the other fellow would be using a weapon he was familiar with.

Secondly, there was the 160 stat point gap. Unrivalled Super Hottie didn’t have it because he didn’t have a guild. On the other hand, Dazzling Spring was with Blossom Valley.

These two disadvantages were already enough to be a deciding factor.

Ye Xiu’s current opponent wasn’t any random player from the Heavenly Domain in which case he could suppress through skill alone. This was a God who was on the same level as Ye Xiu. His achievements were only a bit less than Ye Xiu’s. Let alone normal players, even Wei Chen wouldn’t be able to compete with Zhang Jiale right now.

Ye Xiu was able to take advantage of the small opening, but he could gain a slight advantage for a bit. Without any alarm, Zhang Jiale relied on his two advantages to easily reverse the situation. Thus, Ye Xiu had to call for help.

However, the players from Blossom Valley wouldn’t give him the opportunity.

After identifying Zhang Jiale, protecting this duel from outside interference was even more important than than the boss.

“Blow him to bits!!!”

After hearing Ye Xiu calling out for help again, the players from Blossom Valley became very excited and gave another wave of cheers.

Zhang Jiale also attacked amidst the cheers as if he had returned onto the stage.

“Hey, why are you being so serious?” Ye Xiu spoke, while controlling Unrivaled Super Hottie and looking for an opportunity.

“You don’t seem very relaxed either?” Zhang Jiale finally spoke.

“That’s a must. I intend to form a new team and make my way back to the pro scene. Of course I have to be serious. I’m doing business here! If you want to bully noobs to feel superior, couldn’t you go somewhere else? Hurry and pretend you DCed.” Ye Xiu said.

“Didn’t you just say that bullying noobs doesn’t feel good? I find it quite nice bullying you.” Zhang Jiale said.

“I’m conducting serious business here. I don’t have time to fool around with you!” Ye Xiu got angry.

“You’re still not going to give up?” Zhang Jiale asked.

“Why do I have to give up?” Ye Xiu asked in reply.

“Haven’t you already gotten what you want? Why do you still want to keep going?” Zhang Jiale asked.

“I’ve never heard of anyone getting tired of winning championships.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re still thinking of winning a championship?” Zhang Jiale laughed.

“Winning a championship is very addicting. I really cherish my memories of it.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck……” Zhang Jiale turned depressed. Ye Xiu clearly knew of his circumstances, yet this fellow was still discussing the feeling of winning a championship. He was sprinkling salt onto his wound!

“I don’t feel like I need to retire yet. As long as there’s a chance, I will never back out, even if it’s just for one more day.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Big bro, you’re also in retirement right now, okay?” Zhang Jiale said.

“Struggling isn’t limited to just the pro scene. This here is still Glory. This is our true starting point.”

Chapter 586 – Provoke Relay

The two Gods didn’t stop moving their hands, when they spoke to each other. Unrivaled Super Hottie and Dazzling Spring spun around each other, fighting back and forth. Occasionally, Unrivaled Super Hottie would shout out “Clerics!”, reducing the quality of the match.

“Charge over and help!!”

An unexpected order came from Tyrannical Ambition’s side.

Those two players were fighting fiercely. The fight for the boss was turning white hot as well. Players continued to die in battle. The boss’s aggro kept on shifting between the three guilds through the usage of Provoke. Blossom Valley wasn’t focusing too much on the boss, so they had already fallen slightly behind. As for Tyrannical Ambition, Unrivaled Super Hottie had given them the advantage by being the first to establish aggro. Right now was the perfect moment to firmly grasp the lead. Who would have thought that their guild leader would order their main force to support Unrivaled Super Hottie......

Even though the players didn’t understand the reason, they still followed the order.

The players from Blossom Valley tried their hardest to stop Tyrannical Ambition, but Tyrannical Ambition’s strength didn’t lose to them one bit. Tyrannical Ambition couldn’t crush Blossom Valley with one strike, but they could still focus their forces onto a point and create a small opening.

Under Jiang You’s orders, the players from Tyrannical Ambition quickly rushed through the opening and provided a line of defense for the Clerics. The Clerics immediately began casting their spells and healed Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“Ha ha ha ha.” Unrivaled Super Hottie laughed. When the players from Blossom Valley saw this guy laugh, they gave him a look of disdain and began healing Dazzling Spring as well.

The two players were being healed like crazy and neither of them had the destructive force of a obss. Their health bars were always full. No matter how hard they attacked, their health bar never dropped.

“What’s the point of a fight like this?” Zhang Jiale looked up at the sky.

“Ha ha, let’s see which side’s Clerics will run out of mana first!” Ye Xiu said.

“Shameless!” Zhang Jiale was speechless. With the way they were fighting, even though his health never dropped, as a Spitfire with leather armor, he definitely wouldn’t be able to survive as long as a Knight with heavy armor. Against a normal opponent, Zhang Jiale could widen the distance between them and kite the opponent, but he was currently against another God. Kiting him wouldn’t be so easy. Even if he were able to widen the distance for a moment, he would quickly be chased down.

Thus, Zhang Jiale decided not to waste his energy fighting Ye Xiu . He tossed Unrivaled Super Hottie aside and directly rushed into the chaotic fight between the two guilds. From this point of view, it could be seen that Zhang Jiale had the upperhand over Unrivaled Super Hottie. If he wanted to run, he could easily do so.

“Running again? Please stop giving up so easily!” Ye Xiu shouted as he chased after Dazzling Spring..

“I’ll come clean you up in a bit.” Zhang Jiale replied calmly. Following afterwards, he blasted apart the group of enemies he had charged into. His offense wasn’t something ordinary players could defend against. The bright lights swallowed up numerous players. The players from Blossom Valley had been prepared. They were all in the same team as Dazzling Spring, so none of them took any damage. Tyrannical Ambition’s side was much more tragic. They were unable to resist. They wanted to fight back, but they couldn’t even find their opponents.

From a certain perspective, Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms fighting style was a type of offense and defense. He didn’t rely on the skill effects to defend. Instead, he used the visual effects that were supposed to just be for decoration. These beautiful flashes of light would cover up Dazzling spring, so the players wouldn’t know his position. Where were they supposed to attack?

This technique was similar to Vanishing Steps. It wasn’t something the system had purposefully intended for, but rather something the players had found for themselves according to how the game worked.

Even though the damage that could be dealt by a single person was limited, Zhang Jiale was a God, who could increase the pace of his attacks with his playing. His ability to deal incredible amounts of damage in an instant was regarded as a model for many teams. This extravagant playstyle looked like it covered an extremely large area, but in reality, the damage was focused on one target. And only Zhang Jiale knew who this target was. By the time his opponent was able to figure it out, it was usually too late.

And with so many enemies around him, it was naturally very difficult to see who his attacks were focused on, even more so for normal players on a lower level than him. The health of some players fell slowly, while the health of other players fell quickly. But from an overall outlook of the battle, everyone was being attacked without any distinction between them.

For his fighting style, the more numerous the enemies the easier it was to confuse the enemies.

The players from Tyrannical Ambition were helpless. Suddenly, they saw Dazzling Spring shoot out from the bright lights, but he didn’t stop attacking. However, this time, instead of attacking all around him, his attacks were focused on one player.

Everyone thought they would be able to guess who this target was, but when they turned to look, everyone was stunned.

This guy wasn’t Unrivaled Super Hottie, but a Knight from Tyrannical Ambition. This guy didn’t have any sort of conflict with Dazzling Spring, but right now, he had become Dazzling Spring’s target.

“Ha ha, not bad!” Unrivaled Super Hottie finally rushed over, but Dazzling Spring didn’t even glance at him as he continued to attack that Knight. He didn’t even turn his head when Unrivaled Super Hottie slashed at him.

“Give me a Focus!!” Everyone heard Dazzling Spring shout. Afterwards, his attacks instantly engulfed that Knight. But this Knight didn’t fall. The Clerics supporting him had been prepared and had started healing him awhile ago.

This Knight was an elite from Tyrannical Ambition. His equipment was better than Unrivaled Super Hottie’s, so with Clerics assisting him, he was able to survive the burst. When they saw that Dazzling Spring was still attacking this Knight, they finally came to a realization.

“Provoked! He’s been Provoked!!”

“Hurry up and give him a Focus!!!” Blossom Valley finally realized as well, but they were too late. Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted “Next!” and another Knight from far away used Provoke. Dazzling Spring turned around and ran over to that side. Blossom Valley’s Clerics wanted to cast a Focus to dispel the Provoke, but after the Provoke had been relayed, they were no longer in reach. In order to get closer, they would need to ask if Tyrannical Ambition would kindly move aside.

“Hurry over!!”

This time, the players from Blossom Valley shouted these words. Except this time, the situation was completely different. Last time, Unrivaled Super Hottie and Dazzling Spring had been in a harmonious 1v1 environment. Even though both of them had been within Blossom Valley’s troops, no one else was attacking Unrivaled Super Hottie besides Dazzling Spring.

But this time, Dazzling Spring had been Provoked into Tyrannical Ambition’s troops, but he didn’t receive the same treatment. As soon as Dazzling Spring fell into the enemy’s hands, Ye Xiu shouted without any shame: “Kill him! What are you waiting for!!!”

The players from Tyrannical Ambition all attacked Dazzling Spring. How much health could a Spitfire have? In addition, after being Provoked, his movements were limited and didn’t really have any way to dodge the barrage of attacks. In the end, he could only survive a bit longer than a normal player before dying.

“Okay okay. He’s dead now. Stop charging towards him and hurry up and kill the boss.” With Dazzling Spring dead, Unrivaled Super Hottie immediately appeared between Blossom Valley and Tyrannical Ambition as if nothing had happened.

“F*ck! Kill him!!” The players from Blossom Valley heard his statement and went mad. What boss? Unrivaled Super Hottie’s existence was much more disgusting than the boss’s. Everyone threw their attacks at Unrivaled Super Hottie, not even caring if they themselves took damage.

Even a pro Knight wouldn’t be able to take this huge storm of attacks! Unrivaled Super Hottie ran away and involved the surrounding players. These players weren’t able to react in time and were instantly killed.

“So hot-headed!” Ye Xiu grumbled as he ran. The players he passed by gave him salutes. This guy carried a halo of a aggro. To be able to make the enemies attack without any regard for their lives, how capable was that?

“What’s the situation with the boss?” Unrivaled Super Hottie swiftly retreated from the frontlines and went to ask Jiang You’s Wandering Peak. His objectives quickly switched. After getting rid of Dazzling Spring, he stopped PKing and focused on the boss fight.

“Right now, Samsara has the advantage.” Jiang You was speechless for a good while.

“Too arrogant! I’ll go steal it back!! Knights, follow me!” Ye Xiu shouted.

The Knights looked at him in fear. The several players that were previously near Unrivaled Super Hottie had been killed in an instant from the enemy’s attacks. With such a huge amount of aggro on his head, who dared to stand next to him?

This Unrivaled Super Hottie directly asked the guild leader: “Can I take out the Knights and Clerics and have them join my team?”

“Okay.” Jiang You agreed decisively. He immediately reorganized the teams by putting all of the Clerics and Knights in one team. Then, he added Unrivaled Super Hottie into it.

“Knights, listen to my orders. Stop using Provoke.” Unrivaled Super Hottie instructed.

“What?”

“Wait for everyone’s Provoke to come off cooldown and then wait for my order. We’ll directly take the boss away in one swoop.” Unrivaled Super Hottie explained.

“How is that going to work?” No one believed him. The Knights from the other guilds weren’t dead. If we act, the enemies will do the same. It’ll just be a stalemate again.

“That’s why I said wait for my order.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said arrogantly.

Chapter 587 – Honest Maelstrom Counterattack

In Unrivaled Super Hottie’s team, besides Knights, there were only Clerics.

These Knights were the same class as Unrivaled Super Hottie. They were used to being treated as respected uncles. Now, another Knight had suddenly taken command. None of them felt good about it. As for the Clerics? They were close partners with the tanks. In a situation, where they were wearing the same pair of pants, they weren’t happy with Unrivaled Super Hottie suddenly ordering them about either.

But there was nothing they could do. The experienced Jiang You had anticipated their emotions and said a few words to them. These elites weren’t playing the game full-time, but they were still playing the game part-time. Whenever they did something, they couldn’t just do as they pleased. Now that their guild leader had given them an order, even if they weren’t willing, they still had to listen.

“Knights, retreat!” Unrivaled Super Hottie instructed and the Knights at the front line withdrew.

“Clerics, heal me!” After the Knights fell back, Unrivaled Super Hottie gave another order and rushed forward directly into the enemy ranks. After activating Knight’s Spirit, he immediately used Sacrificial Roar!

The surrounding enemy guild players suffered under the effects of the roar and their next attack flew towards Unrivaled Super Hottie. A white aura emanated from Unrivaled Super Hottie’s shield. Following afterwards, he swung his shield and began blocking the incoming attacks.

“Maelstrom Counterattack!!” All of the Knights cried out in shock.

“Since he activated Knight’s Spirit, it’s an Honest Maelstrom Counterattack......”

Maelstrom Counterattack was another Knight defensive skill. During its ten second duration, enemy attacks had a certain probability of being reflected back. Under Knight’s Spirit, Maelstrom Counterattack had a one hundred percent chance of reflecting the enemy’s attacks back. As a result, it was called “Honest Maelstrom Counterattack”.

This type of skill wasn’t easy to use in PvP. As long as the opponent didn’t attack, Maelstrom Counterattack was useless. At the present, Knights mostly used this skill to interrupt the flow of battle. As soon as Maelstrom Counterattack came out, the opponent would immediately stop attacking, allowing Knights to use this opportunity to reorganize themselves.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s usage of this skill obviously wasn’t to give his team a chance to rest. He had used Sacrificial Roar just before, forcing the enemies to attack him. The Clerics immediately tensed up. They didn’t think this guy would suddenly give them so much pressure.

Maelstrom Counterattack wasn’t Maelstrom Reflect. First, the shield absorbed the enemy attacks and then used the sword to strike back. The Knight wasn’t immune to damage during the duration. Whatever damage the attack should deal would still be dealt. Then, the damage would be returned to the opponent. If not, how else would a Knight be able to show honesty?

The elite Clerics didn’t dare to try and predict anything. They raised their crosses and cast their spells. They used everything they had from big heals to small heals, long cast times to instant casts.

What would the result be like? They didn’t have any confidence. If the enemy attacks directly 100-0’d Unrivaled Super Hottie’s health, it wouldn’t matter how many Clerics they had!

And the result?

No one knew because this Sacrificial Roar affected too many targets. In an instant, everyone’s attacks flew out. It was like Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms fighting style. The attacks engulfed Unrivaled Super Hottie.

But Zhang Jiale’s light show was a form of protection, while Unrivaled Super Hottie would be taking crazy amounts of damage. This was something he had brought onto himself.

“He’s still not dead!!”

The others didn’t know the results, but the Clerics knew that their spells had locked onto Unrivaled Super Hottie. Since their spells hadn’t faded away yet, it meant he was still alive. These healing spells couldn’t be used on dead bodies. Only a Revive would work.

What was he trying to do?

Everyone asked themselves this question. At this moment, everyone could faintly see a silhouette flicker amidst the light. The flick was extremely quick and brief. It was the movement of someone jumping and falling rapidly. Then, everyone saw a shockwave disperse the light. The players surrounding Unrivaled Super Hottie were pushed away and knocked to the ground. Not a single one of them stood up.

“What?”

No one was able to respond for a moment. The light and shock wave had already passed. Unrivaled Super Hottie was still standing there with a whole bunch of white healing aura around him. All around him were players that had been knocked to the ground. The view was crystal clear. Everyone saw the scene and couldn’t help but cry out.

“Are you kidding me!!”

“Instant kill??”

“How is that possible?”

“How did it happen?”

“They’re not actually dead, right??”

All of the players that had been swept away by the shock wave were all dead. Their corpses and their equipment were scattered all across the ground. There were at least twenty players that had been struck by the shock wave. Some were from Samsara and some were from Blossom Valley. Even the Level 70 wild boss Blade Master Lan Rui wouldn’t be able to inflict such damage with one attack. But now, Unrivaled Super Hottie had somehow instantly killed off at least twenty players with one strike. No one on the battlefield was a noob. All of them were peak experts of the Heavenly Domain. This sort of occurrence had never happened before.

Were Knights this fearsome? Then what’s the point of other classes? Everyone might as well just be one…...

Amidst the widespread terror that had taken over the battlefield, Unrivaled Super Hottie stepped forward again. The players from Samsara and Blossom Valley had already forgotten their purpose in coming here. Just this one step made them retreat in a hurry. It was as if this step was a prelude to another huge massacre.

Let alone the two guilds that had been hit by the attack, even Tyrannical Ambition’s side was in fear, especially the Knights. They were so shocked, their eyes were about to pop out.

“What happened?” All of the Knights in Tyrannical Ambition just happened to be gathered together, so they quickly began discussing with each other.

“Were those guys already almost dead?"

“How could there be such a coincidence!”

‘If they weren’t already almost dead, then other than an Assassin’s Life-Risking Strike, how could they have instantly died?”

“It was too hard to see because of all of that light!”

“Was that shockwave from Heroic Leap?”

“Heroic Leap…… I didn’t see him jump…..”

“I thought I saw someone flicker.”

“Just a flicker?”

“If his hands are quick enough, maybe he did a small jump…..”

“Wait, could it be like this!!” Someone suddenly thought of something and shouted. Everyone turned to look at the speaker. It was Tyrannical Ambition’s number one Knight speaking. In other words, he was Tyrannical Ambition’s head tank. When Three Stones spoke, everyone calmed down and listened to him.

“He used Sacrificial Roar to concentrate the enemy attacks onto him. Then, by using Honest Maelstrom Counterattack, he absorbed everyone’s attacks. Finally, he used a Just Heroic Leap to return all of the absorbed damage to each person. With all of the damage he absorbed, of course it would be enough to instantly kill someone. Unrivaled Super Hottie was only able to survive all of that damage because of all of the Clerics crazily healing him.” Three Stones said.

“It can be used like that?” The Knights sucked in a cold breath. They were all experienced Knights. Apart from pro players, no one would dare to call themselves more experienced than them? But now, this Knight just did something they had never thought of before.

“I don’t know. I’ve never tried before. But I just read over the description for these skills and nothing said they couldn’t be used like this. But the problem is that actually doing it is extremely difficult even if you know the theory. You need to be extremely quick and precise with how you used your skills. We probably don’t have the ability to do it.”

The Knights listened and fell silent. They had played Glory for a long time. They recognized their own skill. Even if they knew the theory, if they tried, they definitely wouldn’t be able to succeed. They wouldn’t be able to do it even if they were lucky. The conditions were too strict.

“Who is this person?” The fourth branch Knight, Flight, asked gloomily. He originally thought he could use Unrivaled Super Hottie as a stepping stone to show his strength to the overall guild leader! But now from the looks of it, this guy’s skill level far surpassed him. With just this one move, anyone could tell that compared to him, Flight was just a nobody.

Flight asked something that was on the minds of many of them, but Three Stones didn’t answer. At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted: “Are your Provokes ready!”

“Ready.” The attack had been too shocking. None of the Knights were unwilling anymore. They heard his question and promptly answered back.

“Line up and wait for my command. When you see it, immediately act.” Unrivaled Super Hottie shouted.

The Knights lined up and Unrivaled Super Hottie quickly typed out a “1”.

The first Knight acted and used a Provoke on the boss.

Samsara’s Knights were still resisting. One of their Knights was about to use a Provoke, when Unrivaled Super Hottie typed out a “1”.

Samsara’s Knight acted, but right when his Provoke completed, Tyrannical Ambition’s side sent out a Provoke. The boss didn’t even turn his head towards them and headed straight for Tyrannical Ambition.

Chapter 588 – Crusader’s Trial

Samsara really hadn’t noticed Tyrannical Ambition’s movements from the beginning.

When Samsara’s Knight used his Provoke, the boss had shifted its aggro to him, but had almost instantaneously been pulled back by Tyrannical Ambition’s Knight. Under Ye Xiu’s command, as long as the Knights from Tyrannical Ambition acted promptly, Provoke would be timed perfectly.

Thus, in the eyes of Samsara’s players and even Tyrannical Ambition’s own players, nothing seemed to have happened to the boss. It was still facing whatever direction it had been facing before.

“What’s going on?”

The players from Tyrannical Ambition didn’t understand what was going on, but they weren’t worried. However, the players from Samsara were panicking. The boss was heading over to their enemies. The Knight that had used Provoke was puzzled too. His skill went on cooldown, but why was there no effect?

Blade Master Lan Rui definitely didn’t have any resistance towards it. It might be able to resist other skills, but definitely not Provoke. This was one of the boss’s characteristics. Against Provoke, the boss had absolutely no way of controlling himself.

As a result, Samsara’s Knight just thought he had messed up. He didn’t know how he messed up though, so he felt very ashamed. He immediately called for another Knight to come over.

Ye Xiu saw everything and when he saw the enemy Knight act, he immediately gave another order.

The next Tyrannical Ambition Knight was completely focused. As soon as he saw the order, he immediately used the skill.

Thus, Blade Master Lan Rui continued to have no reaction to the enemy’s Provokes.

The players from Tyrannical Ambition were beginning to understand, but the players from Samsara were all staring at their two Knights.

The two Knights both felt very ashamed. The third Knight had already rushed over.

“My turn!” This Knight shouted as he used Provoke.

His loud voice didn’t mean his hands moved any quicker. In fact, it gave Ye Xiu a heads up. Ye Xiu saw everything clearly, but Tyrannical Ambition’s Knight couldn’t react with the precision of a machine. The third Provoke was just a tad bit slow.

As a result, this time, the players from Samsara finally saw Blade Master Lan Rui turn its head. The third Knight was already smiling to show his triumph, but Blade Master Lan Rui only turned its head slightly before turning back. The boss continued to head away.

Everyone from Samsara became petrified. They finally realized it. When the fourth Knight came out, someone paid attention to Tyrannical Ambition’s movements and discovered that Tyrannical Ambition’s Knight practically acted at the same time as their own Knight. There was almost no difference in timing between them, but when the skill effects came through, the boss would always continue moving towards Tyrannical Ambition.

If the boss moved any further, it would be too late!!

Samsara was alarmed. Tyrannical Ambition wanted to directly pull the boss into their troops. That way, unless they massacred Tyrannical Ambition, it would be extremely difficult to take regain the aggro. Right now, they couldn’t even consider whether or not it was possible to massacre Tyrannical Ambition. Even if they succeeded, they would certainly take heavy casualties. By then, whether or not they would have the manpower to deal with the Level 70 wild boss would be a huge issue.

“Hurry, everyone forward! We have to get it back!!” Samsara’s guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths, was starting to panic. Before, Tyrannical Ambition and Blossom Valley had been in a fierce conflict, so Samsara had been able to take the advantage in the boss fight, but now that the conflict had ended, Tyrannical Ambition had returned and taken away the boss. Even though the shock from Unrivaled Super Hottie instantly killing several players wasn’t small, he wasn’t willing to retreat. Three Realms Six Paths gave an order and personally led the charge to try to raise the morale of his troops.

But right when he shouted, a shadow suddenly appeared beside him. Three Realms Six Paths heard his subordinates warning him to be careful. He had only been paying attention to leading everyone and hadn’t paid attention to his own safety. He hastily tried to dodge, but it was already too late. He was struck directly by a Charge and sent flying. When he turned his head to look, he saw that it was Tyrannical Ambition’s Unrivaled Super Hottie.

For a moment, Three Realms Six Paths thought he was going to die, but he relaxed after seeing his health. He looked out and saw his players rushing forward like crazy. The Knights moved up together. Five of them had lined up and started competing with the enemies.

The five Knights Provoked one after the other, but Blade Master Lan Rui only turned its head twice. Its feet never stopped walking towards Tyrannical Ambition’s troops. The more it walked, the deeper it went until finally, Samsara couldn’t see it anymore.

“F*CK!!” The players from Samsara cursed. It was so ridiculous! Because they knew about this boss’s characteristics, the three guilds had brought more Knights with them. They had predicted it would turn into a Provoke war, but they never would have thought that it would become so one side so easily. It was like a small child playing tug of war against ten big men. The other side easily pulled the rope without any resistance.

As for trying to make more space? Unrivaled Super Hottie led a few troops to block them. This guy was unbelievably arrogant and charged in alone like he was Zhao Yun. The players from Samsara were scared though. This guy had instantly killed twenty or so players. Who wouldn’t be afraid of him?

Everyone ran away as fast as they could from Unrivaled Super Hottie. With such fear in their hearts, it didn’t matter what formation they took. None of them could stand their ground. On the other hand, Tyrannical Ambition had charged into them and caused chaos. Once Unrivaled Super Hottie did enough here, he turned his head and ran towards Blossom Valley. He charged forward alone, but behind him were a bunch of Clerics. Everyone understood the situation now. This guy was running around alone so bravely because of all of the Clerics who were healing him.

But even if they knew, what could they do? Did anyone dare to face him?

No one in Samsara dared to, but Blossom Valley was different. The players from Blossom Valley had already gone crazy. They wanted to take revenge on Unrivaled Super Hottie! The boss? Not important! This guy had killed their God! Even though he hadn’t done it personally, it had clearly been orchestrated by him. Dazzling Spring had been forced deep into Tyrannical Ambition’s troops through use of Provoke. No matter how much of a God he was, he wouldn’t be able to survive under such heavy fire!

The players from Blossom Valley pounced towards Tyrannical Ambition. One was to take revenge. Two was to rescue their God. It didn’t matter if they died. They could revive!

Their momentum was astonishing and they completely ignored the boss. The players from Tyrannical Ambition were having trouble defending. Then, Unrivaled Super Hottie left the circle, killed Dazzling Spring, stole back the boss from Samsara, and was now heading back to save them.

“What are you fooling around for! He already revived! He’s not waiting for you guys!” Unrivaled Super Hottie lectured Blossom Valley.

The players from Blossom Valley went crazy.

Who the h*ll are you? You killed our God and now you’re lecturing us? We’ll bite you to death!

The players from Blossom Valley cursed as they charged towards Unrivaled Super Hottie…...

Tyrannical Ambition’s Knight team was fighting with the boss, but they were paying attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s movements. Seeing the players from Blossom Valley mercilessly rushing towards Unrivaled Super Hottie, they suddenly felt an ominous premonition.

‘Are his cooldowns up?” Someone asked.

“Knight’s Spirit shouldn’t be up yet.” Someone replied. Knight’s Spirit was a Knight’s Awakening skill, so it had a fairly long cooldown, nearly five minutes. Unrivaled Super Hottie killed Dazzling Spring and won back the boss. He had been very efficient since his previous instant kills. It hadn’t been five minutes yet, so Knight’s Spirit shouldn’t have been up. From their analysis, the previous fighting method required Knight’s Spirit. It only worked with Honest Maelstrom Counterattack and Just Heroic Leap.

“Even without Knight’s Spirit, it’s probably still very scary.” Someone said, seeing that Knight’s Spirit wasn’t up yet.

“We can do a simple calculation, he has…..”

“Stop stop, by the time you finish calculating, it’ll be over already.” Someone said.

“But at least he doesn’t need to use Sacrificial Roar……” Someone else said.

Afterwards, the Knights looked at Blossom Valley’s players and sighed deeply: “He can even establish such strong aggro on players, wow…….”

Everyone sighed and shook their heads. Compared to his exceptional technical skill, this guy’s ability to pull player aggro was tyrannical! He’s a perfect model!

“Look, he’s starting to act!” At this moment, someone shouted. All of the Knights turned to look and saw Unrivaled Super Hottie’s shield glow white.

Knight’s Spirit truly had a long cooldown, but Maelstrom Counterattack and Heroic Leap didn’t have as long of a cooldown. These skills were up and could still be used.

“This is common sense…… why does he need to save up his skills for Knight’s Spirit? Knight’s Spirit refreshes cooldowns anyways!”

“True, true.” Everyone was discussing amongst themselves. Unrivaled Super Hottie had used Maelstrom Counterattack to absorb the attacks, but he didn’t use Heroic Leap. Instead, he charged forward with his shield and sword swinging.

“Crusader’s Trial!!!!” The Knights shouted.

Crusader’s Trial was a Knight’s Level 70 skill. It required the player to continuously attack and allowed the Knight to maintain an extremely fast movement speed not any slower than Charge. This skill had six levels. At level one, three strikes could be made. With every increase in level, one additional strike could be made. The first strike was the base. It had twelve times the attack power of a normal attack. Every strike afterwards had the attack power of the first strike, in addition to the combined damage that was dealt by every previous strike.

This skill was said to represent the eight crusades to the east.

Even though the crusades to the east failed, in the game, each attack from Crusader’s Trial was stronger than the last.

The players from Tyrannical Ambition were beginning to understand, but the players from Samsara were all staring at their two Knights.

The two Knights both felt very ashamed. The third Knight had already rushed over.

“My turn!” This Knight shouted as he used Provoke.

Chapter 589 – Retreat in Defeat

“He’s using Crusader’s Trial with Maelstrom Counterattack!” The Knights sucked in a cold breath. In theory, it didn’t violate the game’s rules, but the difficulty of it was simply too high. Crusader’s Trial was a Level 70 skill, so it would naturally be more complex than other skills. Using Crusader’s Trial with Maelstrom Counterattack required exceptionally fast hands. It was something that normal players wouldn’t even attempt to do.

But Unrivaled Super Hottie was doing it.

“Maybe he’s just trying it out? It might not be successful?” Some people found it too difficult to believe. In any case, they couldn’t help but feel a bit sour upon seeing someone of the same class as them being so much better.

As a result, they watched the movements of Unrivaled Super Hottie with wide eyes.

First strike, hit!

The closest enemy, an Assassin, was sent flying by Unrivaled Super Hottie. The first strike of Crusader’s Trial didn’t usually have such attack power, but this strike also included the additive attack power from Maelstrom Counterattack. Even though he didn’t have Knight’s Spirit activated, he had still gathered the attacks of so many enemies. His single strike contained the combined attack power of these enemy attacks.

Assassins weren’t tanky classes in the first place. The battle had lasted so long already, so his health hadn’t been full either. After being sent flying by the strike, he never stood up again. He had been killed instantly.

Next, the second strike!

Crusader’s Trial was a skill with terrifying attack power to begin with, but the attack had to hit the opponent in order to deal damage. Crusader’s Trial added attack power to the next strike based on the damage from the previous strikes, not the attack power of the previous strikes. Attack power and damage were two very different concepts. Damage is how much health the target loses when hit by an attack. If the attack misses the target, then no matter how high the attack power is, the damage will always remain at zero.

The first strike of Crusader’s Trial hit its target. Moreover, because of Maelstrom Counterattack, the first strike had dealt enough damage to instantly kill its target. It was obvious how terrifying the second strike would be. The Knights from Tyrannical Ambition obviously knew how Crusader’s Trial worked, so when they saw Unrivaled Super Hottie activate Crusader’s Trial, they were shocked that he actually managed to pull it off. From his move choices, they weren’t surprised at the power. As a high level damage skill, Crusader’s Trial gave impressive results.

The second strike also hit.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was mainly a melee class. The first strike hit the Assassin and obtained a huge damage number. Even though the second strike no longer carried the effects of Maelstrom Counterattack, the second strike dealt damage based on the previous strike, so it instantly killed an enemy Ghostblade too.

The third strike!

This strike’s attack power had the combined damage of both the Assassin and Ghostblade strikes. Unrivaled Super Hottie clearly didn’t care about which class he attacked anymore. He raised his sword and slashed at the nearest enemy, a Berserker. Even though the Berserker was tankier, the accumulated attack power wasn’t something a Berserker could bear and he instantly died as well.

Next, the fourth and fifth strike…...

Whether or not Crusader’s Trial hit the target indicated whether or not Crusader’s Trial would kill the target. The damage numbers accumulated so far were more than enough to instantly kill any player.

No matter how angry the players from Blossom Valley were towards Unrivaled Super Hottie, if they went up to face him, they would just be killing themselves. Helpless, they could only run away. However, Crusader’s Trial gave the Knight movement speed equivalent to that of Charge. Many players didn’t have the ability to deal with such quick movement speed and would end up running around swinging their sword randomly like a blind cat trying to catch mice, but Unrivaled Super Hottie?

To put it simply, he also looked like he was just randomly swinging his sword, but maybe it was because of luck, or he truly had the ability, every single one of his strikes hit a player. When Crusader’s Trial ended, eight players from Blossom Valley had fallen.

The recklessness of the players from Blossom Valley had been interrupted by this crazy slaughter. The players from Blossom Valley had also deduced Unrivaled Super Hottie’s method. Such terrifying attack power was much scarier than the boss’s. Using this sort of method might have been thought of before by other players, but it was only in theory. However, today, someone had finally put it into practice. It felt like something from a legend suddenly popped up in front of their eyes.

“Would anyone else like to try?” Unrivaled Super Hottie’s stern voice scared them. Eight corpses lay at his feet. Everyone else was standing far away from him. Even the players from Tyrannical Ambition didn’t dare to get close to him.

But it was a bit awkward to just stand there looking at him. The players from Blossom Valley were hoping their God would suddenly descend from their skies and crush this demon, but when they took a closer look, Dazzling Spring’s corpse had disappeared. Dazzling Spring had clearly chosen to revive back at the city. The players from Blossom Valley checked their team list and confirmed that he was gone.

When a character died and revived at the city, the character would be automatically be kicked out of the team.

He already left?

They weren’t surprised. After all, he wasn’t a normal person, but a God. Dead on the ground and waiting for someone to revive him wasn’t something that would happen.

Dazzling Spring!

All of the players from Blossom Valley that had participated in the battle remembered this name. It was just that they didn’t know if this character was really Zhang Jiale’s or if he had borrowed an account to play around with. When this person joined Blossom Valley, who added him, how he joined……. Blossom Valley’s guild leader Blooming Blossom asked the members in charge of management. None of them new. He tried added Dazzling Spring as a friend, but the other side had disabled the option.

If this player was a normal player, Blooming Blossom would ask everyone in the guild chat, but because this player was their respected God, he didn’t dare to be rash.

“Guild leader, we should……” Someone from Blossom Valley asked his guild leader.

“We’re leaving.” Blooming Blossom said.

Everyone else was thinking the same thing. After finding out God Zhang Jiale had been playing with them, no one in Blossom Valley wanted to fight the boss anymore. Plus, there was still that demon, who they might not even be able to subdue. It would be better to just go back and see if they could find a chance to pay their respects to their God. Maybe they could ask for some magic treasures and use those to vanquish the demon. Wasn’t that how fantasy novels like Journey to the West and Investiture of the Gods played out?

The players from Blossom Valley began to leave. Obviously, no one would stop them. Their goal was the boss, not PvP. Seeing Blossom Valley leave, if they weren’t busy at the moment, they would probably express their thanks.

With Blossom Valley gone, Unrivaled Super Hottie could go and focus on taking care of Samsara.

Samsara had experienced instant deaths. They were happy to see Unrivaled Super Hottie going over to Blossom Valley’s side, but now Blossom Valley ran away with their butts bare. Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t stop for a rest and immediately headed for them.

Samsara’s players were suddenly scared. Everyone asked their guild leader for instructions.

Three Realms Six Paths saw this scene. Their morale was already extremely low. In addition, the other side had an incredible expert. Even without this expert, with Blossom Valley gone, it would be a one on one fight against Tyrannical Ambition. The boss had been taken away by Tyrannical Ambition already and taking the boss back starting from a disadvantageous position would be extremely difficult.

Three Realms Six Paths had no other choice. He sighed and ordered: “We’re leaving too.”

Samsara also left. No one would stop them. With Samsara gone, only Tyrannical Ambition was left. Quite a few of them were excited about winning over the boss.

Jiang You was extremely nervous though. He typed out a string of private messages to his trusted aides.

With no one interfering, Tyrannical Ambition could easily take the boss. It was just a matter of time. However, against just a single boss, all of these players were somewhat excessive. Many of them weren’t able to find a spot to attack the boss. They could only wander around. The players that Jiang You contacted were among these wanderers.

“Nothing.”

“Nothing.”

“Nothing.”

One message after the other returned to Jiang You.

“Don’t be careless.” Jiang You replied in a serious tone.

Everyone was puzzled. The guild leader wanted them to pay attention to any ambushes or suspicious players. Everyone had gone in a large circle. Everything was extremely quiet. There weren’t any passersby, spectators, or scrap pickers. There was nothing around.

But since the guild leader cared, they had to care too. They had walked in a big circle clockwise. Now, they were going back counterclockwise. When they came back, the boss was pretty much finished and they really didn’t find anything strange.

Jiang You was unable to get over it. Was there really no scheme? Impossible! It was impossible! That guy couldn’t have just come over to help us, right? He’s got to be scheming something! Since they were fighting against a wild boss, he must be going for the materials, right? But the boss fight was going very steadily. The only way to mess with it was to disband the team. However, only the team leader could do it. Everything seemed absolutely safe, but the safer it was, the more uneasy Jiang You became because he felt like he was missing something.

“Guild leader, it’s about to fall!” A report came at this moment.

“Okay……” Jiang You replied. His character moved forward. At the same time, he joined in with the team in charge of aggro control. The team leader position was transferred over to him. This was something that they often did. If the guild leader was leading the team, then he should be in the correct position.

Jiang You’s Wandering Peak walked towards the boss, but he didn’t look at the boss. He focused his attention on Unrivaled Super Hottie. As for Unrivaled Super Hottie? The situation was already stable, so he was just idling around.

“The boss is dead!” The players cheered, but Jiang You’s heart had leaped up into his throat. At this moment, Unrivaled Super Hottie had stopped moving!

Chapter 590 – The Hidden Agenda

Unrivaled Super Hottie had stopped moving!

So scary! It must be some sort of scheme!

“Everyone, be careful!” Jiang You shouted out in reflex. The players from Tyrannical Ambition tensed up. Being veterans, they didn’t question the order and became fully alert instead, surveying their surroundings.

There was nothing around them.

The Tyrannical Ambition players discovered nothing. Jiang You himself didn’t see anything going on either. The only thing he noticed was that Unrivaled Super Hottie had suddenly stopped moving. He thought this was abnormal, so he panicked.

The players were on guard, but they didn’t see anything dangerous. Everyone was somewhat puzzled. However, Jiang You was still paying close attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Unrivaled Super Hottie still didn’t move.

Why isn’t he moving? Something just didn’t add up. He slowly looked around. Tears streamed down his cheeks.

He finally understood why Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t move.

The boss was dead….

They were fighting the boss. With the boss dead, why would he make any movements? If he actually made any movements, then that would truly be alarming.

There really was nothing going on?

Jiang You was doubtful, but at the same time, he was embarrassed for raising a false alarm.

The guild leader of Tyrannical Ambition wasn’t any ordinary person. Jiang You calmly smiled and said, “I’m picking up the loot!”

The players stared blankly for a moment, before laughing out loud. Their guild leader was just pulling their legs! They laughed, appreciating their guild leader’s sense of humor.

Jiang You walked up to the corpse of Blade Master Lang Rui. He needed to get close enough to the corpse to pick up the drops.

At that moment, one of his subordinates, a Knight named Three Stones, sent him a private message: I’ll cover you.

“Oh?” Jiang You was puzzled after receiving the message, but he quickly understood its meaning.

Could he be waiting for him to pick up the loot and then use that opportunity to suddenly act out and kill him?

This might be what the guy was planning!

Although the stakes were high with a plan like this, there was no other way to steal items dropped by a boss under such watchful eyes. He might not get what he wanted, but he might also have set up ambushes at his re-spawn location. Does he know which main city my account is bound to?

As Jiang You pondered this issue, Three Stones led a squad of Knights and Clerics forward as if they were just going closer to take a look. By doing this, they separated Jiang You’s Wandering Peak from Unrivaled Super Hottie.

They paid close attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie, ready to respond.

Nothing happened.

Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t move even after Jiang You finished picking up the drops.

Jiang You and Three Stones looked at each other

They were both working in the Club Tyrannay’s studio and could communicate with each other in real life. They opted to use in-game means of communication so that they would not be exposed.

“He still hasn’t showed any reaction.” Jiang You messaged Three Stones.

“Could we have been wrong?” Three Stones replied.

“Who else but him could possess such skill?” said Jiang You.

“The Spitfire earlier...” Three Stones’s reply wasn’t very tactful.

“That person was most likely Zhang Jiale!” Jiang You said, but he wasn’t interested in Zhang Jiale. “What do you think of his skills as a Knight?”

“Me? You’re letting me to assess someone on an entirely different level from me?” Three Stones smiled bitterly.

“I just want to know your opinion!” Jiang You was helpless as well. Their game studio couldn’t expect long-term help from a pro player! If they had to assess the strength of a pro-player, they wouldn’t be able to get comprehensive results. This was just like how they had suffered defeat after defeat by the hands of Lord Grim despite knowing that he was Ye Qiu. Their encounter with Ye Qiu in the Western Wilderness was a perfect example. They thought they had the absolute advantage in the Heavenly Domain with their superior numbers. In the end, they still got steamrolled. They didn’t even know what level of strength they would need to defeat a God.

Three Stones couldn’t resist the urge to roll his eyes at Jiang You in real life, “In my honest opinion, he’s as good as any Knight in the pro league.” he replied.

“But these pro players definitely don’t have the time to play the game, yes?” Jiang You said.

“Obviously.”

“Then he must be Ye Qiu!” Jiang You concluded.

“Haven’t we always treated him as Ye Qiu?”

“But why isn’t he moving? He can’t be here to help out our guild, right?” Jiang You was puzzled.

“What if he’s already gathered more helpers and is planning on taking us out in one fell swoop?” Three Stones suggested.

“Are you talking about Heavenly Justice….” Jiang You pondered.

They used to think that Ye Qiu would be isolated in the Heavenly Domain, but in the first few days since his arrival, he had already formed good relations with Heavenly Justice. They had never truly investigated the strength of Heavenly Justice because player-formed guilds were not their main competitors. They viewed Heavenly Justice as a rich man’s toy. They had never thought that their guild would one day become their competitors in the pro league.

The higher ups of the Clubs blamed Heavenly Justice’s sudden momentum on the guild leaders. To have overlooked the growth of a team with such a strong foundation in the game, the guild leaders of the Club guilds could be said to have neglected their duties.

The Club guilds began paying more attention to Heavenly Justice afterwards. Heavenly Justice fully utilized the incidents caused by the guilds to bolster their own strength and popularity. The momentum gained by their team attracted a lot of attention. Despite being supported by a “money warrior”, they insisted on promoting themselves as a grassroots team. They were recruiting massively and throwing out a lot of money to gain benefits, creating a huge wave of excitement. It didn’t matter what Heavenly Justice’s original intentions were, they were able to set up a solid foundation. If the team managed to become famous in the pro scene, the players in the guild would turn into their loyal fans.

With such ambition, how could Heavenly Justice neglect the competition for wild bosses? Player-formed guilds had never been competition for Club guilds when it came to wild bosses, but with Heavenly Justice now at the same level as them, did they need to hide anymore? Could Unrivaled Super Hottie be a pawn of Heavenly Justice?

“Come to think of it, does Heavenly Justice have the strength to face us? Besides, it would be bad for both sides to get involved in open conflict!” Three Stones said.

“It’s different. They’re in an unusual place right now. They could have some unconventional means.” Jiang You said, “Their morale is very high too. It’d be easy for them to rally their forces. Besides, their boss himself is in the game. They can get more resources easily compared to us. If they needed to do something big, just one word from the boss would be enough to make it happen. But then again, would they really need to use Ye Qiu as a spy to pull off such a move?”

Three Stones replied thoughtfully, “By using Ye Qiu’s strength, they can quickly get close to him and obtain more confidential information, right?”

“They can just throw their money at us if they wanted it so badly. If they offered us ten thousand bucks for a piece of information, wouldn’t you sell it?” Jiang You asked.

“This question is too sensitive…..” Three Stones replied.

“There are hundreds of us here. All of us hold vital intelligence about our operation. Do you think not one of them could be bribed?” Jiang You asked.

Three Stones was silent. Despite being a disgusting strategy, money was undoubtedly the most effective way for one to achieve their goals. Ten thousand bucks for some information….. Three Stones would probably have given in too.

“This is why Unrivaled Super Hottie is so suspicious….” said Jiang You.

“How about exposing him right away?” Three Stones said.

“No, we’ll continue observing him. For now, let’s pull back. We’ll decide what to do once he reveals his trickery. When worse comes to the worst, we’ll suffer another loss.” Jiang You was already preparing for the worst case scenario.

“There’s also a chance that he’s not Ye Qiu.” Three Stones was still optimistic.

“I have a plan.” Jiang You had a sudden thought after hearing Three Stone’s words. He moved Wandering Peak closer to Unrivaled Super Hottie after secretly transferring his items to Three Stones.

Jiang You walked up to Unrivaled Super Hottie and spoke with a jovial tone, “Brother, you’re good!”

“Haha, it’s nothing.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied with a laugh.

Even though Jiang You tried hard to confirm the identity of the person through his voice, he hadn’t interacted much with Ye Xiu despite their numerous conflicts. It was hard to recognise him through voice only. Since Jiang You was very suspicious, his voice sounded a lot like Ye Xiu.

“Brother, your skills far surpass the average player’s!” Jiang You said .

“Of course, look at my name.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“Hah! I’m sure you know of our guild. If you want, I can recommend you to our pro team! With your skill level, I think you could make it into the pro league! Of course, I’m not that skillful, I can’t guarantee that I’m correct.” said Jiang You.

“Hehe, the pro league? I’m more interested in the game.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“Haha, if that’s the case, you can join Tyrannical Ambition, brother!” Jiang You exclaimed.

“No problem.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“Four branch guild leader, this brother now belongs to your guild!” Jiang You called out.

“What?” The fourth branch guild leader was shocked. Everyone had witnessed Unrivaled Super Hottie’s skill. He could easily replace Three Stones of the main guild. To place him in the fourth branch? What is the meaning of this?

Everyone thought Unrivaled Super Hottie wouldn’t be happy, but he merely laughed, as if he didn’t mind Jiang You’s decision.

Chapter 591 – Laboring for the Guild

With the boss battle settled, the players from Tyrannical Ambition began to leave Sword Peak Ravine. Jiang You still had his guard up, but everything went smoothly. Unrivaled Super Hottie left the place along with the group just like that.

The players were very curious about Unrivaled Super Hottie. The fourth branch guild leader noticed that something was definitely off, and quietly walked over to Jiang You.

“How should I deal with Unrivaled Super Hottie?” the fourth branch guild leader asked. He believed that the guild leader had some special plan in store. With Unrivaled Super Hottie’s strength, he should at least have been one of the elite core members. Joining the main guild wouldn’t have been a problem at all, but instead, he was exiled to a branch guild. Something fishy was going on.

“He might be Ye Qiu.” Jiang You hadn’t openly share his suspicions before because it had only been a baseless speculation, but with Unrivaled Super Hottie’s performance displayed, and with the pro league as bait, Jiang You was now very certain. Although there would be Glory players who weren’t interested in the pro league, they were the minority. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s firm decision added onto Jiang You’s suspicion. Or rather, he no longer suspected the person. He was entirely sure of it.

“Ah!” The fourth branch guild leader gasped.

“We don’t know his goal yet,” Jiang You continued, “but since he wants to play, we’ll play along with him.”

“Huh?” The fourth branch guild leader was puzzled. Even though he had never participated in the conflicts with God Ye Qiu, he had heard all about them. The Club guilds were a mess because of him! To have such a walking disaster be a part of his guild, the fourth branch guild leader felt his heartbeat increase. He began to feel nervous.

“Even though he definitely doesn’t have good intentions, you’ve seen his strength. We could use him. When he joins your guild, send him to a random team. Use him for hard labor.” Jiang You said.

The fourth branch guild leader was amazed by Jiang You. He had the courage to use a God as a hard laborer. Their guild leader was too incredible.

“But you must pay close attention to him. Put him in a group with someone you trust. It’ll make it easier to keep an eye on him.” Jiang You had already put in a considerable amount of thought.

“Okay, I understand.” The fourth branch guild leader nodded.

“Good, we’ll leave it at that for now then.” Jiang You said, while giving Unrivaled Super Hottie a warm greeting. Then, he took the main guild’s troops and left. Only a fight for Bosses could gather so many people in one place. Other activities, such as dungeon runs were done according to the respective guilds.

Jiang You and his group went far away until they couldn’t no longer see Unrivaled Super Hottie. They were completely safe and sound. Only then could he relax.

“We’ll feign ignorance, and let him work hard to gain our trust! He’ll be a useful pawn, especially when it comes to competing for bosses.” Jiang You told Three Stones.

“Is it alright to bring him along? He didn’t make any movements this time. Maybe his target wasn’t Blade Master Lang Rui?”

“It’s quite possible.” Jiang You nodded, “I think he intends to infiltrate the upper layers of our guild to get first hand information and then act when the time is right for a boss he needs.”

“We’ll need to be careful then. We’ll do things like what we did today. He’ll never be able to make off with the items dropped by the boss.” said Three Stones.

“I’m afraid that he might wreak havoc when he doesn’t find any opportunities.” Jiang You said.

“That would be scary…..” Three Stones recalled the unparalleled destructive capabilities of Unrivaled Super Hottie. His heart was full of envy and jealousy. Who wouldn’t want to be as majestic-looking as him? Three Stones glanced at the sword in his hand and sighed. He would never be as skilled. As a veteran Knight, he could clearly see Unrivaled Super Hottie’s mastery over the Maelstrom Counterattack.

With the players from the main guild were gone, only a few members of the branch guilds were left. Since this time’s boss was special, elite Knights and Clerics of the branch guilds were present. Under normal circumstances, only the Knights from the main guild were required.

“Brother, what next?” The fourth branch guild leader inherited Jiang You’s warmth and acted like he was concerned about Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“Nothing much.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied casually, “I’ve got to recover my experience points!”

“Ahh, that’s a must. How about finding a team to dungeon with?” The fourth branch guild leader asked.

“Sure!” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

With some quick arrangements, Unrivaled Super Hottie was contacted by his new team members.

“See you later.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said goodbye to the other members of the fourth branch guild and left with his new teammates.

“Guild Leader.” The fourth branch guild’s number one Knight, Flight, called out to his guild leader.

“Hm?”

“Are there any special arrangements for Unrivaled Super Hottie?” Flight tried this best to gain some insight on the situation. To put Unrivaled Super Hottie in the fourth branch guild, there must be something wrong. Flight felt uncomfortable. He had always been looking for a chance to prove himself, but no Knight would be able to outdo Unrivaled Super Hottie’s recent performance.

“Uh, we’ll leave it at that!” The fourth branch guild leader answered vaguely. It wasn’t because he didn’t trust Flight. It was due to the fact that he knew the person well. He knew that Flight was wary of Unrivaled Super Hottie, and was reluctant to share such news to with someone filled with negative emotions.

Flight knew that his guild leader was intentionally dodging the question. He was anxious. With such a great Knight around, he felt pressured. The players that had played with Unrivaled Super Hottie would no longer think that Flight was good.

Flight’s worry was proven to be correct.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was highly praised by his new party members, and the entire fourth branch immediately knew of the presence of the top-notch Knight in their guild, even if he wasn’t officially a part of their guild yet.

When Unrivaled Super Hottie officially joined the fourth branch guild of Tyrannical Ambition a few days later, his reputation was already very high. The celebratory welcome he received almost broke Flight’s heart.

“Boss Unrivaled, which dungeon do you want to run?” Quite a few players asked impatiently. His name had already become “Boss Unrivaled”. People with true strength easily earned recognition from others. Although he held no official position, he already had the qualifications in the people’s heart.

“Haha, it doesn’t matter, I’ll go wherever I’m needed!” Unrivaled Super Hottie answered in a carefree manner. The guild members were full of joy. Happy Sheep’s breakthrough with Unrivaled Super Hottie’s help made every team in the guild extremely jealous. As a result, in these past few days, all of the teams were asking their guild leader for Unrivaled Super Hottie. Usually, team members were fixed and wouldn’t be transferred so easily, but for an exceptional expert like Unrivaled Super Hottie, why was he in that team? Why can’t he be in ours? Thus, everyone demanded their guild leader for an answer. The fourth branch guild leader didn’t object. Unrivaled Super Hottie was there for labor anyways! He let them contact Unrivaled Super Hottie and indicated that Unrivaled Super Hottie didn’t belong to any fixed team!

People were basically openly competing with each other for Unrivaled Super Hottie’s assistance. The guy himself didn’t decline any invitation, and went into dungeons with different teams. With him officially in the guild, contacting him became even easier. The team leaders were swarming him with requests.

“F*ck, you guys already dungeoned with Boss Unrivaled a few days ago, piss off!”

“Sh*t, you dare to let Boss Unrivaled go into such a trash dungeon?”

“D*mmit, first come first serve, alright? We invited him first.”

“My ass, look at the chat, I did it first!”

“F*ck, ask Boss Unrivaled which dungeon he wants to go to. That doesn’t count!”

“D*mmit, my words were indirect, but my intentions were clear!”

The guild chat erupted into chaos. Everybody was fighting for Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attention. Flight’s heart was broken once again. He was lucky that the elite squad that he belonged to didn’t beg for Unrivaled Super Hottie’s attention.

“Hahaha, everybody settle down. I’ll go with the brothers that I’ve never dungeoned with before.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“See, Boss Unrivaled has spoken. The rest of you, back off!” Someone immediately said.

The ones, like Happy Sheep’s team, backed off with some grumbling. The guild finally settled down after Unrivaled Super Hottie declared his intentions.

“What are you trying to do…..” Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel envious after witnessing the scene. He’s a God and with this, Chen Guo was relieved. However, she was curious about why Ye Xiu was dungeoning with all of these teams.

Chapter 592 – Sharing the Labor

Ye Xiu spent most of his time on Unrivaled Super Hottie. He didn’t completely stop leveling Lord Grom, but if he had spent his time on Lord Grim instead, Lord Grim would have been around the level 60 threshold by now. Focusing on Unrivaled Super Hottie, going into different dungeons with different parties, working hard as a tank, Chen Guo didn’t know what Ye Xiu could get out of doing these things.

Chen Guo couldn’t hold herself back and asked Ye Xiu, but Ye Xiu was talking loudly into the mic. He couldn’t hear anything from Chen Guo.

Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie had originally been laying low. He rarely said anything, but with his strength already known, the person in charge of the team didn’t dare to order him around. Out of necessity, Ye Xiu had to take charge. With such an expert in charge, everybody on the team was happy to carry out his orders, especially since they achieved good results with Ye Xiu leading. The name of “Brother Unrivaled” became more and more self-fulfilling.

In the past few days, according to Chen Guo’s observations, Ye Xiu had gone into 22 different dungeons with 22 different parties, and all of them were 100-player dungeons. They always cleared them too. In terms of efficiency, Ye Xiu’s addition was astonishing.

Tyrannical Ambition’s fourth branch players was happy to reap the benefits. They had gained the upper hand in their competition against the other branch guilds. The other branch guilds weren’t happy after learning the truth. They swarmed Jiang You, protesting Unrivaled Super Hottie’s presence in the fourth branch guild.

Jiang You didn’t expect that the guy would cause trouble even when he was used for hard labor. He couldn’t help but feel impressed. Ye Xiu really was a God. Everything he did got the attention of others.

The leaders of the branch guilds were naturally Tyrannical Ambition’s absolute core members. They were more trustworthy than the elites within the main guild. With their nonstop complaints, Jiang You had a meeting with them to tell them the truth.

“He’s Ye Qiu! No wonder!!” The branch guild leaders immediately understood after being exposed to the truth.

“Which is why he must have some ill intentions by joining Tyrannical Ambition. However, his motives remain hidden. For now, we’re just using his strength to benefit ourselves.” Jiang You explained.

The branch guild leaders approved of Jiang You’s plan. The idea of using their archnemesis as a work slave was very appealing.

“Even so, there’s no reason that the fourth branch guild alone should keep him to themselves. We deserve a share too, don’t we?” The second branch guild leader said.

“Ha ha ha, we’re on the same side. There’s no need to make a fuss about it.” The leader of the fourth branch laughed.

“He’s in your guild, so of course you’d say that.”The leader of the fifth branch guild rolled his eyes. He knew about Wolf Head’s encounter with Unrivaled Super Hottie. Even though he got bullied, they were still on the same side, so the option of revenge through petty tricks had gone out the window, but after learning the truth, he couldn’t help but feel that the presence of Ye Qiu was like a cheat engine for the fourth branch guild. It wasn’t fair. It was like the fourth branch guild had started using a cheat engine, especially how their teams kept on making breakthroughs in the dungeons. With the members of the fourth guild acting high and mighty after their achievements, didn’t they know that their success was achieved only because such a top-tier player?

Jiang You wasn’t angry at the situation. Instead, he laughed, “Okay, there’s no need to fight. Using Ye Qiu as a slave for our guild is a good thing. It’s a rare opportunity. Everybody should get to have some of the fun, so let’s let him switch between branch guilds!”

With Jiang You making his stance clear, the leader of the fourth branch guild had nothing more to say. They were still people that considered more than obtaining benefits, “Will he notice it if we overdo it?”

“So what? Hehe, it’s nothing! If worse come to the worst, he’ll just leave. We have nothing to lose.” Jiang You replied, appearing to have given the issue a thorough amount of thought beforehand. Despite that, Jiang You had a bad feeling about his plan. Even though they had paid close attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie, a God’s movements weren’t comprehensible by normal players.

The other branch guild leaders agreed. With such a highly intelligent spy, so what if they treated him roughly? We don’t expect anything from you, but since you’re already here, we might as well use you to the fullest!

The branch guild leaders began to argue about the distribution of their “free labor”. Since it was harmless, Jiang You didn’t interfere and instead joined in on the fun. In the end, they voted for the third branch guild to use the “cheat engine”.

“Just one day?! You’re kidding me. How much can he do in one day!!” The leader of the third branch guild was furious when he learnt that he was granted access to the “cheating engine” for only a day.

“Then how many days do you want him for? If you keep him for too long, and he left just like that, then won’t we lose our source of fun?” The leaders of the other branch guilds refuted.

“I’ll at least keep him for as long as the fourth branch guild did.” The leader of the third branch guild argued.

In the end, no one was willing to compromise. There were a lot of branch guilds under the banner of Tyrannical Ambition. If all of them took turns, there might be a chance that there would be some that wouldn’t get the chance to use the free labor. They didn’t plan on treating him well. What if he just left after the first day?

In the end, they completely got rid of the initial decision. They decided to let Unrivaled Super Hottie choose whoever invited him.

“I have something say about this!” Jiang You said after they came to a conclusion, “He has to do it on his own free will. Do not entice him with any conditions!”

“Oh?” The branch guilds leaders were momentarily stunned.

“If we competed against each other for his help, who would benefit from it in the end?” Jiang You continued.

The leaders of the branch guilds suddenly came to a realization. They immediately agreed to Jiang You’s terms.

Jiang You was finally relieved. He was alarmed by the decision of the branch guild leaders. He immediately suspected Ye Qiu’s real intention: throwing himself into their guild and invoking conflict within the guild as an elite that was sought-after by everyone….

How crafty! Luckily, I noticed it! Jiang You thought.

Tyrannical Ambition had made a decision. In the meantime, Ye Xie was becoming increasingly busy. With Jiang You’s approval to use his strength, players other than the ones from the fourth branch guild were asking for his help. Even the ones from the main guild were looking for him. Jiang You didn’t stop these activities. As long as none of them gave away any benefits. Anyone could use Ye Qiu. After all, wasn’t it all good for Tyrannical Ambition?

Jiang You was extremely pleased with his arrangements with Ye Qiu as the branch guilds made excellent progress in dungeons. Tyrannical Ambition was involved with a few more conflicts for bosses during the past two weeks. Jiang You wanted to use him for free labor, but he held his impulsiveness back. He pondered over it and felt like he should use him to clear dungeons to the point where he gave up. Jiang You could never trust him when it came to killing bosses.

However, even though Jiang You was reluctant to deploy his cheat engine, the other guilds weren’t the same.

Blossom Valley’s Dazzling Spring was very popular at the moment. With his help, Blossom Valley was doing very well. The Three Great Guilds couldn’t gain an upper hand against Blossom Valley. Even at the momentous, Samsara was being suppressed. This player’s unprecedented strength had garnered a lot of attention and was shrouded in rumors.

Some said that he was Zhang Jiale, others claimed that the person was Zou Yuan. Some even said that he was a new member of Team Hundred Blossom that would take over Dazzling Hundred Blossom and was playing in game to train himself. There was even a rumor that the person was someone who had trained for years and joined Blossom Valley, ready to show his true strength.

The rumors even went out of hand, but such an expert easily attracted attention of the pro teams. Many had tried to get in touch of this character. Ye Xiu was one of them. He chatted with the person from time to time in QQ.

“You’ve been busy these days, what are you planning on doing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“What about your work in Tyrannical Ambition?” Zhang Jiale answered with a question of his own.

“I’m on official business!” Ye Xiu replied in a serious tone, “You were quite cooperative last time, seeing that you didn’t expose my identity. What do you think? Are you interested in working together?”

“Nah, I just didn’t want to get in your way, seeing that you’re putting quite a lot of effort into it.” Zhang Jiale answered.

“It’s nothing. I’m enjoying it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh really…... That’s good!”

“How about you?”

“Me…. I’m in a bit of a dilemma.” Zhang Jiale replied.

“Is it really that hard of a choice to make? Join forces with me. We’ll be the champions without a doubt!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Sorry, that isn’t one of my options.” Zhang Jiale said.

“You don’t have much foresight.” Ye Xiu complained.

“Foresight requires an investment in time. Do I have the time? I’m not like you.” Zhang Jiale said.

“Hmm….. I understand.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 593 – Time Decides Aggro

Chen Guo paid a lot of attention to Zhang Jiale. With the presence of such a great God on their team, their strength would increase exponentially. This was why Chen Guo paid such careful attention to the interactions between Ye Xiu and Zhang Jiale. She felt that something was wrong with their conversation. Zhang Jiale didn’t seem to be interested in Ye Xiu’s proposal.

Ye Xiu’s “I understand” made Chen Guo even more agitated. The most annoying phrases when eavesdropping on a conversation were “I understand” and “You know it”.

What do you understand? What did you know?! People who used such words were too irresponsible! They didn’t even care about the feelings of the eavesdroppers!

“What do you understand? Huh?” Chen Guo was straightforward. She immediately asked Ye Xiu after noticing that Ye Xiu didn’t attempt to persuade Zhang Jiale.

“What he meant was that even if he returns to the pro league, he doesn’t have much time in his career left. Since he wants to be the champion, of course he needs to cherish the time he has left. Joining a new team like us would be wasteful and luxurious.”Ye Xiu said.

“He said that he’s different from you. What difference is there?” Chen Guo asked.

“I’ve already won a championship. He has not.” Ye Xiu replied.

Chen Guo immediately understood. For a new team like Team Happy to become the champion? Even Chen Guo felt that it was absurd despite having a God like Ye Xiu. One didn’t simply get to become the champion with just a God. The God chatting on the other side was the perfect example.

The poor God was nearing the end of his career. If his goal was to be the champion, he would never join Team Happy. To Zhang Jiale, it was all or nothing, but for Ye Xiu, he didn’t share the same worry to a certain degree.

“What a shame.” Chen Guo sighed.

“Yeah, he gave up on the chance to be a champion.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Uhh….” Chen Guo responded absentmindedly. Unlike Ye Xiu, her confidence was an illusion. Even though a God was strong, it was the pro leagues they were talking about. Unlike the game, there were a lot of other Gods. When she said “What a shame”, she just felt that it was pity they wouldn’t be able to have another God join them, not what Ye Xiu meant.

“Good luck!” Ye Xiu said to Zhang Jiale.

“Out of courtesy, I should wish you good luck as well, but your luck will mean my misfortune. I’m in a bit of a dilemma.” Zhang Jiale said.

“Haha, I won’t be back so soon. Cherish the one year you have left!” Ye Xiu replied.

“If that’s the case, then good luck to you as well!”

“Good luck.”

“Good luck!”

Ye Xiu close the chat window after the two exchanged blessings with each other and sighed. Even Ye Xiu felt regretful being unable to get the help of another God.

Back in the game, Unrivaled Super Hottie was already being invited by hordes of players. Ye Xiu appeared to be picking random parties, but Chen Guo had been observing him for quite some times and found something peculiar.

“Hey, you’ve partied with this group before!” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu had always been with different parties. It was the first time that he had gone dungeon running with the same party twice. Chen Guo thought that Ye Xiu was confused after going into dungeons with so many different parties.

“Yes, I know.” Ye Xiu unexpectedly answered.

“Oh? You’re going with them again?” Chen Guo started to study the party slowly. It was a small group from the Tyrannical Ambition’s seventh branch. Chen Guo could not see anything special from their characters. They were just like any other group that Ye Xiu had played with before. They were mediocre at best.

“Why are you going with them a second time?” Just as Chen Guo was about to throw Ye Xiu her question, Unrivaled Super Hottie received a message. It was from Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader, Wandering Peak.

Before sending the message, Jiang You was also in an awkward position!

They had found a new boss. It was the lvl 70 North Bridge Mage Mordak, which was badly needed by Tyrannical Ambition. However, for the past three weeks the boss had spawned, Tyrannical Ambition was unable to secure the boss.

The first failure was from a fair and square competition against the other guilds, but for their second and third attempt, it was all because of the newly emerged expert called Dazzling Spring from Blossom Valley.

Jiang You was highly criticized by the Club’s higher up due to his failures. Even though they knew that there were a lot of uncertainties when it came to competitions for wild bosses, for a team that desperately needed a certain boss, the game department would still be under a lot of pressure. The manager even made it a point that the next boss must be secured at all costs.

At all costs? Why don’t you guys send a professional player or two to help out?

Jiang You, of course, kept that complaint to himself. It might not be a good thing if the Club sent a pro to aid Jiang You. His task would become easier, but it also meant that he had neglected his duty. As someone in charge of everything in the game, if he needed the aid of pro players to solve his problems, it meant that his capabilities were limited.

Jiang You wished to overcome the problem on his own, unless the situation was very dire. With Dazzling Spring, who was suspected to be Zhang Jiale, on the enemy’s side, it was indeed a dire situation. However, Jiang You also had a trump card. After giving it a lot of thought, he finally decided to deploy his trump card.

If he needed pro players to solve his problem, his capabilities would be doubted, but if he could solve problems that would require help from pro players, it meant that he was very good at doing his job. The two factors were closely related to each other. Jiang You was never purely a player. To him, this was his career.

He was happy to find that Unrivaled Super Hottie was online after receiving news regarding the North Bridge Mage Mordak and immediately contacted him.

Even though this person’s aim was still unknown, judging from his willingness to act as hard labor in Tyrannical Ambition’s branches, Jiang You knew that his summon would bear fruit.

As expected, Unrivaled Super Hottie happily accepted and immediately made his way over. Jiang You took this opportunity to review his troops.

The competition for North Bridge Mage Mordak was tight. It was not because of the fact that the mage was tough. It was due to the fact that the area which he spawned in was quite small.

Upstream of a certain river, there was a bridge known as the “North Bridge”. It was said to be one of the forgotten sites of the great road of Glory. Decaying with time, the North Bridge lost its original purpose. One could no longer cross the bridge without some incredible platforming skills. The bridge was already damaged beyond recognition. The only reason it still stood was because of the system’s logic-defying settings.

North Bridge Mage Mordak always spawned on the North Bridge. He didn’t belong to any leveling areas. He was just a scenery boss.

And how big could a bridge be? No matter where the North Bridge Mage Mordak spawned, he’d immediately be spotted by players.

Competition for this boss was never limited to just three or four guilds. Any ambitious guild would arrive at the scene.

As Jiang You was reviewing with his men, he believed that the other guilds were doing the same.

Not long after, players from each guilds had already gathered on both ends of the bridge. After a brief calculation by Jiang You, about ten Club guilds had gathered.

Herb Garden, Blue Brook Guild, Excellent Era, Samsara, Royal Style, Blossom Valley, Misty Castle, Void Walk, Howling Heights, and with the addition of Tyrannical Ambition, 10 guilds were present.

The players at the bridge weren’t too shocked. They had seen the same scene every week. If a boss was too hard to find, it would be very troublesome for players, but if a boss was spotted easily, the situation would not be any better for them either.

For a rather easy Boss, the high difficulty faced to secure it was because of his small spawn location.

North Bridge Mage Modak levitated above the North Bridge. He was an old man with a white beard, but his body was still well-built. There was a backstory about the old man that happened on the bridge. It was a sad and touching story, but the players that were at the place for the Boss didn’t care about the backstory. The only thing concerning them was how to get to the boss when surrounded by players from nine other guilds on extremely unfavourable terrain.

Nobody was willing to make a move. They were already used to the norm of “watching silently”. It was a disgusting practice that occurred once a week.

A gunshot broke through the silence. Blossom Valley was the first to make their move. Or rather, Dazzling Spring from Blossom Valley.

It was also a scene that people had become used to in the past two weeks. Dazzling Spring’s unprecedented skill allowed him to approach the Boss directly, unlike the other players.

Dazzling Spring leapt onto the bridge. Gunshots rang out, accompanied by zipping bullets and flying hand grenades.

The North Bridge Mage was already on the move. He was another Boss that was very exquisite about the aggro’s direction.

There was also an extra condition to establishing his aggro: the person standing on the North Bridge.

As long as somebody stood on the bridge, he would be a target for the North Bridge Mage’s wrath. The longer a player stayed on the bridge, the higher the aggro value would be. It would be impossible to snatch the attention of the boss away from beyond the bridge. The deciding factor of pulling the North Bridge Mage’s aggro was the amount of time one spent on the bridge.

It was a very important factor, but it was also something that received the least attention of the guilds. To fight for an extended period of time on the North Bridge was not an easy feat. Simply passing the bridge required a very high amount of skill, not to mention fighting on it. With so many contenders, fighting on the North Bridge would only result in countless players falling into the water below.

The situation completely changed with the presence of Dazzling Spring. Zhang Jiale was a God. He could ensure his own safety on the bridge without plummeting into the water. For the past two weeks, he was the first target of the North Bridge Mage’s aggro.

Because on the North Bridge, time decides aggro.

Chapter 594 – The Lost Initiative

Dazzling Spring was the first to move. A scene like this was nothing new. This incident wasn’t exclusive to the North Bridge Mage. Blossom Valley had actively competed for bosses for quite some time and Dazzling Spring was the one who had always taken the initiative to start the boss fights. With such an expert in their midst, they were not afraid of anybody going after them. They seized the initiative easily.

With two weeks of experience, the big guilds were already used to it. The moment they saw Dazzling Spring move, countless players reacted with anger. Their target was not the boss, but rather Dazzling Spring who was the first to jump onto the bridge.

To be able to secure the boss in the countless boss battles, it was the perfect group aggro attraction. The many large guilds gathered around shared the same hatred towards Dazzling Spring. As long as that person was there, the boss would be secured by Blossom Valley again.

Tyrannical Ambition was the only guild that held back. Jiang You was actually more agitated than the rest, but without Unrivaled Super Hottie, he didn’t dare to make a move.

Dazzling Spring stood at the top of North Bridge without worry, dodging attacks from all directions without much effort.

The river was wide, one could see the former glory of the North Bridge that connected both banks of the river, just by observing its battered frame. Dazzling Spring stood at the highest point of the bridge, avoiding attacks from the melee classes. The remaining mid-ranged classes couldn’t even reach Dazzling Spring once he reached the center of the bridge.

If they stepped forward further, they would be on the North Bridge.

Once they were on the North Bridge, they would trigger the aggro of the North Bridge Mage.

Even though the North Bridge Mage’s aggro was currently focused on Dazzling Spring, a boss with such special aggro mechanics would usually have volatile aggro. Even when his attacks were focused on Dazzling Spring, he would still launch surprise attacks towards other players based on the amount of time they had spent on the North Bridge.

Players were already able to grasp the strategy after a long time of studying the boss’s behavior. Under normal circumstances, the players would usually move in and out of the North Bridge to reset the time aggro, but an expert like Dazzling Spring totally ignored the aggro. He hopped left and right, continuously dealing damage to the North Bridge Mage while taking the time to harass players from the other guilds. With the height that he was at, he had the advantage. The bullets shot by him and the grenades thrown by him would eventually drop to the ground wouldn’t they?

Before the players could attack Dazzling Spring, they already suffered from his counter attack. With a surge in his APM, various types of grenades showered down like rain. A Spitfire’s grenades would do more than just create explosions. They had a lot more uses. With his Hundred Blossom style, the North Bridge was lit up with explosions that consumed several players at once.

When the visual effects faded away, there were visibly less players left standing.

Could he take out so many players with just a single combo? It was obviously impossible. But you had to also take note of the players left standing! They were all from Blossom Valley! They had acted according to Dazzling Spring’s attacks, rampaging within the visual distraction created. They were immune to Dazzling Spring’s attacks anyways. There were no allies among the 10 guilds. The players from Blossom Valley hid in the visual distractions created by Dazzling Spring, while creating the same visual distraction wherever they went. They performed the Hundred Blossoms style as a team. The visual effects expanded non-stop, swallowing everything in its path.

Within moments, the players from Blossom Valley had taken control of the North Bridge. The North Bridge Mage was busy attacking Dazzling Spring with his spells.

The boss’s couldn’t be distinguished using conventional means. Despite using the combat style of a Witch, the boss didn’t fly around on a broom like a Witch usually would. He instead flew around with only his magical staff.

There was, however, still a limit to his flying duration. The North Bridge Mage landed on a vantage point and threw Fireballs at Dazzling Spring.

Dazzling Spring leapt into the air, dodging each and every one of the boss’s attack. With his superior geographical advantage, he looked down on the battlefield with a bird’s eye view. The players of Blossom Valley had already rushed towards the boss and began to attack.

The players from the big guilds coughed up blood! Wasn’t this a reenactment of last week’s battle?

They knew clearly what would happen if they dared to charge onto the scene. Dazzling Spring would immediately shower them with attacks.

They didn’t doubt Dazzling Spring’s capability in suppressing the area. His Hundred Blossoms style was designed to mess up his opponent’s vision. The ability to see was the most important aspect in a place such as the North Bridge. If one lost one’s vision, combat would be impossible. The person might even fall into the river by mistake.

The only difference with last week was that the players from the big guilds were actually on the offensive. However, they were cleared away by Dazzling Spring’s counterattacks with the cooperation of Blossom Valley’s players.

“We shouldn’t have even let him get on the bridge!” A player shouted, tears streaming down his cheeks as he looked 45 degrees upwards at Dazzling Spring.

“Everyone, be careful, we must get there no matter what!” Another player shouted, but none of them moved.

The players from the big guilds stood outside the bridge, looking left and right. At this time, they were hoping that somebody else would step forward and act as cannon fodder. Of course, who would be so dumb as to voluntarily serve as cannon fodder?! Obviously no one would. Which was why they could do nothing but stand aside and watch.

The players from the large guilds were bleeding in their hearts. Jiang You was especially worried, and he immediately sent a message to Unrivaled Super Hottie and urged him to move faster.

“Aren’t I already here?” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

Jiang You looked around and spotted a group of players walking towards him along the riverbank. When they were close, Jiang You noticed that Unrivaled Super Hottie was really there, but he wasn’t alone. He brought along the team that he was in with him.

A normal team in one of their branch guilds couldn’t even clear a dungeon properly! Against a wild boss, not to mention competing with players from other guilds, even if there were no other outside factors, they might not even be able to handle the boss! Why did he lead all those people here?

Jiang You was confused, and he could hear Unrivaled Super Hottie’s voice among the approaching players, “Look, the one throwing Fireballs from the top of the bridge? That’s the boss, North Bridge Mage Morlor.”

“Ohhhh!!!” The players in his team shouted in amazement. Even though there were not noobs in the Heavenly Domain, wild bosses were something that not everybody had the chance to encounter. It was an entirely new experience for them.

“That person that is dodging the Fireballs nonstop seems to be the boss’ aggro target. Oh, he seems to be a Spitfire. He has a very big advantage in controlling the entire field from that position. He can use the special geographical condition of the bridge to stop hostile players from getting onto the bridge.” Unrivaled Super Hottie continued.

“But he has to deal with the boss! It must be hard!” A player pointed out.

“Of course, look, there are other players trying to get onto the North Bridge!” Unrivaled Super Hottie pointed out.

Before they could spot the players, Unrivaled Super Hottie sighed, “Ah, he’s a sly one, jumping to that spot. He’s trying to get rid of them by using the boss!”

The Fireballs launched by the North Bridge Mage missed Dazzling Spring and dropped onto the players who were attempting to get on the bridge. They were immediately scattered by the boss’ attack.

The boss’ attacks weren’t like Dazzling Spring’s visual distraction, but the boss’ attacks had high damage, so they had no choice but to dodge. However, they couldn’t dodge the attacks like they usually did on a flat surface, they had to jump.

In their moment of panic, quite a number of them tumbled into the river below.

In the gushing stream, the players floated for a few moments and disappeared under the water’s surface. The average players were never good in controlling their characters in the water, falling into such a fast flowing stream added to the difficulty. To make it back to the riverbank alive depended entirely on their luck .

While some dropped into the water, others were showered by the boss’ attack. Suffering a direct hit would take away a large percentage of a player’s HP, if not instant death. A few grenades from Dazzling Spring cleared away the rest of the players from the bridge.

“Tsk tsk tsk tsk.” Unrivaled Super Hottie sighed, while Jiang You moved his Wandering Peak closer to him.

“Is that Dazzling Spring?” Unrivaled Super Hottie asked.

“Yes.” said Jiang You, “But the boss is called Mordak, not Morlor.”

“Ohh, it’s been quite awhile, I’ve forgotten the name.”

“Dazzling Spring has taken the initiative. It’s tough.” Jiang You said.

“It is, why did you not call me earlier?” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“I notified you as soon as possible.” Jiang You was helpless. Brother, you’re the one who was late…...

“Since the initiative belongs to him, it’s quite hard to turn the situation around.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“What now?”

“I need cover and some support.”

“It’s all on you!” Jiang You didn’t hesitate. Calling him here was to use his strength to the fullest. There was only one rule: he must never be allowed to be the leader of the team.

Jiang You immediately sent Unrivaled Super Hottie an invite, but the system notified him that he was already in a team.

“Add me.” Jiang You said.

And he immediately received an invite from Unrivaled Super Hottie. Tears streamed down his cheeks.

“What I meant was to join my team.” Jiang You explained. He must secure the spot of team leader. The fact that Unrivaled Super Hottie could send him an invite meant that he must at least be a sub-leader within the team. Jiang You had a bad feeling about it.

“Oh okay.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied. He left his team and requested to join Jiang You’s.

Jiang You accepted the request. After confirming that Unrivaled Super Hottie was only a normal member of the team, he then added his guild’s elites to the team.

“What do we do?” Jiang You asked.

“I’ll take out Dazzling Spring and drag the boss to the edge of the bridge. We’ll take care of him there.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“More details please.” Jiang You was puzzled.

Chapter 595 – Rush Upwards Just Like This

Even though Jiang You knew that this person was God Ye Qiu, Zhang Jiale was also a God. He didn’t think that think that Ye Qiu had a 100% chance of winning. In their last confrontation, Unrivaled Super Hottie helped to secure the boss for Tyrannical Ambition, but it wasn’t good to underestimate their opponent. Against an opponent like Zhang Jiale, Jiang You hoped that his trump card would be serious.

But in the moment it took him to blink, Unrivaled Super Hottie had already led his ragtag bunch towards the North Bridge while saying, “Let’s move over here. We’ll have a better view.”

The big guilds that were helpless against Dazzling Spring turned to look, and what they saw was a poverty stricken group from Tyrannical Ambition. They all secretly thought they were some sort of secret weapon. Even Tyrannical Ambition’s own players were baffled by this sight.

Jiang You’s patience had almost reached its limit, but he could only walk up to to Unrivaled Super Hottie.

“How do you plan on taking care of Dazzling Spring?” Jiang You asked.

“I’ll just rush upwards and take care of him.” Unrivaled Super Hottie replied.

“How?” Jiang You continued to bear it.

But Unrivaled Super Hottie hesitated, “How do I explain it to you….”

Jiang You’s patience finally ran out and he asked, “Fine, how do you want us to cover you?”

“After I rush upwards, all you need to do is to keep the Blossom Valley players in check.” Unrivaled Super Hottie said.

“Fine!” Jiang You was done. What he wanted to know was how Unrivaled Super Hottie would turn the tides for them, but Invincible Super Hottie’s answer was always “just rush upwards.”

Just rush upwards?

What nonsense! Everybody knew how to rush upwards, but the problem was, they couldn’t. Jiang You wanted to know how, but Unrivaled Super Hottie appeared as if he couldn’t give a proper explanation.

Jiang You anxiously followed Unrivaled Super Hottie to the edge of the bridge. The other players noticed Unrivaled Super Hottie’s presence and the fact that their guild leader created a new party. They rubbed their fists in anticipation of the upcoming action, but Unrivaled Super Hottie sent a “nodding” emoticon and said, “I’m rushing in.”

And then, he just rushed in.

Simple, rough, no tricks, no deception, and no numerical superiority. Unrivaled Super Hottie stepped onto the bridge alone.

Dazzling Spring and the Blossom Valley players had stayed longer than Unrivaled Super Hottie on the bridge. Despite that, the boss threw a glance at him the moment he touched the bridge, though he didn’t launch an attack.

It was one of the specialties of the BOSS. The old man cared a lot whenever somebody stepped onto the bridge. The poor NPC. He’d never understand that to prevent anybody from ever setting foot on the North Bridge, all he needed to do was leave the North Bridge. Players wouldn’t usually try and cross a broken bridge like this one. It was too risky to cross the river using it.

The boss didn’t divert his attacks towards Unrivaled Super Hottie, but the Blossom Valley players couldn’t hold themselves back. The moment they saw the Knight “Unrivaled Super Hottie”, the aggro of the Blossom Valley’s elites immediately shifted towards him.

This is what it meant to “provoke with only one’s looks”.

“Nobody make a move!” Blossom Valley’s guild leader Blooming Blossom said to stabilize the emotions of his guild members. Blossom Valley’s current combat style was built around Dazzling Spring. The player was actually very quiet even among Blossom Valley’s inner circle. He would, however, agree to participate whenever invited to a competition for a wild BOSS. He didn’t talk much, just like the average party member, and would only speak a sentence or two when needed.

Everybody could guess the identity of Dazzling Spring. Even when he stayed silent, his position as a core member of the guild was already set.

Blossom Valley’s attacks were basically adjusted according to Dazzling Spring’s attacks. Seeing that Dazzling Spring didn’t take any immediate action, Blooming Blossom stopped his men from attacking as well.

In the few seconds of hesitation, Unrivaled Super Hottie had completed three jumps.

Continuous and quick, Unrivaled Super Hottie began jumping. Although he wasn’t as stylish as Dazzling Spring, it was still a sight to see a heavily armored character moving with such agility.

There were no intervals between his jumps, as if he could do it even with eyes closed.

Within moments, Unrivaled Super Hottie was already halfway across .

Dazzling Spring chose that exact moment to launch a sudden attack.

Bullets and grenades flew towards Unrivaled Super Hottie.

The players, who tried to charge onto the North Bridge, were faced with similar attacks. In their own confusion, some fell off the bridge due to their own mistakes, while others were thrown off due to the shockwaves and explosions, while quite a number of them died from just the damage alone.

Unrivaled Super Hottie was different. He showed no hesitation and carried on jumping upwards, darting between the visual disruptions created by Dazzling Spring.

“He…. really is rushing in?” Jiang You was speechless.

Unrivaled Super Hottie braved through Dazzling Spring’s attacks and continued his jump upwards.

“Can he make it? Even if he didn’t die, how much health would he have left by the time he reaches the top?” Jiang You was worried.

“Clerics! Go see if you guys can heal him up!” Jiang You immediately gave the order.

The clerics from Tyrannical Ambition immediately went into action. They moved forward and healed Unrivaled Super Hottie, but with Dazzling Spring’s continuous attacks, they couldn’t even spot their target and couldn’t land their skills on their target. They tried very hard to grasp any chance they could to locate Unrivaled Super Hottie. After all, Dazzling Spring needed to handle the boss as well, so he couldn’t pay full attention to Unrivaled Super Hottie.

The advantage in numbers had finally been made obvious at that moment.

Even though most Clerics failed to grasp an opportunity to heal him, but with their sheer numbers, some of them eventually got lucky. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s health was maintained just like that.

But as Unrivaled Super Hottie reached a new height, he had moved out of range of the Cleric’s healing skills.

Some of the Clerics moved forward in a desperate attempt to catch up with Unrivaled Super Hottie and set foot on the North Bridge.

The boss viewed every living soul who dared to set foot on the North Bridge as the same. He glared coldly at them one by one. Dazzling Spring, on the other hand, didn’t share the BOSS’s sentiment. When Unrivaled Super Hottie set foot on the bridge, he ignored him, but the moment the other players were on the bridge, Dazzling Spring stopped his harassment towards Unrivaled Super Hottie and began bombarding the players with his attacks.

Two clerics fell into the river instantly. Their fates unknown.

Dazzling Spring didn’t hold back against other players.

But did he hold back against Unrivaled Super Hottie? The crowd soon realised that he did not. They realised that it was a trap.

If getting closer to Dazzling Spring was Unrivaled Super Hottie’s objective, he had already closed two thirds of the distance, but right after he hit the two thirds mark, he lost his support from the Clerics. The remaining one third of the journey would be one where Dazzling Spring could take care of Unrivaled Super Hottie with his advantage in range. He could even cooperate with the Blossom Valley players to deal with Unrivaled Super Hottie.

He didn’t attack Unrivaled Super Hottie because he knew that the guy was good, hence he set up a trap for him. With Unrivaled Super Hottie’s current awkward position, maybe Dazzling Spring would make a move?

The problem was that Dazzling Spring didn’t allow Unrivaled Super Hottie to freely move around. He kept on harassing him!

But Dazzling Spring’s next wave of attack showed the players that they were wrong.

To deal with an opponent who was on an entirely different level, one must also use some unconventional methods.

The Hundred Blossoms style, that was enough to suppress the average player, was just showing an opening when used on Unrivaled Super Hottie.

Totally ignoring him would be too obvious. His intention of seemingly eliminating Unrivaled Super Hottie earlier on was the real trap. The moment Unrivaled Super Hottie placed himself in this awkward position where he couldn’t move forward and could no longer retreat, that was exactly the best time to go all out.

Dazzling Spring had been waiting for that exact moment for a long time. He had even secretly made preparations. Unrivaled Super Hottie’s position was exposed to him that was at the top of the bridge and the Blossom Valley players below. Those who could hit Unrivaled Super Hottie had already launched their attacks.

Unrivaled Super Hottie immediately began to show caution.

The landing spots around him were all covered by Blossom Valley players. Even the bystanders were beginning to feel despair for Unrivaled Super Hottie, but he was still jumping. Jumping forward and upwards.

He was still “rushing upwards”.

Jiang You had a strange feeling in his heart after observing the scene.

The pro God, who he supposedly hated the most, was currently the one who he respected the most.

Always moving forward, never giving up.

Jiang You believed that the captain of Tyrannical Ambition, Han Wenqing, would have done the same.

But such a method would bring more harm than good in certain times. This was exactly what was happening to Unrivaled Super Hottie. If he wanted to move forward, he would need to bear the brunt of the attack.

Firm Defence.

Spell Reflection.

Shield Wall.

……

Knight defensive skills were used one after the other in perfect rhythm as Unrivaled Super Hottie continued his rush upwards. The Knight players on scene were already worshipping him. It still wasn’t enough though. The opponent’s attacks weren’t that easy to deal with. Even though Unrivaled Super Hottie was persistent, if he couldn’t escape his opponent’s attacks, his health would eventually hit zero.

“Who asked you to show off!!” Jiang You was depressed. He classified Unrivaled Super Hottie’s actions as “showing off”. He couldn’t accept the fact that the person he hated the most was so similar to their captain Han Wenqing.

At that unexpected moment, a white light showered Unrivaled Super Hottie. It was a Cleric’s Heal.

Chapter 597 – I’ll Be Leaving First Because I’ve Got Stuff to Do

Unrivaled Super Hottie crashed down with Heroic Leap. Compared to the free falling Dazzling Spring, who knew how much faster he dropped, it would be too late even if Zhang Jiale wanted to dodge. He could only curse a few times. Truthfully, he might have anticipated that this would happen, but the instant he jumped after being Provoked, he already knew that the situation was very bad.

It was true that as as God, he had the capability to dispel the taunt and switch directions in midair, but unfortunately, his opponent was also a God. His opponent wouldn’t be surprised that he could do it. In other words, when his opponent used Provoke, his opponent had already prepared to counter his next actions.

The Knight’s sword smashed into Dazzling Spring’s body. The displacement induced by the attack made it so that he missed his original landing spot, causing Dazzling Spring to continue to fall.

Zhang Jiale hastily looked for a possible landing spot, but Unrivaled Super Hottie unexpectedly continued to pressure him, following him downwards.

This guy!

Zhang Jiale was already aware that Ye Qiu wasn’t thinking about landing anywhere after hitting him down from his high point. Right now, Ye Qiu was planning on dragging him into the water.

As a result, everyone just watched as Unrivaled Super Hottie struck Dazzling Spring with a Heroic Leap and then dropped rapidly.

Unrivaled Super Hottie still had Knight’s Spirit activated. A streak of white light followed behind him like a shooting star. Dazzling Spring tried to escape from his predicament by attacking a few times, which just added to the splendor of the shooting star. However, his efforts were in vain. The two fell straight into the water, leaving behind a trace of their trajectory as well as a splash that hit the Blossom Valley players on the bridge.

Everyone was dumbfounded.

Most of the players were still thinking about the stealthy heal by Little Cold Hands, who had quickly been hit into the water by the enemy. Who would have thought that those two experts would suddenly fall into the water together?

The river was vast and extremely deep at the center. When the two experts hit the water, they were immediately swept away by the current like all the other players. The players still hadn’t registered what had just happened and stared dumbly at the fast flowing currents beneath the bridge until a huge fireball suddenly exploded on the bridge. Several Blossom valley players cried out as they tumbled into the water below. Only then did everyone wake up.

Even though the two experts had left, the North Bridge Mage was still there! Their true purpose was to fight for the boss, not watch two experts have a go at it.

But without Dazzling Spring, Blossom Valley had lost their foothold. Even though a portion of their players had grasped the high ground, how could they have the same level of control over the situation as Zhang Jiale? Let alone suppressing the onslaught of enemy players rushing onto the North Bridge, with Dazzling Spring gone, the North Bridge Mage’s was completely focused on them.

Because they had stayed on the bridge longer, the North Bridge Mage placed priority on them over the players who had just stepped onto the bridge. All sorts of spells flew towards the players from Blossom Valley. With their skill level, one mistake meant falling into the water. The terrain and the boss made it too difficult for them to save the situation. What’s more, the enemy guilds had suffered under Blossom Valley’s hands for the past two weeks. They had a tacit agreement to not fight against each other and first allied together to vent the frustration built up over the last two weeks on Blossom Valley’s players.

In an instant, the players from Blossom Valley turned into dumplings and were struck into the water. If a player was thrown into the water, it didn’t matter if the player died or not. The players from Blossom Valley were wiped clean. The North Bridge Mage no longer had too many targets left and fired spells randomly.

Everyone was feeling very excited.

What a familiar scene! This was what the fight for the North Bridge Mage should look like! The boss’ battle power wasn’t actually too frightening, but the hard part was the location.

One, it was too easy to find him. Two, the terrain was difficult, so the battle always turned into a huge mess.

Once the North Bridge Mage started casting spells randomly, players constantly fell into the water. No one was a stranger to this scene though. Everyone calmly faced the boss. Without the expert from Blossom Valley, everyone felt a hundred times more confident.

Only Jiang You was uneasy.

The North Bridge Mage was something Tyrannical Ambition needed. The formidable Dazzling Spring had been taken care of by Ye Qiu, but in this type of chaotic battle, no guild had an absolute grasp on victory. Tyrannical Ambition was no exception. At this moment, they needed a peak expert watching over in order to have a better chance.

Jiang You cautiously commanded his troops, while hastily asking Unrivaled Super Hottie for his situation. He hoped that Unrivaled Super Hottie hadn’t died and hopefully landed nearby, so that he could hurry up and return. This wasn’t impossible. In Glory, every character automatically knew how to swim, so they usually wouldn’t drown. However, once a player fell into the water, the current was too rapid, making it difficult for them to figure out their position in the water. If they couldn’t find the surface to replenish their air supply, wouldn’t they suffocate? In addition, there were all sorts of rocks in the water, which would deal damage if collided into. The faster the current the more damage the rocks dealt. Characters who fell into the water didn’t have much health to begin with. Before they could drink any potions, the rocks would kill them.

Ye Qiu was a God though, so Jiang You felt like he wouldn’t die because of these reasons. Normal players would panic and be unable to figure out their position, but a God shouldn’t have that problem, right?

As a result, Jiang You expected Unrivaled Super Hottie to have reached shore already. But then again, Dazzling Spring wasn’t a simple character either. He probably wouldn’t die in the river so easily either. If he came back to the battle, that would be troublesome too! Perhaps the two got out of the water at the same time and were fighting right now?

Who knew how many situations Jiang You had thought of already. Unrivaled Super Hottie soon returned a message. Jiang You hastily looked at it and coughed a mouthful of blood.

“I have stuff to do, so I’ll be leaving first. Good luck.”

What was this! What the f*ck was this? What do you mean you have stuff to do, so you’ll be leaving first? What’s more important than this wild boss? Jiang You was so angry, his hands were shaking. He replied: “The boss is such an important matter. You can’t just leave like that!”

“Brother, I’m still busy forming a new team. I don’t have the time to keep playing with you.” Unrivaled Super Hottie answered back, making Jiang You feel like his soul had parted with his body.

This guy wasn’t even trying to hide his identity anymore. If a spy revealed himself, it meant he had already completed his mission, so he didn’t care anymore, but the problem was that they knew his identity as a spy before, so why did he feel hurt after seeing his “I’m actually a spy” personality? In this type of situation, he should be saying “I already knew you were a spy.” It should have been a beautiful moment, so even though he knew, why couldn’t he say it?

“If I return, I won’t be there to help you fight for the boss, but rather to take the boss for myself. Are you sure you want me to come back?” Unrivaled Super Hottie followed up.

“See you later!” Jiang You decided.

“See you later?”

“I don’t want to see you ever again!” Jiang You changed his words.

“Ha ha ha :D” Unrivaled Super Hottie laughed and added a laughing emoji. Tears streaked down Jiang You’s face. Okay, there’s no point in placing any hope on him any longer. I should hurry up and lead my troops seriously. I have to win this boss with my own effort. Now that there were extraordinary experts causing chaos, it was up to each guild’s strength. They still had a chance.

So at this moment, Jiang You heard a firm voice coming from the other end of the North Bridge.

“Hold your positions! You have to hold your position! Protect the Cleric and send the Cleric forward!

“A Gunner go up with an Aerial Fire! You’re still not going up and you dare call yourself an expert??”

“There doesn’t need to be anyone over there! Thieves, just place a few traps!”

“Don’t just rush in there! Go around! Be a bit more dirtier and despicable, okay? Dude, you’re an Assassin. Why are you charging forward like you’re a Knight!!”

“Over there! Over there is over there! The f*cking enemies understand, but you don’t understand? Give coordinates? If I give coordinates, the enemies will also hear and it looks to me like the enemies respond faster than you dimwitted fools. You idiot. If you fall into the water, you’re dead. Tsk tsk tsk!”

Who was this guy!

His firm voice carried an unbelievable amount of confidence. All of the players gathered here were the elite experts of each guild and the top players of the Heavenly Domain. Even Jiang You wouldn’t have such confidence when talking to his troops. Just who was this guy?

Jiang You looked towards that direction, but he couldn’t identify the speaker. However, the other end of the North Bridge was gradually became more and more stable. The guild that had grasped the upper hand was Samsara.

Was it because of that person’s leading? Another unknown expert? Jiang You’s heart palpitated. He had a bad premonition. It felt like this fight for the boss would be another wasted effort…...

Not far from the North Bridge, on the surface of the river, a huge tree trunk was floating on top.

A wave rose up. There seemed to be someone inside. The instant the wave rose, a character suddenly jumped out and turned 180 degrees, landing on the tree trunk. When he landed, he held a gun in one hand and a grenade in the other hand. His gaze stared at the incoming wave. It was Dazzling Spring.

One second, two seconds, three seconds…….

Zhang Jiale didn’t loosen his guard. He knew that a certain someone wouldn’t die in the water like that. As he was swept along with the current, he hadn’t been able to find a suitable place to stand until now. There was no way that guy would be unable to get out of the current.

Right when he was thinking this, an abnormal movement came from the wave. Zhang Jiale immediately noticed it. He focused and a Knight burst out of the water. He held a sword in his hand and landed majestically on the tree trunk.

“The same thing again!!” Zhang Jiale saw Heroic Leap and shouted angrily. He fired his gun and threw his grenade at him.

“What are you talking about? If I didn’t use it, how else was I supposed to get up here?” The Knight said as he landed.

Chapter 598 – The Heart of a Champion

Zhang Jiale was slightly startled, but he quickly understood what had happened.

Knights were a heavy armor class, so they were affected by weight, which meant that their ability to jump couldn’t compare with leather armor classes like Spitfires. Moreover, Zhang Jiale intentionally picked equipment that would increase Dazzling Spring’s jump ability. It was easy for Dazzling Spring to jump from the water current onto the tree trunk. However, if one were a Knight, like Unrivalled Super Hottie, it would have been impossible to achieve this act with a simple jump. As a result, a Heroic Leap had to be used in order to jump out of the water and land on the tree trunk.

Even though Zhang Jiale already understood all of this, the attack had still come out. However, it was impossible for the knockback from a Spitfire’s attack to knock back a Knight, who was descending from a Heroic Leap. Unrivalled Super Hottie used his shield to defend himself when the attack hit, guaranteeing his position on the tree trunk. Zhang Jiale didn’t want Dazzling Spring to be shaken into the water, so he jumped away the moment the Heroic Leap descended. He pulled his gun out and fired another bullet, using Aerial Fire to cross the river and back onto land.

“Not bad, not bad.” Ye Xiu praised him as if he were a rookie. At the same time, Unrivalled Super Hottie walked along the tree trunk and back onto the river bank.

Zhang Jiale was still taking precautions. The muzzle of Dazzling Spring’s gun never left Unrivalled Super Hottie’s body from beginning to end.

“Enough, enough. Put the gun away. We’re done.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“What are you trying to do?!” Zhang Jiale was a little melancholy.

“Testing your skill.” Ye Xiu said.

“......”

“You would have died,” Zhang Jiale was speechless for a while before continuing. “If not for that cleric.”

“Hehe, that Holy Heal was quite brilliant, wasn’t it?” Ye Xiu spoke.

“If it was just a coincidence, then let it be; but if that was intentional, then it was indeed very brilliant. Who is that person?” Zhang Jiale asked.

“A player from Tyrannical Ambition.” Ye Xiu said.

“Player? Only a player? Just a normal player?” Zhang Jiale didn’t really believe it. To take advantage of the visual effect’s distraction to conceal his movements and to use Holy Heal at the pivotal moment, all of the observational skills and judgement required was reflected in those series of actions were practically at a pro player’s level. This person turned out to actually be a normal player.

“Exactly!” Ye Xiu said.

“What a talent!” Zhang Jiale spoke.

“Agreed.” Ye Xiu said.

“Wait……” All at once, Zhang Jiale suddenly thought of something. “You got this crappy Knight account and infiltrated Tyrannical Ambition just to find such a Cleric?”

“I don’t have any other choice left. The standards for you Gods are too high. Plus, you all lack foresight. I was left with no option but to unearth talented people from among the crowd. If I wanted to look for Clerics, wouldn’t it be best to start looking from Tyrannical Ambition?” Ye Xiu spoke.

Zhang Jiale expressed his agreement. This was like how there were more Battle Mages in Excellent Dynasty and more Spitfires in Blossom Valley. This effect was entirely because of the Gods. Fans worshipped a God because of that God’s class. Fans supported teams because they worshipped these Gods. Then in the game, they would strive to join their favorite team’s guild.

As for Tyrannical Ambition, their team Tyranny possessed two Gods, Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie, so among their guild members, the ratio for the classes of Striker and Cleric were relatively high, so their Strikers and Clerics were generally better than those of other guilds. To find a skilled Cleric, it would be quite logical to start from Tyrannical Ambition.

“So you got this Knight because the Knight is a tank class and, in a dungeon group, there’s no other class that knows a Cleric better than a tank. And you finally found a Cleric using this method?” Zhang Jiale said.

“Mhmm, that’s right.” Ye Xiu said.

“How long did you spend?” Zhang Jiale asked.

“A little over two weeks!” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Not bad. Your luck is quite good.” Zhang Jiale said.

“Hahaha, you want to talk with me about luck?” Ye Xiu spoke.

Zhang Jiale turned gloomy. With the nickname of “unluckiest God in the league”, luck was indeed his ultimate weakness.

“Where is that guy?” Zhang Jiale changed topics. He was quite curious as to the whereabouts of the expert Cleric.

Unrivalled Super Hottie’s view switched towards the rapid river. After a long while, Ye Xiu said. “He probably drowned.”

“Cough, what?” Zhang Jiale didn’t fall into the river, but he still choked. “Drowned?” He didn’t dare to believe that the Cleric, with such exceptional judgement and observation, would drown. Zhang Jiale felt that it was more likely for Ye Xiu and him to drown on this tree trunk.

“Hey, if he really was exceptional in every aspect with absolutely no weaknesses, then how would I be able to uncover him? He would have been discovered long ago and taken to who knows where by someone else much earlier on.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what exactly is the weakness of this expert that covered up his excellent talent?” Zhang Jiale said.

“According to my initial observations, he has good judgement and a good grasp of time. However, his mechanics are fairly ordinary. He also reacts slowly in complicated situations.” Ye Xiu spoke.

Zhang Jiale thought for a while before he expressed his agreement towards the circumstances that he understood so far: “Such a weakness wouldn’t have affected his earlier play. However, if he’s in a dungeon team, it really does cover up his strengths, but are you really sure that his performance wasn’t just a coincidence?”

“I’m sure, especially after that last performance.” Ye Xiu said.

“Did you just use me as your lab rat?” Zhang Jiale said.

“Look at how you’re phrasing it.” Ye Xiu said. “I was just using you to test how qualified he was.”

“......”

“As for you, why are you helping Blossom Valley so much with these bosses? What are you doing? Are you repenting?” Ye Xiu joked.

“Yup.” Zhang Jiale unexpectedly expressed his agreement.

“You……”

“I owe them.” Zhang Jiale sounded a bit pitiful.

When Ye Xiu heard him speak in such way, he was startled: “You’re not planning on returning to Team Hundred Blossoms?”

Zhang Jiale didn’t reply, but had basically answered without replying. If he planned on returning, then there was nothing to be embarrassed about by answering. It was precisely because he wasn’t planning on returning that he couldn’t say the answer aloud.

He used to be Team Hundred Blossom’s captain and ace player. His lack of responsibility in his retirement process already drew a lot of criticism. If he returned and didn’t choose his previous team under the hopeful eyes of Team Hundred Blossom’s fans, Ye Xiu could easily imagine what sort of condemnation Zhang Jiale would have to face from the public.

But if he would rather bear such pressure, which team would he end up choosing?

Ye Xiu predicted that the answer wasn’t so simple. From the current look of Zhang Jiale’s expression of regret, he wouldn’t return to Team Hundred Blossoms, not because he was feeling embarrassed from his sudden retirement, but because after already letting down Team Hundred Blossoms once, he was going to abandon the team again.

What was it for?

Of course it was the championship victory that he had seeked but failed to get for all these years. This time, for the sake of the championship, Zhang Jiale would spare no expense and would gamble everything he had. One could imagine how much hope and expectation he was filled with this time. For that championship victory, even if he received it, it would be filled with controversy. Perhaps even the radiance of winning the championship wouldn’t cover his actions of abandoning Team Hundred Blossoms twice.

Did his recent interaction with Zhang Jiale make the decision even more painful?

Ye Xiu didn’t think so. This was because in Ye Xiu’s eyes, the emotions that he had triggered were mostly memories of the past, which would make him feel unsubmissive and unwilling to leave. As someone who needed to start over again, Ye Xiu couldn’t give Zhang Jiale much hope. He didn’t have anything that would make him gamble everything. When he asked Zhang Jiale to join him, Ye Xiu could only say it in a half-joking manner. After all, Zhang Jiale was different from Wei Chen. If he wanted to come back from retirement, even Ye Xiu felt that he wouldn’t need to explain anything if he wanted to return to Team Hundred Blossoms.

But now, Zhang Jiale was obviously making a bold decision. Ye Xiu couldn’t imagine Zhang Jiale cooperating with him. His reason was explained above. His team didn’t have the weight to give Zhang Jiale a reason to make such a sacrifice. Ye Xiu believed that there would only be one thing that could make Zhang Jiale make such a vital decision and that would be the championships.

Of course, there was no such team that would win the championships immediately after he joined, but the team would have to be one where Zhang Jiale could see boundless potential. This team would definitely not be like Ye Xiu’s where he had to run around in the guilds of the online game to choose if there were any people with talents left unnoticed. This team would definitely let a person see the cover and immediately think: the championship was theirs.

Which one would it be?

Tiny Herb? Blue Rain? Tyranny?

Or would it be Samsara? Misty Rain? Void?

Or even the current Excellent Era?

With a God like Zhang Jiale suddenly joining any of these teams would make anyone feel that the team was abnormally strong, so Ye Xiu, at this time, really couldn’t guess which team it would be. Zhang Jiale obviously wouldn’t tell him either. A figure like him joining would normally involve a team-swapping storm. To even allow Ye Xiu to know that he would come out of retirement but wouldn’t return to Hundred Blossoms was already a very hot piece of gossip for the news. Just by leaking this piece of news would be enough to have the media pursue and argue until the competition season ended.

“Good luck……” Ye Xiu wholeheartedly blessed him. For the sake of the championships, Zhang Jiale could even make such a decision. Although he was currently a little ashamed to face it, Ye Xiu believed that he would overcome this mentality. This was because the heart of a champion should never be viewed lightly. This wasn’t to show-off, but for glory. The glory that hung high in every pro gamer’s hearts and eyes. The glory that had been commented as addictive by Ye Xiu.

“I must have good luck!” Zhang Jiale didn’t return the blessing to Ye Xiu, but instead carried on Ye Xiu’s words and gave himself an additional blessing halo again.

“Okay, I will continue fighting for the boss!” Zhang Jiale’s spirit was raised.

“The people from Blossom Valley have probably been wiped out.” Ye Xiu spoke. He now understood why Zhang Jiale was currently madly helping Blossom Valley to fight. Perhaps it was to take away some of the guilt left in his heart, or maybe because it was to use whatever method he had left to do something for Hundred Blossoms. Ye Xiu didn’t need to ask which the actual reason was.

“It doesn’t matter. After a player dies, they can immediately return. This is one part of the game that I like over the competitive scene.” Zhang Jiale said.

“Then I hope you succeed!” Ye Xiu said.

“How about you? You won’t come back?”

“Me? I’ve already reached my goal. I will let the boss be for now!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh…… then I will also need to bless for your wish to be fulfilled. I hope that fellow will completely meet your requirements and also not despise you as a God from Excellent Era, hahaha.” Zhang Jiale said such, while his Dazzling Spring had already turned around and sprinted back toward the North Bridge.

Chapter 599 – Proceed With Care

He did all this just to find a Cleric!

Chen Guo had only just learned Ye Xiu’s goal in infiltrating Tyrannical Ambition. After she moved over to hear the conversation between the two Gods, she realized how everything came together.

However, the issue Zhang Jiale brought up before he left was indeed a problem. How could they get a person they had just met to enter their own team?

While Chen Guo was still thinking about this issue, she suddenly found Ye Xiu looking at her.

“What are you looking at?” Chen Guo asked.

“You should deal with this matter.” Ye Xiu said.

“What matter?” Chen Guo asked.

“The matter of getting that Cleric to join our guild.” Ye Xiu said.

“What?! Why me?! I don’t even know that person!” Chen Guo said.

“Does it matter whether you know that person or not? Just say that you admire his abilities and you just so happen to be recruiting for a team, so you would like to ask if he’s interested.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is it that simple?” Chen Guo was uncertain.

“Otherwise?” Ye Xiu asked in reply.

Chen Guo thought about it: true, if anyone wanted to invite a person to join them, wouldn’t they just directly ask them? Chen Guo gave a guess and felt like the possibility of success was quite high. This was because a normal player yearned to be a pro. As long as you didn’t pop out and say something weird like: “Hey bro, your bones are marvellous. Did you know that there’s some sort of spiritual aura spurting out from your ID?” Otherwise, most players would be interested in something like joining a team.

“Okay then. I’ll try to get in touch with him.” Chen Guo agreed. She was always active in helping with things that were related to the formation of the team. There was no reason for her to be making excuses when there was something for her to do. Boss Chen wasn’t that reserved.

“What’s that person’s ID?” Chen Guo asked, as she logged onto her Heavenly Domain account.

“Little Cold Hands。” Ye Xiu spoke.

Chen Guo had been watching from the side, so didn’t actually notice Little Cold Hands. She only knew that he was able to use Holy Heal at such a crucial time to turn the tables. Then after that, Ye Xiu followed up by controlling Unrivaled Super Hottie to knock Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Spring into the water. In fact, it wasn’t just Chen Guo, even Zhang Jiale didn’t know this Cleric’s name.

After logging onto Chasing Haze, Chen Guo searched for the character’s name. The information came out very quickly and she was immediately surprised: “Wait, she’s a girl?” When Chen Guo first heard the ID, she thought the name Little Cold Hands was pretty feminine. Now that the character appeared, it was actually a female avatar.

“Ahem……” Ye Xiu coughed with a strange expression.

“This Cleric doesn’t happen to be a male playing as a female, right?” Chen Guo noticed the oddity.

“You’ve got incredible foresight.” Ye Xiu said.

“What sort of person is he?” Chen Guo was astonished. This was because there were seldom players in Glory who played with avatars of the opposite gender for their character. After all, Glory’s voice communication was a part of the game, so it was the universal method of communication. It wouldn’t be pleasing to one’s eyes nor ears when a character had a beautiful and charming name, while they constantly spoke out in a rugged, masculine voice.

“Nothing really. Apparently, the account was given to him and he was just too lazy to care about the gender, so he just played with it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.” Chen Guo replied.

Seldom does not represent none at all. In the end, there were many male players who played female characters and the same went for Glory. The reasons were strange and unimaginable, but a reason like playing on a given account was pretty rational and reasonable.

“Never mind, I don’t discriminate against those types of players.” Chen Guo said while she was already preparing to add him as a friend.

“Hang on, hang on. What are you planning on doing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Add him as a friend and invite him join our group!” Chen Guo said.

“Add him as a friend and just say: “Yo bro, I’ve been admiring your strength for a long time, would you like to form a team with me?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo stared blankly. True, if she added him as a friend, how would she start the conversation? Little Cold Hands wasn’t a pro player. If she just added him as a friend from out of the blue and directly asked him to join, it would feel like stopping someone on the street and say: “Hey bro, your bones are marvellous” or whatever; She would most likely be treated as a scammer.

“For now, you need to actually get in touch with him and show that you’ve seen his talents. Then, you can naturally recruit him, right?” Ye Xiu said on the side.

Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu. She suddenly felt that, if she directly added that person as a friend and tried to recruit him immediately, he probably wouldn’t buy into their trickery. Only if she did what Ye Xiu told her could that person be convinced.

True, for no particular reason at all, Chen Guo suddenly had a feeling of “tricking”.

“Say, why don’t you do it?” Chen Guo felt that Ye Xiu had other reasons for making her go alone.

“Ahem, aren’t I doing this to avoid arousing suspicion? See, Zhang Jiale even said it before he left, to be aware that he might despise my identity. If I just went and directly said, ‘I’m Ye Qiu. Come with me.’ What if I only end up being spit in the face? Therefore, it’s better if you do it!” Ye Xiu said.

“Wouldn’t he still have to interact with you afterwards anyways?” Chen Guo said.

“Yes, but just say that I also happened to be roped in on the side of the road!” Ye Xiu said.

“What nonsense.” Chen Guo threw her mouse. She felt that Ye Xiu just threw aside something nonsensical for her to do.

“Well he is a fan of Tyranny. With my identity and background, we can’t be careless in handling this matter.” Ye Xiu said.

“Tyrannical Ambition. He doesn’t have to be a Tyranny fan, right?” Chen Guo said.

“I said so because I have a certain level of understanding towards him.” Ye Xiu said.

“To what degree do you know him?” Chen Guo asked.

“Well, he’s a Tyranny fan. He’s an hardcore fan of Zhang Xinjie.” Ye Xiu said. “Apparently.”

“Apparently?”

“Yup, maybe he was bragging?” Ye Xiu said.

“Does he have a need to brag about that?” Chen Guo really wanted to pull Ye Xiu’s ear over to give a good growl.

“To sum it up, I think it’s more reliable if you’re the person to get in touch with him.” Ye Xiu said.

“Aren’t you a little irresponsible to fool somebody like this!” Chen Guo said.

“Look, you’re essentially the team’s manage. Recruiting team members is also a part of your responsibilities. Your formed team has me and also him. It’s something decided by you as the boss. Do we, the members, have any right to be picky? You should have this kind of working attitude. Don’t just be a fan and think like a fan.” Ye Xiu lectured her.

Chen Guo was stupefied after being lectured. She only started to regain her senses after a long while: “Are you lecturing your boss?”

“I wouldn’t dare. I wouldn’t dare.” Ye Xiu hastily noted.

“What do I do if he doesn’t agree?” Chen Guo asked.

“Then….... We can only take a step and make plans for the next. There’s nothing we can do if he truly doesn’t want to join our team.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Uh, I think the problem isn’t too big. If a normal Glory player is offered something like being in a pro team, the player shouldn’t have any over conflicting sentiments.” Chen Guo could see the expression of regret on Ye Xiu’s face and thought about the hardships of forming a team, so she started to comfort him.

“I hope so.” Ye Xiu said.

After the two finished discussing, Chen Guo prepared to take action. She grabbed her mouse, but held it in the air.

“If I don’t add him as a friend, how do I get in touch with him?” Chen Guo asked.

“Oh.” Ye Xiu nodded, on his side, he sent a message to Little Cold Hands: “Where are you?”

“I just drowned, so I’m currently heading back to the North Bridge! What’s happening over there?” Little Cold Hands.

“Look.” Ye Xiu showed his screen to Chen Guo.

Chen Guo was speechless. Sometimes, things really were that simple.

Unrivaled Super Hottie withdrew from the North Bridge mage boss fight, while Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze disguised as a passerby.

Upon arriving at the North Bridge, the battle proceeded with many highlights.

After wiping out Blossom Valley, each guild took a position on the battlefield on either ends of the Northern Bridge. All the major guilds were fighting in a huge mess.

On the eastern head of the bridge, Samsara had grasped a slight upper hand. The players had gradually gotten ahold of the advantageous terrain on their side. The long-ranged classes took the high ground, while the support and control classes were in the middle and the melee classes at the bottom. Samsara’s tactics were clear and incomparable. They sufficiently took advantage of the condition of the North Bridge’s terrain. Their positions were not only divided between the front and the back. They also had the upper, middle, and bottom paths as well. All of these arrangements had been organized by a rough commander with a loud voice and high spirit.

As for the western end of the bridge, it was still a mess. It was hard for any of the guilds to seize the upper hand. However, the resulting position of Samsara at the eastern end gave some train of thought to the guilds on the western end. All of the big guilds started to imitate without understanding the true substance, but the problem was that this train of thought was given to everyone, so it resulted in a position where everyone was in a deadlock.

Jiang You was worried! Very worried.

He was worried by both the state of this competition over the boss and over Unrivaled Super Hottie’s unhurried exit from the battle.

He wanted to calm down. He reminded himself to calm down, but his heart wouldn’t calm down. He was unable to seriously observe the current situation and carry out a wise, strategic decision. He couldn’t help but have the silhouette of Unrivaled Super Hottie float up from the bottom of his heart. This fellow had infiltrated their guild for two weeks and during the two weeks of hard labor, Jiang You couldn’t figure out his aim at all, but then he just suddenly announced his leave and meant it. He didn’t seem to be snatching the boss, and had just left it hanging there. The last thing he ever did was to jump romantically into the water with Dazzling Spring…...

What sort of evildoing did that fellow do?

Jiang You didn’t believe that Ye Qiu only came to their guild to stride around idly. This guy was a God afterall. Why would he use up his time for such leisure? Also, between the lines of his later messages, Jiang You had a sort of feeling that: it wasn’t because Ye Qiu was leaving that he didn’t care about his identity being revealed. It felt as if he wasn’t afraid of being suspected right from the beginning.

To be completely unafraid to have himself revealed, were all Gods this arrogant when they became spies? But why would his aim be hidden so deeply, so much that they couldn’t see a hint at all? What changes did Tyrannical Ambition go through during the few weeks when Unrivaled Super Hottie mingled with them?

Jiang You felt that the problem must have been hidden within. However, apart from gratifying changes, such as having many of their groups surpassing their progress in dungeons for the past few weeks, it seemed as if there was no bad effects to worry about at all.

Was the evildoing hidden among the good things?

Jiang You couldn’t help himself but to keep thinking about these questions, how could he make clear commands? Originally, Tyrannical Ambition was determined to get this boss, so the troop arrangement set out for today was arrogant, but under Jiang You’s absent-minded commands, they had fallen into a pitiful deadlock. When they were pushed to the point where they had no alternatives left, a shadow suddenly joined the fight and started a massacre. That person came in an unstoppable manner as if he didn’t care about the guilds at all.

The shadow opened up a path through the crowd. Some died, while some remained alive, but he was already gone. After a few rises and falls, he instantly snatched the high ground!

Dazzling Spring!!

He’s back!

Chapter 600 – First Contact

No one thought that Dazzling Spring would return so quickly and massacre in such a tyrannical manner.

He killed his way through the crowd. Once he seized the high ground, he began blasting away once more. At this moment, there were no other players from Blossom Valley on the North Bridge apart from himself. Dazzling Spring didn’t have any helpers this time.

Even though it was like this, his killing made Jiang You’s group want to jump into the river one after another.

Dazzling Spring didn’t wait for them to respond as he climbed higher and higher. On the other hand, they had been fighting hard for so long, yet they still hadn’t been able to seize any high points. Dazzling Spring strolled along alone and seized, under their gaze, the most beautiful spot on the bridge.

Jiang You and the other guild leaders all had one thought in mind: why did this b*stard choose our end of the bridge and not the other end?

Zhang Jiale wasn’t only limited to this end of the bridge though. After taking the high ground, he glanced in the other direction. He was shocked when he looked.

Judging by the position of the Samsara tags on everyone, Samsara’s troops were arranged in a beautiful formation.

It seemed that it would be a bit difficult to deal with?

Zhang Jiale had this thought, but he didn’t hesitate. He bravely rushed towards Samsara’s troops…...

By the time Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze reached the North Bridge, the battle had become indescribably chaotic.

Compared to Dazzling Spring’s attacks against Samsara, the messy entanglement between Tyrannical Ambition and the other guilds at the bridge’s western end was like a childish bore. Even they felt a little bit embarrassed for themselves.

The level of skill involved in the battles on the two ends of the bridges weren’t on the same level.

It was like how Unrivaled Super Hottie had challenged Blossom Valley on his own before, making everyone realize that it was a fight between two experts.

Only this time, the solo challenger was Dazzling Spring.

As for Samsara, a loud voice continued to command their troops.

The guilds present all knew each other’s background. They interacted with each other numerous times a week. No one in Samsara had this kind of voice. The voice didn’t belong to their guild leader Three Realms Six Paths or any of the senior figures in the guild.

Just who was this person?

Because of the chaos, no one was able to identify their commander. Otherwise, the guilds on the bridge’s eastern end would have attempted to get rid of this person as quickly as possible, no matter what the sacrifice. This person’s importance to Samsara was unrivaled.

As for his arrangements, even an expert like Dazzling Spring was having trouble against them.

However, Zhang Jiale was still a God.

After a few probing attacks, Zhang Jiale exploded into his Hundred Blossoms style. He leapt onto the bridge and headed across in a certain direction.

Everyone had turned towards Dazzling Spring long ago. They quickly caught the direction Dazzling Spring was charging towards. A Warlock was jumping up and down, trying to dodge Dazzling Spring’s attacks.

However, Dazzling Spring refused to comply. This time, it was as if he was determined to sacrifice everything to kill this Warlock.

Could that Warlock be the commander?

They had to help! This would be a crucial moment!

All the guilds that had been beaten down by Samsara’s formations were filled with vigor all of a sudden.

They hadn’t retreated yet, which naturally meant that they hadn’t completely given up yet. Seeing Dazzling Spring’s offense, they felt like it was the perfect opportunity to turn the tides. As a result, the guilds ignored everything else and began assisting Dazzling Spring to kill off the Warlock.

“F*ck!!!”

Everyone heard the loud voice curse.

A crazy assault, without regard for anything else, was very hard to defend against. Even more so with an expert killer like Dazzling Spring joining in.

Just when everyone thought that this Warlock would die, he actually leapt into the water before the attacks arrived.

Yes, he ran away!

Jumping into the water before being struck by any of the attacks was an act of escape.

In the world of gaming, where lives were as inexpensive as paper, in an intense battle like fighting for a boss, a character, who seemed to be the commander, actually chose to run away. At that instant, everyone paled. This behavior lacked any sense of shame and was utterly wretched. It was something even a noob wouldn’t do! The Warlock’s actions made everyone deeply shocked.

The players present couldn’t help but remember a phrase that loud voice often said: “Could you be a bit dirtier??”

Yes, you could! You really could! You’re too much!

At such a time, several players even had a disdainful emoji popping above their character’s heads. There were even Samsara players who did it and similarly despised such shameful actions.

At this moment, a God’s temperament needed to be talked about.

This direct move didn’t distract Zhang Jiale at all. Being dirty was a type of strategy. As a God, he need to be able to adapt to any situation. When he saw the Warlock jumping down into the water, Zhang Jiale immediately had Dazzling Spring switch targets. Almost at the exact same time that the Warlock jumped into the water, Dazzling Spring sent several nearby Samsara players into the water to keep him company.

Samsara’s formation was instantly broken. The players from the other guilds regained their composure and hastily hit Samsara while they were down. On the other hand, Dazzling Spring left. After seizing the high ground a third time, he began attacking randomly again. He wanted to control both ends of the bridge. Everyone else was itching to drag him down and kill him, but they didn’t have ability to do so.

The North Bridge’s unique terrain was like an aquatic battle. Normal players couldn’t deal with it, so even though Zhang Jiale was by himself, he could easily make the guilds want to flip a table.

When Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze arrived, she missed the utterly wretched escape into the water. She didn’t care much about the fight for the boss. Her only mission was to search for the ID “Little Cold Hands”.

Even though she knew his name, it wasn’t easy finding a single player in such chaos. Chen Guo didn’t dare to approach the battle too carelessly either. Fighting for a wild boss was a sensitive subject. If a bystander didn’t keep their distance, it was possible they would be suspected of trickery and be killed.

Chen Guo had Chasing Haze go around in a wide arc, but she couldn’t find Little Cold Hands. When she turned her head around, she noticed that Ye Xiu was looking at her screen and she hurriedly asked him if he saw Little Cold Hands.

“Nope.” Ye Xiu also shook his head. His eyesight was keener than Chen Guo’s, but he wasn’t able to find any traces of Little Cold Hands either.

“He wouldn’t be on the other side, would he?” Chen Guo said as she looked towards the other end of the bridge. It was the position where Samsara and the other guilds had set up their front. Because of the distance, it was impossible to read the names clearly.

“It shouldn’t be possible!” Ye Xiu said.

Tyrannical Ambition’s position was on this side. If he ran off to the other side just for fun, then his judgement would be very disappointing.

“Maybe he hasn’t arrived yet?” Chen Guo controlled Chasing Haze to go around in another circle, but she still wasn’t able to locate him.

“Wait wait. Turn your view to the right, turn, turn again.” Ye Xiu spoke.

Chen Guo’s mouse moved bit by bit.

“Stop, there’s a person over there.” Ye Xiu pointed to Chen Guo’s screen at a tree not too far away from where they stood.

“Really?” Chen Guo hadn’t noticed. She had mainly been searching the people in the crowd. She didn’t even notice the tree.

“Is it him?” Chen Guo asked.

“I don’t know.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll go take a look.” Chen Guo didn’t have anything else to do, so she went to look behind the tree.

After adjusting her view, she saw a person behind the tree. Chen Guo immediately had Chasing Haze walk closer and quickly saw her target.

A female Cleric with the ID: Little Cold Hands.

“It’s him.” Chen Guo was happy. She was about to walk up, but she suddenly stopped after a few steps.

Who knew when this Little Cold Hands had come to this spot, but he wasn’t moving. He was just hiding behind the tree, looking at who knows what. How would she be able to persuade him? She couldn’t just say: Bro, your peeping skills are peerless. I’m planning on creating a team. Come with me and I’ll unlock your full peeping potential!

It sounded so sketchy!

Chen Guo was thinking and she unconsciously had Chasing Haze come to a stop.

Maybe she could say that she saw his excellent healing skills on Unrivaled Super Hottie, so she was interested in having a chat with him, but to show such admiration only based on a single move might make her come off as a scammer?

Chen Guo couldn’t think of how to introduce herself, so she didn’t have Chasing Haze go up yet. She turned her head to look at Ye Xiu: “What is he doing?”

Ye Xiu also shook his head. He wasn’t familiar with Little Cold Hands to the point where he could predict his thoughts.

At this time, Little Cold Hands turned his view and saw a stupefied Chasing Haze.

Seeing how she had been spotted, Chen Guo thought for a moment before deciding to let Chasing Haze go forward. Little Cold Hands didn’t run away, but rather she just stood under the tree, staring at Chasing Haze.

“Hello.” When their distance seemed about right, Chen Guo gave a greeting.

“Hi.” He replied. Originally, it would have been unsettling to hear a masculine voice coming from a female Cleric. However, even though this person’s voice was also masculine, his one-syllable reply felt as if it had some softness in it. The person’s voice and the character’s looks weren’t as conflicting as Chen Guo had imagined it would be.

So strange…… Chen Guo thought quietly in her mind.

“I saw you before.” This was the introduction Chen Guo had thought of.

“Oh?”

“Before on the bridge, that Holy Heal of yours was brilliant.” Chen Guo continued.

“Ha ha, it was alright!” His modest tone gave Chen Guo a good impression of him.

“If you don’t mind me asking, that wasn’t a coincidence, was it?” Chen Guo said.

“Ha ha, there was a bit of luck involved.” Little Cold Hands said.

“Then from what you’re saying, you’re a pretty skilled player!” Chen Guo said.

“I’m just so-so!”

“So it’s like this. I’m planning on forming a pro team and I’m looking for a Cleric. Are you interested in joining?” Chen Guo said.

“Oh? Ye Qiu’s team?” Little Cold Hands asked.

Chapter 601 – Many Questions

Little Cold Hands was direct. He didn’t try to beat around the bush and asked for the truth. This truth was what Ye Xiu had wanted to hide and was why Ye Xiu had Chen Guo deal with this matter instead of doing it himself. However, they were exposed from the beginning. Chen Guo instantly felt embarrassed. She couldn’t bring herself to answer him at the moment, so she turned her head and looked at Ye Xiu.

“What happened?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We’ve been seen through.” Chen Guo said.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu didn’t seem to be too surprised. “So what did he say?”

“It’s my turn to talk now.” Chen Guo said.

“Then say what you need to say!” Ye Xiu said.

Then Chen Guo also showed the brisk side of her and happily admitted: “Yes.”

”Oh, then this team has some weight to it.” Little Cold Hands said.

Chen Guo was confused for a moment. When she first mentioned that “Holy Heal”, this fellow appeared to be quite humble, but this sentence sort of implied that he thought of himself very highly. How could someone say something like Ye Qiu’s team only had “some weight to it”.

“Was that Unrivaled Super Hottie, Ye Qiu?” The more Little Cold Hands asked, the deeper he got.

Chen Guo turned around to look at Ye Xiu: “He’s asking about Unrivaled Super Hottie!”

Ye Xiu nodded his head, so Chen Guo answered with another: “Yes.”

“What was his aim for sneaking into Tyrannical Ambition?” Little Cold Hands continued to ask.

He was currently speaking in an arrogant tone. As for Chen Guo, she was the type who could be persuaded by reason, but not coerced. When Little Cold Hands was being humble and polite, she had a good impression on him, but now that he suddenly acted all haughty, she immediately felt unhappy. If she continued to say that Ye Xiu did that just to find a Cleric and picked him, wouldn’t it please him to death? As a result, Chen Guo decided to just blab: “No particular reason. He just wanted to play on a side account to sharpen his skills.”

“To sharpen his skills? With Ye Qiu’s level, what skills could he need to sharpen by joining an average team in a guild?” Little Cold Hands was able to see through the lie with ease. Chen Guo felt gloomy and found Ye Xiu continuously shaking his head beside her, expressing his disdain towards her lie.

“In short, we think your skills are quite good. What do you think? Are you interested in joining us?” Chen Guo didn’t care, because truthfully, she favored the frank and blunt method. If he was interested in joining, then he could join. If not, he didn’t have to. It would be over and done with. If a clear and straightforward answer was given, why would there be a need to chit-chat anymore? In any case, everything had been exposed.

“If he really is Ye Qiu, then I do have some interest.” Little Cold Hands spoke, “But you’re not just borrowing his name to bluff me, are you?”

Chen Guo could see that he was starting to doubt her and wanted to faint. However, in the end, this was still official business, so she didn’t directly show her fearlessness and patiently continued: “It’s true. Didn’t you guess correctly from the start?”

“Then where is he? Why didn’t he come to find me himself?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“It’s because he was afraid that you’re a Tyranny fan, so you might not like him because of his background as the God from Excellent Era.” Chen Guo spoke the truth.

“Oh, that’s true, but it wasn’t very wise to send you because a lot of people know about your relationship with Ye Qiu!” Little Cold Hands said.

“Yes yes yes. We were too careless, but now that you already know about it, how about you give us a definite answer about whether or not you’re interested in joining!” Chen Guo said.

“How could my decision be so easy?” Little Cold Hands was very shocked. “If I joined Ye Qiu, then I wouldn’t just be playing around for fun anymore, no? The goal would be the Pro Alliance, wouldn’t it? With the championships as the goal, it means I’d have to become a pro player, right? This is an important decision that could affect the rest of my life. Do you think I’d just be able to casually throw out an answer in a few seconds?”

The long chain of rhetorical questions made Chen Guo speechless. After a long while, she powerlessly said: “Then you can think about it. You can give me an answer anytime you’d like.”

“You’re just going to leave me like this?” Little Cold Hands continued to be surprised.

“Then what do you want?” Chen Guo asked.

“You should at least introduce your future plans and your current situation, right? For example, the other team members apart from Ye Qiu. For example, how much financial backing does your team have? What’s the direction and aim of the team’s development? What would be my compensation and salary be? How many years would I have to sign for in the contract? Are there three insurances and one fund or five insurances and one fund? Does your team provide food and housing accommodations?” Little Cold Hands continued with another chain of questions.

This time, Chen Guo didn’t feel upset. She also realized that what she was discussing with Little Cold Hands was indeed a very serious and important issue. On the other hand, she was recruiting him like how she would for a dungeon party in the game.

“Okay!” Chen Guo hurriedly hastily corrected her attitude, “As for our team, Ye Qiu will be the captain. We’re currently in the preparatory phase. We will be signing up for the Challenger League next season and fighting for qualifications into the Pro League. As for our members, we’re still in the middle of recruiting them. As for the investment, I’m currently the investor. As for salary, if you intend to join the team, then we can sit down and discuss it, are you satisfied?”

“Oh? You’re the investor? Namely…...the boss?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Pretty much!” Chen Guo answered with a bit of guilt because she realized more and more that it wouldn’t be an easy thing to support a team in the current Glory league. She wasn’t confident that she could really support the team all by herself.

“Pretty much? What does that even mean?” Little Cold Hands grasped this point.

“Currently, I’m the only investor.” Chen Guo said.

“You mean that in the future, someone else could become a shareholder, or do you mean that you aren’t completely sure about the issue, so you gave a vague answer?” Little Cold Hands said.

“Okay! I’m not sure. We’re currently in the preparatory stage of creating the team, so there are a lot of questions that we’re still figuring out.” Chen Guo said.

“Also, you mentioned that your team would be getting the qualifications into the Pro League through the Challenger League? From the looks of it, your resources are very limited and you don’t have confidence in any of the other paths to the Pro League, but for the Challenger League, even if we have a God like Ye Qiu, we can’t be sure that we would definitely reach the end. After all, in the Challenger League, there will be two eliminated pro teams joining too, right? Under these circumstances, what would the contract for our wages say? Would our contract have a clause saying it’s half-professional? That if we happen to win our way into the Pro League through the Challenger League, the contract would automatically change into a full professional contract? If the team fails, the contract would automatically be terminated and everyone can just return home and do whatever?

Little Cold Hands threw out a mountain of questions once again. These were all things that Chen Guo had never thought about before. She was unable to ward off the blows at the moment. After hesitating for a long while, she gave another vague answer: “We’re still thinking about these issues. We can discuss the specifics once everyone has gathered together.”

“Oh look, another uncertainty! You really are unsure toward all the issues. Don’t tell me that you’re planning to say if I have any intentions on joining, then I should give you around three to five hundred yen as a deposit? If that’s the case, then I don’t have any other doubts toward your identity.” Little Cold Hands said.

“Of course not……” Chen Guo was gloomy, but she couldn’t bring herself to blame him because their team still lacked a decent and proper plan. Chen Guo was unsure about what Ye Xiu was planning, so she really couldn’t say anything. She was afraid that Little Cold Hands would ask more questions right now, so she firmly raised the white flag: “Actually, Ye Qiu is the one mainly responsible with creating the team. How about I have him find you to talk about all of this!”

“Don’t tell me, you don’t have any thoughts of your own? You’re that careless of an investor? Are you throwing everything to Ye Qiu to do? Could it be that he’s your relative?” Little Cold Hands still continued to ask.

“Ask him, ask him……” Chen Guo could only say these words. She ruthlessly pulled Ye Xiu over from beside her. “You talk to him!”

“Talk about what?” Ye Xiu asked.

“The team’s plans, the members of the team, our financial backing, if he needs to sign a contract, sign what sort of contract, if he gets three insurances and one fund, does it cover food and housing, and also, if I’m your relative.” Chen Guo summarized everything emotionlessly. She was about to go crazy.

“Ha ha ha, this fellow has done a lot of thinking!” Ye Xiu laughed, while taking Chen Guo’s headphones.

“Just hang it over there! I want to listen too.” Chen Guo said.

“Why don’t you just put it on speaker? It wouldn’t be as exhausting for you.” Ye Xiu said.

“And I was afraid of it being too noisy!” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu held the mic near his mouth and said: “Hello, hello?”

“Ye Qiu?” The other side asked.

“It’s me, it’s me. I’ve heard that you have a lot of questions!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yup, my first question is to confirm that you’re the one who picked me and not that foolish lady who spoke earlier?” Little Cold Hands said.

Ye Xiu gazed innocently at Chen Guo, who sat beside him. To his surprise, Chen Guo didn’t seem to have the energy to be angry because Chen Guo felt pretty stupid about her responses to Little Cold Hands.

“Yes, I was the one who found you. Moreover, that ‘foolish lady is not my relative. She’ll be our boss.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? She’s so stupid. Her money must be easy to swindle, right? Is that why you chose her as your investor?” Little Cold Hands said.

“I forgot to tell you. She can hear our conversation right now.” Ye Xiu had to say.

“......” Little Cold Hands, who had kept on asking questions, finally became silent. He then started said: “Hello boss, I hope that after you heard the reminders I gave you, you should be more aware of the risks that the Challenger League holds and to be cautious in investing.”

“Thank you.” Chen Guo’s face was covered in tears.

“Then let's get to business, please tell me about the current state of this team!” Little Cold Hands said.

“The situation is just as boss said. It’s currently filled with uncertainties. If we can’t assemble enough members before the Challenger League starts, then everything will just be for nothing.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is this your main concern right now?” Little Cold Hands said.

“Indeed.”

“Even if we managed to form a team, how can you be so certain about the Challenger League?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“As long as it’s a competition, then no one would dare say that they are one hundred percent certain. However, a team like ours, which is made from scratch, needs to be tested through something like the Challenger League. If we can’t even perform well enough in the Challenger League, then even if our team enters the Pro League, then we would just be returning to the game very soon. To enter the Pro League through the Challenger League is so that our investors don’t have to take such dangerous risks. This is our responsibility to the investors.” Ye Xiu said.

“What you mean is that Challenger League’s aim is actually to examine this team’s quality and worth?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Correct, the one who would actually be taking on the risk of elimination would be me. As long as you guys perform well, then the Challenger League will help you achieve enough to ensure your future.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 602 – There’s Always Something That’ll Work

Ye Xiu’s lingering words sounded solemn and stirring. Even Tang Rou, who was diagonal from him, heard his words and felt moved. Chen Guo didn’t need to be mentioned. Her fragile heart had already shattered to pieces. She didn’t know what to say. Chen Guo hated how she couldn’t take out her heart and sell it to achieve her dream.

In the game, Little Cold Hands was clearly touched as well, except he was also clearly an extremely calm and rational person. He didn’t completely give in like Chen Guo. After a moment of silence, he continued: “This sort of future can also be won by performing well in the official Pro League as well, right?”

Little Cold Hands completely ignored the huge risk Ye Xiu would be taking in the Challenger League. He continued to be ice-cold, making Chen Guo want to interrupt and curse him, but Ye Xiu calmly answered: “Correct. However, there’s another issue. I can see that you’re someone who is very clear-headed. You should have a good understanding of your own skill level. Do you think your skill is actually good enough to perform well in the pro scene?”

“Probably not.” Little Cold Hands said, “But at least I have potential. If not, why would you come looking for me?”

“Right, but your potential can be found anywhere in the training camps of the pro teams. We looked for you because our resources are limited. On the other hand, your situation happens to work out for our team. You’re still far from the pro level and need training. Directly throwing you into the Pro League would be the same as throwing an elementary school student into university. Do you think you would be able to grow in that environment? In comparison, the Challenger League would also be quite good. It continuously eliminates weaker team, allowing for a slow and steady increase in difficulty, which can be used to accumulate experience and raise your skill level progressively. It fits you too perfectly.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Okay, from what you’re saying, this is a really rare opportunity for me.” Little Cold Hands said.

“Seeing as to how you have such a detailed understanding of the pro scene, it looks like you’re quite interested in becoming a pro player.” Ye XIu said.

“Of course. I would think most players in Glory share this dream.” Little Cold Hands said.

“Now you have the opportunity to make that dream a reality.” Ye Xiu said.

“However, after having my potential recognized by a God, I’m quite eager to try and register for Tyranny’s training camp.” Little Cold Hands countered.

“Ha ha, if you really plan on doing that, I wouldn’t suggest Tyranny. Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie is too important to the team. His position on the team far surpasses that of just a Cleric. Until he retires, even if your Cleric skills are even more outstanding than Zhang Xinjie’s, you still wouldn’t be able to replace him as the team’s Cleric. In addition, for a God-level Cleric character like Immovable Rock, Tyranny has definitely made sufficient preparations for its next successor once Zhang Xinjie retires. If you really go to Tyranny, your competition will far surpass your imagination because your competitors won’t just be you. Also, because of the importance of Zhang Xinjie in Tyranny, the team won’t have much space for a Cleric to grow. Rookie Clerics in Tyranny have difficulty gaining experience in matches. Currently, Tyranny doesn’t have any rookie Clerics in training. My guess is that Tyranny will look for a transfer from another team as Immovable Rock’s successor once Zhang Xinjie retires. Your competitors will be seasoned pro players, possibly other Gods. Student, are you ready for such an undertaking?” Ye Xiu explained.

Little Cold Hands was silent for a moment before answering: “Then from your perspective, which team would fit me?”

“Without a doubt, it would be my team. Didn’t I just say that?” Ye Xiu said.

“What will your team be called?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Happy……” Ye Xiu replied and then turned his head to ask Chen Guo: “Right? Or are you planning on changing it?”

“Probably not?” Chen Guo also asked.

“You don’t even know the name of your own team?” Little Cold Hands was somewhat speechless, “Would it hurt to sound a little bit more reliable?”

“We emphasize practicality. Something like a name is like a fleeting cloud. It doesn’t matter what it is. The name could even be Fleeting Clouds.”

“Don’t joke around!” Chen Guo angered. She cared a lot about the name. Even though Happy didn’t sound as powerful as Tyranny, it gave a lot of other emotions to her. She could accept a name change, but something like “Fleeting Clouds” wasn’t something she couldn’t accept.

“Boss, Team Fleeting Clouds actually sounds a lot better than Team Happy. Happy…… it sounds like some small grocery store or Internet Cafe on the side of the street.”

“Ha ha ha ha, you’re right!” Ye Xiu was about to die from laughter.

“Really?” Little Cold Hands thought Ye XIu was talking about Team Fleeting Clouds sounding better than Team Happy, but Ye Xiu’s nonstop laughter was making him somewhat confused.

“Do what you want!”

Little Cold Hands heard the boss humph.

“We can talk about the name later! Do you have any other doubts? If you don’t have any, you can start considering it.” Ye Xiu said.

“If I don’t have to pay any fees or make any cash deposits, I think I can accept the offer. How about we talk about the contract now?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“What requirements would you have for the contract?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Seeing your dire circumstances and my current skill level, I don’t really have any qualifications to talk about any conditions, do I?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Correct. You think of yourself as too much of a treasure. If you have too many conditions, I’ll just have to continue picking up grass.” Ye Xiu said.

“But if you keep on going back and forth looking for recruits like this, wouldn’t it waste too much of your time?” Little Cold Hands said.

“Without a reliable team to count on, there isn’t really much else to do.” Ye Xiu said.

“How many players have you found for your team so far?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Including you, we should have around four.” Ye Xiu said.

“The other two?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“One of them is a Warlock. For now, you won’t be able to get in touch with him. The other one is a Battle Mage, who’s currently in the tenth server.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about Mu Mu? Doesn’t she count?” Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu talk about Wei Chen and Tang Rou and hastily asked.

“She can’t for the Challenger League!” Ye Xiu said.

“Mu Mu? Su Mucheng?” Little Cold Hands listened.

“If we can smoothly enter the Pro League, she’ll be be a part of our team.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh oh, I finally hear a reliable piece of information from you.” Little Cold Hands sighed.

“What about that Steamed Bun?” Chen Guo asked again.

“I haven’t talked about it with Steamed Bun yet. Who knows what he’s thinking.” Ye Xiu said.

“Steamed Bun can think?” Chen Guo had managed the guild in the tenth server before, so she had interacted with Steamed Bun Invasion several times already.

“He’s not a real steamed bun! He’s an actual person too!” Ye Xiu defended him.

“Isn’t it about time you mentioned it to him?” Chen Guo said.

“Have I talked about it with him before? I forget……” Ye Xiu said.

(“Isn’t it more like the author forgot?” Chen Guo said.

“Most likely. That useless trash. I hate him!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.)

‘Then should I go talk to him about it?” Chen Guo said. (Author note: this “him” is referring to Steamed Bun Invasion. Please skip over the part in parentheses……)

“Did you forget that we’re in the middle of a conversation with a certain someone?” Ye Xiu reminded Chen Guo. Steamed Bun Invasion was an entirely different matter.

“Ahem!” Little Cold Hands coughed.

Chen Guo felt so ashamed that she wanted to die.

“Okay, Little Hands, I’ll be direct. You tell me what your requirements are for the contract and then give us some time to think about it!” Ye Xiu said.

“The Challenger League will test the quality of the team and the quality of the individual team members too. You wouldn’t dare to be certain that the players you’ve gathered are enough to form a pro team, right? After smoothly passing through the Challenger League, what if some of the team members don’t perform well enough. Would you kick them out after entering the Pro League?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Your attitude decides everything. If your attitude doesn’t prove to be a problem, you’ll be good enough and you’ll perform well.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying you won’t deny such a possibility!” Little Cold Hands said.

“Of course. Nothing is set in stone yet.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what happens if another team is interested in me, would the team allow me to leave?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“So you were concerned about this. Ha ha, if you really do rise to become an amazing talent, even if we wanted to, we wouldn’t be able to stop you! If you’ve been paying attention to the pro scene, then you should know that teams don’t usually force players to stay if they aren’t willing to stay. That wouldn’t be a win-win situation. If something like that happened, both sides would need to negotiate until both sides are satisfied with the results. Is that satisfactory answer?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then what will the specifics of the contract look like?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Since we’re unreliable, we obviously haven’t even started writing up contracts yet, but if you go online and do a search, you should be able to find similar contracts prepared by other teams. You can use those as references.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re saying that I have to prepare the contract myself?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“That isn’t impossible.” Ye Xiu said.

“If I wanted to back out right now, can I?” Little Cold Hands said.

“You’re joking :)” Ye Xiu sent a smiley face.

“Fine, but I still need to confirm that you’re Ye Qiu.” Little Cold Hands said.

“Would it be good enough if I went on Lord Grim and sent you a message?” Ye Xiu asked.

“There isn’t any proof that Lord Grim is Ye Qiu.” Little Cold Hands said.

“Go ask your guild leader.” Ye Xiu said.

“......”

“Or I can give you old Han’s or Zhang’s phone number and you can ask them yourself?”

“.......”

“Oh my! I don’t think I have their phone numbers. I can give your their QQ’s?”

“......”

“Or you can video chat with Su Mucheng.”

“......”

“Or I could go look for Huang Shaotian and have you experience how talkative he really is?”

“......”

“There has to be a method you can accept, right? You can choose any of them.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s fine. I believe you……” Little Cold Hands said.